[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, February 10th, 2008, Xbox HD DVD gets a price cut, old favorites are revealed for Street Fighter 4, and is an Oscar-nominated movie soon becoming a video game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not joining us tonight, sadly, is the one and only DarkSakura, also known as Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is unfortunately out with sickness.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's been having, you know, just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Subway was out of white bread, I had wheat, and wheat tastes like cardboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bread is bread.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not even really wheat bread.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like they took white bread and kind of dyed it brown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is Subway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't expect huge differences.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did your cat scratch you or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I see big old claw marks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's my cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry you hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's because when she gets up in her tube sometimes, she starts to freak out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But she's playing and stuff, so what do I try to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I try poking at her all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried petting her on her head, but then she just grabs her claws and she kind of catches me sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks a lot more painful than it actually was.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, also joining us tonight, you might have heard his voice there just a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Puppy, also known as Black Lab, or Ryan, depending on whatever we want to call him.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you, Puppy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had some insomnia this week and kind of capped it off with,
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting woken up at 2.30 in the morning last night by gunfire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, fun!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear about the gunfire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were your neighbors, like, fighting or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or what's the deal?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was probably something in the mall parking lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's been like just a crazy week in everybody's neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was gunfire in your neighborhood, and the house across the street from the studio here burned down a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the outside, it makes Rob's house much easier to find to get here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's unfortunate for those that affected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I didn't even notice it because that house was so run down to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: It burned down?
[SPEAKER_02]: Couldn't tell.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyhow, let's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not talk about neighborhood drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll start it off with how was your gaming week and we'll go ahead and start off with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, I'd like to say I have brought back the Ever360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is back to life again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: The trick was I needed more heat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't stop until I got to about 850 degrees to 1,000 degrees and sure enough, that worked.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now I have six working 360s.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just loaded, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then let's see I played this week more Smash Brothers Brawl and that's pretty awesome I actually got to dive in a little bit to the subspace emissary mode and it's pretty fun they have some really crazy looking enemies in the game just some weird stuff but it's pretty cool and then I've unlocked Rob the Robot we went through the challenge but I actually took off work half a day to go visit one of my customers who really wanted to play the game so
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, though, if I play through the entire Subspace Emissary stuff and then finish all the other crap, I might get bored with the game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I actually need to play some people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than Smash Bros., I also played Silent Hill Origins, actually, on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went back to try that again.
[SPEAKER_03]: and pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I'm looking forward to it coming out on PlayStation 2 because I just don't like being tethered to my TV with a little cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it might be a little bit better if I have a little bit more room to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I also played a lot of Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still trying to knock people off of the leaderboards for the Showtime rankings.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love how listeners will add us on Xbox Live because they enjoy the show and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just kind of want to play a game with us occasionally or what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas Loki makes it his mission to dominate our listeners in whatever game he's playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like, oh no, I can't get beat by no listener.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to control the burnout map.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, right now I have about 26 of the roads, so I still have a ways to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, other than that, played a little bit more DotStream on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, tried playing Crysis again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually uninstalled Crysis, reinstalled Crysis, tried to get that last level to fucking work again, and sure enough, it does not work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still, I can't pass that last level in the game because it glitches out, and it stops working.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I am sick of Crysis, although I did load up the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The physics, a little custom map that someone made to play the physics of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually released a new version of the map last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you can slingshot barrels in the people and stuff and catapult things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that though, I fucking hate the last level of Crysis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they not test it at all?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just really broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is bad because the rest of the game is pretty cool but it's just that last level right as you're about to finish the game and kind of get the payoff from playing through the entire thing oh no, you can't do that that would be too easy so I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo 3 Halo 3
[SPEAKER_05]: Even with the updates that Halo 3 finally added, and are going to add in the near future, I still will be playing Call of Duty 4 instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pretty bold statement, that it's better than Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually found it much more enjoyable than Halo, just because there's a lot more reality to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: As opposed to, oh, armored space guys punching each other in a grossly malformed way.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then other than Call of Duty 4, I sadly have fallen back into my Puzzle Pirate habit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: How has Puzzle Pirates changed?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you were last addicted to the game, what, about two years ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, I stopped playing it about a year ago because I didn't have the time to anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then apparently a lot of stuff changed in that year.
[SPEAKER_05]: They brought a bunch of new puzzle games in and added some new player versus environment stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's getting popular and I just found out, they just made an announcement that they're selling game cards at Target now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they must be making it big or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm noticing with the facial hair that you're starting to sprout here, you're starting to look like a pirate a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was much longer earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, I could just throw on an eye patch for a party.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great radio too to talk about puppies' look.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a little facial growth that makes him look like a pirate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they can see it on Justin TV because you're blonde.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could probably stand right in front of the camera and they wouldn't see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you go give them a nice close-up when you're done?
[SPEAKER_02]: Give a nice close-up of your mug there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give a nice little mug shot there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else for your gaming week you want to share?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rez, various board games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't Rez incredible?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really wish that I had a high-def TV to play it on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do, and it's sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate to rub it in, but yeah, you really do want one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to have surround sound, too, when you're playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seriously almost dug up my old surround sound system that's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually hooked up here in the garage.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost brought that into the house just to play Res HD with, but I'm going to get a new sound system when I get my tax refund.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I thought about getting a better TV with my tax refund, but I've got other stuff that I need to pay for first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, now go supermodel for the camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll talk about my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, I want to mention in chat room, because this didn't come up earlier, TigerClaw says, Sky, I just realized OLR is competing against the Grammys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, I mean, the Grammys...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I find them to be incredibly irrelevant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see that article on Dig earlier this week about the biggest Grammy snubs of all time?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It shows how there's all these big name artists that always get snubbed by the Grammys when there's people that were more deserving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I brought up tax refunds earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm curious, in our chat room, those that are getting tax refunds, if there's anything in gaming that you're contemplating spending your tax refund on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let us know in our chat room, chat.orangemonstrator.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll read those in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mostly spent, besides Poker Smash, playing a couple different games.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I talk about that a lot here on the program, but it has been a lot of my gaming week recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it really went to the next level this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how many hardcore WoW addicts we have that listen to the game, but tonight...
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And we only have 10 people in our guild that can even do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I notice it's tough to really arrange the times to go in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we did an awesome job.
[SPEAKER_02]: For anybody that does know WoW, we killed Attuneman, we killed Morose, and we killed Maiden today.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in our first weekend, we killed three of the bosses in Karazhan, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently, I'm sure there's lots of people out there who go, Whoa, my guild killed four bosses, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_05]: My guild killed it all in one night.
[SPEAKER_02]: For us, when we were mostly casual players, it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just wait until you try to move on to 25-man content and you've got three different groups going to Karazhan at once and they're like, oh, we don't want to split up, we don't want to go all together and then you'll end up breaking apart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drama, drama, drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we don't want drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're all, most of us actually live here in the area and our guild was formed mostly from real-life people like my boyfriend is in the guild and like Irene is in the guild but she's not level 70 yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the other people you've heard on this show are in the guild and yeah, good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're finally doing that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking at chat room, seeing what folks are saying they're going to spend their tax refunds on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, my tax rebate is going towards an HD camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191 says, I'll probably spend my welfare, I mean stimulus package check on a new PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: After that thing was passed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm already spending that on a new computer because I need something at home that can run AutoCAD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, DMN's going to use his refund to come visit the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's coming back to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll use that refund to pass it to the children.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that they just have to pay rent.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can choose to battle your creature with one from their hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's all these enhancements cards that'll increase your strength, your defense.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of a game where you really have to think before you play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a very unique concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of interesting to see it on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, they didn't really change a lot from the first game, and the animations are not really...
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything to jump and scream about in this new age of gaming or whatever you want to call it with the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You look at the Eye of Judgment and there's very intricate battles that happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: For all the shit we give that game on this show, the battles look kind of cool when the cards do battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here in Cold Sept, it's like if a monster attacks with the claws, you see big claw marks go across the card.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's basically like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just in high definition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, like, literally the cards do battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of amusing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's incredible English in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, like, one of the lines is something like, I had to escape the poverty or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember, like, very literal translations in some of the cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, for me, I think this game is mostly a second chance for people who missed it on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's not a full-price Xbox game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like that middle tier.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's $39.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not quite as much as you pay for a brand new Xbox 360 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pretty good deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually didn't own Cold Sept on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my friends a couple years ago did.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I got exposed to it the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We spent a lot of nights just playing Cold Sept.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just like in Magic, as you go through and battle monsters, you get to keep some of their cards and build them into your deck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a pretty intricate game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, the Xbox One also has the new Xbox Live mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and apparently, uh, poor old Sheevum finally got his Xbox 360 and got, that's one of the games he's been playing all the time now.
[SPEAKER_05]: After he got Rez, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking at Portal Combat in our chatroom says, Cold Sept is the only game you can play while reading Entertainment Weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think the game's that boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not a fast-paced game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You read Entertainment Weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_02]: You read Entertainment Weekly?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else anyone wants to share with their gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's people out there that actually paint cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: What does that have to do with games?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's creepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you do during this program?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we pay you to surf the internet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight's housekeeping, obviously, there's no Jamie here tonight, sadness.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to try to give her a call a little later in the show so she can participate in one of her regular segments.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the good news is, tonight...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: that's the cool thing about it so I'm really looking forward to it it'll be coming up in part B so stick around and make sure you're in our chat room other than that just the usual plugs for us on MySpace at Orange Lounge Radio our live journal at Orange Lounge we have a Facebook community called the OL Army so search us out there help us spread the word about independent radio and independent podcasting and that's it now Loki do you think you can take some time away from Painted Cats to read us some news stories I think I can
[SPEAKER_03]: So we've had this for a while now, the Xbox 360 arcade model, the one replacing the core.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now Japan's going to get a chance to have it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to get theirs March 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, the arcade system is the one that features no hard drive, but it has a memory unit, as well as five Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to actually cost 27,800 yen.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is about $20 less than we'd pay for it in the United States.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hopefully that will help drive more Xbox 360 sales because right now they're hurting.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is the one that doesn't have a hard drive, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it doesn't have a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would think all the games that people are interested in playing in Japan probably require that hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess Blue Dragon doesn't require a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just for game saves and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lost Odyssey...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think of the more Japanese-centered game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't think Lost Odyssey requires a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not, or Devil May Cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess none of those games do.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's just PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: They require the hard drive for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep thinking Final Fantasy XI as well, which was really probably the first Japan-centric game that I can think of, anyway, to come out on the Xbox 360 on both shores, even though it was an already existing game, so it wasn't that hard to get out here, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've tried all sorts of bundles in Japan, and so far it hasn't really helped.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they've only sold, like, what,
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hey, look, I want to play a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, I can't save it unless I buy a card.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT in chat says, if a series of top-notch Japanese games don't do it, this won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's, you know, there's a lot of good stuff coming out that's kind of, you would think, appeals.
[SPEAKER_02]: You really have to generalize to say a lot of this, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really appeals to the Japanese audience, you know, like Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I hear that game didn't do so well over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't get very good reviews over there, but, you know, I don't know if,
[SPEAKER_02]: When I was at GameStop getting Cold Sept, the guy who was actually thinking of buying Cold Sept, actually he was holding it up when I walked up to the counter reading the back of the box, and I told him that was the game I wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he told me he was excited about Lost Odyssey as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am excited about Lost Odyssey, although I have low expectations for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only see it as probably going to be slightly better than Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we will see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know a lot of people are really into this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Black is also coming out for the Xbox Originals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Black for Black History Month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just, I'm trying to find, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're trying to be funny and failing miserably.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not trying to be funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I, that was a little, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be weird if they did try to tie it in that way?
[SPEAKER_05]: Would that be more insulting to the game or to Black History?
[SPEAKER_02]: Black History.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you saying the game was not that great?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good, but it's not, it has nothing to do with Black History Month.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I'm just being your normal crazy self.
[SPEAKER_02]: Always controversial, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're getting some download content for Mass Effect coming March 10th.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a brand new set of missions called Bring Down the Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has actually a brand new race that they're introducing as well in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess they're calling it the
[SPEAKER_03]: Batarians, Batarians, Batarians, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They look like an ant.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got like a bunch of eyes and a weird little bat nose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, they look like a quasi-bat-ant thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you'll be able to, you know, go to the colony and actually be able to save them and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, gigantic space bats, I guess that's what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's only going to be 400 Microsoft points or $5, so that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to add about 90 minutes to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, there's going to be 50 achievement points you can earn from it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing, though, I remember reading about this, though, is it's midway through the game, so if you have a save that's kind of towards the end of the game, you might already have passed the ability to play this, so you have to start a new game, which kind of blows, but
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you had just one save file to begin with, you're already failing at RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT in our chat room makes a good comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says he will wait for the special edition of the game with all the download content included since we all know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for how long?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't know how much DLC is coming for Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, it could be two years until that edition is released, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll probably be a year because that's what they've done with some of the other ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I haven't really noticed Microsoft Games doing that where they come out with content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you didn't see Perfect Dark come out with another Perfect Dark Zero or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there have been others.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there was Oblivion, Marvel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's a few.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, see, Marvel and Call of Duty, that's all Activision.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so they tend to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Microsoft does not.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, would that be Bioware's decision?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it would be their decision.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would just say buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're really desperate for download content, otherwise, save that $5 for a new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put that $5 down towards Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to spend $5 on 90 minutes of entertainment, or do you want to spend $5 on an Xbox Live arcade game?
[SPEAKER_03]: That could end up being a lot more fun, or at least, I don't know, not many Xbox Live arcade games that are 400 Microsoft points, but still, it'd be a lot more fun than 90 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd spend it on food.
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX 360 HD DVD Player
[SPEAKER_02]: For you math whizzes, that means the HD DVD player is now costing $130.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the HD DVD player has been dropped to $130 in the US and Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it was even cheaper if you looked on Amazon a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazon was running an $80 deal for a little while, probably trying to clean out their inventory in recent HD DVD...
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I own an HD DVD player, I have for quite a while, and I kind of think it's over, and I'm kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I bought the wrong one this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted one just for Matrix, but I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if inevitably Blu-ray wins in a year or so, and I don't mean these preemptive Blu-ray wins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blu-ray wins when HD DVD folds, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: If that happens in a year or whatever, then Matrix will come out on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know it will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it will, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Wars movies will all come out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rad isn't on DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: What isn't?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rad was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is Rad?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rad is a BMX bike movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of those, you know, fight for the underdogs thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had an entire sequence where they did a musical dance number using BMX bikes at a school prom or homecoming or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Cop Rock out on DVD?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That needs to be out on DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a TV show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Rad and Gleaming the Cube is another one that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I gotta love the 80s movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gleaming the Cube, I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotta love the 80s movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how I know Gleaming the Cube?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's a trailer for it on Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, as an independent radio person, you know that's one of my favorite movies ever, is Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, that's for another time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monster Squad, Rad, and Gleaming in a Cube.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do yourself a favor, watch them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know they were really cool back in the 80s, and they're not so cool now, but hey, it's nostalgia, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dang, Joshi16's got a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wizard?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is The Wizard out on DVD?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it did finally come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were released in August or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took them a while, but it finally did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't own it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to put that on my birthday wish list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, wait until high def.
[SPEAKER_02]: High def wizardry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do need a high def Super Mario 3 or whatever that... Remember the lame announcer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I want to be able to have, you know, he touch my breasts in 7.1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So another game getting some download content, Project Gotham Racing 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to bring some brand new cars as well as some new modes and of course more achievements.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of the downloads, they're going to have one that's free.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called the Free Challenge Pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a playable hydrogen powered pergo flux car, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tourist mode where you just drive around the city and admire the scenery with no goal whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And free roam cat and mouse mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, the free roam stuff is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're taking a little page from Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, seven unlockable achievements.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Premium Challenge Pack, which is going to be $5 or 400 Microsoft Points, includes 700 new cars, including the 1987 BMW M3 E30 DTM and the World Challenge Arcade Mode with 20 new events in three themed chapters and three more unlockable achievements.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these will be available on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing Says Love Like A Downloadable Hydrogen Car
[SPEAKER_03]: She wouldn't touch the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: She doesn't know how to do that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: She can't even figure out how to play a DVD on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I want to go back and read some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot about this DVD release.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a big DVD release that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: NYRfan says, I saw The King of Kong the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see King of Kong yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get that DVD?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoop-de-doo.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they made me buy Donkey Kong for the week because they were going to do this big King of Kong contest thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never fucking paid me for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they ended up not doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we decided not to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, where's my five bucks?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, thanks, bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Joshi16 in chat says about The Wizard coming out in high def someday.
[SPEAKER_02]: So much batter in HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they should call it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The It's So Batter edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it needs to be in 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you know they're doing that with a lot of... Power glue!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they're doing that with a lot of old Disney movies at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're coming back out in 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toy Story.
[SPEAKER_02]: All those are going to come out in 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: Toy Story is easy because they just have to render it with two camera angles.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's simple stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, Loki's going to go home and make Toy Story 3D for all of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll make a sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can crap it out in a sec.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else that's going to be making its way to Xbox very soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now this, here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a movie that needs to be in HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think this is out in HD yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tron is winner.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Tron, of course, the original Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is already out on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we all knew this game was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Discs of Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other Tron arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is going to be coming out on Xbox Live and it makes its way when?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why, this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: February 13th is the big day for Discs of Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, how would you feel if Nelly got you Discs of Tron for Valentine's Day?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be much cooler.
[SPEAKER_02]: I fucking hate Discs of Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like the Tron games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disoftron is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think of a game that it was very much like.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like, it's really just an over-glorified Pong.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you've seen the movie, you remember that disc thing they would play?
[SPEAKER_02]: They did that little dance and they'd throw the disc in the air and it would bounce off the wall or whatever and hit the platform and make part of it disappear.
[SPEAKER_02]: And ultimately you're trying to make your opponent disappear.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like that, but a real game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have that at Disneyland, like actual discotron.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be cool?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you don't necessarily... I mean, they could do it with some sort of motion capture stuff where they
[SPEAKER_03]: You're in black lights, one person's on the other side, and you make the motion like you're throwing a disc, and it makes the image of a disc go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just need to make sure the platform actually falls out from underneath you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you fall to your untimely death at the bottom of Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you become a slave at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it could be like that, you remember that game show they had on Game Show Network?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nick Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, Russian Roulette.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Game Show Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hosted by Mark L. Wahlberg, which is like, how do you describe Mark L. Wahlberg?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, he's the total, like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, what's a word to describe him?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, he hosts that Moment of Truth show now, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Douche.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if you ever need, like, a total asshole to host your game show, like, Markel Wahlberg's the guy to call.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so he was awesome on, and I mean that as a compliment.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he hosted Russian Roulette, and you would pull, and I know we have an international audience, so maybe not everybody has heard of this show, although they probably stole it from another country.
[SPEAKER_02]: You would...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you know, as people missed questions, lights would light up on the ground, including one that you were standing under, and you had to pull the lever and spin the lights, and if the light landed on you, then the floor would open and you fell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, obviously, in the game show, you just fell a few feet onto some padding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd like to believe that.
[SPEAKER_02]: How awesome would that be?
[SPEAKER_03]: In my mind, they fell through a wood chipper, but that's, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: you win $100 oh I want the money fuck you you're going through the floor I'm keeping the $100 sorry to get off track here Grand Theft Auto 4 the website's actually been relaunched for the game including some new video footage that they have of it one is a mock commercial for a wireless communications company including where they say that there's no drop calls and they have reliable handsets where the guy throws a handset at someone's head and stuff it's pretty fun
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, if you want, there is a lovemeet.net quiz, which is going to be the fictional kind of eHarmony or whatever website that's going to be in the game for dating people.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can take your quiz and figure out what personality type you have.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know we did this at work and we came up with pervert, so that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm assuming they're going to be adding some more content to the website as the weeks go along.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: The site that was running Destructoid was actually going to have a list of the achievements as well until Rockstar said, uh-uh, don't put those up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they wouldn't be threatened by lawyers.
[SPEAKER_03]: They decided not to put the content up there and kind of retracted their original articles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad a large, well-established, respectable website like Destructoid will also run away with their tail behind their legs when threatened.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, I'm referring to like a year-old drama, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Faceit, that's a history of this show that will never be let down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to interrupt, I just had to work that in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I mean, and I think also to their, you know, defense, you probably won't put that stuff up anyway because it would spoil a lot of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They basically, you know, said, hey, you know, in the respect for this game coming out in a few months here, just not put this up yet because that will spoil a lot of the story for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want to spoil a game like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there's also some minigames you can play in it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of them, they mentioned DARTs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poole, and some other game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure this stuff would be on PartnerNet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's out there on the public internet, it's free information.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is from an insider that works at Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's public information, they have nowhere to complain.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's an actual leak like this, they have the right to take it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: DMN is anticipating there will be a 15-gamer score achievement called Bitch Better Have My Money.
[SPEAKER_02]: DMN also predicts a 30 gamerscore for lukewarm coffee I hope there is an achievement that pokes fun at hot coffee There really should be There should be an achievement like hot coffee and it's actually you go buy coffee You actually do buy hot coffee Or you blow up a Starbucks or whatever they call it in Grand Theft Auto A little parody name or something That'd be funny
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and we're getting live in our work here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much do you think you can kill in 15 minutes?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can kill quite a few people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually in Saints Row I can rack up a score of 20 or more if we're playing just rockets.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's just all out, we usually end up being around 10 to 15 kills.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if we do teams, like six-man teams, oh man, we're going to own everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, because we have so much experience in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll learn all the little nuances.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not even going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I don't think anyone's actually going to want to play online during our breaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll force them to, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will be up to that challenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know how y'all feel about this, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: As cool as Grand Theft Auto is, it's not really my kind of game, but this is one I could definitely play a lot of online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Street Fighter 4, and this is going to be a fun one I bet to play online pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, it's really no replacement for the arcade, and I think we all need to remember that, because sadly arcades are dying and they're turning into ticket-spitting machine heaven.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, Street Fighter 4, like it or not, it will be online, and what makes it very cool is that
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They're all back, the original eight fighters in Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's some scans from Famitsu Magazine that actually show them in their new art style, and it's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's even some more stuff with Crimson Viper.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not just the original eight are going to be in Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_02]: The family's growing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone did post the achievement list, I guess, on Destructoid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then I retract everything I said.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spoilers ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I retract everything I said.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have an achievement for demolishing 20 buildings using only your rocket launcher.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, how do you know it's legit?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my next question.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's someone's blog, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So take with a grain of salt, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to say any others?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Out of town, stay hidden for six days.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of the achievements.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see if there's anything real quick for the hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see anything on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's probably not going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a nice thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the hooker one on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if this is legit or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I'm saying when it shows up on somebody's little blog, I'm not saying that it's necessarily a lie, but you do kind of have to take it with a grain of salt because there are people out there that want to lie, and especially probably because of the lulls that people are having over the whole, well, they know the list, but they can't spoil it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would think there would be a lot more achievements than that there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's an achievement that says, I get it, and I'll read the first letter of each achievement name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's fake.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, uh... You're stupid for believing this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you suck donkey cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, lovely.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it says.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although that would be cool if that was real.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, Rockstar really should do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that's their hidden thing to piss off the senators.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, when you take the first letter of each word, it says, you know, senators are all gay or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you suck, Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't trust anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice touch there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Loki got pwned.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get pwned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it's legit!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I think they might cut T-Hawk.
[SPEAKER_02]: The characters, nobody really used.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would bet some of the Street Fighter 3 characters are going to be in this too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to have a ton of fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty of room for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if they don't put Dan in it, there's going to be a riot.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will be a riot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Tigerclaw says, I wouldn't be surprised if Akuma is in Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, Shang Long has to be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you must beat Shang Long to stand a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: One game which we thought for a second there, we thought, oh my god, hell froze over, but Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently there was an interview for the Dallas Business Journal where 3D Realms President Scott Miller confirmed all sorts of stuff including that Duke Nukem Forever was coming in 2008 and that Duke Nukem 3D was going to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: and some of the stuff they said we haven't officially announced any platform for Duke Nukem Forever but of course hitting the big three makes most sense PC, PS3, and 360 and he said 3D Realms is negotiating with Microsoft to get a release window of sometime this year on the title that's of course for Duke Nukem 3D on Xbox Live Arcade and he confirmed that Duke Nukem Forever would be coming out in 2008 to home consoles
[SPEAKER_03]: But shortly after he was claimed to have said all this stuff, 3D Realms was like, uh-uh, we never said that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently, which they said, George Broussard of 3D Realms said, In what appears to be an unfortunate turn of events, there seems to have been some confusion between what was off the record and what was not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I suppose we're used to dealing with the gaming press and not mainstream press.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know if that means that... Yeah, it is actually coming out in 2008, but... Shh!
[SPEAKER_03]: We never said that!
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that type of thing, or... I think they're more afraid of the space-time continuing damage that would come from actually confirming this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They basically said the release date is still when it's done and will be until that appropriate moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Platforms have not been finalized or announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can... It'll be done when it's done...
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop asking!
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the question, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should just put that on a big piece of paper and fax it to any website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, this will be an instant purchase for me, but, I mean, do I really care anymore about... I mean, this isn't like some huge epic game anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just kind of, eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's limping along to the finish line.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd buy it just to see how terrible it actually turns out to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's not going to be... I mean, it's going to be borderline terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, Duke Nukem 3D was borderline terrible, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute, Duke Nukem 3D was kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was rad, but see, it had the cops, shooting hookers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had the B-movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool for the same reason Evil Dead is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's also cool because they use a lot of lines from Evil Dead as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one thing that's not cool is going down and burning things down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what's even more not cooler is to brag about it on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so you know for this, we've got to give out another one of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, it's another Orange Lounge Radio Stupid Award.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Orange Lounge Radio Stupid Award this week goes to a user on GameFAQs, and their name is JediKnight12345.
[SPEAKER_02]: JediKnight12345 made a post in the current events section of the GameFAQs forums, and what he was doing is he was asking the folks on the forums if he should burn down a school and a church.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what happened a little later in the town of Palmyra, Missouri?
[SPEAKER_02]: He burned down a church.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so this boy was arrested on suspected arson charges.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know his real name because he is under the age of 18 and they withhold that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we can't give out the stupid award by his real name.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he certainly, if he's over the age of like four, he's old enough to know better.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even at that age, you should know better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we really need more reason not to go on the GameFAQs forum?
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel bad for GameFAQs, because everybody's just using this as a reason to attack them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, well that's what he gets for going to GameFAQs, ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm like, okay, ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their community was...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: But then they wouldn't be anonymous like they are on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't catch me, I'm on GameFAQs.
[SPEAKER_02]: AmazeSatsuma says, 12345, how did you know the combination for my briefcase?
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, as if even just asking about it wasn't bad enough, it should also be noted that JediKnight12345 went back to the forum and bragged that he had in fact burned a church and school down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he posted pictures of it!
[SPEAKER_02]: on GameFAQs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, to the users of GameFAQs credit, other forum posters immediately went and found the local news station in this area and contacted them and the authorities and all that and contacted people that could do something about it and turn this guy in, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hooray to the GameFAQs users that turned this guy in.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are exempt from the Stupid Award this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, Jedi Knight 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, it's your Stupid Award.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations, you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: He played too much Dracula, or Castlevania, throwing the holy fire and learned how to start fires.
[SPEAKER_02]: So playing too much WoW as a mage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the complete idiocy of this guy makes me angsty.
[SPEAKER_03]: He fires a magic missile into the darkness.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know this brings on the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your FUs of the week, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, my FU of the week goes to a headache that's coming on right about now, and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate getting headaches on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's always on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not having anything to do with this show, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, I get headaches on Sundays.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you're allergic to Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm allergic to the holy day, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, Poppy, do you have any FUs you'd like to give this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, FU to insomnia, letting me get about a
[SPEAKER_04]: 10 hours of sleep over the course of four nights, and FU to the charger from my laptop for going up, and now my laptop is running on battery power until it eventually dies.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to Sears.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to give too many details about purchases I made a while ago, but oh my god, I had to go back to the store like twice in one day to clear up this issue that I was having that, you know, wasn't even like my fault with Sears.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: You probably wouldn't guess Juno as the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would they make a game based off Juno?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Teaching little girls about pregnancy adventures?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen Juno, but I hear it's about teenage pregnancy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not exactly sure how that makes a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they make a game out of Napoleon Dynamite?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure how they'd make a game out of that either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Juno to me...
[SPEAKER_02]: Feels like it might be this year's Napoleon Dynamite.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really funny now, but when it comes out on video, there's going to be a big backlash against it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just you wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, there is a panel at DICE, the summit going on in Las Vegas right now, during the Intellectual Property Migration Specialists.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says people are making a game based off Juno just to cater to the casual market.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they didn't specify really anything about the game but apparently it was I don't know he said it's probably going to be following Nexon's free to play business model so I don't know so it would be like little mini games for free or something I'm sorry this is probably going to be about as good as that Dirty Dancing game that came out or possibly the what was it that one based off Prince's Bride
[SPEAKER_02]: Ryoma in our chatroom says, Sky, Juno is a lot less stupid than Napoleon Dynamite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Napoleon Dynamite I hated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen Juno, so I thought Napoleon Dynamite was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think it was like the most hilarious movie ever made, but I did find some things very amusing in that movie, like the grandma especially, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make me another Quesadilla.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when she got in the dirt bike accident, it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Battalion Wars 2 makes its way to the Wii on the 15th along with 8-Ball All-Stars and the DS Castlevania, the Dracula X Chronicles, a big game that came out here a little while ago Europe, you're finally getting it on the PSP on the 15th as well as Coated Arms Contingent also on the PSP Cooking Mama 2 finally comes out on the Nintendo DS for you guys not as bad of a delay though, we just got it here about a month ago Cruisin' makes its way to the Wii, I'm sorry
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tekenshi 3 comes out on the Wii Dark Messiah of Might and Magic Elements comes out on the Xbox 360 Coming out on the DS, a big title, Final Fantasy XII Revenant Wings Which Loki was kind enough to get me for Christmas and I still haven't played, I'm very sorry Loki But I feel like I need to finish Final Fantasy XII on console first, I will, soon
[SPEAKER_02]: Multi-platform wise, you've got a game called Jumper coming out on PlayStation 2 and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: NBA 08 on the PlayStation 3, coming out on the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Destiny of Zorro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm, that sounds like it could suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, but certainly not leastly, where would you Naruto fans be without a release for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Naruto Ninja Destiny in the UK on the DS on the 15th of February.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the US, we're getting quite a few things coming out, including Lost Odyssey, that we've been seeing some pretty strange commercials for on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes it look like some sort of hippie game, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I fast-forward all commercials, so what makes it look so horrible?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the music that they picked for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what's... I don't remember what the name was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it's just... But it's something about White Knight talking backwards...
[SPEAKER_03]: Conflict Denied Ops PC, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3 PC, Penumbra
[SPEAKER_03]: Black Plague, Jumper, A Griffin Story, Warriors of the Ancient Arts, Dark Messiah of Might and Magic Elements, Space Force Captains,
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also a new episode of the Sam & Max game, episode 203, The Night of the Raving Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's, of course, on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Carrier Strike Force on PC, 13th Century Death of Glory, Wipeout Pulse on the PSP, Innocent Life of Futuristic Harvest Moon, special edition on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Futuristic Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was on PSP before.
[SPEAKER_03]: RPG Maker VX on PC, and finally on PlayStation 2, and they moved it up quite a bit from March, Ratchet & Clank Size Matters on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got moved up a whole friggin' month.
[SPEAKER_02]: One man on the chessboard Get a hand and tell you
[SPEAKER_05]: All of this on this Jefferson Airplane.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: White Rabbit, my Jefferson Airplane.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is right there on the side.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I am not up on my Jefferson Airplane, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, this week, this weekend I want you to go, or next weekend I want you to go get some CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want you to get Jefferson Airplane.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want you to get Foghat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pink Floyd, Journey for Good Measure Clearwater Revival Smoke a Big Bonk
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding, we don't endorse that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other fun stuff, of course, this is the scraping the bottom of the barrel stuff, but oh, I forgot to mention also the Cobalt Blue in Black DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: That came out today as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, Go Diego Go Safari Rescue 1, PlayStation 2, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta pick that one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was also a Dora the Explorer game coming out, but I don't really care what that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Balloon Pop on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that parody of Dora the Explorer they had on Saturday Night Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I wet myself laughing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll save that for another show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, Balloon Pop for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a really cheap puzzle game, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rock Band, they're getting the drum sets.
[SPEAKER_03]: The standalone drum sets are supposed to be coming out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So look for those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great $90 prep rolls.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's $80 peripherals.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was $90 for the drum sets.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, $80.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still expensive, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on to Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: And coming out in Japan on the 14th of February on the Xbox 360, WWE Smackdown vs. Raw 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how popular wrestling is over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they have their own wrestling league over there because I've seen some YouTubage.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you want to experience the American version, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also coming out on PlayStation 3, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it appears to be one of the bigger releases this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a lot else.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're not a Rasslin' fan, you can get Medal of Honor Heroes 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does come out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, there's also a bundle with the Wii Zapper making its way to Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the PlayStation 2, Decapo, the origin, comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pachinko Game, Jisen, Pachislot, Hisoho Selection, Salerman, Kintaru, Slaughter, Kintaru, Ore no Sora.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's one name.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's another Sega Pachinko Game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I need to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kimikis comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poison Pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like it could be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And another wrestling game, Wrestle Angels Survivor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good price.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like a good TV show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Might be a price reduction on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see what's coming out on the handhelds on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Digimon Championship, a game called Happy Happy Clover comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just in time for Valentine's Day, Otomeki Koi Kakume Love Revo DS comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's take a quick look at the PSP, see if there's anything of note for you guys over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Medal of Honor as well coming on the Sony PSP, Medal of Honor Heroes that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And
[SPEAKER_02]: Where would your life be without another Gundam game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mobile Suit Gundam, Giren no Yabu, Axis no Koei comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's a Korean date, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: That must have already come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it, your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if you're a little bit late to, say, returning your books to a library, if you happen to be in this neck of the woods here,
[SPEAKER_03]: you actually can play DDR to possibly avoid late fees apparently the story is of a librarian's annual patron appreciation day where he lets attendees to avoid overdue fines by donating non-perishables to a local soup kitchen or playing a quick game of DDR pay for play system, they didn't really discuss that
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know where this is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to go there and play DDR for their late fees.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're fucking paying me money for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's certainly a creative method.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's creative.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also a pretty creative game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a lot of people that loved Myst Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, they don't have much longer to love this game because GameTap will be shutting down Myst Online in 60 days.
[SPEAKER_02]: They made the difficult decision earlier this week that Myst Online Uru Live will be going down in 60 days.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's somewhere in April when the game will be coming down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what's really cool is Rick Sanchez, who has actually been on our show before.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was on almost about a year and a half ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually posts on the GameTap forums and kind of had to make that very difficult post because, you know, like any MMO, there's rabid fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, Myst Online is no exception.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had its share of rabid fans, and they're not happy to hear about the game going.
[SPEAKER_02]: People want refunds and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: MistOnline.com will stay active as a tribute to what was in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in Rick's post, he said they were looking at, quote, a wide variety of possibilities for maintaining the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: He swears up and down they're not just a bunch of evil corporate types who do nothing but count pennies and wear Brooks Brothers suits.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, I don't know how many of you guys have played MistOnline.
[SPEAKER_02]: I checked it out a couple months ago for the sake of reviewing it on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what I noticed about the game is that there are real live people that play the game in a making the story work type of capacity.
[SPEAKER_02]: For instance, if you were a new person, you could go to these classes in Myst Online to learn about the world of Myst.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it wasn't an automated thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was actually someone there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like when I went in there, the person said, you know, hello, Sky, are you, because that's an online name I use as most of you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The person said, hello, Sky, are you here for the class today?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like, okay, just take a seat over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get started soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually have people in and I imagine that's got to be a very expensive thing to maintain.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I say kudos to GameTap for giving it a try and if the rest of you are pissed off, be pissed off at the fact that people didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why it shut down.
[SPEAKER_02]: If your MMO doesn't have enough people playing it to keep it running, it shuts down.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the end, though, the rabid fans will find a way to maintain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've had that experience before when I played Myth a long time ago, and when Bungie finally shut down the servers for Myth 2, like,
[SPEAKER_05]: God, how long ago was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Too long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't more than a month before players had brought up their own servers that Bungie actually endorsed and said, hey, you're free to go ahead and play these servers now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll turn the other cheek for this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, Josie16 in chat, chat.org.com says, Missed Online was well thought through.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too bad to see it go.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the problem with Missed Online, even though they had the class and everything, I found it very hard to just get in and go.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like, I think the reason why WoW, like, one reason WoW is so fucking popular is that I don't know how many of you have sat down to play it, you know, despite how you feel about the game, but you can get up and running in World of Warcraft relatively quickly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there's kind of a learning curve as you level from levels 1 to 10, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why people are like, oh, you can get to level 10 in an hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because level 1 to 10 is really the learning curve for noobs, and it really walks you through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the same bitch as Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if Final Fantasy XI didn't have the Final Fantasy name in front of it, that was a very hard game to just get up and running in, to kind of figure out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when we first bought Final Fantasy XI, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: We bought it the day it came out on the PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was back when we were living together.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were so lost the first day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't realize that the world extended beyond the first little area.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like,
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna kill bunnies for the rest of my life!
[SPEAKER_03]: This is fun!
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you go into, what's the thing after, it's Ronfro's the first area.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you go into Lathene Plateau, and you try to kill a bunny there, and they just murder you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're like, I just got raped by a bunny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do you hate me so much?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, now I remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so glad I didn't have to deal with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I miss it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: One game I'm probably not going to miss either is Midway's brand new This is Vegas!
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently if you're too, I don't know, poor to go to Vegas to be a whore or to gamble, you can do it in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't really say what it was that you would be doing in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently you would be able to live out your fantasies in Vegas by fighting, gambling, driving, and partying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Strangely, no mention of hookers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, in the trailer though, there was hooker-like people.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, so this is Vegas, coming to Xbox 360, PS3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'm just, I'm wondering if people are going to start doing, you know, this is Sparta, and this is Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure it's somewhere on YTMND already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure it's already there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a weird idea for a game, but.
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle Quest is going to be getting a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Press release put out this week from D3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was mentioning the forthcoming sequel to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the quote from the press release.
[SPEAKER_02]: The company will also be releasing video games based on Aardman's popular Shaun the Sheep character in 2008 alongside the eagerly awaited follow-ups to the best-selling Ben 10 and Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now see, I don't know what I'm more excited about, sequel to Puzzle Quest or Shaun the Sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never fucking heard of it, but that sounds pretty awesome, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sheep.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't remember Ben 10 being that popular, but okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently it was popular enough for them to make a live-action movie about, even though the only reason I know that is because I watch too much Cartoon Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe something that's more popular in another country, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I've never heard of it personally, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows what 12-year-olds are watching these days other than Hannah Montana.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure this... Don't get me started on how fucking nuts it is that, like, the theaters are, like, packed with little girls and their moms going to see Hannah Montana.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know that movie is, like, crushing everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hear people talking about it at work all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a recording of a concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like... Not a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't talk about how the DS prints money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Miley Cyrus has money coming out her ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder when she's going to do a cover of her dad's achy breaky heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or duet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure this is pure coincidence that I have this story, but apparently Mastiff has licensed the rights to the Major League Eating I didn't even know there was Major League Eating, but apparently they're going to make a Major League Eating game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game will play out like a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we'll show people on screen eating.
[SPEAKER_03]: You will have a mastery of offensive and defensive weapons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like watching this show on Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to watch people eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I am having dinner, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not like, oh, it's the fish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boom, food good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should do that one day on the show, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you will have offensive and defensive weapons, including burps, belches, and mustard gas.
[SPEAKER_02]: This sounds like the ultimate 12-year-old boy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tee hee fart!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, the technical mastery necessary to avoid emptying one's stomach and vividly colored reversals of fortune.
[SPEAKER_03]: As they like to put it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was worth the effort to even make that eloquent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, are you that desperate for licenses?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it is Mastiff, so, you know, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they just came out with a Top Gun DS game, like, not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little late.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, last week we had Major We, and this week we have Major Eating.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd think it would go the other way around.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goddamn, if this isn't a story that won't ever go away, is Apple's getting into gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Apple's getting into gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Newsflash, Apple's kind of already... Well, A, Apple went into gaming a long time ago and didn't do too hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pippin, hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apple's already, like, they're getting their big toe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they're putting their big toe in the water and saying, hmm, me...
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got some pretty awesome games on the iPod now, like Peggle on the iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I've officially reviewed it on the show or whatever, but Peggle on the iPod is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a system that game was made for.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pretty awesome game on the iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Phase, basically Guitar Hero for your iPod of sorts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, more people probably know what I'm talking about when I talk about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to educate them.
[SPEAKER_02]: HitStun in chat says apparently the iPod version of Peggle is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Peggle is probably the best game you can get on the iPod right now, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and I love Sonic the Hedgehog and all that stuff too, but Peggle, just because of the nature of, you know, how you rotate the gun to fire down the... It's like, imagine if Plinko was a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's basically what Peggle is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can rotate the little gun with the dial.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works perfectly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a, like, online version of Price is Right, the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Use the touch wheel to spin the big wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got derailed.
[SPEAKER_02]: We went from Apple to talking about Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: A trademark apparently was filed on February 5th that now has the room reels going again because Apple has updated its trademark to now include toys, games, and playthings, namely handheld units for playing electronic games and
[SPEAKER_02]: Hamheld units for playing video games, standalone video game machines, electronic games other than those adapted for use of television receivers only, LCD game machines, electronic educational game machines, toys, namely battery-powered computer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Safety Net
[SPEAKER_02]: This could be.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just going to make it pink and pretty and stupid idiots will buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brace yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am agreeing with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me of all people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you are an Apple fanboy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do not think that Apple... I think they got lucky with the iPhone jumping into a completely new market, but they... I think if they try to get into gaming, they're going to fail.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't...
[SPEAKER_05]: Style and design is not going to win when it's the software that sells the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm not necessarily talking about the MacBook Air and stuff like that, just that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying they choose to go aesthetics over functionality for a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that works for some people, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the problem is I don't think it's going to work for a console system or it's going to work for a handheld system because they're going to want to change it constantly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the PlayStation 3 does the same damn thing, but still, you can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just going to get confusing, and they're going to want to do a ton of different things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be like the PSP, but they're going to change it a lot more.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not like you can release a new system like you can release a new version of an iPod, and it'll still have the same technology and functionality.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they'll end up releasing something new six months later, and it won't be able to be backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't be surprised if you see the iPod go a little further into gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could totally see them putting out a controller or something that plugs into the iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes more sense, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think that's as far as it's going to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see them releasing a whole new thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see it as some type of extension or enhancement for an iPod.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The best games that will ever come out for an iPod will probably be made...
[SPEAKER_05]: by random people, not by Apple, that use the iPod Touch's touchscreen functionality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, apparently, PopCap might be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which makes sense, because the type of games that PopCap puts out is perfect for the iPod audience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Casual stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Pirates on an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, Part A is about over and we're going to be getting into Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, by the way, if I haven't mentioned yet, in Part B tonight, I've mentioned this a lot actually, we're going to be playing a brand new game we've never played before here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody in chat can play and possibly win tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But before we get to that in Part B, we have to do one more segment here in Part A. And for that, we have to bring somebody special on the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, caller, are you there on the line?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Jamie, how are you feeling?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm feeling stuff that I can't say on the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're just kind of feeling a little sick this week, basically?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's viral.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's never any fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sorry to hear that you're sick, but you'll be back next week, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just didn't want to get you guys sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care about my co-workers so much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I got it from my co-workers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're going to go back and get some more of them sick then, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I figured if they were going to get sick, they would have already gotten sick from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, anyway, Jamie, we just couldn't do this segment without you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're at the end of Part A, as you may know from listening or what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to do the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's get in the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura, what classic game have you picked for the listeners to celebrate this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: The classic game of the week is one of my personal favorites.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Ys III, where it's from Ys, which is, you know, being Ys III, it is the third in the series.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this one's actually different from the other two.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if anyone else was a big fan of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I'm right, this was out on MSX.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was...
[SPEAKER_01]: I got used to the Super Nintendo version, but it was also out on PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, I've actually got the Duo version of this somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the special thing about this one is that it's sort of a departure in gameplay from the previous ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, with this one is that the previous ones were the whole top-down, you know, old-school Zelda-style, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Overhead View, and this one had primarily side-scrolling.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd have to actually mash a button to swing the sword and to attack, and you also had rings that you could equip for different special effects.
[SPEAKER_01]: So instead of having magic, you would use your ring power.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it was a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very, I thought, unique for the time and the type of RPG that it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it also had, like, some really fantastic music.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love this game a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's take a listen to the music real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, one thing I should say about this game, a very common mispronunciation of the title, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it looks like Y's, because it's just the letter Y. It's Ys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's Ys.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, if you actually look at the name, the Japanese title, Romana, it says Isu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that help?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the most recent Ys game, if I'm not mistaken, because I think we brought it up on a previous edition of the show, they ported, or I guess they made a new version of this game for the PSP, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: If I'm right, I think it was Ys V, technically, the Ark of Napis Simp.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then there was a Windows one that was like a remake of Ys III, which was the Earth of Stalkana.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was more like an expansion of Ys III.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, you know, this game is so classic that it still continues to live on today in sequels.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I mean, anyone who's got, you know, Super Nintendo, if you can find this one, you should be able to find it really cheap still.
[SPEAKER_01]: I recommend picking it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe someday a virtual console?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: I would hope so, but we'd probably get Ys I and II before we got Ys III.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there you have it, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your classic game of the week, Wanderers from Ys, the third game in the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: The music you were hearing was from the MSX version, but you can find it also on Super Nintendo and TurboGrafx, if I'm not mistaken?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, it was a Turbo CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Jamie, we look forward to having you back in the house next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rest up and feel better, and say hi to Dan for us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he's in there playing Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you guys have the new Smash Brothers, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, we don't have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: A friend of ours brought it over, and so they've been going through the whole adventure mode in there with the amazingly compatible team of Samus and Pikachu.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: You wait until I'm out, and then you do the new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, because we have to fill time, because you're not here to give us your viewpoint and interrupt Loki when he's talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, DarkSakura, we love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should play in the game tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be funny if you win.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't ever get the show to pull up on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, that's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, DarkSakura, take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next week, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Auf Wiedersehen.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for this Part A here of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break, though, and we'll be back with plenty more.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to close all my chat windows here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to be asking a qualifying question to qualify for tonight's game in Part B. Basically, one contestant will be coming in via the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to give you a question, very similar type of question you might hear in tonight's game.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you think you know the answer you're going to send me the answer in a private message in the chat room if you don't know how to send me a private message ask somebody and you are going to send me your phone number and by sending me your phone number that is consent that you approve of us calling you please make sure you are by your phone in the next hour or so
[SPEAKER_02]: and that we don't get any surprises of mommy or daddy picking it up so don't submit an answer to this if you do not have control over your own phone so here it is this is the qualifier question you're gonna send me the correct answer to this question and then you are going to send me your phone number if you want to play and we'll pick somebody randomly out of those that submit the correct phone number so here it is and I'm putting this in the podcast because I felt those listening in the podcast might want to play along
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the qualifying question.
[SPEAKER_02]: What game is this music from?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't yell it out in chat or you're giving it away for everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here are the correct answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, one of these is the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here are the answers you have to choose from.
[SPEAKER_02]: A, Nightmare on Elm Street.
[SPEAKER_02]: B, Halloween.
[SPEAKER_02]: C, Friday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: After tonight's break.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.