[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: But the problem was he already bought the game, so he has no use for the code.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to pay it forward tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of our OLR listeners is going to pass on the code to our winner tonight of the match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So thank you, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody say it with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to be giving that away a little later in the show, but before we do that, we have got to get back into some gaming news, and Loki's going to kick it off tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_07]: There's two big games that they announced on Nintendo's reports for 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a huge surprise, though, that Animal Crossing and the new Kirby game are coming to the Wii in 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most likely, though, it's only the Japanese Wii in 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe shortly after, in 2009, we'll see Animal Crossing here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully, though, I would hope it's this year as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no word on exactly what, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii Music, Disaster Day of Crisis, Super Mario Stadium, Baseball, and Everyone's Common Knowledge Television, which I'm assuming is not coming over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It also shows Mario Kart Wii, still expected for Spring in North America, and Quarter 2 for Europe.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, do we know anything more about that Animal Crossing on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, is it actually going to be an MMO or anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, all we just kind of know is it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and I would imagine keep your expectations low because if you're expecting an MMO from Nintendo, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't embrace online, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point, good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, I do love my Animal Crossing, so I'm hopeful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's just leave it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hopeful.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, if Animal Crossing and Kirby don't do it for... Actually, wait, let me backtrack a little bit, because I know, DarkSakura, you're a big Animal Crossing fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: If Nintendo happens to be listening right now, what do you hope that they implement in the next Animal Crossing game on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would actually like to see... And maybe this is a little bit odd, but I'd like to see a character be able to be the mayor, I think, of the town, instead of having...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be the Tom Nook conglomerate.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like to see you be able to control development of the town.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, new shops, new things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sort of expand the whole thing that makes a town work.
[SPEAKER_08]: So like a promotion?
[SPEAKER_08]: A way to promote?
[SPEAKER_08]: Get a job and promote up so you're just not Tom Nook's bitch the whole time?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want the ability to put Tom Nook out of work.
[SPEAKER_07]: and put him on the street.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make him do bitch work for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make him sleep with the fishes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you a big fan of Animal Crossing, Moe?
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually have issues with Animal Crossing and Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're too boring.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about Kirby?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you a fan of Kirby?
[SPEAKER_12]: I do like Kirby.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you hope they put in the next Kirby game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, if it's going on the Wii, they should do something like Canvas Curse.
[SPEAKER_12]: Canvas Curse was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Canvas Curse was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Parappa the Rapper
[SPEAKER_08]: and yeah, it's another music-based game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Major Miners Majestic March.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, it's Major Miner Majestic March.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming from designer Masuya Matsura and artist Rodney Greenblatt.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what you're going to be doing in the game, you use the Wii Remote to keep tempo.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Unjamalami 2 on the Wii
[SPEAKER_10]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you a band nerd, Mo?
[SPEAKER_12]: I wasn't a band nerd.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was a theater geek.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were a theater geek.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was the AV nerd and the theater geek.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think this game might still appeal to you?
[SPEAKER_12]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I could wave my hands around like a tardigan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it'll be like most Wii games?
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be fun for an hour and then sell it back?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you excited about Major Miners?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no interest in this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then let's go to the next story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for our soccer fans, actually, well, I'm sure there's plenty of soccer fans in the UK, as in real football.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have my own bias.
[SPEAKER_10]: Electronic Arts, though, is saying that they are not releasing UEFA Euro 2008 on Wii and DS in Europe at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, they pretty much have the market, I think, because they had FIFA 08 last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Euro 2008 Euro 2008
[SPEAKER_08]: Am I the only one that sees the humor in that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're just not bringing down the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of the two soccer games that EA puts out, it's the lesser of the two.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it doesn't sell very well over here, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, fine, Debbie Downer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one likes obscure soccer games, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'll just play FIFA if they want to play FIFA.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it's just like...
[SPEAKER_07]: EA tries to put all these weird ones out there like Arena Football or Rugby and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, don't knock the Rugby game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I'm sure in their respective areas they're good, but no one buys them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or at least not that many people buy them.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe one of these new games will prove you wrong, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe this game will prove us wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eternity's Child.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game that was originally designed to come out on the Xbox 360 as part of the XNA program, but now they've been porting that over to the WiiWare service that's still not out yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is scheduled sometime quarter to 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will set you back 500 Wii points, so it's nice to see that there will be some more inexpensive games on the WiiWare service.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all hand-drawn by cartoonist Luke Bernard, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty cool looking platform game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully we'll hear more about the WiiWare service in a couple weeks during Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm guessing that's when they're going to drop the bomb on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, WiiWare should have been out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: We thought it was going to come out late last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it should be coming out sooner rather than later, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_08]: JAPAN SOLD HALF MILLION COPIES OF SMASH BROTHERS BRAWL IN ONE DAY
[SPEAKER_08]: Those numbers coming from a Japanese blog, Amiibo.jp.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, it's reported that Brawl is the fastest-selling Wii title.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sold through 80% of its initial stock, and that was 500,000 copies.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now everybody's wondering, is it going to match that in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Mo, I know you work in a game shop, so you take pre-orders for this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does it look like it's going to smash records left and right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Jesus Christ, yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Japan has a smaller market than the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: does anyways, and that's not even counting Europe, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll easily sell 500,000 copies in one day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't be surprised if it sells a million copies in the first day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, how many people in America actually own Wiis, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be about...
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be done.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be about one in eight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Still more and more selling, you know, as this date approaches in March, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think you could top Halo?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Day one, probably not, but overall, I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Overall, maybe, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it might top Halo 3, but not Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Halo 3 was pretty huge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, in the long run.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the long run.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I believe Halo 2 doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every game's going to be Grand Theft Auto 4's bitch anyway, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how many copies of, you know, Grand Theft Auto San Andreas sold just because of the drama over that, do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, how many people now do you think are going to be, oh, what's this one going to do?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going to be the new thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I think that honestly it is going to sort of overplay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope not, but I'm pretty sure it will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, look how amazing Grand Theft Auto 3 was when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just absolutely awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I took a day off of work to play that game, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I took off a week of school to play Final Fantasy VI
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy VI is pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: You would need like a whole week off of work, though, when that game first came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I pretended I had the flu.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on with some more gaming news and things we might call in sick for in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know that I'd be calling in sick for this if I can... There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stupid Firefox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo has registered a patent for a casing for Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it is quoted as saying, A video game controller for video game and receptor assembly.
[SPEAKER_10]: A receptor having a shape substantially similar to a component appearing in the video game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The receptor may be a gun-shaped subunit, is what it also says.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there's a drawing that was included with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're actually, in fact, I'm pulling up the drawing right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: A Teddy Bear?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm pulling up the drawings now just to see everything else that was on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, Acrobat is slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, DarkSakura in our chat room at chat.originalsradio.com exclaims what some of us are saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are they really considering doing some of those?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, a teddy bear?
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of those are just what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's kind of stupid for them to even try to patent, you know, putting, you know, like a tennis racket or fishing rod controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've already got them out there for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're a little late to the game, just like they were with the whole zapper attachment and stuff for the, you know, the Wii and also the Wii wheel that's going to be coming out with Mario Kart, which is completely retarded, but
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, I guess people want that crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't make a game any better.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have to go really into detail as far as these patents go, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will immediately throw away that wheel when it comes with Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Out the window it will go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, there's the one on here for the wheel, and the one that looks like the zapper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is sort of cool, but the helmet one, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've had virtual reality helmets from Nintendo before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they trying to give us all migraines again?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I still haven't forgiven them for the virtual boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: The chair is kind of cool, but they have one also that looks like it's trying to remake the Power Glove.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's so bad!
[SPEAKER_10]: There is...
[SPEAKER_10]: The racket one makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a skateboard one on here, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the bike is like, what are they going to do, bring us Prop Cycle?
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting thought from AlphaCanongram in chat says, it's to prevent others from creating crap to ruin the Wii, but it didn't work.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they've already, that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: If this was to prevent other people from making this crap, they're a little late.
[SPEAKER_07]: They already have this stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't patent something after it's already been out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess maybe you can, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know really they should be threatened by putting a Wiimote in a teddy bear.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I would do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is it for, like some teddy bear hugging game?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so I can hug him and squeeze him and love him.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the baby shaking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You see, but they can't use a baby, so they have like a teddy bear.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can shake the teddy bear all you want to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kill Teddy Ruxpin the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they are, and I have to, this is coming out sometime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: within the next few months, they are bringing the Build-A-Bear workshop to the Wii instead of just the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can create virtual bears.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do it on the DS already.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I did not pay 80 bucks a piece.
[SPEAKER_12]: But do you still have to do the little dance with your hands in the air and the spinning?
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least I can do it in the privacy of my own home.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's another bright idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently someone thought it was an awesome idea to bring out Saw, the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: That seems like fan service or something to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, this is... Brash Entertainment has made an announcement that they're going to make an interactive Saw game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it going to be like Manhunt?
[SPEAKER_12]: And get banned everywhere?
[SPEAKER_07]: And even worse than Manhunt somehow?
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's just going to be PlayStation 3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the other thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking, though, they're going to try to build off the controversy of Manhunt 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course...
[SPEAKER_07]: 2009 people will forget about Manhunt 2, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, this game is so wrong on so many levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did a story on Manhunt 2 last week and I've already forgotten about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because A, you know, obviously people are totally, you know, they look at video games and movies in complete different ways when, you know, obviously they shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the Saw franchise is just as gory as, you know, Manhunt 2 and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is just going to continue to give video games a bad name and fuel Lord Voldemort's fire in the courts.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we call, rhymes with
[SPEAKER_08]: And that means we have to bring in the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first of my FUs of the week, because I have had a pretty crazy week, goes towards needles.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm not really afraid of needles, because, um, I don't know, I'm just really not afraid of needles anymore, but this is a really big freaking needle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got a cortisone shot in my hand, and it actually wasn't that bad, because my regular doctor is really cool and lets me watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other doctor wouldn't let me watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was mean.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: But then my hand hurt for a couple of days and I couldn't play anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I have to go to an orthopedist next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm a little bit antsy about surgery because I've only ever had surgery once in my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that was Wisdom Teeth.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know how long I was messed up after that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Four months.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, F you to my stupid tendons.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you have any FUs of the week you'd like to give out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, my FU of the week goes to Microsoft for making the shoddy system of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm tired of having to fix this stupid three-ring system.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really pissing me off because what I have to do to fix it, in other words, take a heat gun to it, involves me pulling off the heat sink and then I heat it up and do all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to put a boiler at it so it looks like I'm actually cooking the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then after that works, I have to put everything back together, reapply, you know, the...
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been doing this at work, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, have all the parts strewn all across, you know, the conference room table.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, uh, this last time, this better fucking work, because I am getting really fed up with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other system I fixed works perfectly.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one is being a little bitch and won't fucking work, so... Fuck Microsoft, because there's no reason that I should have two systems dying to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU of the week goes to insomnia because I've had it most of the week and I think it was causing me to get sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'd like to counteractively give a thank you of the week to Airborne because vitamin C is awesome and made me not get totally sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: But FU to lack of sleep and getting sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mo, I don't know if you're familiar with this segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have anything you'd like to just say FU to on the air?
[SPEAKER_12]: The fact that I still suck at Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will never get first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just never will.
[SPEAKER_12]: Console.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give me a keyboard and a mouse, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe just some people weren't built to play console shooters.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can get the running down, and I can get the shooting down, but if you want me to point, I'm screwed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just use the caboose method.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let everyone else kill each other off.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, they all know that I'm the weaker player, so everyone picks me off in multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, I know you're busy with Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl, but do you have anything you'd like to give an F you to?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything that's making you angry?
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazingly, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, F you to you for being so perky.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the cool thing about this game is you can actually pause it and then rotate around and take snapshots.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, for those that weren't listening to the bonus segment, we are playing Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl here in studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake's walking us through the game here, and you can watch the action on our Justin.TV feed, which should be archived.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure somebody will make a highlight out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Justin.TV slash Orange Lounge Radio if you want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not for much longer.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to be pointing the camera back on the studio very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Black Lab in chat says we need more studio view on cam and less Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Soon, I promise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe after a couple more matches.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, that's going to do it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get back into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this almost makes me want to bring on the FUs of the week again because I'm so ready for this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Spore...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, apparently now, during an EA conference call, the CEO of EA, John Riccatello, told the audience that Spore will not be making fiscal 08.
[SPEAKER_08]: But will it be making calendar year 08 at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or will it be actually pushed back to 2009?
[SPEAKER_08]: And still within the 2009 fiscal year, but literally like a year from now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the CEO was not going to give a specific date.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does seem, though, confident that the game will be out before the holidays.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that could be like December 24th.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, actually, it could be after Christmas because it could be like Kwanzaa he's talking about as the holidays.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be Chinese New Year, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be January, who knows.
[SPEAKER_12]: It could be July 4th, that's still a holiday.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, of 2009.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows, but I don't like hearing that Spore keeps getting delayed because I'm so ready for this game to come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think he celebrates sleep year as a holiday, so he's referring to next sleep year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, let's get back to some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I do have some happy in regards to Knights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank God, we need it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you, Sega.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're having different, I would have to say, celebrations that go on every month as far as different content in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, they say that you use the Wii Weather Channel to change the weather.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is another bit of additional hidden content.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you basically raise your own A-Life and the hidden content will let you have different monthly celebrations since it's going by the Wii's time clock.
[SPEAKER_10]: So in January they have of course the New Year with fireworks.
[SPEAKER_10]: In February they have the Chinese New Year.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they have a big dragon hanging out and firecrackers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: In March it's carnivals and the people in the game will have masks on
[SPEAKER_10]: April is Flamenco-inspired roses.
[SPEAKER_10]: May is the Boys Festival, which is a Japanese holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's May 5th, and there's a big carp streamer hanging in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: June is weddings.
[SPEAKER_10]: July is the Bull Running Festival.
[SPEAKER_10]: August, all the residents in the game are going to be playing instruments.
[SPEAKER_10]: September has full moon paper fans.
[SPEAKER_10]: October is the Halloween theme with witches and pumpkin lanterns and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: November is autumn leaves falling and fruit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And December is Santa and the Christmas tree and all kinds of Christmassy stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_10]: Christmas nights, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if this is going to actually break my household tradition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you've never said that on the show before, that you love Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think every week Jamie finds a reason to bring up Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, happy 4th of July, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to play Christmas nights this December.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ever since I moved to California, every Christmas we break out Saturn and we play Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's having to tell this story to Moe because she's like, oh, Moe maybe hasn't heard this before.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just like telling the story.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like Christmas night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Traditions are good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did have to borrow my French-Japanese copy of Christmas night since it's exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just gets a nice hard case and not a paper case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: This sounds like a fun way to at least pop in the game once a month and kind of check it out, see what's going on, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a cool thing, but what if they have a...
[SPEAKER_10]: Different things to happen, you know, over different years, you know, something that could be updated in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, remember, like, Animal Crossing had all the funny stuff that happened on holidays, and it gave you a reason to, like, turn on the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, even New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played in six months.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's New Year's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if you don't want to wait a year long, just mess with your time clock in your Wii, and you can see all these within, like, an hour.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the spirit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, cheater.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not cheating.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm exploiting time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never give this man a TARDIS.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, why don't you exploit some more news for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the latest copy of the official Xbox magazine has the content for Rock Band outlined for March, which reminds me that I haven't bought the February issue of the official Xbox magazine, which had those three free tracks on there with freeze pop and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puppy has the CD, one of our frequent guests, Puppy, and maybe I'll make him come to the show next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So bring your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puppy, come to the show next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bring Xbox Magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, some of the packs that they have outlined, March 4th, we're getting the Thrash Pack, which is going to have At the Gates, Blinded by Fear, Evil Thrashes, The Haunted with Shadow World,
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not familiar with any of those, but here at the gates, Blind About Fear is supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: On March 11th, they've got some individual songs, including Bad Company with Shooting Star, which is a cover, Leonard Skinner with Simple Man, and The Police with Message in a Bottle.
[SPEAKER_07]: March 18th, they have the Nine Inch Nails Pack, including March of the Pigs, The Collector, and The Perfect Drug.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, March 25th,
[SPEAKER_07]: has the metal pack with Iron Maiden's Wraith Child, which is a cover, Black Sabbath Supernaut, which is a cover, and the one I'm really looking forward to, Metallica with Fuel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that song I said should have been in Rock Band in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm assuming all of them are going to be $4.40 for the pack and $1.60 for each song individually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_08]: No idea though what's coming out for February though.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, those of you guys on the Wii have been missing out on all this Rock Band goodness, but maybe not for much longer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, going back to the EA conversation, apparently it was confirmed that there is the coming launch of Rock Band for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: The CEO, John Riccatello, referred to a coming launch of the Wii version of Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: And IGN said, I don't know, they just really wanted to seek out a firm confirmation that
[SPEAKER_08]: and got him to admit that yes, the game will be making a Wii debut.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no release date given, nothing else given.
[SPEAKER_08]: But by the way, in a related story, I don't know if you heard about this, but some standalone microphones came out for Rock Band and they say something on them about works on the Nintendo Wii, which is hilarious because there is no Rock Band on the Wii yet and they don't work anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: So EA had to put out a My Bad right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that'll be a retail nightmare when the Wii version does come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: People say, I bought this microphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: It said it's going to work on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't understand why they don't work on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a fucking USB microphone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, those have got to be pretty standardized anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the USB on Nintendo is retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, like USB .5.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually slower than USB 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, now it's time for us to get to one of our favorite segments here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a chance for you to talk to us a little bit with the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every week you send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura picks out a few of her favorites and reads them on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, DarkSakura, why don't you put your hand in the mail back there and pull out a few emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did we get a lot of emails this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God, we did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess you can't read them all, but pick some of your favorites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there were a couple that were really long, including one from our friend who made us the offer from Disney World.
[SPEAKER_02]: We must do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're making jokes about the stalker thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: We know better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, this one, um, is, um, I'm just going to use, go by the email name, uh, Lord Katakos, because there's no signature on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I am new to the podcast, and I was wondering if you guys and girl ever talked about MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_10]: I enjoy this game a lot, um, a lot more than Ragnarok, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, anyway, my undead mage could destroy any of your World of Warcraft accounts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you guys, uh, like, got the micro and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep giving out the spanks to the noobs.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, that is my priest pic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I'm on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he sent a picture titled Ugly Mages.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the mailbag is got PMS.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it doesn't let me actually really get to take a look at the images.
[SPEAKER_10]: So sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have never played MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of people that like it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you played it, Mo?
[SPEAKER_12]: I loved MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell us a little bit about MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just... Well, that's a cute little banner.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell us a little bit about MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like Ragnarok, where it has the little guy avatars and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just another RPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a chibi good time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it's a chibi good time.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're supposed to be making one for DS, and I'm waiting for that anxiously.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would never happen, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It should be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, okay, so it looks like there are some MapleStory fans here, so you're in good company.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one actually is addressed to Loki from Azurame.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't quite remember, but in a past episode of OLR, I remember you stating you were able to play games on your Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this true?
[SPEAKER_10]: Please answer back, thanks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it means the imports, which we've obviously proven.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I can play games on my Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you've been listening to tonight's show, obviously since we have Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl in the house and it's an import copy, yes, you can play import.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because I have a mod chip in mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one comes from Osfer.
[SPEAKER_10]: It turns out my parents will finally be getting high-speed internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, believe it or not, I've had to suffer the pains and torture of dial-up for years.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I resort to web browsing on my iPhone for now.
[SPEAKER_10]: iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: But in about a week, I'll be able to finally listen live and even work up the nerve to call in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Talking to you guys would be like talking to celebrities, so yeah, I'd be nervous.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm sure talking about gaming would put me at ease.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks, and I hope to be a live listener soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: How come I can't access your chat room on iPhone?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've done it with other sites before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it because it's Java?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: The iPhone has problems with Java, but I think that
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't updated my software on my iPhone yet, so maybe that will change.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know I can't watch any YouTube videos if they're embedded, unless I actually just use the YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's because it's the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, iPhone's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, and I didn't mean to sound like I was bashing our emailer when they said that talking to us would be like talking to celebrities.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just, you know, it's a compliment.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, we're just...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't card Moe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can pull out my wallet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm 22.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I want to really quickly, before I get to the next email, I'm so sorry, but there was a very good question asked in chat that I think is a thing to address right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And someone in chat, they didn't change their nickname, so I just know them as OLARMYRecruit9348 says, someone please tell me how to find Moe on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it made me realize I'm so rude.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never let Moe plug her stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So please, plug away.
[SPEAKER_08]: How can they find your performance from Moe?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can look up the username Amixia.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you can actually go to youtube.com slash Amixia.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's A-M-I-X-I-A and it's me being a retard with my digital camera and the color tends to change because it's a really bad video camera.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's awesome, but it's me being a retard.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Amixia on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're listening to us being retards right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It works.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're in good company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other websites you work with?
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a live journal.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can check all my YouTube stuff on there because I'll post those publicly.
[SPEAKER_12]: My username is Furious, spelled exactly like Furious.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have the most awesome username ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a pretty good username.
[SPEAKER_08]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_12]: I also have a website.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's...
[SPEAKER_12]: Pride.net, and I never update it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the last video on there was never going to give you up, so I should probably fix that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's just like we have a PSP site that I never update.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't update our websites either.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Pride.net has updates.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were supposed to have a new URL on our website like the first of the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: It didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now there you go to our listener.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, you can get back to emails now, but that was something very important.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is very important.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is.
[SPEAKER_10]: So next one comes from Ali.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ali.
[SPEAKER_10]: On episode 264, I'm glad you're keeping track of episode numbers because I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki goes on an anti-MacBook Air rant.
[SPEAKER_10]: As an Apple fanboy, I must say that the MacBook Air is a triumph of engineering and a beautiful machine, and I don't think it was intended to play video games on.
[SPEAKER_10]: As an Apple stockholder, I can say the MacBook Air blows chunks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Insert love the show drivel here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not that I have a problem with it not being able to play games, I really don't care, and I'm sure it can because it's got a core 2D processor in it, but it's just that it doesn't have a CD-ROM drive, or a DVD-ROM drive, or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to basically hijack a drive off another computer, or you have to buy a $99 drive that plugs into the single USB port that's on the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just not very... Yeah, it's thin, okay, props for that, and I'm sure it has a nice battery life, but it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Once again, all aesthetics and no functionality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio, the finest in video game radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We never talk computers at all, just video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Computers play games, therefore it works.
[SPEAKER_07]: We talk consoles, consoles play games too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine, fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, can I keep going now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: This comes from Ryoma.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, I was just listening to Part B of Episode 265 today, and as excited as I was to hear you talk about Smash Brawl, I have a little something to add to your discussion about the demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the Japan Official Smash Brawl page, there are two more demos that seem to be exclusive to Japan, Mother 2, Earthbound of course, and the original Fire Emblem, which is where Marth comes from.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, I understand that those two games are out on the Japanese Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, I'm pretty irritated with the fact that Nintendo seems to love to torture us Americans, apologies to all overseas listeners, with the idea of having a new Mother game having Earthbound ported to the GBA, DS, VC, what have you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still love Nintendo to death, and the only next-gen system I have is a Wii, but their seeming lack of interest in what American gamers want is growing frustrating.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just made two cents with much love from Chicago, Ryoma.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can understand why they're not bringing some of those games over, because Earthbound, I'm sure, has quite a bit of dialogue in there, and they have to localize it, where it's not just, I can throw a copy of the ROM onto the Virtual Console Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I don't understand why they wouldn't put something they'd say localized in
[SPEAKER_07]: The UK and bring it over here because, I don't know, that's just lazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, The Doctor here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just to ask what happened to random talk about Battlestar Galactica?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shane moved away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just wondering because after a while, DarkSakura just stopped.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never talked about Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're getting her confused with Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Rob, you still need to send me that MP3 file, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Battlestar Galactica comes back in April.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure you will hear random Battlestar Galactica chat come back in April.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because this show never gets derailed, ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been busy playing Wild Arms and Castlevania Symphony of the Night on my PSP after I paid for them on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_10]: some Call of Duty 4 actually a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and Rez.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck yeah, Rez.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck yes, Rez.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is one addicting game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listening to last week's show while writing this, they retracted their retraction.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, it was literally a WTF, but I like saying what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Rob, I challenge you to some Undertow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, I was going to go now so you guys can move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Peace.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really bad at Undertow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think you want to play me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play me at something I'm like halfway decent at, like Puzzle Fighter or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have one more email that's really, really, really, really, really freaking long.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Sky, Loki, DarkSakura, and guest host.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_10]: First, let me apologize for my bad grammar, as I know you tend to be a stickler for proper grammar, and I tend to disregard proper grammar and spelling whenever I write anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm used to IMing, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, bite me.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_11]: I brought you cake.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: You did buy me cake.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was delicious cake.
[SPEAKER_11]: Email.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was delicious and moist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Delicious and moist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, Oscar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Regarding the Fox News report on Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_12]: End of email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lately with news, it seems that the way to get a top story on the news is simply find something that has a soap opera or scandal written all over it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Scandal sell, and it also had to do with sex, which we know the old saying about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, children, since the stereotype to a lot of non-gamers is video games are kid stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were I a news show producer or a news show host and saw something that implied there was a lesbian sex scene in Mass Effect, I would run with a trashy story like that because if it is true, that can mean a big ratings hike for the show and a possible raise slash promotion for yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since video games are considered the current evil that is corrupting our youth, much like rock and roll in the 50s and 60s, violent films in the 80s and 90s, and rock and roll, again, just before the focus shifted to video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know that was both Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, him, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still remember journalists trying to pin the Columbine High School Massacre on Marilyn Manson.
[SPEAKER_10]: It makes any scandalous video game story easy prey.
[SPEAKER_10]: With a chance that could be...
[SPEAKER_10]: that could get a casual gamer concerned parents and people who would act like sex in video games I gotta see what games they mention and start playing them as well as your regular audience to tune in when they might not have also since few outside of gaming world would read or hear any follow up on the story on the net regarding the false statements of the report it would be a quick and easy reading so not everyone would have heard the bad journalism backlash disgusting?
[SPEAKER_10]: yes but it also means modern day journalism tactics as well ok discuss so I can take a break
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, you're preaching to the choir here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do understand probably any network would have done it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's something about the whole sensationalism of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like Fox News in general has kind of done this stuff before.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_08]: CNN probably would do something like this too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean it just kind of depends on  but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actual news to be reported on out there with an election going on right now and things going on in other countries and things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just shouldn't waste our time with that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, and didn't they pull the statement like a couple days later when her book on Amazon started getting tanking reviews?
[SPEAKER_08]: She sort of said, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: She was like, oh, okay, maybe Mass Effect wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of like a half-assed apology, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was like, I made a real bad judgment call or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But she didn't really say, I'm sorry, gamers, or I'm sorry to the gaming community and to the mature gamers out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: She didn't really say anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: She just said, oh, I done fucked up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't make a statement on Fox News 1, and then once you realize that your review on Amazon is dropping hugely, it took a nosedive.
[SPEAKER_12]: She was like, okay, maybe Mass Effect wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to read out of that email?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's plenty more.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: As for the... Well, you know, really this is... Actually, I do have to say this is actually more of what...
[SPEAKER_10]: We've discussed on the show as well, but I really do like this email, and I'm going to post it on the forum, if I remember to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to move on to the drinking game portion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: In other news, I know the game series is a bit touchy subject for you guys and already has great music, but how would a custom soundtrack of Dragon Force or Death Clock be for a Katamari game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Metalocalypse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it would really change my outlook on the franchise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love its fun, cheesy quirkiness, and I think Dragon Force soundtrack version of the game would make me love it even more for its mass chaos, death, and destruction, as I do love games with mass carnage.
[SPEAKER_10]: One last thing, sorta.
[SPEAKER_10]: The OLR drinking games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Got a big laugh at the chatroom saying, take a drink whenever Loki leads off the story with anyways, since that first was the first thing that crossed my mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am very conscious of that now, and I have been not saying that.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's okay, because now it's part of the drinking game and you want people to drink.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't want them to die.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: They already take a shot every time I say an off-color comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every five seconds?
[SPEAKER_07]: People should be rushed to the hospital already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, he has some suggestions for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whenever the show goes off on a tangent about food... Hey, we've had cake all night, so... Mmm, cake.
[SPEAKER_10]: Delicious cake.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whenever there is Sony bashing after some Sony news...
[SPEAKER_10]: The word addict is used after someone mentions playing an MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anytime a and he uses the blanking expletive is used outside of the FUs of the week segment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, they can't do that on me then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anytime DarkSakura goes What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need the ferret.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whenever Loki bashes the Mac
[SPEAKER_10]: Anytime there's a mention of that former video game channel that shall not be named.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anytime there's a mention of that blood-sucking lawyer that shall not be named.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, GameProTV?
[SPEAKER_07]: With the dreamy J.D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Roth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anytime Rob says heart to DarkSakura after making fun of her.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was the opposite this time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Raven's Dolphin is the first caller on the Skyplane segment...
[SPEAKER_11]: and any mention of Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any caller that calls in on a Skype line that's got a bad connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there is a whole thread going on in the forums and I encourage you to add to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are actually making an OLR drinking game in the thread.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's some more examples of what's going on in the thread here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, Sky, take a drink every time Sky says, fired.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_08]: Mentions the bet or the tingle costume thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tells a joke that no one laughs at or is met with resounding silence.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura gives an F you to bad drivers or her co-workers or to stupid people in general mentions Shermie the cat and says reject false icons as her final thought
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't said that in a very long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, how can you not get into a discussion about the Olive Garden when it gets mentioned?
[SPEAKER_12]: The minestrone soup is delicious.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the minestrone soup.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too many beans in the minestrone soup, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's what makes it so great.
[SPEAKER_10]: The potato soup.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go back to Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_10]: I owe you anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of which, kind of going on a food tangent here real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drink.
[SPEAKER_07]: They started carrying these soups at Rayleigh's now where it's
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually the soup from the guy in New York, you know, the soup Nazi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, they call him the Soup Man, but not Soup Nazi.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I tried one the other day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, it looked cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: The prospect of getting soup from him, you know, was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: No soup for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Come back in one year.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the fuck did that have to do with video gaming?
[SPEAKER_12]: Tangent food!
[SPEAKER_12]: Food tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Were you paying attention?
[SPEAKER_07]: I finish eating!
[SPEAKER_07]: Email!
[SPEAKER_07]: You cook soup in Cookie Mama.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're Ford's video game related, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_07]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I love the show, keep up the great work, and I've really enjoyed DarkSakura's Classic Game of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really do miss the old advice column.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to see it come back.
[SPEAKER_10]: My advice is, don't be stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sound advice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you guys are ever in the Napa area, feel free to drop me an email.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be glad to take you and your spouses slash boyfriends to dinner at their restaurants around the valley.
[SPEAKER_08]: Free food.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love deals for free food.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a huge massive PS, but Rob, I'm going to leave it for you to read your part later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to get back to some news now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shula Shula
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: CryEngine 2, at least the console port of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: at the Game Developers Conference, which is coming up actually in a couple weeks here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So hopefully because of that, we will see maybe Crysis come to, you know, console system.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember some talks, or rumors at least, of Crysis coming to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that'd be pretty cool to see happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: But either way, you know, maybe give something else for game companies to use other than the Unreal 3 engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and now their engine is fully optimized because if you play it on the PC, the thing eats your PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, no matter what kind of hardware you have in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess because it wasn't fully optimized.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Crytek, for putting out a wonderfully polished game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not optimized one bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if Crysis isn't your thing, which I don't know, I haven't really gotten into Crysis, but I don't know, I could probably get into this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's coming to North America soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a game called Arcana Heart, and it's coming to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, here's the thing about this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an all-girl fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All babes duking it out in the arena.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of like the Asuka 100% series or...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not quite dead or alive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's just put it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are fully clothed girls, at least the ones here in this screenshot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, there's a lack of boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, there is a severe lack of boobies, which is an important issue.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we do have a little bit of panties in that particular shot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Samus.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyhow, Atlas has said that the PS2 is still a viable platform.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no reason to abandon a veteran system just because it isn't the newest thing around.
[SPEAKER_08]: So some of the Japanese titles that haven't made its way over here yet, Atlas Plans, or sorry,
[SPEAKER_08]: Atlas plans to bring over here to the States pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Arcana Heart has been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will be coming out on April 8th.
[SPEAKER_08]: 11 different customizable girl fighters.
[SPEAKER_08]: $29.99 is the price.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: We certainly don't have working designs anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well it's about time for us to play a match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what time it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's time for the match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need some theme music for match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Jake, you're going to have to pause Smash Brothers for a little bit because we need you to play a match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, the way a match game works, well, let me get the contestants, then we'll do a match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Mo, why don't you come over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't have a whole lot of people say me, but we have about that area right there is a few people that said me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So which one of those names do you think is the best, which should play tonight in the match game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mo's thinking.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburger is going to be our chat room player tonight in the match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburgers are pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Cheeseburger left chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's epic fail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye, Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_08]: You lost your opportunity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so who else do we have?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Cheeseburger, you left at just like the wrong time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we have One Night Stands as now our player.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll get in touch with you in chat shortly.
[SPEAKER_08]: And let's open up the Skype line if you want to play with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is something burning?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it might be the thing behind you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just that hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, is anybody calling us yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe nobody wants to play on Skype, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, here we go, we have a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, SSJ100Matt, congratulations, you're going to be our other contestant on the match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you get to play against One Night Stands in chat, who has yet to confirm with me that he is playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is live radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_01]: Live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Should we cue up the Jeopardy music?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we should just play the theme music again because it's so much fun to listen to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see him freaking out.
I see him freaking out in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I think he got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There he is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I think he's got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He sent me a private message.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, SSJ100Matt, you ready to do this?
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt, you there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think everything's broken tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let me remind you all how this works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Jake, you gotta pause the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me remind everybody how this works.
[SPEAKER_08]: What we're going to do is we're going to have three questions for you tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in the questions, they all have a blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a blank somewhere in the answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ever watch the match game in the 70s?
[SPEAKER_08]: The reruns on Game Show Network?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, it's just like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boy, game stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to ask three questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: There will be a blank in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So our celebrities will think about their answer and write it down on a little piece of paper.
[SPEAKER_08]: On my invisible keyboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then our callers will try to match.
[SPEAKER_08]: and for every celebrity they match, they get a point.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how it works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, all you have to do is think of something funny that goes in the blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or real.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all you have to do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go for funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully one night Stan is understanding what's going on because I just got a message that says, Sweet, I don't know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which means you're probably going to win.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100, Matt, you're up against some stiff competition tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did Cheeseburger come back?
[SPEAKER_10]: Cheeseburger came back and said, what did I miss?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's what we'll do since we have a code.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it ties 0-0 tonight, if nobody manages to get a point on the board, then we'll give Cheeseburger the code.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so Cheeseburger is hoping that everybody is broke.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll hope that everyone's a failure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody fill in time while I type out how to play this to One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Zero Samus on screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was funny, though, because... I think we have Kirby getting smashed.
[SPEAKER_07]: She has, like, her suit, but there's, like, a thong built into the suit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, he understands now.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, she has a thong and shiny ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, enough of the porno here.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so we have One Night Stands, SSJ100 Matt, and Cheeseburger playing tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's our first three-way match game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburger is simply hoping that no one matches anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go, question number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura was not happy to see Jigglypuff return to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, she likes to always look on the bright side.
[SPEAKER_08]: She let all her friends know that she will actually be looking forward to Jigglypuff in the game because she can kill her by blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is not happy that Jigglypuff is in the game, but no worries, she can kill her by blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_11]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have an answer, Mo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't say it yet, but do you know one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have one, Jake?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, he has one.
[SPEAKER_08]: S2100 Matt, do you have an answer just in your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I got one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I'm waiting for One Night Stance to send me an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So once again, the question...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura was not happy to see Jigglypuff return to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, she likes to always look on the bright side.
[SPEAKER_08]: She let all her friends know that she will actually be looking forward to Jigglypuff in the game because she can kill her by blank.
[SPEAKER_08]: And One Night Stands is still trying to come up with an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a tough question.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a hard question.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma, that was me doing the laugh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you talk a little more about... Oh, okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: She can kill her by... What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Having Kirby eat her.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And OneNightStan says she can kill her by... Thwomp smash.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thwomp smash.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if there's a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, she can kill her by...
[SPEAKER_10]: by repeatedly bashing her in the head with Mr. Saturn until she dies a bleeding, horrible, oozy death.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be a very difficult one to match, but it's a good answer, but unfortunately not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ladies first.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mo, she can kill her by?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to say Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rape, sweet rape.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, from Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, gosh, look at the time.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Rape O'Clock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: What time is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Raping time.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone knows the show already.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kept it pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: She can kill her by... Fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire!
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like all these answers so far.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake.
[SPEAKER_08]: She can kill her by...
[SPEAKER_08]: I also went with fire because fire always makes it better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, fire would have been a great answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my answer was she could kill her by, in reference to last week, condemned to explosive babies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, also not a match.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Cheeseburger's in the lead right now because it's 0-0, meaning Cheeseburger might win, but there's still two questions to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you ready for the next question, SSJ100 Matt?
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't believe you were singing High School Musical 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't either.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sad you recognized that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll watch it after the show, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: The next question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki was so inspired by Mo's performance of Still Alive in Studio that he decided to pick up a guitar and learn how to play a song for the OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week, he will be performing Blank live on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ding ding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ding dong man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, Jake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki was so inspired by Mo's performance of Still Alive in Studio that he decided to pick up a guitar and learn how to play a song for the OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week, he will be performing Blank live on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Think you know an answer yet, Jake?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let those gears turn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to look at chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, the chat has some funny shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: OneNightStance, seriously?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just take an answer from chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh, I think I like one of these answers better than the one I wrote down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's too late.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still waiting for OneNightStance to give me an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt, do you have an answer in your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, then we're just waiting on OneNightStance.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got to stop dancing to the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got an answer for One Night Stand.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki was so inspired by most performances still live in studio that he decided to pick up a guitar and learn how to play a song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week he will be performing... Chocolate Rain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chocolate Rain for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Night Stand says, Mario's theme or stupid response Spice Girls want to be?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we'll see if either one of those matches.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if we let him out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guess who thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we're going to go with Mario's theme because that's what he said first.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, he's going to perform one live on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Dance?
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moe, he will be performing what live on the show?
[SPEAKER_12]: Dragon Forces through Fire and Flame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Forces through the Fire and Flames.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not an answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what did you pick?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we'll just pick what the chat room says.
[SPEAKER_07]: Theme for Tingle.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even know what the Tingle theme is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, your answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Swinging Jazz Ambassadors of Swing with My Monkey Done Left Me and Took All My Jello.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Acoustic Dragon Force would be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, The Monkey Left Me and Took All My Jello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn that monkey.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, and my answer was also Tingle's theme was my answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, unfortunately, no match.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is one more question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburger's very excited right now because it's 0-0, and if it stays 0-0, then Cheeseburger wins by default just for having a cool nickname.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wins a free copy of Res HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't have to do shit, but disappear from chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: If I win, I'll give it to Cheeseburger also.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, shiz.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you already have the game, SSJ100Mad?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, actually I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then Cheeseburger, shit, just sit there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't do nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just sit there and look pretty, Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just sit there and look pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's one more, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Giants won.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in a generous mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Night Stands is not out yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question number three, the last question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very disappointed to hear that Spore was delayed yet again.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was all ready with the time off work to play the game all day and all night this spring.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, Rob said, I guess I'll just play blank all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very disappointed to hear that Spore was delayed yet again.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was all ready with the time off work to play the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, I guess I'll just play blank all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding, Jake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Still thinking?
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep those gears turning.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100, Matt, have you thought of an answer?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So is One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: One Night Stands is getting the hang of this now.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's got it this round.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody else good?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, you almost... Okay, you got it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well, Rob said, I guess I'll just play...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know that was a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moe, I guess I'll just play... Major Wee.
[SPEAKER_08]: Major Wee all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good use of a Part A reference.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, oh well, I guess I'll just play... I went in with the realistic answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: World of Warcraft all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, oh well, I guess I'll just play... Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oblivion all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are both very good answers.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I said...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I said Imagine Babies, then One Night Stands wins it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If not, Cheeseburger wins it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob was very disappointed to hear the Sporos late yet again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well, I guess I'll just play World of Warcraft all day.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's World of Warcraft, not Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that means Cheeseburger wins!
[SPEAKER_08]: Just for sitting there and looking pretty in a 0-0 show.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt, you lose, so we hang up on you, but do you have a quick plug?
[SPEAKER_08]: Giants win!
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry One Night Stands, you did good, at least you got the hang of the match game, I hope you had fun Cheeseburger, private message me your email, you win match game I love how someone wins match game that didn't even play
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how I roll.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is how we roll here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is how we roll.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have any more stories?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more story, and then we're going to open up their Skype line.
[SPEAKER_07]: So not to be outdone by the Wii yet again, PS3 devs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have put out a little video saying, look at what we can do with the PlayStation Eye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we can do that VR shit too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo, we're awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, basically kind of impressed by what they've done using the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_07]: They kind of did this very similar thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually looked like it used the exact same program.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's running on a PS3 dev kit to give that head tracking effect.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, I'm pretty impressed by the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to buy it yet, but I'm impressed by what you can do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you know, the little tech demos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I would like some actual games that use this technology instead of just look at what we can do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, but it'll never come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But just look at what we can do.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: What will they do, do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they better do something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that one where it's the combat type game, like the old Atari combat, but you can scan in your picture that you want to use as your tank.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can just draw a picture.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can put an actual tank on there, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or like the Lunar Lander game that you make by drawing the pictures and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they should be doing with the eye instead of just, I don't know, games where I have to move a ball around by waving my arm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Trial of the Tupac, Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_07]: Last Minute Stories, Japan Post is giving away red DS lights, so yet another color you won't see over here in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_07]: The PS3 is getting their own greatest hits, including such wonderful games as Resistance Fall Man, Folk Soul, or Folklore, I think that's what it's called over here, Ninja Gaiden Sigma, Gundam Target in Sight, which I think sucked,
[SPEAKER_07]: and RidgeRacer7.
[SPEAKER_07]: All those are going to be available for 3,800 yen, which translates to about 3,599.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just picked up the phone, and who is there on the phone on the Orange Lingerie Skyline?
[SPEAKER_03]: None other than Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eating a bag of chips by the sound of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, Legend of Zaku?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, nothing but just coming back from just, you know, going to Dave & Buster's or Super Bowl shit and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, was it wild and crazy when the Giants won?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, it was kind of quiet when the game started, but then as we further went through, there was a lot of people there, and it was just madness on the way out of Times Square.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you actually watch the Super Bowl or did you just play DDR all night?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I actually had my buffalo wings, my beer, and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually avoided DDR today.
[SPEAKER_03]: But besides that, I don't know if you want to bring up Supernova 2 since it was probably brought up by other folks anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't talked a lot about DDR recently on the program, but what are your thoughts on DDR Supernova 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it's like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's just Betzen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Betzen holding us back.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're holding us back for the fact that we can't even unlock songs right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're being forced, against our will, to basically have to go as far as importing a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're basically just telling the arcade owners that we have good relationships with, better than Betzen's, to just avoid it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not worth it without EMUs or a means of unlocking it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you're pissed they didn't bring the Japanese-only EMU system over to America to try and add a little something to the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't we kind of lucky to have DDR still going in the arcades in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was...
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, in no way am I blaming Konami, because they're actually making a good effort in bringing it over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: They tried it with this game, they tried it with Guitar Freak's Drum Mania, which hasn't seen a release date yet, but if Benton is trying to half-ass their way into this, the only thing I can see is Konami...
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Giving us a little Betson hate here on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what can Betson do to make things right with DDR?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's say there's a Supernova 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can they do to make things right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's pretty much what...
[SPEAKER_03]: What they had to do anyways, since I know this is most likely, the way they were picked out anyways was, you know, a contract.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, since Konami put that bid, you know, bid out, you know, gave bets in the contract to distribute games in America, by not, by basically, you know, asserting Konami's will, you're, you know, that would be on the, you know, that would be grounds for breach of contract right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: and, you know, Konami will sue for, you know, if it got that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami will sue?
[SPEAKER_03]: If it was putting a damper on their sails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we gotta wrap up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any last minute thoughts, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty 4 kicks Halo 3's ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Call of Duty 4 kicks Halo 3's ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: It does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you a Call of Duty fangirl?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, good times.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_12]: Call of Duty 3 sucked, but for good reason.
[SPEAKER_12]: Call of Duty 3 was fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was an Infinity Ward.
[SPEAKER_07]: Call of Duty 2 I liked, because there was one level that you can download that had a giant tower in the middle of that, and we absolutely loved playing multiplayer on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's whoever can stand, you know, king of the tower, I guess, instead of king of the hill, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Call of Duty 3 was okay, but Call of Duty 4 was a lot better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, well, because Call of Duty 3 was a completely different team.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I have some big news before we go to this next call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburger...
[SPEAKER_08]: has deferred the prize, saying that unfortunately he only has a Wii, so the prize does him no good.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the prize will go back into the prize pool, and we'll give it away next week here on the program in another lame game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So tune in next week for your chance to win Rez HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheeseburger says instead, my birthday is on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say happy birthday on the show instead, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: So happy birthday, Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good birthday on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: And cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_12]: So precious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the sky flight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought we had someone on sky flight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hello, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before I start, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie stepped out for just a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: She stepped out for just a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: For a giant wee.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I think she's taking a major wee.
[SPEAKER_08]: So do you have, can we relay something to her?
[SPEAKER_08]: What would you say if she was here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, me or you, because I just wanted to say to her, I can have the Guinness, that's all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there a major lag tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the cam's slowing things down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be on my end.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there is, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We forgive you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can have the Guinness.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll relay the message to her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything else you want to say about the program?
[SPEAKER_04]: Join the show so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed part eight because out in a row of friends getting tattooed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you missed Mo's lovely rendition of Still Alive.
[SPEAKER_08]: How dare you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I will catch the replay on Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is back.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you want to say to Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can has a Guinness?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you can has.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can has Guinness.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can has Smithwick's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smithwick's is what I called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of tired of the DDR bashing by the diehards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we just let it be, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: We already realize that Konami doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing what they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just leave it be, because I'm just a happy-go-lucky player.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just happy that we even have the game in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we just leave it at that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't we just all agree that DDR is gay?
[SPEAKER_12]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I can say that, because I am, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it gayer than you or gay as you?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR is not gay.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR is just... DDR totally does not like to sleep with other DDRs of the same gender.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've said the DDR argument so many times I'm like blue in the face.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to look at pretty Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl more.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all I want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: A few episodes back, you said something about any things you would do to make DDR better.
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of glanced over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you do to make it better?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really have to hear what you would do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would scrap all the code that they've ever used to make DDR and build the game from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to force them to think of some new ideas on how to make the game original again.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I would bring over some of the people that helped on the Xbox version if they're still with the company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Additionally, I would think about how to make the game more competitive than cooperative in nature.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, yes, there was the dance battle mode or whatever in Supernova.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think a mode like that should be the focus of the game next time and not an afterthought.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Literally redesign the fundamentals of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the game can still be single player and have those modes and it can have some cooperative features in it, but make it more of a tournament game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Relaunch the game as Dance Dance Tournament or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Ranma, we gotta let you go try and get some more calls, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo World is now taking Classic only for Wii consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo World is only accepting plastic for Wii console sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the sign in the window when you walk in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: No checks?
[SPEAKER_08]: No cash?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Same as Apple is doing with the iPhones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Plastic only.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thanks for the heads up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our man in New York City.
[SPEAKER_04]: Catch you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our man in New York City, DJ Ranma S, right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So is Zaku in New York City.
[SPEAKER_08]: And SSJ100, this is a New York show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our contestant was New York City, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Plastic, come to think of that, that actually leaves a data trail.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: The cash money is almost untraceable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do one more call tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, after playing that game, I kind of just wanted to call in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you apologizing for your horrendous performance in the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm totally kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you did good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm totally kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Games are so much easier when you're just watching and playing them, or playing along, but when you're actually a contestant, it's so much weirder.
[SPEAKER_08]: The radio is high-stress stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just ask Mo.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did she say before the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: She was going to throw up chunks of her pancreas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to throw up shards of my pelvis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you think I picked his name?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: What else did you want to say?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, what else did you want to say, One Night Stands?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, a couple weeks ago, I actually wrote in an email for the first time, and it was actually right on the air, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was just, you know, just felt like saying hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, I just wanted to know about the whole ASEN thing, if you really were coming out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I can't even think of anything right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, what was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: You were asking about what coming out here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: What was that you just said?
[SPEAKER_08]: You dropped out for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for calling One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing personal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Skype hates us tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm punishing the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're closing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the future, we might just have to shut off Justin TV or something when we do Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nothing personal.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what the hell's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to do it for our Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we encourage you to send more emails to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com or leave us voicemails.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can always call the Skype line when we're not live at 1-877-GAME-OLR and leave us lovely voicemails.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's always a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any more last-minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, actually, a couple things real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Monster Hunter, apparently Capcom is releasing this grip for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks stupid, but it's the Monster Hunter grip accessory, and it's lame-looking.
[SPEAKER_12]: That looks absolutely retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it is retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, do you have anything last for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire!
[SPEAKER_08]: You can Photoshop... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: One is a caption and me dancing with Pikachu is the one to caption.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Photoshop is me and DarkSakura attacking Loki is the Photoshop challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: So good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there's some animated picture of me swimming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what the hell that is.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all in our forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the Caption Photoshop Contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't miss it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we can't give away that res code any other way, we might have to do it there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope, though, our listeners want to win some free shit because all I'm going to say is that coming soon, we're going to be giving away a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: More details in the coming weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go around at this point and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jake, I know you didn't say much tonight, but you were entertaining the Justin TV crowd with much playing of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, what do you think of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl?
[SPEAKER_08]: Two words, fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm tired and I want to go to bed.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Need to find cage match song.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mo, thanks so much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm glad I'm not dead in a ditch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nerve-wracking?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is always the part after the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we hope you enjoyed the cake, and thanks so much for taking a chance and coming on our program.
[SPEAKER_08]: We hope you had fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for inviting me.
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come back sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't even have to bring a new song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank God for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just come over just because you want to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_12]: My Texan wife just made me lose the game, so anyone out there playing the game, you just lost.
[SPEAKER_12]: And hi to my Texan wife.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aw, a special shout-out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_08]: Cake.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: to get our name out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to do it for another week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week on the program, it looks like we'll be giving away Res HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still have Actdeft's code to give away.
[SPEAKER_08]: And who knows what other insanity awaits us next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll just have to tune in to find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So until then, I'm Rob, she's Jamie, he's Loki, and we're out till next week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!