[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: We asked a trivia question, and the trivia question was, which one of these games is this music from?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nightmare on Elm Street Halloween Friday the 13th Friday the 13th
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not going to be picked tonight, but you will get a chance to play in the chat room, so all hope is not lost.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may still win either a copy of Rez HD, or if you don't have an Xbox, one of our other prizes from our new prize table I'll talk about a little more later.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you did say Friday the 13th, you might want to stay by your phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the meantime, we're going to get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fooling at Home.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been available on PCs for a long time, and just not really that recently, but
[SPEAKER_03]: on the PS3 as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they have hit 1 million users actually, at least on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1 million consoles contributing to a cure for cancer or God knows what else they're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in the name of science.
[SPEAKER_03]: Calculating votes for the 2008 primaries or who knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Making a better caffeine molecule.
[SPEAKER_03]: Better caffeine molecule.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is something they need to work on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Finishing Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is also something they need to get to working on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also mentioning the PlayStation 3, which Folding at Home appears on.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a brand new Japanese PlayStation 3 that's going to be coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to come with a 40GB hard drive and a 6-axis wireless controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is the Satin Silver PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It comes out on March 6th.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will cost you 39,980 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to translate that into U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: dollars, that's 376 U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's the Satin Silver PlayStation 3, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, of course, everybody in Japan loves different colors
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, that's really all there is.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 3 in a new color.
[SPEAKER_06]: How this is news, I don't know, but it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to EGM's Quarterman rumor column, in their March issue, they talk about how that God of War Chain of Olympus, or Chains of Olympus, will be heading to PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, this is a rumor, but seeing their trend so far with, I don't know, Twisted Metal head-on, Ratchet and Clank Size Matters,
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to be too surprising if they port the PSP game to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hell, it will sell a lot of copies, so not so surprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Silent Hill Origins.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was another one that was ported from PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other Sony news, Flow will be making its way to the PlayStation Portable, and it comes out on March 6th.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is coming out from Super Villain Studios.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why you would want to get this when it's probably going to cost you more than it did on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: How much is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't have a price yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, you're going to get it through the PlayStation Store, so I guess it is the same relative price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what a pain in the ass to buy something on the store and then transfer it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't actually touched the PlayStation Portable Store yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't even looked at that because I know now they're starting to re-release.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're starting to put full PlayStation Portable games on there now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they had Wipeout Pure you can download and a bunch of other stuff, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because they figured that everyone else is already downloading it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's join the party and charge for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no one will still buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a cool idea to have original games on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, what they need is a link to actually be able to view that store from the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I mean, as far as I'm aware, now they don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't remember the URL for it, so I ain't buying anything from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a bee in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, that's scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that a bee?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's just a fly.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty big for a fly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you scared?
[SPEAKER_03]: I will inspect.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not scared of the bee.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, you know, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, you do news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll take care of the bee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, another game that's going to be coming out here for the PlayStation 3 also is going to have... It's a fly, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't be scared.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, you've grown big here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like Devil May Cry 4 that had a mandatory install.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not really mandatory.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that one was more of an optional install.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hot Shots Golf 5 in Japan right now has a 5 gigabyte, that's kind of ironic, install before you can play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, this is probably going to be on the US version of the Hot Shots Golf.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say on tour is what it's called or out of bounds.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of sucks that this trend of now these games having to be installed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's why you need your 80 gig system or 40 gigs or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Install these damn games on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That actually makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know, well, again, to play devil's advocate I suppose a little bit, if the PlayStation 3 is supposed to be more like a computer, then we shouldn't be surprised, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I'm still kind of a little frustrated at the fact that consoles like the Xbox 360, you don't install games like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they have, the only game I know that you can install stuff to it, actually there's two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's a Football Manager game in the UK, and then there's also Final Fantasy, you know, 11.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, that you have to install on every console, so that's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just all because of that Blu-ray drive being slow, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, on a smaller scale, Sony is doing these preload things as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a brand new Monster Hunter game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Monster Hunter Portable 2nd G is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what this has in common with the last story is that you actually have the option to copy what's on the UMD to your memory card on the PSP, and that will decrease load times.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of the same concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, we should emphasize it's optional here.
[SPEAKER_06]: and not required, which makes sense because there's PSPs out there where your memory card might be very small, like mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only have a 32 megabyte memory card because I bought mine a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought the PSP a long time ago before they started coming with a gigabyte memory stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's funny, though, that you can install it to the PSP memory stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yet, all this time, they've been trying to stop people from installing it to their memory stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, how they're so ironic.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's time to move on into another segment here we like to do on this show pretty regularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week we like to hear from you guys and your emails that you send us at Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we open them up and read through the emails in a little segment that we call The Mailbag.
The Mailbag
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to chat real quick, though, I've got to say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to read these comments here.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says, I smell lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think so?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe from the battery company, but I hope they don't try to sue Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not their fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the fault of the battery manufacturers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's dig into the mailbag here and see what folks have to say tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, it's mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll read this one first.
[SPEAKER_06]: This comes to us from... We'll call him Nathaniel...
[SPEAKER_06]: P, I guess is the name based on the signature there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear cynical and acrimonious cast of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acrimonious cast of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a varied gamer when it comes to my playlist and currently I've been playing Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Though I am also varied when it comes to my music.
[SPEAKER_06]: I listen more to classical orchestrated symphony type music.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the few rock bands I find enjoyable are the fine gents of Rhapsody or Rhapsody of Fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was hoping if you knew whether any of the band's numerous songs would ever appear in any Guitar Hero 3 downloadable content packs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we've heard anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you're going to see much more independent music come out in these packs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually that's something that kind of happens towards the end of the cycle.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so much in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: But some indie band out there spilled the beans that they were going to be Guitar Hero 4 and posted this entire probable song list from the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it kind of made a lot of people go, I don't know about that, a little apprehensive to call it actual news.
[SPEAKER_06]: But certainly Guitar Hero always has like 20, 30 independent songs in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I would say go for Guitar Hero 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: The band will get out there more that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: This email comes to us from PKJr92 and sends us this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I have just two questions or comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: First is directed to Loki and it's about the Eye of Judgment bet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just not possible, considering the caliber of the game, and I don't think ratings are in negative numbers, to reach 1 million ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to make it more reasonable, make it 500,000 copies sold, even though it probably won't sell more than 350,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki is too safe, and I think he knows it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, here's my second question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was the whole point behind Loki taking the bet in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as you chatters want it, Loki does not want to come here and dress in a Tingle outfit and set the Eye of Judgment on fire or whatever we talk about here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't really want to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because you know people will take screen caps on Justin.TV and it'll be all over the internet the next day, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine, but I mean, and I understand, I don't think it's going to hit 500,000 either, but you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already reduced it so many times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lifetime of, you know, ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, here's my second question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why all the hate towards the PlayStation 3 with the exception of Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, there's almost no support from Sony, but if you have a high-def TV, the games look amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I realize that not everyone has a nice TV, but the games still have the ability to be more in-depth than Xbox 360 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the PlayStation Network is free!
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd be pissed if I had to pay for PlayStation Network, because it's seriously...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not worth my time, I would say.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He also wants to say, by the way, thanks for broadcasting on Super Bowl Sunday considering not everyone is in love with football.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the Stanley Cup finals are a totally different thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much all of Canada watches.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, sorry for going on and on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, a lot of Americans watch the Super Bowl, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are in the minority of not watching it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just saying, I was just thinking that, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't broadcast from Canada, so... That is true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know when the hockey season ends or starts, so... Hockey's pretty fun, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of these days I'm going to get Melody to take me to a Sharks game in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because she gets season passes and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to another email.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one comes to us from Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: You people have influenced me to make an OLR Dragon Force movie contest.
[SPEAKER_06]: See thread on OLR website.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that would be at www.orangehaunchery.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Click on Forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: You record footage of you playing your favorite games and play Dragon Force in your video.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was influenced by the Yaris video and your mentioning of Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope it goes well.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those who might be new to our program, we said that you can make a bad game even better most of the time by putting Dragon Force music to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Dragon Force is just that awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so some of our listeners have taken it upon themselves to do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now Sakura Max wants to make a little contest out of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I say go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what we can contribute for prizes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we're trying to reserve some things on the prize table for something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: But maybe we can dig up something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a complete side note, Dragon Force sucks ass live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: When did you see them live?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't, but I know they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard on the radio that they were going to be playing live at some event.
[SPEAKER_05]: coming up in like two months from now in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just decided, oh, hey, I'll see what they sound like live and went to YouTube and was terribly disappointed.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here comes the next email, one of two remaining emails we're going to read this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry if we didn't get to your email, but we got a few this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This comes to us from J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is a Loki hate mail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me back away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love these emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to write in and completely put over Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: His anger and cynicism on the show not only make for hilarious radio, but most of the time echo my own thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quite a few times, though, it seems like he's very out of place because Rob and Jamie are pretty optimistic people and it's usually silent after one of Loki's rants.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not one of those, let him have the stage silent moments, but an uncomfortable, what's this guy's deal silent moments?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was surprised to hear that Loki and Skye used to room together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just so interested in the relationship between all you guys because you seem so radically different.
[SPEAKER_06]: What say you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: And so we wanted to kind of create a show that had that feel of, you know, going to dinner and talking smack about games and talking about the community or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of a... I guess you could say it's a spin-off of another show I used to be on, Under Station Live, which is a very similar kind of vibe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's why we're here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Loki and I used to be roommates because there was just a point where Loki was looking to move out the same time I was, and it just made sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, as far as us being silent when he does rants and things, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes there's just no way to respond.
[SPEAKER_06]: Relatively on this show for a live radio program, there's not a lot of dead air.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep in mind that when Jamie, myself, and Loki are all here, we're juggling from story to story, trying to kind of glance at the parts of the story we actually want to read on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're trying to read the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're trying to bring up different things.
[SPEAKER_06]: So sometimes we can't totally focus on what's being said.
[SPEAKER_06]: So sometimes I kind of get in that mode where when Loki rants, I just let him rant.
[SPEAKER_06]: I go, okay, Loki's ranting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just kind of let him do his thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it is insanely funny to listen to, and the listeners love it, so why not, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone loves Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in terms of multitasking, Loki's still doing that now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he's playing his fucking game while I try to do the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am contributing to the show, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just spin the black circles, only two keys, and I can do that with one hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, one more thing in J-Rod's email that I think is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, Jamie's not here to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: She said, also, I attached a picture I took before I went to see Rambo that you guys might like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome show and keep on rocking.
[SPEAKER_06]: And J-Rod's signature as always, this email is sponsored by the Olive Garden, home of the never-ending salads and breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's the email in front of the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is who I assume to be J-Rod wearing a Silent Hill shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually own that exact same Silent Hill shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I hope Pyramid Head was going to go in there and cut up some pasta for you guys to have.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, F you to the Olive Garden for getting rid of the dish I like there, the Tuscan chicken dish.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, they got rid of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a new thing that's pretty good though and I don't want to hear from the listeners to go, Olive Garden isn't real Italian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: You win.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not real Italian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Some days...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, my grandma, she spoiled me and my brother.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just with food.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, buying you video games and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, of course, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: One last email here, and it comes to us from Gray Fox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, OLR gang.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, I would just like to say that it's cool that Rob and I are now officially friends on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I can look at all of his sexy pictures without him even knowing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoa, did I say that out loud?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not that creepy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you are a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, oh my God, I'm as bad as Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was wondering if it was possible to listen to some of the first episodes you guys recorded.
[SPEAKER_06]: The podcast feed only lets me go back to listen to October 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to put a custom firmware to run Homebrew on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, and keep up the great work, GrayFox.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope another fly lands in Rob's coffee, because that was friggin' hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and say no to exploding babies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully, the fly problem in here seems relatively taken care of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except for the one.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was the one.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was the one.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was flying around here earlier, and he flew in front of my face.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's not being too annoying as his brothers and sisters were a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Relatively, the fly problem's been in check here in the studio, and I think that's as it's been getting warmer outside.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: You should hear the old show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, my God, it was a mess.
[SPEAKER_06]: In a good way.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a fun mess, you know, but it was much different.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think it's kind of one of those things where I want to let, and I'm sure Loki and DarkSakura, we want to let true fans of Orange Lounge Radio who like our banter and stuff, we want to let them hear it, but we don't want to put it out there so much that people are going to hear that thinking that is Orange Lounge Radio today because they would be, like, really off.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_05]: And back when the studio was like a six by six foot square box.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drunami says in the chat room, the old OLR was a great clusterfuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe like in the forums or on the LJ community or something, I'll put an old episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Facebook for you, obviously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll put an old episode up there so you can kind of taste what it's like.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know like Misty...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DDR Angel when she was around.
[SPEAKER_06]: She hasn't been around a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I know both of them really keep a lot of archives.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'll try to put up an episode that even Misty doesn't have.
[SPEAKER_06]: And everybody will like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least those that want to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send us some emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you're a member of Steam, you have a lot of other friends that are going to be on there, of course, because Steam has hit 15 million accounts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's quite a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, lots of good content that they have on there, and they keep adding more stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, apparently, Valve had a lot to do with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their Steam-based sales have jumped 158% over the holiday season compared to the previous ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely a viable source for gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still have yet to even check out Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever used Steam?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I buy games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to get in trouble for that someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, what about its other elements?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it doesn't have, like, the X-Fire thing built into it, too, where you can, like, message across games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I like X-Fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: NYR fan loves Steam in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says Steam is the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kicks games for Windows ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying I pirate games on the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't bought games on PC in a long time because up until recently I haven't had a PC that can run games.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last game I bought on PC was Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess Crysis since that came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that came with my graphics card though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking forward to some stuff coming out like Spore and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll buy that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's go over to the Nintendo Wii, because we haven't been showing Nintendo a lot of love tonight, and we want to talk about some stuff that's coming on the Wii soon, and that is everyone's Nintendo channel.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might remember this came out in Japan a little while ago, and it was kind of like a preview channel.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could check out some new games that were coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, not that you really download full demos and stuff, but you get, you know, interviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, it's one giant infomercial of a channel, but the big thing was the DS downloads.
[SPEAKER_06]: That you could get.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could get DS demos beamed to your DS channel,
[SPEAKER_06]: and the question was, when in the hell is it coming to the US?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the answer is about next month.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is coming from an insider source reporting to Kotaku, who ran the story earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_06]: The channel will be home to some of the same sort of video game videos that you see on Xbox Live and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Convention videos might actually start popping up on the channel once it goes live in the States.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming because Penny Arcade Expo is up in that same area where Nintendo of America is, maybe that's one you can expect to see?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't be surprised because I want to say March is also the estimated time for when the WiiWare channel is going to launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I bet all of this is going to be documented when they... I don't know if they have a keynote at... I want to say they do a Game Developers Conference, which is... God, I think that's next week or the week after.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly, I'm not going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know talking to some buddies over at All Games, or at least listening to their shows, All Games Interactive, our friends over there, only Jessica is going, and Bobby B's not going this year, which is kind of too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to go, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to get little peeks from a developer angle.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also you get to see stuff you might not normally see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm expecting them to talk about WiiWare since that makes sense from a developer's standpoint that they would want to address that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, there's rumors that Microsoft is going to have something similar to a YouTube of gaming type thing that they may discuss too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll see announcements like that, talking about their network upgrades and crap like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say really quickly before we get to the next story, Tiger Claws in chat, and he's a big listener over at AGI.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I think he came to our show because of All Games and our syndication there.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says, Jessica's bringing the Justin cam with her, he thinks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of cool if she's taking that cam with her.
[SPEAKER_06]: Justin TV is a great way to get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish we were able to go more mobile with Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we can because we have a laptop and a camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's not easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're not together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, you can get the cameras loose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, most people put the camera in the backpack, or I mean, put the laptop in the backpack and have the wire sticking out and put the, I mean, you can do it with that eyesight because that eyesight pops right out of the base and you can just strap it to a helmet.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could do it, but it's just, it's hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it wouldn't run for very long on that laptop's battery either because the laptop doesn't function when it's closed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if that's a setting I can change on there, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to see us out and about in public?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's have our privacy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mine works with the
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Those games are... Endless possibilities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, endless possibilities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when you're drunk.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, oh god, and you can have Red Blob versus Blue Blob, Penis versus 2DX controller, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, before we get into our next news story, we're going to be getting into tonight's new game very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as I mentioned, the entire chatroom has the possibility to participate, but you have to participate through private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: During tonight's game, the chatroom will be locked, and you will be unable to speak in the chatroom during the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is to prevent cheating from you guys for helping each other out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have to play this game through private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you are interested in playing tonight's game, you have to send me a private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm Sky in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's S-K-I-E.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send me a private message that just says, me.
[SPEAKER_06]: or I want to play, me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send me a private message if you want to play and we'll let you know the next part very soon when we reveal what we're going to be playing tonight and the contestant who's going to be coming in over the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So while you guys send that in, I've got one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo has apparently revealed that they have sold 10 million virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So even if you think that, okay, so $10 million, the lowest price somebody's paying for those is $5.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's $50 million they've earned on the virtual console games, considering most of this stuff was written off, gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're never going to profit off this stuff again.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there it went.
[SPEAKER_06]: and free money basically from the virtual console and Satoru Iwata who's of course the president of Nintendo talked about that this is proof of the value of digital distribution however not totally discounting the retail channel saying that the retail channel is still important but also admits that retail is not quite as profitable it's low profit margins on the box titles so could Nintendo be stepping more and more into digital distribution who knows possibly quite soon
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, not anytime soon because they're freaking slow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are they going to put all those digital downloads?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can't digitally download a Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Balance Board and all that crap you gotta buy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before you get to your story, Loki, I want to say for those in chat, if you try to do a private message conversation via DCC, it will not work.
[SPEAKER_06]: The DCC client that's built into MIRC, you need to do it another way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at Dark Tetsuya's post in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: He shows you guys how to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So please get to doing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Famitsu Magazine had some details on the brand new Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to sport 32 courses, Mid-Air Tricks, and of course, Mii Integration, which sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be remaking, I know, some of the tracks that were in Mario Kart DS, as well as pretty much all the Mario games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, they are saying that 16 of the tracks that are going to be from other games and the other 16 are brand new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, I wish there was more brand new tracks and less of the
[SPEAKER_03]: 12 player online matches will also be available and you'll be able to play 4 player split screen and I think you can play 2 player over online too so you can do 2 people per console as well ghost downloads, time trials will also be available and you can also of course choose a bike or a cart I wonder which version of Rainbow Road they would use
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's quite a few.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know if they don't do Rainbow Road just right, people are going to be pissed.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you ready to get to tonight's game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well let's get to tonight's game.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, you only have about 15 more seconds to send me a private message or you are out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You cannot join the game midway through.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are out if you don't send me a private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: Time is almost up.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, we need to get one contestant on the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hopefully if you answered Friday the 13th in our thing earlier, you might want to stand by the phone because it could be ringing right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's put in the number of our contestant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry for any delays or dead area here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's ringing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, is this Tiger Claw?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yo, what's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to be playing a game with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Claw, it's a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: How would you say your knowledge of video game trivia is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would guess so-and-so.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Considering that I've been around since it was invented.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that...
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you playing Pong back in the day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, my first video game was Pong, and after that was Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome, well then maybe you have an advantage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think you know enough about video game trivia that you could beat the entire chatroom at Video Game Trivia?
[SPEAKER_04]: 1 vs. The Chat Room
[SPEAKER_06]: One vs. The Chatroom
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, then you'd be perfect for winning this code.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the thing, TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: If at any point during the game, we're going to ask you some questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: If at any point during the game, the chat room beats you, we're going to give it to one of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: XBOX 360 XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody that's in chat, pretty soon the chat is going to go into lockdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will not be able to speak publicly within the room.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to get very quiet in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will only be able to play this game through private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be asking Tigerclaw multiple choice questions with three possible answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will have about 30 seconds to send your answer to me via private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then Tigerclaw will answer the question.
[SPEAKER_06]: If he gets it right...
[SPEAKER_06]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Those that got the right answer will be eligible to win the prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will pick one of the chatters randomly to win the prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll kind of explain that a little more as we move through it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see how many chatters are actually playing tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to see how many chatters we have and who you're playing against, TigerClaw?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably the entire chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just about.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have just about the entire damn chatroom we're playing against tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frisbee, two.
[SPEAKER_06]: RossDLUT, three.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS191, four.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68, five.
[SPEAKER_06]: Junami, six.
[SPEAKER_06]: PKRuno, seven.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amazatsuma, eight.
[SPEAKER_06]: SJ100MAT, nine.
[SPEAKER_06]: SolarWing, ten.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTatsuya, eleven.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ryoma, twelve.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheeseburger, thirteen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, fourteen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trishlicious, fifteen.
[SPEAKER_06]: 15, KevinDDR16, SonOfDad17, Zenny18, SeedStore19, RavensDolphin20, and AJMix21.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's you versus 21 people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think you can do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got to do your best.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: So everybody in chat, wish each other luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll give them just a minute to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: and here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The chat room is now locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody will be able to type in chat and help each other out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get to the very first question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ops, you have the power to override that, but I ask for your silence during this time because the Ops in our chat have the power to override that like Ranma and them, but I ask for their silence.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, you will only have a little bit of time to send your answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ready for the first question?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, here you go, Tiger Claw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: The category is classic sports games.
[SPEAKER_06]: In what 8-bit sports game was Gradius featured as a minigame?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it A. Blades of Steel, B. Double Dribble, C. RBI Baseball?
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, here's the question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Claw, don't yell it out until I have a chance here to share this with the chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: In what 8-bit sports game was Gradius featured as a minigame?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it A. Blades of Steel, B. Double Dribble, C. RBI Baseball?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we'll take a little musical interlude here while we let the chatters submit their answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chatters, you have about 30 seconds to get your answer in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, uh... Wait, hold on, I got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've played all those games before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot to tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do get one little lifeline, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, lifelines in the game shows?
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally forgot about this part.
[SPEAKER_06]: If at any time you are unsure about an answer, you can have us eliminate one incorrect answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I will tell you two people from the chat room and how they answered the question.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can help make your decision from there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you only get one of them through the game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're unsure, I just want to let you know you have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So TigerClaw, though, sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_04]: A. Blades of Steel, B. Double Dribble, C. RBR Baseball I'm going to have to take one of those lifelines.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've played all three of those games before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking NES games, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there NES games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so you want to use that lifeline?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be all over right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to eliminate one wrong answer from the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to tell you two answers here.
[SPEAKER_06]: One is correct, one is incorrect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's some answers from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma has said that the answer is Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frisbee has said that the answer is Double Dribble.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those is right.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those is wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: RBI Baseball is definitely wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: RBA Baseball being out and your lifeline gone, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Blades of Steel or Double Dribble?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm going to go with Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, the correct answer is Blades of Steel is the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: So congratulations, Tiger Claw, you move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see how many people you knocked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out Frisbee, we know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out GS-191.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out GS-68.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out Solarwing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for playing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you knocked out Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out Son of Dad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out Zenny.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knocked out Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13 people left.
[SPEAKER_06]: So not bad, you took out 8 people on that first question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you ready for the next question?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Question number 2 is in the category of Super Nintendo Shooters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which of these games was known in Japan as Area 88?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it UN Squadron?
[SPEAKER_06]: Flanix, or R-Type?
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, the question is which of these games was known in Japan as Area 88?
[SPEAKER_06]: UN Squadron, Flanix, or R-Type?
[SPEAKER_06]: The chat room will have just a moment to submit their answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's give them some thinking music to do so.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to be so sick of this fucking song by the time the night's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I think I know what he has.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, hold on, we gotta give a chat sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go, Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which of these games was known in Japan as Area 88?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it UN Squadron, Flanix, or R-Type?
[SPEAKER_04]: The answer would be UN Squadron.
[SPEAKER_06]: UN Squadron?
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe Cheeseburger's out, he said C
[SPEAKER_06]: Trish Lissus, I'm sorry you're out, although I love that name.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now we're down to 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've gone from 21 to 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not bad, Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ready to do it one more time?
[SPEAKER_06]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is question number three, and it's in the category The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which one of these is not a monster name in The Legend of Zelda?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it A, Gleok, B, Aquamentus, or C, Kraken?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chatroom has a few minutes to reply.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, since I played Legend of Zelda 1
[SPEAKER_04]: and the third one, SNES.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to have to probably say C, Kraken.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, C, Kraken.
[SPEAKER_06]: First, I have to eliminate two people for not submitting on time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So sorry, Ryoma.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sorry, Kevin DDR, you didn't get your answers in on time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're already... Oh, Ryoma just barely got his in.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's back.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The correct answer is...
[SPEAKER_06]: Kraken is correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see if you took anybody out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was an easy one, personally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three have got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Piker Uno didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, you're out.
[SPEAKER_06]: He said Aquamentus, which was one of the bosses in Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seed Store also said Aquamentus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, buddy, you're out.
[SPEAKER_06]: AJ Mix also said Aquamentus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, you're out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now the mob is down to six people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tigerclaw, you're doing awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kraken, by the way, was one of the elementals in Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And our next question is all about Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ready, Tigerclaw?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's going to be tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wrote it before the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's your question.
[SPEAKER_06]: In which Final Fantasy game was there a character named Ferris?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it A, Final Fantasy IV?
[SPEAKER_06]: B, Final Fantasy V, or C, Final Fantasy IX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, that's A, IV, B, V, or C, IX.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the character's name is Ferris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's give the chat a chance to think.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need the full soundtrack to this show, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a different song for when they were doing the... Well, I only have the one, so shoot me.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to start it off before you question by saying how many... One versus... Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: One versus six.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, somebody's walking away with a prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of these seven people is going to win the prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw, it's time.
[SPEAKER_06]: In which Final Fantasy game was there a character named Ferris?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it A, Final Fantasy IV, B, Final Fantasy V, or C, Final Fantasy IX?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to have to say Final Fantasy IX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's see if that's the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Final Fantasy game that had a character named Ferris was Final Fantasy V. I'm sorry, TigerClaw, you have lost to the mob.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is where the mob cheers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, no problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not too familiar with Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I kind of took a guess there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, I've been listening to you guys ever since I heard you from all games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've been listening to your show ever since.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Tiger Claw, thanks for supporting us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And did you enjoy the game at least?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you have fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I sure did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now for your consolation applause from the audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, your consolation applause.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody give Tiger Claw a round of applause.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Tiger Claw, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thanks, and you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the chatters are wondering, which one of us is going to win it?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see who's going to be knocked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have that person moves on, that person moves on, that person moves on, that person moves on, that person moves on.
[SPEAKER_06]: All six of them got it right in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we should narrow the field a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to narrow the field a little bit with one more question?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, fine then.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll narrow the field a little bit with one more question.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, in order to do that, we've got to put this in moderated mode again so they can't cheat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So some poor people were just trying to chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is the fifth question.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fifth question is in the category Games Rob Hates.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I didn't have the question fully typed out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody fill time for just a moment here.
[SPEAKER_03]: What games do you hate, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hating this level of Spin the Black Circle.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been going at this one level for like 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got close to the end, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate... Oh gosh, let me think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything Barbie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to eliminate a few more people here on this question for games Rob hates.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the game Bubsy...
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever played Bubsy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Bubsy 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the game Bubsy, which of the following did you collect for points?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it A, Cheese Pieces, B, Yarn Balls, or C, Leaves?
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually put 1, 2, 3 in chat, but it shouldn't be that big a deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, was it Cheese Pieces, Yarn Balls, or Leaves?
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, I wasn't part of the mob at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, all the chatters are in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cut off the theme.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go through one at a time to see who got it right and who didn't get it right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, the correct answer in the game Bubsy, which of the following did you collect for points?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was not cheese pieces.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was not leaves.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was yarn balls is the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he's a cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And how many of the chatters do you think we eliminated?
[SPEAKER_06]: None.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all six.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Puppy, I need you to pick a number, one through six.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to do, I should have brought out my dice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you're going to roll a dice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's between Ryoma, DarkTetsuya, SSJ100, Matt, DrewNami, RawSteel, UT, and Ranma is what's remaining in our chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did it hit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Four.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our winner tonight, boys and girls, of one versus the chatroom, SSJ100, Matt, give it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: A winner of trivia and luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm asking SSJ100 Matt if he's going to take the Res HD code.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seem to recall last week he didn't want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, he wants the other prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: So SSJ100, Matt, coming to you very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to be getting a copy, courtesy of our friends at PopCap Game, Bejeweled 2, the hit sequel to Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, this is the full version.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not the crap, well, I shouldn't say the crap version, but the reduced version that you play online.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the full version of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're kind of thinking, well, I don't really want Bejeweled 2, this will make an awesome Valentine's Day gift for somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: My wife loves some Bejeweled 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ladies love Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Bejeweled comes to us from our friends at PopCap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Four different modes of play in this version.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll keep you going for hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Classic mode, action mode, puzzle mode, endless mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100 Matt wins Bejeweled 2, courtesy of PopCap Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you guys think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chatroom, did you guys like that prize?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or did you guys like that game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you guys think the game went well?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our first run, it went pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how much it's going to translate to the podcast where people can't play, but I think for the live listeners, that was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's just as much fun as watching a game show on TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm hoping for the podcast listeners and the folks listening to all games, they could kind of think in their mind how they would have done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they could have had the chance if they were here live on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know everybody that watches a game show thinks they can do better than the person on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's always the way it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Piker Uno says, I didn't know any of the answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says it was fun, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Knight says it should make it its own show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Piker Uno says, make a Bomani edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Son of Dad says, more fighting game questions needed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ryoma says, more trivia.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm sure that segment will make a comeback in a future edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope you guys enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to go to the Skype line very soon, but quickly, another couple stories for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Bandai Namco has definitely taken a different approach for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the DS, they're releasing a game called 99 Tears.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is basically 99 different stories that you'll read that are very depressing that are supposed to make you cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because apparently they think that it's very therapeutic to cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanna play this game and I'm never gonna cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this should be a challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, make Loki cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: When was the last time you cried?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you a crier?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real men cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to ruffle the personal life feathers, but I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me, I cry at every sad movie I watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, I think I watched an episode of Wife Swap the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I cried at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't take much.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I waste my time on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly tonight, before we get to the Skype line, the Sega is going to be bringing a brand new game to the Nintendo DS, and it's very similar to one of their old cult classics, The Typing of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the new game they are bringing out, The English of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: The English of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: First words you will learn...
[SPEAKER_06]: Brains!
[SPEAKER_06]: The British of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: The interesting thing, though, it's House of the Dead 2, but ported to the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what you have to do, you have to translate words into English from Japanese, or the zombies will eat you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes the zombies speak out loud, and you have to translate what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's going to be all kinds of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to see how that plays out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have to write it out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because sometimes those handwriting recognitions suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said blue!
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish this game would come out the other way around.
[SPEAKER_06]: Japanese of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe learn some Japanese or some other languages.
[SPEAKER_06]: English, English of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Southern English of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Grammar of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet Jamie would love that.
[SPEAKER_06]: If she was here, she'd suggest a proper grammar game or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which actually was not proper grammar in me saying that, but oh well, who cares.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I need to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a lot of fun stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to open up the Skype line for your calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quickly though, any last minute stories from Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a few actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Already it's confirmed that there's going to be a Professor Layton sequel because the game manual says there's going to be a sequel and it will have a code in it that you use in the first game or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shane has been talking to me about how wonderful Professor Layton is like all week long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plastic Yellowways
[SPEAKER_06]: I want some melting Legos in my Indiana Jones game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've replaced them with anonymous genocidal occultist trench coat wearing master race.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I want the anonymous genocidal occult trench coat wearing bastards to have their faces melt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Ask them good news and bad news regarding 2DX at Sunnyvale Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2DX at Sunnyvale Golf Land, one of our local arcades, got some attention lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody wrote an article about classic arcades or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know who that guy was, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe I'm plugging it here on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I will point out how convenient that the person used the arcade they used to go to all the time in that article.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure it was a real challenge to write it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyhow...
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68, what's on your mind regarding Beatmania Golfland?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good news, we have two DX DJ Troopers as of this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice!
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll have to go play, but what's the bad news?
[SPEAKER_09]: The machine is unlocked well ahead of what's supposed to be in Japan, and that means if you plan on going in or between now and most likely May, you can't take pictures of the machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't take pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are they policing that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can't... You don't usually see that in arcades where you're completely banned from taking pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just challenging people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, is it a location test that they're doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: For real.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, here's how you're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: GSCCA, I will tell you how to get around this right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get one of those... I even have this on my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get one of those phones that records video.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me get the camera phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you get a camera phone and what you do is you kind of stand next to the machine and you hit the record button and then you pretend you're talking on your phone while you're recording the screen right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Easy as pie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it'll be up on YouTube and somebody will get shit in their pants.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I just sent you a link via private message and that explains why we can't take pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, are they, because usually it's the new songs people want to know and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are people not allowed to write the songs down and then post them on the internet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean... Sorry, I don't expect you to know that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it'd be like the fact that the machine is unlocked well ahead of schedule.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at the post here on our friends at Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_06]: The distributor has asked that no pictures or videos be taken yet due to the fact the machine will be fully unlocked with all hidden feature songs per my request and as a present to all the players at Sunnyvale Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is about three months ahead of Japan and we cannot have secret stuff leak on the internets.
[SPEAKER_06]: So please, people, assist me with this small task of not allowing pictures or videos to be taken yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they have a big sign hanging by the machine or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you've been.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, like,
[SPEAKER_09]: I went this Saturday and I pulled out my camera and then one of the players told me not to take pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're self-policing it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, most likely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe, I mean, I wonder if I can talk to them about, like, having them put a sign in, like, maybe set up a security camera, like... Yeah, a security camera really could be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: In a sense, they're breaking their own rules.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, for me, this sounds like a challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Facing away from the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, plus I can imagine some guy who's never played a single-ball mining game
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it is a challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, when somebody says don't, you want to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: The community maybe just doesn't want to spoil or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we probably shouldn't be spoil sports.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I'm not going to get to Sunnyvale Golf Land anytime soon anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do kind of want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played an arcade Beatmania game since E3 when they had the machine there that one year randomly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the last time I played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, yeah, I don't remember the last time I played Geek Mania.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100 Matt in chat has a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most people on the forums will say PIX or GTFO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, fine, we'll get PIX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we'll get PIX.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not opposed to getting PIX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ban me from SVGL?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's ironic about this is that, like, even if we...
[SPEAKER_09]: This game's not supposed to be in the U.S., so we're not allowed to take pictures to begin with.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's not even supposed to be in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: to begin with.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, well, we had the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: location test, but that failed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, I'm waiting for the next story where somebody gets beaten up in the parking lot over taking a picture of this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68, we gotta let you go to get some more calls, but thank you so much for your call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey there, this is Let's Have Tea
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's have tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's have some tea and chat a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is up, my friend?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to plug the game Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_10]: To anybody who hasn't checked this game out yet, I know it's kind of old, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: I finally got a chance to play through it, and it's well worth the $15 on the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's definitely out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I'm a big adventure game fan, and it's pretty much the first, like, adventure game that's really got my attention since, like, Mario 64 or Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it... I hear a lot about the sense of humor in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it the sense of humor that draws you in?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: The game is seriously, just ridiculously twisted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: you infiltrate the minds of a lot of really interesting characters and a lot of them are in like a loony bin so there's a lot of weird stuff going on I didn't see a lot of this game I've uh and so maybe I need to take your advice and go check it out I've watched it being played by somebody else but it was I didn't see a lot of the story I just saw the actual game and to me it was kind of like oh I think I've kind of seen this game before but you're saying no it's worth a second look it really stands out right it's
[SPEAKER_10]: It's definitely worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say they make a Psychonauts 2 someday, which with all the cult following, you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you most like to see in Psychonauts 2?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, in the story of it, they totally opened it up so that there's a possibility.
[SPEAKER_10]: But really, just the way that Psychonauts 1 worked out with the sense of humor and the
[SPEAKER_10]: The way that they were able to develop the different abilities throughout the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Usually in sequels, they aren't able to rebuild abilities like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like if you take Banjo-Kazooie from Banjo-Kazooie, it's hard to add even more to the game when the original game limits what you do by the moves that you have.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can find the old Xbox disc, you can play it with backwards compatibility as well, so either works.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's also a PS2 and PC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: No excuses for not playing this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's have tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much for what we'll call the not quite classic game of the week, because it's not a classic yet, but it probably will be in a few more years.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have one more question for you before we let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really like to drink tea?
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's Mr. T. Are you more of a coffee drinker?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm actually not really into any of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought it was a clever name and thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I grabbed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you win.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially when you consider you don't like tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even I like a little tea here and there.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's have tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks so much for reminding us about the greatness of Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great one, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we can do a couple more calls, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Skype wants us to rate the quality of that call.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was the call quality?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you say 5?
[SPEAKER_06]: Very good?
4?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say it's either 4 or 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it a 4, because I've had issues on other calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sending the whole thing, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now answer 30 more questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma!
[SPEAKER_07]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: E.M.U.s
[SPEAKER_06]: That would seem likely, because the IP address So things that would have to be unlocked by EMUs wouldn't normally be available here So if they can unlock everything here, and we don't get EMUs, that just means that they're plain assholes for not unlocking at all Alright Konami does have a record Kevin DDR in chat says, no one knows how Somebody does, obviously, because this machine's added done to it But I get what you're saying I bet it's up, up, down, down, left, right, left Nobody who can spread the word knows how, I guess
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma, what else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Irene said earlier, I went to a Ren Faire this weekend, and out of all my costumes, I found one that would be perfect to blend right in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I just have to give a little background because the Ren Faire thing came up during our bonus segment, which the podcast people don't hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: So podcasters, just know we were talking about the Ren Faire earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not completely out of place, his comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was like a... It was a Ranma remix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not adjust your iPods.
[SPEAKER_06]: We heard the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: DMN, make a song out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma, I'm sorry, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: A good fit with our show or video games or what?
[SPEAKER_06]: With video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now what is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you wear your Black Mage?
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a Black Mage outfit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you wear it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you get a lot of people coming up to you wanting to take the old picture?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you take pictures with large-breasted women in corsets?
[SPEAKER_07]: I decided to keep those pictures to myself, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: At those Ren Fairs, you know the Las Vegas rules apply.
[SPEAKER_06]: What happens at Ren Fairs stays at Ren Fairs?
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not allowed to take pictures of the women in corsets and put them up on the Internet or the SVGL management will get very mad at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some people actually thought I was Vivi from Final Fantasy IX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, because Vivi does look like a Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the best thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone walked up to me and said, You're Orko from He-Man, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Mage does look like Orko.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_07]: After hearing that five, six times, I said, The next Ren Faire, I'm going to do a Jedi and I'll do Orko.
[SPEAKER_07]: See what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Ranma, glad to hear you had fun at Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe next time you're in Cali, we'll take Irene to one together, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe you should take her.
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably will.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she sent me a private message with one that she wants to go to now, but I've been too busy doing the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me look, actually, real quick while we're on the subject of Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, no, I accidentally closed it during the game because I needed to keep my private message window clean during the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you like the game tonight, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_06]: You came very close to winning.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad you liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have to do it again sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Ranma, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more call?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully it doesn't get caught in the loop.
[SPEAKER_06]: The crazy... Sucked into a black hole.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not ringing off the hook, so Loki, do you have any last-minute stories you want to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: OneUp is going to be changing their scoring policies, apparently, how they rate games, which is quite funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, instead of the point system, they're going to be changing it to letters, like grading system from A plus to F.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet there's ten different letters in between there and nothing's changing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, because they're admitting, you know what they are, they're admitting, well, I guess it's not really admitting.
[SPEAKER_03]: EGM is going to do the same thing, it's all going to start in March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because what I'm saying, like, I don't know, A through F has a different kind of connotation to it than 1 through 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, F is failing, it's a miserable game, whereas I think in the 1 through 10 world, 6 is seen as failing, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess that's the point I was trying to make that I didn't do very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: But who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, technically enough, it's a 60%.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one review site on the entire internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realize it's a big one, but, you know, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also a magazine, EGM, and Games for Windows.
[SPEAKER_06]: We live in a world where there's demos readily available.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make your own decision.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I read reviews once in a while, but I haven't found a game reviewer I really 100% trust and like yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe the guy from Zero Punctuation.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, he's too negative.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny but negative.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the phones and take one last call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, this is Ross Deal UT.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross Deal UT.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is up, my friend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing, just shooting shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how that goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we do here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I've got a few things on my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not too many, but a few.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, there's this...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, there was somebody linking that already on the chat, this marine who went missing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically what happened is that the family thinks that maybe...
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty 4 Call of Duty 4
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't want to give away any of the plot line, but you invade a Middle Eastern country and a nuclear device goes off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a very gritty game, you know, and I could definitely see where somebody who's been to Iraq, who's maybe having problems with post-traumatic, you know, might play that game and get a,
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a bad reaction from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're saying that he might be actually trying not to be found.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounded pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not a game he should have been playing in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the question is...
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they have it out there enough for this guy to know maybe he shouldn't play this game as he's very sensitive on these type of topics or suffering from this post-war syndrome?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it the responsibility of the makers of this game to put some type of disclaimer on the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game might be too real for some people.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is, though, with post-traumatic stress disorder, that sort of thing,
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be any number of things that trigger it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any number of things could remind somebody or give someone a bad flashback.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very unpredictable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a lot of mental disorders, it's going to affect people in different ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only that, but modern warfare, you know they're going to at least deal with the Arab angle somewhat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just going to say, very unfortunate news, no matter, you know, where it kind of falls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just kind of unfortunate that, you know, maybe this was the type of game he should have played with other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's kind of the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Call of Duty 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Yars.
[SPEAKER_03]: He played Yars.
[SPEAKER_03]: and he's like, oh my god, I have to run.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's a different kind of trauma.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a place in hell waiting for you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, RustyLUT, we don't have too much time.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else did you want to say real quick tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was this industry blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of these industry analyst people was talking about how there's a problem where the industry has no real room for anything
[SPEAKER_02]: between the tiny budget casual games and the tens of millions of dollars blockbusters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me put up a link right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as far as the American market, I can certainly agree with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We either see the huge budget Call of Duties and Gears of War or we see PopCap.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not as diverse a market as, say, Japan where
[SPEAKER_02]: There's stuff all over the budget spectrum.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is an opinion piece I didn't read before tonight's show, so it's a little harder for me to comment on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we have enough variety in our styles of games that we have out there right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not so much styles, but we need a real be real.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look at the American market, it's PopCap games type of deal, and then there's Gears of War, Call of Duty, you know, really big budget games, and there's not a lot of stuff in between.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if you compare that to Japan, where you see stuff like Chuu!
[SPEAKER_02]: Litten no Nechanbara, you know, people just throwing crap out there, hell, even Puzzle Quest, which managed to become a hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, what this guy's talking about is you can't really experiment with
[SPEAKER_02]: when you're dealing with a budget of $20 million, $30 million because there's too much risk involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, there's really only so much you can do in a little budget 2D game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So either extreme, you're not really having a lot of room for new ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't there a similarity with movies though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it seems like most movies are either the art house cheap ones or the explosion Michael Bay, burning money live on screen type of movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not a whole lot in between there either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's the be real basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a whole lot for what people want in that middle market because...
[SPEAKER_05]: The American market is a lot different than the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot more people in Japan that play games for one, but there's either you've got the hardcore gamers that have been doing it for years, or the people that are just the casual gamer market, and there really is no target audience for something in between.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd think that the hardcore would be the most receptive of something like, well, you look at Puzzle Quest, or
[SPEAKER_02]: Chulip, or Nechanbara.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just an idea being thrown out there with maybe a $2 or $3 million budget.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, you should pick up Puzzle Quest GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and perhaps this is just a spot where video games just have a hard time, but there has to be some place where you can actually do meaningful experimentation, because you can't do it in the casual space.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's just not enough, there's just not enough, you know, there's too many limits.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know... I suppose it would be hard to convince your wife that going to see Rambo would be a good Valentine's Day present, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I think that's also part of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have an industry that's confined to the idea of hardcore and casual.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't hear about hardcore moviegoers, casual moviegoers.
[SPEAKER_02]: You hear people who like action, romance.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's very particular crowds for types of movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, the B-movie alien weirdness has its own following.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to have that sort of market presence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for lack of a better term, market segregation, demographic scanning, because casual hardcore is perhaps a little too general.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Ross DLUT, some great topics, some very deep topics you're bringing up tonight, but unfortunately we are running out of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thanks for your call and provoking some good discussion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, before I go, I'd like to do a plug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've started up a YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: YouTube.com slash user slash rawsteelut Put up a link in the chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what will we find on said YouTube channel?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now it's mostly music videos that I've compiled up, but I have a few vlogs as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm just kind of looking at some of the things that are in this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you kind of make your own anime music videos and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, gaming music video.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, not anime.
[SPEAKER_06]: GMVs, not AMVs.
[SPEAKER_06]: GMVs, I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And like I said, I also have a couple of vlogs using the PlayStation Eye, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is quite an effort.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll go into that next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see you later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, best of luck with vlogging.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a nice one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross Steel, UT.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's always kind of the devil's advocate in chat, but then when he calls in, he's the nicest guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be car surfing in Saints Row 2 and that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait for Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ghost Ride the Whip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently they have a picture where you have crashed a biplane into a building.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or driven it through a mall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is even better.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm all about a game that allows you to drive a plane through a mall.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all know what's waiting to happen later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a feature they should have had in Dead Rising, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Puppy, thank you so much for being here tonight and participating in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking head number three for the night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you'll have to come back again soon, and it's probably kind of nice not getting talked over tonight because there's a lot far less people in-house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and I had my own microphone the entire time.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thanks for coming, and stay away from the gunshots in your neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will certainly try to.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't want to see Puppy get put down.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would not be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any final thoughts though, Puppy, real quick?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was looking on your prize table here and saw these applications for passports.
[SPEAKER_06]: The passport applications are not prizes.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just making sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we're not giving out Rob's passport application as a prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just something I'm working on for a trip I want to take in June.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, by the way, you know how they say it takes forever to get a passport right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: My roommate went in and he got it in a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: A week.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a renewal.
[SPEAKER_05]: New.
[SPEAKER_05]: My brother managed to get one when he went to Italy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It took him like a week and a half to get his when he went to Italy earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thankfully I'm not going out of the country.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just going to Texas to meet for a Puzzle Pirates party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to get William to take me back to Canada because I really want to go to Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just trying to decide right now if it's going to be Vancouver, which I've already been to and I love, or Toronto, which I've never been to but I really want to go to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toronto's winning in my mind right now, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Canada once.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Victoria, and I got stuck having to go to those botanical gardens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I love the Bouchard Gardens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you go knocking them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless you go in, like, fall, then there's not a lot to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think William told me he went to the Bouchard Gardens once in October, and I'm like, dude, you went at the wrong time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, enough travel chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, any final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: The spin the black circle thing is...
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty addicting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except I'm on this one level.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's been playing it all fucking night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I have been participating, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: This does not take that much participation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, if he had been playing the Velociraptor Safari game, you wouldn't have heard a peep out of him, unless it was maniacal laughter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, my final thought is next week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually going to be out of town because it's holiday slash anniversary weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going out of town.
[SPEAKER_06]: We may have a late start to the show because of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: More information to come later throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure exactly what the plan is yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are looking forward to being back here next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frisbee suggests I vote because of Valentine's Day this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to have William, Nellie, and Dan as guests on the show next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that will happen either.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know we can't do this without you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, if you like Orange Lounge Radio, if you like what you hear, please tell two friends about our show because that's the only way we get to spread the word.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have any big magazines or websites that back us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are literally an independent operation run out of somebody's garage, and it's your voice and talking and word of mouth that helps spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another reason to support us, we are not changing our review system to letters.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, we're not.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to stick with the whole vague reviews that we've always done here on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until next time, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: She will be DarkSakura back with us next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you then here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!