[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, February 24th, 2008, community games come to Xbox Live and Zune, Microsoft officially abandons HD DVD, and Nintendo reveals that there is much more in store for the Wii Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Hi everybody out there on the internet, and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we are back from an unexpected vacation last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll tell you more about what's going down in just a little bit, but it wouldn't be a show if I couldn't introduce my lovely co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Over there is the one and only, happiest bunny on the farm, Miss DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing, Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm satiated.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're satiated?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've had a mostly unsatisfactory day as far as things to dine on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've had a
[SPEAKER_10]: Power Bar, and Ice Cream.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's also pretty nasty.
[SPEAKER_14]: McDonald's, it's nasty, but in smaller portions.
[SPEAKER_14]: Burger King, that's the only fast food that's not so nasty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't had Burger King in a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's one really, really good thing that they would occasionally have on their menu.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: That I actually miss.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those chicken sandwiches that were on the long buns.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hello to everybody in our chat room at chat.orangelongeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we're live on Justin.TV with our webcam, and they have a chat room as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: We try to keep an eye on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's justintv.com slash orangelongeradio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It always has the video archive of our shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see our smiling faces, or tonight, according to one of our chatters, frowning face.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a comment from a NYR fan in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.orangelongeradio.com says, Rob sounds sad this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sad, I'm just sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's not one thing, it's another.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, last week we weren't here with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happened is that I was in Long Beach.
[SPEAKER_04]: William and I were away for the weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: We went to the Star Trek tour in Long Beach.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up, don't laugh, it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what wasn't awesome was my car breaking down over the grapevine on the way there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I had to find a mechanic in Long Beach Saturday morning, paid him like $450 to fix my car, but they did do a lot on my car.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then as I was driving home,
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the stinking lights came on again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something's wrong with something in the oil.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would explain it, but it would bore you to tears.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably told like 50 different people about what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So needless to say, I couldn't rush home on Sunday and I made it back late.
[SPEAKER_04]: So unfortunately, we didn't have a show on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now this week, I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if it's not one thing, it's another.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're starting late tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, podcast listeners, you guys don't hear a difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for those listening live tonight, we're about 15 minutes late because the Wi-Fi in studio wasn't working and some of our computers couldn't get online.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's just February is broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a refund.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie wasn't here two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, February is just broken.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's because I was sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was nasty, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're up against the Oscars tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oscars suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares about the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even a good name.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bunch of stuck-up people sucking each other's... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do they call it the Oscars anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's Oscar?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the award, but it's actually the Academy Awards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you could probably read it on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did they name it after somebody named Oscar?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's short for something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oscar is short for something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just talk about our gaming week, shall we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be better than those Oscars.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: What games would you give an Oscar to this week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Played some Half-Life 2 and lots of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now have another character over 100.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rebirth, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_10]: So.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played... I looked at my copy of Imagine Babies, laughed, and put it back up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, although it spawned an interesting conversation about whether or not you could raise them like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I thought it was kind of silly.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there was also some more burnout going on in my house, but I think that Dan's getting tired of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it'd be cool, though, if you could raise them like Pokemon and then have them fight in underground baby cage matches.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'd be like cockfighting but with babies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Put little razor blades on their feet.
[SPEAKER_10]: But babies couldn't actually fight because they don't have any motor coordination when they're that little.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why you hop them up on crack and then, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have a one-year-old battle when they're old enough to walk.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I played Wedding the Game, which was me just sitting there going, how much more can I drink?
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, this week I played a few things.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got around to playing some Lost Odyssey, and that game is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It reminds me a lot of Final Fantasy VIII, just not necessarily, well, I guess a little bit like the gameplay, but more of just the environment reminds me of Final Fantasy VIII.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's good, and I like the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I played more Burnout Paradise because it's available, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe it's allergic to your job.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had these screws in it that were too large so it was causing the board to bend too much.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I replaced them with some different stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I did a 12 volt mod on the fan and also put heat sinks on different chips in there and made heat sinks out of pennies and aluminum tape for the bottom of the board.
[SPEAKER_14]: So hopefully with all that stuff done, it should work.
[SPEAKER_14]: If not, I've already soldered in a fan connector for additional fans.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I just found my Dremel today, so I can cut the case open to put a 120mm fan on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other things I've been playing...
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually was trying out, and we'll get to some of this stuff later, the X and A community games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they had a few that were pretty cool, some that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of which that was pretty cool was The Dishwasher.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew it would be The Dishwasher.
[SPEAKER_04]: The minute I played that game, I was like, this is Loki's dream game right here.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not my dream game, but it totally could be a TV series or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was just really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Something you would see on Adult Swim.
[SPEAKER_14]: But absolutely bloody game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It kind of reminds me actually a little bit also of Alien Hominid or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the exact same thing I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: But less shooting, more slashing with swords and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other things I tried.
[SPEAKER_14]: I tried Gummy Car or Jelly Car, whatever the fuck it was called.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really... I mean, it was a neat idea, but...
[SPEAKER_14]: Not executed too well?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what makes Jelly Car hilarious?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is when you realize that all the noises are some guy doing it at his microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I laughed my ass off playing Jelly Car.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's very customizable with its little completely different looks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you can play the blueprint-looking things.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can kind of completely change the look of the game and the options.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't even play with the options.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can mess with the options and make the game look completely different.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, other than that, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of the levels, though, seemed kind of broken, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, then there was Culture, which was neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, it's an interesting, like, puzzle game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: With flowers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty flowers.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then, um, gosh.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played that, was it, uh, Little Gamers, I think it was called?
[SPEAKER_14]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's actually just based off of a webcomic, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it was...
[SPEAKER_14]: It was okay, but it just reminded me a lot of, like, there wasn't a lot of movement or dodging you can do.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was just kind of shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, you know, and very bloody.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, hey, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was pretty much it, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: There were some games that they showed off at Game Developers Conference that I wish were on there, like Ice Sheep, or, um, what was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: There was a dancing one, like a breakdancing thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, wait a minute, did you, and I'm sorry, I ran in the house and you were talking about your game of the week, but I didn't hear anything about N. Didn't you play N this week on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you loved that game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love N, but I haven't gotten a chance to download it, and I really, I mean, it's, I've played it before, so, you know, it's not, it's not like I'm, I don't know, I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, finally, I was going to say I played Space Invaders Extreme.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually was playing that this afternoon, and awesome game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really needs to be an Xbox Live Arcade game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's coming out the DS and on PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Absolutely cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: All the stuff in the game kind of goes with the music.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like when you're firing and stuff, it's all in time with the music.
[SPEAKER_14]: And stuff kind of remixes a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a little like Mizuguchi and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have little bonus things that go in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plus the backgrounds are all really flashy and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Definitely worth picking up when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're all done with your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I will move on to mine, because I just wanted to say, I did play M this week on Xbox 360, and it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least I should clarify, I only played the demo, I didn't play the full version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to give a false impression or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I played the demo of M, because I remember Loki spoke very highly of this game, and I remember playing it a little bit on the free web thing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX LIVE COMMUNITY GAMES
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think, and it's kind of fun, I just think $800 is the wrong price point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think $400 would have been a little more appropriate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably would have bought it for $400.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially when you consider it's based off a free web game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like I've played a lot of free games on the web like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although there's a certain sense of humor to end that I think is really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I like watching little stick guy get blown to bits.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it certainly has a very, you know, kind of action pace.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: In this day of those microtransactions, you really kind of think about every point, and I just don't think it was worth 800.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that was money well spent, I am madly in love with Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the game I have totally been waiting for on the 360, and I know, you know, I'm going to admit it, I am kind of biased, well, I don't want to say I'm biased, but I definitely have a preference towards Japanese RPGs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's no big secret.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are the type of games I like.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't play a lot of sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like these type of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so, you know, the Xbox 360 has been sorely lacking in this department.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had Blue Dragon, which was, it was okay, but it wasn't great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a good game, not a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we had Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Decent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think better than a lot of people gave it credit for, but it started to get a little monotonous towards the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lost Odyssey, I'm loving it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's tearing me away from WoW, which is saying something, you know, because you hear about how much I've been playing World of Warcraft lately and doing this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I cannot put down Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's funny because I've been reading reviews because I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I usually don't read a lot of reviews on the internet, but I was kind of curious what the critics think of Lost Odyssey, and I was very surprised to see on Metacritic that the game only has like a 76 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am shocked.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is like an old school RPG, you know, it's so old, you know, everyone's complaining that it's like
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: They really didn't change much between each other.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't have to innovate on something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't try to reinvent it if it's good in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's a comment in chat I have to respond to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.NormalNationalCenter.com Ross Steel UT says, so Sky likes games that are all the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's your perception of these types of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I look at sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I look at these Madden games and I go, they're all the same to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: These games are all the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the story that go along with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not necessarily the combat and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just kind of, yeah, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, you know, it's grinding or whatever, but... You know, and I've heard people say it's reminded them too much of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll admit, there's a lot in this game that reminds me of Final Fantasy X. I wouldn't call it Final Fantasy VIII because it has a good combat system, unlike VIII.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Final Fantasy X, it really reminds me of.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the combat system.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know, it innovates it on it enough where, like, I love the ring thing because it makes you pay attention to kind of what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad we have games like this to hold us over.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if you enjoy Japanese RPGs in the slightest, you are doing yourself a disservice by not at least checking out Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't listen to reviewers, because their big complaints are they don't like these type of games in the first place, which, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is not going to win you over to the Japanese RPG world.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't like the Final Fantasy games, you're not going to like this.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why they have places that rent games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just because one guy doesn't like it doesn't mean you should base your opinion on that one guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of these reviews I read are just like,
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, well, this game's been done so many times, that's why I hate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: No?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, who cares?
[SPEAKER_14]: Action movies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, it's an action movie with guns in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, should I not go see it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because this one had guns too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just beautiful to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: My roommate, who doesn't play a lot of games, the game he's been playing a lot lately is Cold Step Saga.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the one game he's been getting really into lately, because he likes the more puzzle-type games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's been watching me play Lost Odyssey, and he's always kind of appreciated the Final Fantasy games too, and he's just like,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I will kind of put this out there as a disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only about eight hours in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't had a chance to really fully immerse myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be one of those games that gets shitty and monotonous as it goes on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a possibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for right now, I'm saying it's money well spent, and I've fully enjoyed the eight hours I've put in so far, which is more than some games I've dropped six months off.
[SPEAKER_14]: My only gripe in the game is these dreams that you have, which are basically reading a bunch of text, and there's no real cutscene.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would think with a game that is...
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought the writing was amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I would have appreciated it more like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't even have to be anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: It would be just still pictures or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just a little bit more effort put into it other than just having text.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more fangasm over this game and then I promise I'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can send your emails about what a fanboy I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: The voice acting in this game is actually really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm using the English soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_04]: English voice acting in these games is usually pretty terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I actually think it's very well voice acted so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, just shocked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my roommate said the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, wow, the voice acting is actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: The comic relief guy especially is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just the way the cutscenes are done, all the comic books start.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could sit here for an hour and have a fangasm about how wonderful I think Lost Odyssey is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to play it more, and I'll let you know if it starts sucking, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll keep an open mind about it, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of one of those games that's really hard to put down.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, rounds in Cold Step Talk can go on for like an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm having a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I'll do it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have a lot else to share.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, then let's get to tonight's housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wanted to formally apologize for last week's show, or lack thereof.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, what can we say?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a free show, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're here tonight, and actually I gotta admit,
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight we're only going to do a short show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to do just one part.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not going to be part A, part B, just because of the fact that I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm having a hard time being here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other week, probably wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're not consistent, then people will go look elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, not that that's necessarily a bad thing because there's lots of great independent shows out there, but that's how you lose listeners, is that if you're inconsistent, then people look elsewhere to fill in time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I hate, I hate missing a show, but it had to be done.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, you can join our MySpace community at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our Facebook community is the OLR Army, and our live journal community is Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other thing I want to plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely has nothing to do with video games, but it's another passion of mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something I've been getting into over the past six months is these ORGs, these online reality games, where people play games based on reality shows on web forums, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of strategy involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're into the strategical thinking that goes behind a lot of shows, such as Survivor and Big Brother and all those types of shows that are on TV...
[SPEAKER_04]: SurvivorLJ.livejournal.com So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: That Netflix is soon going to be streaming to the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is based off some type of survey that Netflix has been conducting recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the question that was in the survey was this, quote, If as part of your Netflix membership you could instantly watch movies and TV episodes on your TV with your PS3 or Xbox 360, how likely would you or anyone in your household be able to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: EA is rumored to be working on The Sims 3 and this is actually not a rumor because that's according to The Sims Studio creative director Rod Humble and this was on a forum called Quarter to Three.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, Rod Humble says there will be new information
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yet another way to kill Sims.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see if Sims 3 comes to light, maybe some type of link between the PC and the consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's just the console fan in me, because The Sims is kind of at heart a PC game, even though they've had all those spin-offs on systems and such.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims is kind of a PC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it'll be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all about connectivity between all the crap I have and my friends have.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other story we missed last week, which I think is kind of funny, there's some filmmakers that are going to be producing a documentary about
[SPEAKER_04]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_04]: Landfill
[SPEAKER_04]: A quote from the Auburn University students who are putting this together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, we are proud to announce our upcoming documentary, E.T.'
[SPEAKER_04]: 's March.
[SPEAKER_04]: Over the course of a week this March, we will go on a road trip from Auburn, Alabama to El Paso, Texas.
[SPEAKER_04]: From there, we will take the actual path of those 14 trucks took that faithful day into the heart of Alamogordo, New Mexico.
[SPEAKER_04]: Along the way, we will take in the video game culture of our great country.
[SPEAKER_04]: The documentary will be released for free via the internet this summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I almost went to school there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's kind of interesting that they're going to make a whole documentary about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, video game documentaries, King of Kong did very well.
[SPEAKER_09]: The DVD should be out now, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to borrow it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an interesting watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need Netflix it or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really want to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like I'm totally missing something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll loan it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll also loan you this other one I have that's really stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's about the first... They claim they're the first ever internet...
[SPEAKER_14]: Kind of like an internet radio show about games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's uber stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually watched the game review show.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to this week's news.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I really want to touch on from last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week, ironically enough, was a little bit of a slow news week because this week we started getting into Game Developers Conference and some big bombshells dropped at GDC, correct?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unfortunately, this year they didn't have keynotes from a bunch of other people like Nintendo and Sony and stuff like that, but Microsoft was there and they were doing their keynote.
[SPEAKER_14]: Their big thing they announced, of course, was the Xbox Live Community Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will be kind of a
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Tons and tons and tons of stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, they said now 10 million people on Xbox Live get to play your game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's all user-created content.
[SPEAKER_14]: They put up a brief sampling of about nine games or so on there, including some of the way you talked about Jelly Car and Dishwasher and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So pretty cool stuff and very exciting, especially if you're into game development and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: And XNA, as far as I'm aware, I think,
[SPEAKER_14]: The software is free.
[SPEAKER_14]: All you have to do is pay for the membership if you want to upload your games.
[SPEAKER_14]: $100 a year.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you're really interested in that stuff, I'm sure Bobby Blackwolf will probably all over this kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seem to recall he was creating some type of Crazy Eights game from what I was following on a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now maybe that he'll be able to post it to the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: He might finish that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to ask him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't talked to him in a little while.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then...
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course, other things that they announced to go along with that is that you will finally be able to game on your Zune as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to allow XMA games to come to the Zune and you'll be able to play them kind of similar to playing stuff on an iPod or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they said, of course, XMA Zune games can also support custom soundtracks since it is an MP3 player.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you'll be able to take your games from Windows to Xbox to Zune.
[SPEAKER_14]: And...
[SPEAKER_14]: You haven't really announced anything else additional to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't know if it's just me, this news is fucking huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: This news.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is like, I think a lot of us saw this coming, but I kind of see this as kind of a turning point in gaming, and I think this is what is going to set the Xbox 360 really apart from its competitors right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is huge news.
[SPEAKER_14]: They said at the end of this year they're going to have a thousand games on Xbox 360 and that's not including the Xbox Live Community games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what this is?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is YouTube but with video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's YouTube of games that they were... And that's kind of what it's going to turn into.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know people's opinions is that a lot of the user stuff is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of user-made stuff is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you look on YouTube, and yeah, a lot of YouTube is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's these 14-year-old girls doing their blogs and shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one wants to watch that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I understand that a lot of it's crap, but at the same time, I think these people are actually... I mean, YouTube is free.
[SPEAKER_14]: Any idiot with a camera can go and shoot something and throw it up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_14]: This, you actually pay membership...
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to have the tools to develop the games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to be somewhat intelligent to even do this.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not an easy thing to just throw something together and put it on there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would be really interested to see this stuff on here because a lot of it is going to be independent games.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to have people that are developing some of these free web games to put it on there now and they can make a little bit of money off it and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also at the same time, it's something that Sony or Nintendo doesn't have that they can –
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and for those that say that the user-created games are crap, fucking go check out that Dishwasher game and the Jelly Car game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put it next to some of the things that they're actually charging money for on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the, you know, they got some crappy games on Xbox Live Marketplace right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there is certainly some good stuff that can come of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a lot of great independent games that, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, yeah, there's going to be a lot of crap that you're going to have to weed through, but I think this whole community kind of aspect of it where it's the peer review, I think that's kind of a smart way to kind of weed it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not everything independent is crap either.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, look at, you know, N Plus started off as an independent game.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have Tamiki Fighters.
[SPEAKER_14]: That started off as an independent game.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have, you know, Everyday Shooter.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just a ton of stuff out there that, you know, was independent stuff that is now becoming mainstream and
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just, you know, a lot of times it costs a lot of these people a lot of money to develop these games, and if they don't have a lot of money to put into them, they can't get a wide release for them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now this is allowing people that may not have the funds to advertise their game or do anything like that to do a lot smaller scale and advertise their stuff on websites and that kind of thing, and then throw it on this community arcade and have a lot of people actually get to play their game instead of just not ever hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I do think that the fact that these games are going to be playable on Zune I think that's huge too because I think Microsoft can really be positioning themselves to do a game handheld if they want imagine if Microsoft releases a portable gaming handheld not necessarily a Zune but something that is more along you know as strictly a gaming machine imagine they release it and they support XNA on this handheld boom this thing comes out it instantly supports thousands of games
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's what I think is big.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kind of see, like, this could be Microsoft positioning the chess pieces and kind of seeing how much this takes off.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many people do this and put this on their Zune?
[SPEAKER_04]: How many kind of get into this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I kind of think this is big news, and we're really looking down the next couple years of gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'm, you know, running around screaming like a lunatic cultist, which is fine, but I think this is huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I look forward to seeing some of the games that are going to come out from this.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think they would call it if they did a Microsoft handheld?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Microsoft handheld system?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the Xbox, but the Xbrick?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xgame.
[SPEAKER_11]: It could be like the Xpaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Paper, rock, scissors?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox says Frisbee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, make it sound like a Mac product.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd sell it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about something like Xbox Go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something really quick to the point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't that kind of have the ring of, hey, it's an Xbox product, but you go and you take it places.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a fine name.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to trademark that name right now so Microsoft can't use it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I have some interesting news.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know, everybody, well, for the most part, loves Portal.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a big, big internet phenomenon, especially with that psychotic song at the end of the game that's so funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that song, Still Alive, is going to be in a rock band.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a triumph.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we've got to get Moe back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You realize we've got to download this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, we've got a whole band going right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki can play the drums.
[SPEAKER_04]: You enjoy bass, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can play bass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play whatever guitar.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure you should play the drums when we play at the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then you two can fight over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play regular guitar.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just not singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Mo can sing because she's got a pretty voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: She can do the singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll have ourselves a little OLR house band.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe by the time that comes out, we'll have the rock band stage kit.
[SPEAKER_14]: We can have the smoke and the lights.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob almost snorted his coffee.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you really wasting money on that stage?
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to get it because it sounds so stupid that I have to get it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's one of those things.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just, I'm not spending money on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll use store credit, you know, obviously.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that is money that you could spend on something more better.
[SPEAKER_04]: More better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, more better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I spend money on stupid things, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll have to look at it to see what it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if it's something really retarded...
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the chat room is up in arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki must sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki must play vocals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it was also stated, though, that they've confirmed that another portal is in the works.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, the words Portal 2 were actually used.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other news, Madden 2010, Final Fantasy XIV, Kingdom Hearts 3, and all these other games confirmed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, here's the thing about, you know, the Portal 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was kind of like, you know, her comment was, oh, I think that they've announced this already.
[SPEAKER_14]: She didn't say that, you know, they have.
[SPEAKER_14]: But obviously they're going to make a Portal 2, duh.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, oh my god, sequel to a game that made a lot of money?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always think it's funny that it was a throwaway to begin with, pretty much, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it was more of a nod to an old project.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think it's because we all know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Portal, little game with not that big a budget, I don't think, has humongous success and practically a cult following.
[SPEAKER_04]: God's gonna have a sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of last year's Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just hope they don't run it into the ground like they did Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my only concern.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can too much Portal be too much of a good thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, too much Portal when you're intoxicated is too much of a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fully support Portal 2, but when we start getting Portal DS, Portal PSP, Portal your brain out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Could you imagine Portal DS?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it would be all sorts of lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, I just stick to the formula that works, make little improvements as you need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about multiplayer Portal?
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be a processing nightmare.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just put a giant knife on the end of the portal gun.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Portal deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_14]: Giant bayonet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine what a portal deathmatch would be like.
[SPEAKER_14]: Confusing as hell.
[SPEAKER_10]: With no actual weapon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the comparison between Portal and Katamari leads AJ Mix in our chatroom to say, me and my portal.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Son of Dad says, Portal 5, Disney Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, lordy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: A game that I'm kind of looking forward to, strangely enough, Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though the first one kind of lost interest in everyone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm all over this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am all over some of these more recent announcements.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the huge things that they announced in Fable 2, co-op play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty big for a somewhat role-playing adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get co-op play.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you and someone else own Fable 2, you can suddenly go into their single-player world, do your thing, and then leave.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just spread rumors about them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the same idea like in Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: If somebody's playing the game, you just kind of hop in and join.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, and leave.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the demo that they showed, actually, Jamie, Peter's character, who is a woman,
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I have very high hopes, so I'm hoping I'm not let down, but I am a little bit worried.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, you have the little doggy companion that follows you and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, this is big, Xbox Live minigame that will interact with the full Fable 2 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: or you can do 50-50, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would happen, though, if a really high-level advanced character came into your world and gave you an uber sword?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there anything to safeguard the game from essentially cheating like that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know about that, but, you know, if it's like some Final Fantasy games, you have to be a certain level before you can use, you know, X sword, but yeah, I mean, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to think back to the first Fable, it's been so long.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what we did in Crackdown, you know, someone would come in with a rocket launcher and give it to you, and there you go, now you have a rocket launcher, it makes the game a hell of a lot easier, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm looking forward to this game and checking it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of funny, the whole Xbox Live connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what it reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_04]: It reminds me of the Pocket Station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember Chocobo Breeding?
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't Chocobo Breeding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was some type of Razor Chocobo, like a Tamagotchi type thing that you could have on a little Pocket Station for Final Fantasy VIII?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it kind of reminds me of that, but instead of something in your pocket on the go, it's Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the comparison I get in my mind.
[SPEAKER_14]: The great thing about the Pocket Station game is it'll play itself, so all you have to do is just leave it on a PlayStation system and just leave it running for days at a time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_14]: You come back and you have thousands of items.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm looking forward to Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: Another game that's coming out here pretty soon in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: will be Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo has officially announced a date for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be coming out May 19th.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, around the same time, the WiiWare service will be launching in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: May 12th.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they did have a press release and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, this game is insanely popular in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just absolutely selling millions of copies, and I'm sure it will do the same over here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to keep Wii Mania alive in soccer moms' households.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just need them to announce another.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, I knew this was coming out this time.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, I know when some other games are coming out, but I can't say that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, Wii Fit's going to be doing awesome, and there'll be some other games before it that'll be even more awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking in the chat room, and let's see, who called it Wii Fat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody called it Wii Fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was GS68.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd be like an eating game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh eat as much as you can then get on the balance board uh and then um I'm very happy that we finally have a date for WiiWare finally kind of after all this speculation oh it's gonna be out last Christmas oh I guess first quarter oh second quarter now we have a date so that's finally when Nintendo will kind of be
[SPEAKER_14]: Get on board with what everyone else has been doing for years already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's something else that they're enacting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a payment service called Wii Connection Pay and Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that you can buy the WiiWare stuff with Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they said there's already, you know... We've got that with the virtual console, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is a little different, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is actually for online play in certain games.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to pay with Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's for download content and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I was getting to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've pretty much already said it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard this concept...
[SPEAKER_04]: said before for what Xbox Live should have done, is that especially for these retro arcade titles that you play them once and you're kind of done, wouldn't it be nice if you actually only played a quarter to play Tron?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here's a great example.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Tron, but Disks of Tron, that game gets old a little bit fast for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it was one of those games that's better left in my memories of being a seven-year-old, is Disks of Tron.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I wish I could have only paid 25 cents to play it once and then be done with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo in chat asks a good question, says, but Rob, isn't that what the demos are for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm, kinda, but what if you can get really far on one quarter?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's how the old school arcades work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes you're really good at a game naturally, you know?
[SPEAKER_14]: I took this news as something totally different.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought that this was going to be, like, extended services that they're going to be adding to, like, we say, for example, voice chat or something in a game, and you would have to pay extra for that kind of thing, because they were saying that, I thought they were saying that this was actually going to be used in disc-based games as well as,
[SPEAKER_14]: um you know the WiiWare games and stuff but I guess I read that wrong I don't know because I was understanding you know okay their service kind of sucks right now as far as what they have available online and so some stuff they were going to add later on or in order to finance that they were going to charge for some of the services like say for example you know leaderboards or friends lists or something like that online similar like live services but
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the other things I was going to bring up is that
[SPEAKER_10]: There is the whole Nintendo channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're supposed to be getting that over here and in Europe, which will let you get to screenshots, videos of new games, play demos of DS titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then after you've played for an hour, you can rate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you only, of course, do that through the Nintendo channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it'll keep track of what you play, what you use to find new games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's basically...
[SPEAKER_10]: TVO, SD Cards
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll get manuals online, too, from the Wii Shop channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can check them out so that you know what you're paying for before you do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can only get them, of course, through your Wi-Fi connection.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're, again, going to be based on what you like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another thing that they're launching in Japan that we're probably not going to get is...
[SPEAKER_10]: Another type of channel that shows TV program listings so that you can see what you want to watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then again, we basically already have that already built into cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: TV Guide Channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the TV Guide Channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it doesn't really say anything else about that, but they're saying that they're not going to bring it out anywhere else yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: I doubt we're going to get that since I think it's all for Japanese channels anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless we really care what's on Japanese TV, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, between everything Jamie's saying here about what's coming to the Wii and what we were talking about earlier with the XNA Creators Club, this is going to be a really big year for digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then if the Netflix thing turns out to be true, this is a big, big year for download stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's the way everything's going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we've all known that for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: To see it actually happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one thing to talk about, and it's one thing to see how it plays out, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm also curious to see how the Wii Balance Board plays out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently, according to Reggie Fils-Aimé, over 10 Wii Balance Board games are in development.
[SPEAKER_04]: The most common problem with a peripheral, they come out, there's only one or two games for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that game fails, the whole damn peripheral fails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody that bought it feels like they wasted their money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it seems like, you know, when these peripherals come out, companies are throwing a lot of money behind it to try and make them take off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's certainly one thing that they're doing with the Wii Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe the fact that it's already done so well in Japan helps, who knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Reggie Fils-Aimé commented in something he was speaking to with IGN.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said, quote, there are over 10 games in development that take advantage of the balance board.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we know so far would be Wii Fit and then the skiing game that Namco's putting out, but who knows what else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could it be that the other Wii balance board games are some of these download titles that you'll be able to play?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or another WarioWare game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I bet a WarioWare game's a given, actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: To kind of go back to that last story we were talking about, Nintendo's Takashi Aoyama, actually they were saying his description of the service was that Nintendo will begin collecting fees for some services that will allow us to adapt flexibility.
[SPEAKER_14]: So in other words, it's subsidizing additional services like new channels and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it will be something that's on boxes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like they said, it's going to be an orange logo that's going to be right next to the Wi-Fi Connect logo.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I think this is something additional.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not just like an arcade kind of format where you pay X amount of Wii points to play a game or something like that online.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll have to see when it finally comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, Why couldn't anyone bring back the Sega Activator?
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of peripherals that didn't do so hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's another reason why games like Parapar didn't really take off either.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had similar type of peripherals.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have an activator.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had one, and I disassembled it because I was going to turn it into a Parapar controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't that ironic?
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no time in my life that I owned an activator.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, so another game that of course we're looking forward to pretty soon is Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: and luckily the rest of the world knows when it's coming out, except the US.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't that ironic?
[SPEAKER_14]: But apparently though, Mario Kart Wii will be hitting Japan on April 10th, also coming to Europe the day after on the 11th.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, it's going to be bundled with the Wii wheel, a piece of plastic crap that you're going to stick the remote in.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, you do not need to use that to play the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, you'll have as many control options as Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: did.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's awesome, including GameCube and classic controllers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, if I use Logic, if it's coming out the same week in Japan and Europe, wouldn't it be logical to say that's going to be the same time frame we get it here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I have some fun news and stuff that, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I can say when it's coming out because it already has.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is our UK virtual console.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is pretty cool because this is actually, speaking of the Activator, this is a game that I bought with my Activator.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I love Eternal Champions CD a lot more.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a really good transition.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just saying from the Activator to the Eternal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a really good transition, that's all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to take time out to acknowledge that really good transition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel very confident now in my announcing skills.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: As if an endorsement from me is what's needed.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm ruining the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, Eternal Champions is like one of those, like,
[SPEAKER_10]: If you have wanted violence in video games, this is what did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had your overkills, how each level would have this super destructive, violent move.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had people from all over the world and all through time.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had a robot kickboxer and a caveman.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's your face that had the really cool snake-looking dress thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: She was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we have any Sega CD games that have come out on Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sega CD?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I can think of.
[SPEAKER_10]: If we're getting Turbo Duo games, and why can't we get... Night Trap on virtual consoles?
[SPEAKER_04]: Please say we can have... Or, dude, I want Criss Cross to make your own video.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fantasy Star 2
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is... It's another 800 Wii Points game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's actually, I'd have to say, probably tops to me in the series because it had Ney in it and she was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Dark Knight in chat would like you to know the girl's name was Jetta Max.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I should have remembered that because my favorite character on Gem was Jetta.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's another story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus it's a pretty cool car.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: for the Phantasy Star games, it was like you had your different viewpoint where you played from behind the characters and could attack for your different scenes and your little dungeon crawl areas it was really cool, I'd have to say the story wasn't all that great, but it was just a fun game to play
[SPEAKER_10]: and moving forward we also have Street Gangs that was a Nintendo NES game for 500 points and it's not worth and actually the cool thing about this is you want to know what's super cool about it?
[SPEAKER_04]: what?
[SPEAKER_10]: River City Ransom is what it is ah okay yep which the Japanese name of it was Hot Blooded Downtown Story
[SPEAKER_04]: When the guys die, did they actually say, BARF!
[SPEAKER_10]: They make more punch noises.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's all I remember is in the NES one.
[SPEAKER_04]: When he killed people, they'd go, barf!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I will have to, if you would like, I would have to find my burn of the PC Engine Duo ones that you can see.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's
[SPEAKER_10]: Psychic Storm
[SPEAKER_10]: And this game has a subtitle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan calls it, I Get Pissed Off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because when they say Psychic Storm, they say it in a very thick accent, and Dan thinks they're saying, I Get Pissed Off.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's another one that I'm going to have to get from a friend of mine that I think I've talked about on the show before, that's called Sylphia, where it's a shooter game with fairies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be, actually, like, maybe we could do something where, like, we bring in a whole stock of games, and, like, we'll play each game for an hour, and we let the chat vote on which game we'll play next or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you know it's going to be over as soon as I put Dracula X in?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you won't get me off that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe save that for last.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, the last game on the list is Adventure Island for 500 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Adventure Island is just, it's classic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: Wonder Boy Monsterland
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Adventure Island Super Adventure Island Super Adventure Island Super Adventure Island Super Adventure Island
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, though, I would really, really like to see... I haven't seen, at least as far as I've paid attention, I haven't seen any of the Alex Kidd games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would personally like to see Alex Kidd in Shinobi World.
[SPEAKER_04]: You seem to bring that up every chance you get.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want Alex Kidd in Shinobi World.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of these days it's going to be my classic game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Japan, Japan, Japan, Japan
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on February 28th, Call of Juarez and the Idolmaster live for you on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Idolmaster is pretty big over in Japan, and so it's a pretty big title coming out this week for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the PlayStation 3, nothing!
[SPEAKER_04]: But you do get Guitar Hero 3 next week, so stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also in Japan, coming out on the Nintendo Wii, ChoroQ Wii, sorry, ChoroQ Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uchi Suri Sega Bass Fishing
[SPEAKER_04]: will be coming out as well on the Nintendo Wii in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to the PlayStation 2, Burnout 3 Takedown comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a price reduction, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's actually a new release.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Approach 2, First Priority comes out from one of my favorite companies, Princess Soft comes out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming out, lots of price reductions, Medal of Honor Frontline, Need for Speed Underground 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this title, Night Wizard the Video Game, Denial of the World is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds so emo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Denial of the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the Nintendo DS, Soma Bringer, as well as Akajawa Jiro Mystery, Yasu Kyoku is coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the PSP in Japan is Nothing But a New Pouch in Mint Green.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no games.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The US is getting quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pot of Pawn on the PSP, it's a pretty cool rhythm game, also a bit of action thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the 360 and PC, no PS3 version for this, Frontlines Fuel of War, another military first person shooter.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lost Viadomus coming to Xbox 360, PC and PS3, good spin off of this show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Turning Point Fall of Liberty on 360 PC and PS3, kind of an alternate World War II shooter game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Naruto Ninja Destiny on the DS, it's a Naruto 3D fighter game.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Sims 2 Free Time for PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lost Planet Extreme Condition on the PS3, which includes bonus characters like Mega Man, Frank from Dead Rising, and some of the other characters from the PC version.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blast is only $39.99, so pretty good price for a game that came out a year ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Destroy All Humans, Big Willy Unleashed for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Love the Destroy All Humans series.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mazes of Fate DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an RPG, kind of a traditional one for the DS there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Agatha Christie's, and then there were none for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: An adventure game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Arma, Gold Edition for PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Heavenly Guardian for PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of an anime-style 2D shooter game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Puzzle Guzzle for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's another... Puzzle Guzzle?
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Guzzle.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the dumbest name I've ever heard for a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to the makers of Puzzle Guzzle, whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Age Tech.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's a bad name.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a bad name.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some GameStop-exclusive stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fantasy Aquarium...
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, you can raise all sorts of different fish and sea life, including dolphins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seaman 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just going to say, can you raise a seaman?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if you can.
[SPEAKER_14]: This actually is also coming out, not a GameStop exclusive.
[SPEAKER_14]: Block is Portable SteamBot Championship.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is actually a game that was in that SteamBot Chronicles game, which I thought was very niche anyways, and now you can play it away from the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: And
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, Bubble Bobble Double Shot on the DS, hopefully with level 30 as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Brain Assist, that's coming out on the DS from Sega, yet another brain training game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sega Bass Fishing for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not necessarily using the Dreamcast fishing rod, but you can pretend with the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_14]: and Spitfire Heroes Tales Royal Air Force for the DS by Destineer because they put out a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I believe that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I like this title that's coming out next week though.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a horse riding sim.
[SPEAKER_14]: But if you say the name of the title a little bit, it sounds weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's Ride Friends Forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't say that out loud really fast, because that sounds really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, and Tigers, or Pets, Wild Animals, Tigers game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, because now you can raise tigers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, and Bratz Super Babies.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go ride friends forever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Only friends let friends ride friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, is that it for US releases?
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, yeah, and this isn't really a game, but, uh, the extra guitars for Guitar Hero 3 are coming out for PS3 and the Wii now, so, um... Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if you're looking for extra guitars.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a copy of Bejeweled I'm seeing on the table over there?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually already been given away, I just haven't gotten to the post office yet, so... I was like... Oh, it was the week you weren't here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I'm baffled by that, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bejeweled 2, even better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what I thought, um,
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys were talking about obscure games.
[SPEAKER_14]: This isn't really obscure, but I guess it's obscure now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Commander Keen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_14]: Play some of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember those.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bunch of EGA-colored games.
[SPEAKER_14]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what other game, though, I was thinking about just the other day?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Jazz Jackrabbit.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Jill of the Jungle?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was rad.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about our UK releases?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about them?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know me, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: My favorite PC game is so super obscure right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 28th, we have Lost on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: 29th, we have 8 Ball All-Stars on DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have Asterix at the Olympic Games comic series.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we have a French version, I think, because the title's in French.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have Beautiful Katamari on the 29th on Xbox 360, Blacksite Area 51, Bleach, Shattered Blade, and the Blade of Fate, Wii and DS respectively.
[SPEAKER_10]: Destroy All Humans, Big Willy Unleashed, Fish Tycoon, Frontlines Fuel of War on Xbox 360 and PC, Guilty Gear XX Accent Core on Wii,
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamster All-Stars, King of Clubs, Lost Odyssey, Lost Planet Extreme Condition, Namco Museum on DS, Persona 3, Spongebob Atlanta Squarepants, The Spiderwick Chronicles, Warriors of the Lost Empire, and Zoo Hospital.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds like an exciting week over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a long wait for beautiful Katamari.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say so.
[SPEAKER_14]: Epic and Apogee are 3D Realms now.
[SPEAKER_14]: They really need to go back and remake a lot of their older games like Shareware.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are some IPs that need to be gone and revisited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who doesn't want a new Jill of the Jungle 3D shooter or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, people are looking for that good female heroine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, speaking of new IPs, based on old ideas, possibly, Activision apparently has filed a trademark for a game name called DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just couldn't stop there, could you?
[SPEAKER_14]: You just had to go and
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think a lot of us have seen this coming for a long time, and of course the reason why a lot of us... Remember, Orange Lounge Radio, hello, look at our name.
[SPEAKER_04]: We started a long time ago as a station dedicated to music-based video games, and one of them specifically was Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think a lot of us called this a long time ago when we started seeing Guitar Hero's success.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Konami's going to sit on it and not do anything with it, somebody else is going to pick it up and run with it, and I think that's what we're going to see happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure Konami is going to license the rights for their controller type design and that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they've already done one here.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we know that they have trademarks and copyrights in place for stuff like that, like Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Sega does also have the Kraken DJ-1 licensed over here too.
[SPEAKER_14]: But here's what I'm wondering though with this is,
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, really all they're doing, and I mean this isn't that big of a surprise because most buying games are like that too, all they're really doing is just swapping out a guitar for, you know, a turntable and buttons.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, if that's what they're going to be doing with this.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're really whoring that Guitar Hero franchise and kind of running it into the ground, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to be a clone of Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're not going to do that, but
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be interesting to see kind of what happens with it, what they decide to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're going to see something like frequency amplitude, but with a different type of controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what it's going to be, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hope it's something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking this is going to be announced at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Microsoft is officially, well, along with everyone else...
[SPEAKER_14]: They will, of course, still warranty the product and stuff like that, but they're no longer manufacturing them.
[SPEAKER_14]: In other news, and this hasn't really made it out there that well other than a rumor, they have dropped the price to $50.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's official.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you can actually get one so I can hang it with my LaserDisc player and the Betamax in our closet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, if you're looking for something cheap...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God I have Stardust.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Batman Begins.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I hope that that comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, I think if you can get a hold of one of these for pretty dirt cheap, I mean, just hold out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just like UMDs, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those UMD movies, they're dirt cheap because no one wants them.
[SPEAKER_14]: And people start trying to get rid of these things, and I think you'll be able to find them pretty cheap.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plus, I mean, there's no real difference between those and Blu-ray movies anyways as far as image quality goes.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I don't think you're going to notice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know about some of you guys, but me, as somebody who picked up an HD DVD player, I'm mad that it's all over, and that makes me angsty, and that means it's time for the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: My FE of the week goes towards this stupid, clearly compensating for something man driving a truck.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had a very, very rainy day.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was very rainy, very windy, kind of nasty.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's this one particular turn where it's a little sharper than I think that it needs to be to turn, and it's pretty much a two lane left turn.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so, this one guy was in the inside lane and I was in the outside lane.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when we turned in, he basically cut me off in the middle of the turn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which isn't, you know, just rude.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's incredibly dangerous.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something that only an idiot would do.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he cuts me off and then he starts to spin out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I start to spin out because I was trying to, you know, avoid the tail end of these
[SPEAKER_10]: Retarded, you know, small penis truck.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, in his spinning out and me losing control, and I actually, you know, steered into it, managed to get myself straightened out.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the time I got my car, you know, back lined up and everything was fine, he swung out again, and if I hadn't stopped when I did, then he would have pretty much taken off my bumper.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: The other really kind of scary part about this is that, you know, there's that, well, I'm sure those of us in the room know, there's that ditch on the side, and I didn't want to go in that ditch.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have got my car dirty.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was just really the fact that there are people who should have to take psychological exams before they are permitted to drive.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: This person driving this truck was clearly of poor judgment, very, very poor driving skills, and substandard intelligence.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, F you to stupid people who drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: My F yous ought to be pretty obvious this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to being sick, F you to my car not working completely right when I pay a lot of money for my car, and F you to the Wi-Fi here not working, and just F you to February.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to my 360 sort of working, or at least playing games with me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Once I think it's working, I've tested it extensively, I take it to work, it starts up, 10 seconds later it freezes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It really fucking pisses me off because I can't figure out what's wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Although I'm getting close to where there's nothing more I can fix on it, so I'm going to have to cut a hole in the side of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just because I think that's necessary that I get the Dremel out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it'll look cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: As it is, it sounds like a jet coming out of that thing now that I've, you know, 12-volt modded the fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and I broke an intercooler too because I took it apart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, but... That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's keep moving on with the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, for supposedly being a short show tonight, I don't think we're going to be that short of a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of like one long show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun, right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're having fun, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have fun the more drunk I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, we're fans of the Commodore 64, wouldn't you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yes, we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: By we, I mean Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Commodore 64 was my first gaming system, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I had an Atari 2600, but I played tons of games on Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the C64.
[SPEAKER_10]: My first one makes me cry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would make me cry too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Commodore 64 is coming to the European Virtual Console later this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first two games to be out are Iridium and International Karate.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it looks to me like they're also going to be charging for them 500 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's not a...
[SPEAKER_10]: Any kind of notice as if we're going to be getting them over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think the other thing that they've recently announced is Master System Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope some of the classic Commodore 64 games come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, I think about it, and a lot of the games I played on Commodore 64 were like ports of arcade games and things that are out in various other types of ways now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there were some like old C64 games that were kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of them required a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want Impossible Mission, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want more than anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest is going to be getting a sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest Galactrix Puzzle Quest Galactrix
[SPEAKER_04]: or what the deal is.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Galactrix.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not Hexic.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's clearly different.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently now it has a whole sci-fi theme as opposed to a fantasy theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to withhold judgment until I play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does look like it has spells and all that good stuff from the old one, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what they say about too much of a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't oversaturate the market with all these, you know, subpar puzzle games that you slap the name Puzzle Quest on or you're going to be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, again, this game might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Bookworm Adventures is rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be knocking Bookworm Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides, it's two different people.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're talking PopCap games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That apparently likes to take PopCap games and remake them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Puzzle Quest was just like Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's the only reason Nelly plays it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob with two B's in chat says, I want Puzzle Quest Pirate's Booty.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need a good pirate puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, we have Puzzle Pirates.
[SPEAKER_14]: So EA, being the pompous asses that they are, decided, hey, we're fucking EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to try to buy Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to offer you two billion dollars.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, of course, you know, Take-Two looked at it and said, no, sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why I think this is interesting?
[SPEAKER_04]: Correct me if I'm wrong, but doesn't Take-Two own 2K Games?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, Take-Two owns 2K Games.
[SPEAKER_14]: They also own Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, buying this would have EA would have a monopoly on most sports.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, if that happened, EA would have a sports monopoly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy talk.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's EA talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not surprising to hear about all these murders.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, listen, our games may not be great, but you have no other choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's interesting that Take-Two just said, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: When your companies look at being bought like that, though, sometimes it's not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it was unsolicited.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, you know, they weren't saying, hey, who wants to buy us?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, EA is just like, hey, we've got $2 billion.
[SPEAKER_14]: We want to buy you because Grand Theft Auto is awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: But see, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think, like, you know,
[SPEAKER_14]: 2K and Take-Two, they may have had financial trouble earlier, but I think they're going to make a turnaround, especially with Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to make all sorts of money with that shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: This reminds me of the whole Microsoft-Yahoo thing that's been going on the past couple weeks, where apparently Microsoft's been trying to buy Yahoo, but Yahoo's been kind of saying no, or the stockholders have been saying no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like just because you have the money doesn't mean they're going to sell to you.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: If I was to take two, I'd be like, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not going to sell my company for $2 billion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in other news, though, Orange Lounge Radio is up for sale for the highest bidder.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will take $2 billion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trust... Each.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll put EA presents EA's Orange Lounge Radio by EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_14]: We would sell out like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I will talk... Hell, presented by Madden.
[SPEAKER_14]: Madden's Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't give a crap.
[SPEAKER_14]: $2 billion, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: I...
[SPEAKER_14]: Do whatever they want the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine Madden's Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd be foaming at the mouth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Featuring the gay guy, the angry man, and the woman who... We'll build a room of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who I love and adore.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to know what sucks?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wasn't thinking about what I'll spend that much money on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Technically I was, but I was thinking pay off credit cards, pay off student loans, buy a house.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then move to Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft has made the first bid for Orange Lounge Radio at $2.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need more money!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's sell the station on eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you want to?
[SPEAKER_04]: We should do random eBay stuff because...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, I don't know if you know, when they were having all this stuff on the Gorillaz website, they actually sold 2D shoes on eBay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we could do stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I need to say something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat room, knock it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't say this station is actually for sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: So bidding is not up to $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll sell a date.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go out with somebody.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're married.
[SPEAKER_10]: So?
[SPEAKER_10]: My husband will be fine with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get free food and we get money.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, I'll tell you what, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you know how that one Guitar Hero controller or Guitar Hero game or whatever was sold for thousands of dollars because some father took it away from his pot-smoking son, supposedly?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that copy of Bookworm Adventures, that copy was stolen from the President of the United States.
[SPEAKER_14]: From his secret bunker where he's holding Bin Laden.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that we should put that on eBay.
[SPEAKER_14]: and see how much money we can get.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's an image of the Virgin Mary in the plastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, just so that you know, there's a chance that we may have Dan next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan the man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have we even... My God, in the six-year history of this show, has Dan ever been on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, he has.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't there when it happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you were.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan was at your guys' old place before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he did.
[SPEAKER_04]: He did come to the show once there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we have the picture from the webcam.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Ron Jeremy thing was great because we were like, dude, the stories are just not all that great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's just watch porn or watch, you know, porn documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the days, the good old golden days of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ross DLUT says, Loki, we know that's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_14]: WA doesn't know what a book is, much less bookworms.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: So that lucky nuts guy emailed me back.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one who I was kind of upset with for my comments about physics.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he said he was sorry for making me angry and they were just poking some fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to let you know that I go on PMS-related tangents quite regularly.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you're going to deal with women, you just got to get used to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have...
[SPEAKER_10]: That going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although I have to say that it was more or less of a WTF moment.
[SPEAKER_10]: So don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So next actual email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, OLR team.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're a team now?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: We put the EA in team.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that mean that we have to go on team buildings and have the company pay for lunch?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't have a company.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or lunch money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have been listening to the podcast since sometime last year when I discovered it while browsing for websites that were formatted for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Loki, another one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I won't go into a long dribble here, but suffice to say, I really enjoy listening to you rambling on about games, The Olive Garden, and Moist Cake.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since I travel a lot doing my job, it's hard to play all the games or even to keep up with what's going on, what's coming out all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Knowing that I'm missing out on something but not knowing what is worse than listening
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks Ego++ to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's when I usually get to listen to the podcast on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since I work in Spain during the summer months, I can't listen to OLR live due to the time shift, but if my internet connection doesn't fail on me this weekend, I might make it to listen to you live this Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: After all, Venezuela is at least on the same side of the globe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally, a short question.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've already mentioned Yahtzee from Zero Punctuation once, and I was wondering if you could maybe get him over to the skyline to drop in for a quick chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: His video reviews are a weekly highlight for me and I would love to see OLR chat with him for a while.
[SPEAKER_14]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's in Australia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: And busy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says, Thanks and keep up the independent, informative, and very funny show.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is from MVH808.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that was very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey folks at the OLR headquarters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got two quick questions here.
[SPEAKER_10]: First is for Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know this show doesn't condone shady topics, but bear with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I originally purchased a Wii key for my Wii because people in my home like to maul discs.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'd rather have backup copies lying around than $50 discs.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what is your thoughts on this mod chip?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which Wii mod chip do you use and how hard is it to install one of these because I have not the slightest experience in soldering?
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, how many Subway sandwiches with white bread would I have to bribe you with to install mine?
[SPEAKER_10]: You can have ham and cheese.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I have a CycloWiz.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's CycloWiz V2.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever the second series.
[SPEAKER_14]: V version 2, I think, is what it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're really freaking tiny.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it was kind of scary trying to solder it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the thing about the soldering, though, is...
[SPEAKER_14]: It actually, the one I have, it has a thing called quick solder and basically there's two points on the board that you fill up these holes with solder.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, you have to put flux on the board because the solder didn't want to stick to it at first.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then once you've got that on there, the chip is basically on there and what you can do is you tin two wires and solder them onto three really, really, really tiny points on the board and connect it to the chip.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't easy at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I got lucky, I guess, that it worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just be careful, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: And don't electrocute yourself.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're not going to electrocute yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember, you're going to void your warranty.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you will avoid your warranty, but to be honest, I wouldn't worry too much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just worry about bridging stuff that you shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those three points on the board that you would be soldering wires to are really close together, so if you put too much solder on there, they will bridge each other, and it just won't work.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you can always take the solder off there and also make sure you don't lift any of the...
[SPEAKER_14]: Traces on there as well by putting too much heat on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just, you know, be careful.
[SPEAKER_14]: Use really, really, really small gauge wire.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, I think I used 30 gauge wire, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can't remember.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really, really tiny stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: NYR fan in chat confessed, I electrocuted myself once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be careful.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just, yeah, be careful with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love the Cyclo Wiz.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, they're the only ones that were running, you know, at
[SPEAKER_14]: We know about Nintendo and having especially...
[SPEAKER_14]: Assembled Stuff Yep, they love the tri-wing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, one person wouldn't always be relied on to be there and you'd always have a fresh perspective from someone.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought it was a really cool idea and figured I would pitch it over there to sit on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we do have guests fairly regularly, but... Okay, my mic's been totally off that whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've probably been able to hear me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit, where was I?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, I was saying, I think the door is already kind of open.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: But the door's always open to our guests.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I remember back in the day, there were some people that it seemed like they were here every week for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say like DDR Angel was here at least every other week for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when he was here, Shane was here every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, just depends on what's going on that week.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's more or less the, do I have anything else going on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Olive Garden, Home of the NeverEnding Salads, and Breadsticks
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shall I move on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Rob, Jamie, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just thought I would chime in with my thoughts about the game you played last week, one versus the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the week you weren't here, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just thought I'd fill that in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was badass and officially my favorite game of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It allows all the live listeners a chance to play and win, not just the caller.
[SPEAKER_10]: For podcast people, it's fun, too, just because trivia gets you thinking.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, I agree with that person who said there should be a Bimani edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, three random thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: One, I laugh so hard at Ranma's little loop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fun with video, fun with video, fun with video remix.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two, every time you guys spot a fly in the studio, you should all give a girly squeal on the count of three just for shits and giggles.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has been that bad lately, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one's for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says you should call your mom and talk about the Wii with her on the show just because Rob's talk with his mom a while back was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, enough with this email.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be live soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's from Osfer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I would say we should call my mama, but it's a quarter to ten right now in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually, I think my mom would be awake, but she would be winding down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll save it for Mother's Day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, yeah, let's call my mom on Mother's Day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Mom!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm in jail!
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm in Rob's garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is kind of like jail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only more comfy, with better insulation and computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even Gold Banjo in chat says, I missed that one versus the chatroom game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you guys do it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: The reception was very, very positive.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will do that game again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email!
[SPEAKER_04]: With more music, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, with more variety of music next time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, OLR Croop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm at least going to read the email and then I'll kick you so you can brace for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because this is GS68, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless you want to do the honors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, I'll kick him.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally, I would just like to give a shout out to Orange Lounge chat room for being the best friends I've ever met.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, yeah, you guys get crazy sometimes, but it's that craziness that keeps me distracted from whatever is depressing me.
[SPEAKER_10]: and if the depression is too big, it's nice to have an outlet for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hell, even when there's no show, I lurk in the chatroom just to see who's inside and join in whatever's getting discussed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to say that you guys, and girls, are a great bunch and make up a good 60-70% of the fun during the live show and that I love you all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aww, that's sweet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aww, that's nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Violin music, violin music.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys are what set the difference between listening to this show live and listening to it via podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's to many more episodes of Hilarious Chatroom Moments.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then it says, takes a shot of water, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm running out of non-alcoholic drink ideas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, great show, OLR and DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: And thank you, Pound Orange Lounge, for keeping me sane through this Sunday and Wednesday nights.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love, GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a very sweet email.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, comments like that and the little groupies we have in Orange Lounge, our chat room and everything, just, you know, keep us going and let us know we're not wasting our time here, that we really are...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, letting people have a good time on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just about having fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, next email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Sky, DarkSakura, and last but definitely least, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry I had to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I live in Australia, and I don't know if you've noticed over there, but I've become very irritated at the fact that the Japanese gaming companies such as Square Enix see fit-to-release games like Kingdom Hearts and a few...
[SPEAKER_10]: and a few months later think to themselves, hey, I know how we can rip off some people and piss off foreigners and then release something like Kingdom Hearts Final Mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if they realize it, but not only are they missing out on an incredibly large fan base, but they're leaving a great big gaping hole in plots for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand that they may be busy, but really, think of the children.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was in bold text, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I'd like to point out that I'm trying to spread the word to every online community I'm in so that we can reach our goal with eye of judgment, or as it's more commonly known, that piece of trash would rather burn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you all for something to keep me laughing on the best in the morning with numerous strange looks, and as I'm listening to the podcast on my PSP, I shall try to get on the chat room one morning and join in on the fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're sincerely, One Winged Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad to hear we're making the wheels on the bus go round and round.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this one's actually a poem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yay, poetic emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: By Strip Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that name.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is called The Lay of OLR, or Damn It, I Wish I Had Remembered to Upload Some Extra Podcasts Last Night.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sit and stare at my computer screen and eat my workday lunch of fine cuisine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I browse through my podcast list, which grows thin, wondering where my OLR has been.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it Thursday already?
[SPEAKER_10]: Far too long since last I heard that OLR theme song or the classic Game of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_10]: No FUs either.
[SPEAKER_10]: At traffic, none vent.
[SPEAKER_10]: I direct my browser to the website and reminded of why I'm in this plight.
[SPEAKER_10]: The OLR crew could not meet Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: for that real life thing had to get in their way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sit back in my chair and give a sigh longing for this show on which I rely to help ease the pain of a boring job and yet no anger I can feel at Rob, DarkSakura, or Loki since these three give us so much entertainment for free.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so to next week's show I now look toward but for the moment damn I'm freaking bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well here we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Heart, heart, heart.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then someone wants us to put a song in rotation.
[SPEAKER_04]: What song's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Elder School's 4 intro song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already in rotation.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that you're probably not listening quite long enough to actually hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's actually there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But does that mean they want to hear it on the show, or they want to hear it in the 24-hour rotation that's on the station when we're not here?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm thinking in the rotation, because, I mean, just suggesting a song to put in is what it looked like.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the mailbox just went down, so that's the last one I'm going to read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here, I'll give you a little taste.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go, that's all you get.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it sounds like the Wi-Fi might be down in studio again.
[SPEAKER_14]: It just came back.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a perfect time for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luckily, the computer that broadcasts out the signal for Live 365 and all that stuff is wired.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually have a ginormous wire that runs all the way out here into the garage just for this computer so that we don't have those types of problems on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one more story for you guys and we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that has to do with Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Activision is going to be offering refunds for the Wii version of Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, all over that whole sound issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember about how the sound was a mess?
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't actually the surround sound or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all mono sound or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Activision is offering refunds for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you do not want to actually replace your disc...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually replace the disc with money.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get a refund.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if that's something that interests you, check Activision's site for more details.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, seriously, just stick with the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of y'all have those big sound systems and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't want to cut back on all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to open up the Skype line for your telephone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number to call us, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The phones are open now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just turned them on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go ahead and give us a call, and we will talk to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a couple calls tonight, not a whole lot of them, but I'm sure some of our listeners have some things to say about things like DJ Hero, maybe the XNA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really curious to see what you guys have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, while we wait for the buffer and for folks to get the phone number and call in, do we have any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magic the Gathering is coming to PC, Mac, and Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: So suck it, I have judgment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Microsoft, of course, and Epic announced Gears of War 2 coming November 2008.
[SPEAKER_14]: No word on the details of what's going to be in that, but of course the Unreal 3 engine has been enhanced and all fun stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Silence Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, this is Rostio UT.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hello, Rostio UT.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much, not much.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just a few things.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, yes, I was going to mention the whole EA deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was incredibly relieved to hear that they rejected EA's offer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I think we all know that it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: that it's basically they're trying to get rid of the NBA 2K franchise because the NBA has so far been resistant towards exclusivity talks and this is pretty much all they have left.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: What better way to get rid of your competition than buy them out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's good to see that Take-Two realizes that sticking around and keeping their company is going to make them more money in the long run.
[SPEAKER_06]: They already had a hit with Bioshock
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have an enormous hit with GTA 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: And NBA 2K is doing amazingly well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's really no reason to jump ship just yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just worried that... I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just going to say, I just think EA, it just creates such a monopoly out there in the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we're starting to get to this point where you've got EA, Activision, Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega, Namco, Konami There's less than 10 at this point, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like back in the day there were a million It hasn't gotten that bad yet, but that is sort of the direction we're going and it is sort of sad because you see that happen and pretty much innovative game ideas would be impossible under that environment We all saw what EA did to Origin, Bullfrog and Westwood
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, people just have to remember that they also don't have to buy Madden every single year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the thing is, I don't think it's gamers who buy Madden.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just sports fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: They probably don't buy anything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, which is why EA doesn't really have to try.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the whole reason an Xbox 360 Core Edition exists is for those people.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are people that bought an Xbox 360 for Madden and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's it and that's not going to be a market for third parties and I think most third parties realize that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's probably what, two million people?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what Madden sells every year, like a million and a half, two million every year?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the only people that buy Madden are those type of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably a certain percentage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably there's a percentage of that million that buy nothing but Madden and maybe the other occasional sports game like the basketball game or the street or underground editions and racing games here and there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's clearly not the majority of the gaming audience and I would really hate to see the entire industry screwed up by that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I do see a silver lining.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all saw what happens when the actual talent leaves and they rebrand.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I remember correctly, Molyneux was part of Origin originally, if I remember correctly, and then he went on to form Lionhead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you are correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think we're going to see that eventually, especially with a lot of the studios like Bioware.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't do a lot of...
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of sequels.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might just stick around to complete Mass Effect and then be out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just pack up and rebrand.
[SPEAKER_06]: You see that a lot in this industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do see a lot of guys getting up and leaving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you wanted to comment on on tonight's show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a personal note about the show itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do enjoy the show, but I do have to say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I do... I do wonder why...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we get so much into the mod talk, like the letter segment.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that guy was making a flimsy excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all know he wants to see a Wii Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I don't see why you guys have to serve, basically, thieves.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know?
[SPEAKER_06]: That always troubled me, and that always, you know, as much as I like the show, that always sort of tugged at me a little bit, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, I think from our perspective, this show is kind of about the gaming community and all the things that are going on in the community, the good stuff and the stuff kind of behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_04]: So whether that guy was being honest or not, you know, I suppose we'll never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it is important sometimes to talk about what goes on in the whole, you know, dark side and gaming and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: to kind of see how the companies respond to that or how they don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like, for instance, I find this whole thing back and forth with Sony and the people that hack the PSP back and forth, I find that whole thing hilarious, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: In a way, I shouldn't say, like, hilarious, but I find it fascinating how constantly Sony patches it and somebody breaks it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's just that whole... It's so interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But certainly... I can certainly see where someone would find it interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just find it disgusting because...
[SPEAKER_06]: You see the turnaround.
[SPEAKER_06]: PSP software doesn't sell as well as it should, at least until recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are good PSP games, and they don't do well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now you see the same thing is going to start happening with the DS as the R4 gets more popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gaming community is fine, but there's no need to promote this cancer, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think at the same time, though, us not talking about it is not going to make it go away, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's not going to make it go away, but the last thing anyone needs to be doing is giving tips of all things.
[SPEAKER_06]: At that point, you might as well just offer torrents on the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we've heard your opinion, and hopefully you've heard ours.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thanks so much for the call, as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or use the name on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gear68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: About DJ Hero, I'm pretty... Yes, about DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a feeling it's going to succeed pretty well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Guitar Hero took off pretty well.
[SPEAKER_05]: The drum part of Rock Band is getting a bit of attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm pretty sure it's going to go for DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there potential there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I would say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm waiting to see the official E3 announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Assuming that it's going to be the Beatmania spinoff that we're all thinking it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which it may not be.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a distinct possibility this is not the Beatmania clone people think it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be more along the lines of Kraken DJ, which if you've played that game is drastically different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I realize both games involve turntables, but the play between them is so, so different.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there is no controller that comes with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a lot of speculation.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people are thinking, oh, well, they stole, quote unquote, I'm using that term loosely, they stole Guitar Freaks, so they're going to steal Beatmania now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we have a damn good reason to believe that to be true, but we don't know for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, there's a chance that it might flop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me, look at Beat Media US.
[SPEAKER_05]: That failed horribly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of folks say that, you know, Beat Media, oh, they saw it on the clearance shelves and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can tell you, it met Konami's expectations of what the game was going to sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why they didn't make a sequel, your guess is as good as mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually thought for a while there, from what I, you know, just observe at different things, I thought Konami was planning a sequel here in the US for whatever reason they chose not to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, too bad the original came in limited releases, so now we can't find an American Beatmania controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I tried one over at E3, I mean, Final Mate, sorry, and the controller was like light years ahead of the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they made improvements on it on its way over, so, and, you know, for a lot of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: and hardcore Bomani community fans, the whole reason to buy Beatmania US was it was sort of a greatest hits with a better controller for a decent price.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's kind of a bummer they never did release a sequel here in the US, but at the same time, I would hope maybe they have bigger and better things planned, but I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that guitar revolution pattern that they came up with last year or the year before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if they follow a patent, then there's got to be some use for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where there's smoke, there's fire?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of hope that Konami's going to surprise us, but I've said this to Konami indirectly on this show before, and I'll say it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're not going to do it, someone else will, and I think this whole trademark thing just kind of goes to show that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Konami should be...
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe there's people that go, oh, this wouldn't do well in the U.S., and then it's going to do well because they didn't innovate it for the U.S., I guess is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like I've had this conversation a million times on the program, so that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight, GS68?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I finally got Apollo Justice this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the perceived system, which is basically where you, during a witness's testimony, you look at their, you look at their, you find nervous habits during their testimony and point them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because, you know, when they lie, they make those kind of habits and such.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard a lot of good things about Apollo Justice, but right now I'm too busy with Lost Odyssey, but I will check it out at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've read the, like, the...
[SPEAKER_05]: The cases aren't written very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, case two wasn't... I thought, though I kind of disagree, the first case was pretty good, and the third one too, and I'm partway through the fourth one, but second case, eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, every Ace Attorney game has its crappy cases.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so it's hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as overall you have fun, that's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, GS6TO, we've got to let you go to get to a couple other calls, but thanks so much for calling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll take one more call if anybody wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Launch Radio on Skype or our username.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is our username on Skype or our phone number.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we got one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, it's SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I want to call about two things.
[SPEAKER_01]: One, I want to talk about the XNA Club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really happy that these big companies are starting to go all toward user-created content and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's what's going to change the gaming industry pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is something big.
[SPEAKER_01]: To tell a personal story, I have a friend who's currently working on an XNA game.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's doing it in his spare time.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has his own job.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's a computer engineer, and he kind of wants to get into the business.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think doing this is going to kind of get him into the business.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is absolutely a way to get noticed.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be some great talent discovered from this.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I think this is the beginning of a new chapter in gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to keep talking this up, but I think this really is that big.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will play out that big.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's just like independent movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: The greatest things are not necessarily the most known things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to say that all user-created content is garbage, I cannot agree any less with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the last topic I wanted to bring up was, I'm not sure if you guys saw this, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: ESPN has signed a deal with Major League Gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody linked me to that earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, tell us a little more about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just took a quick glance at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dark Knight sent me the link.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just glanced at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's just getting a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this will bring up the whole debate about whether or not gaming is an actual sport and all that, but
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about in the way it's portrayed, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about the way it's kind of handled and the way it's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's a little bit too sensationalistic, then it's going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if they take it somewhat seriously, I think it'll be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I mean, I've always kind of, I don't want to say this, I feel embarrassed to say, but I always kind of saw DDR was, in a sense, a sport.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember a long time ago that they were talking about bringing DDR to the X Games, but nothing came of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just think it's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as a sports fan, I'm kind of annoyed that we're going to be able to see kids talk trash with Halo, and meanwhile we can't see hockey games on ESPN.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Only, that's, it's only with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this will be delegated to the Ocho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100, Matt, thanks so much for your call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got to wrap it up, so have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I said have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm definitely starting to feel the weight of the show carrying down.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's time to start to wrap up so I can take more drugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, drugs, los drogas.
[SPEAKER_04]: All legal ones, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dayquil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be thinking I'm into that shady stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Ninja Gaiden 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's scheduled now for June 3rd in the US.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will also have a cool new feature where you can do basically record your action or killing of things so you can play them back and I'm assuming upload them to friends and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is a neat little feature that they're adding into this game
[SPEAKER_14]: Boom Blocks, that's that first game by Spielberg.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to have a head tracking option in there where you can use the second Wii Remote to basically track your head movements much like that demonstration that we saw online.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I was thinking, that YouTube thing that guy did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you'll need to have, of course, some sort of visor with two infrared lights on it or a wireless sensor bar or something that you use in that sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: That you have to build yourself, but it will support it, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of a nifty little Easter egg.
[SPEAKER_14]: A game that really wants me to get back into playing MMOs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Real Time World showed off a game during GDC called All Points Bulletin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row, the MMO.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's kind of weird, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's no leveling or anything in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: You either, of course, play on the side of the law or the criminal side, and you have to do organized crime.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, of course, you start off the game wearing normal clothes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they had a pretty cool game that they made up, the Geek Squad or whatever, with Miyamoto in there, and that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it has a really cool character creator and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really want to play this game, but I don't like it very much.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is kind of a little bit of controversy here.
[SPEAKER_14]: British Magazine is unveiling Xbox Live's GoldenEye info this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard that was debunked, that it was a concept thing that they were going to be showing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it wasn't the real deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out later that it was bogus.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks cool either way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely fueling the fanboy flames of our GoldenEye desires on 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: No surprises.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: This week on Xbox Live Arcade, we're getting Triggerheart Accelia.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of those bullet hell games that should be coming out for 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also on Rock Band, we're getting a Nine Inch Nails three-pack, including March of the Pigs, The Collector, and The Perfect Drug.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which, if you'll remember, that was actually one of the packs that was supposed to be coming in March.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dates get moved around sometimes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then finally, some weird company, Shenzhen Nodging Technology Company Limited, made a Famicom cart for Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess it's fully playable and they've got all sorts of stuff from the game and of course done in the Final Fantasy looks like two or three graphics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has this been ROMed yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably like those Tekken on the NES cartridges.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like Final Fantasy, like one of the older Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there really that big of a market for more
[SPEAKER_04]: Games on the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess those consoles still exist in some households, but most people, at least in these parts, are still having to... This is specifically Advent Children, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if it's Advent Children, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody probably just stole the logo off the wrong thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Without bothering to Photoshop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if DarkSakura doesn't have any last-minute stories, I don't have any either.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there is one more thing we just could not finish the show if we did not do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a last-minute story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, then let's take it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a milkshake.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a story.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's news to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, we just could not end the show if we did not have an opportunity to respect our elders by paying tribute to a classic game, as we do every week here on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time for DarkSakura to bring in her classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: The classic game of the week is one that I'm sure a lot of people will agree with me on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely one of the top games in the side-scrolling shooter genre.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that is none other but R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: R-Type is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, I'd have to say that R-Type is probably my favorite shooter, even though I'm not all that great at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This music's like the best ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first level music is so much my favorite in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what sets this shooter apart from other games, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: This particular shooter has a very unique weapon system.
[SPEAKER_10]: You get this item called the Force, which is, since you're watching the clip, you see that ball that's right in front of it?
[SPEAKER_10]: You can pick up different power-ups for ones that make it grow based on different types of energy power-ups you pick up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you have a red one that's a counter-air laser.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the one that's on right now, the blue and red sort of spiraled-looking laser.
[SPEAKER_10]: You also get a rebound laser that shoots these thin beams that bounce off the walls, which is actually, certain weapons are better for certain stages.
[SPEAKER_10]: You also get the counter-ground laser, which is basically like a flamethrower that goes out on the ceiling and on the ground, which is a very, very, very good thing to have for the third boss.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually for the third level, because the entire level is the boss battle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other various things that you can get are these little spheres that will float above and below your ship that will shoot missiles for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other cool thing about the Force attachment is that you can move it around.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, the ship one is, I think, the third level.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, you can fire it off and have it sort of hang in midair, although it will try to reattach itself.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you can have it attached to the back of your ship and fire the weapon from the back, and you can have it attached to the front.
[SPEAKER_10]: And have it, of course, fire to the front.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, a lot of the bosses are supposed to be really hard, but they all have a trick to them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the first one...
[SPEAKER_10]: there's one place where nothing will hit you and you just fire off the force thing and it will just kill the thing for you one of the stages is you fight this heart of this creature and there's a place where you can nestle your ship in and fire off the force thing by the place where the little heart of it pops up and you don't get hit you kill off all the tentacles and you
[SPEAKER_10]: And that is hardcore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on top of that, I've seen someone beat it in the arcade on an actual single quarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I notice our chatroom is in a little bit of a Gradius versus R-Type debate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Care to comment?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, is there room for both games, or is one better than the other?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all a matter of what you prefer, because Gradius is a different style of shooter, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, and this is, again, just my opinion, I think it takes a more skilled player to play through R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really think it takes a lot more skilled and patient of a player to play R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, we've had many sequels since then.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've had, if I'm correct in order, after this came, we had R-Type 2, and then, god, there was some other game, let's see, Super R-Type came out, R-Type Leo, R-Type 3, R-Type Delta, R-Type Final, and there's recently been an R-Type Tactics game, which
[SPEAKER_10]: R-Type Command
[SPEAKER_10]: That you'll get to the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Japan, though, it came out on two HuCards.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a little bit of trivia is that when on the Japanese Virtual Console, you actually still have to download R-Type in both parts.
[SPEAKER_10]: As opposed to one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they came out with an R-Type Complete or something that was a PC Engine Duo combination that had the entire thing uncut.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, other games, though, that were...
[SPEAKER_10]: Rumored to have been spawned by R-Type, though, were Polestar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although Polestar actually dates back to the very early 80s, but a lot of the gameplay in Polestar is a lot like R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also a game called Resonant that came out in 91, very similar.
[SPEAKER_10]: A Magic Series core, the game called Magic Dragon that was supposed to be almost everything exactly like R-Type with redone sprites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like we haven't seen that before in Super Mario 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, for the game Turrican 2, you actually can see the force in a hangar, and the third level of that game is based on R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: And another game, and this is actually, and I almost picked this as my classic game, but it's a little on the obscure side.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a game called, if I'm pronouncing it right, Zexys, which is just spelled X-E-X-E-X.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got it in America as Oreus.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a Konami game.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's also that same type of shooter game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, very, very classic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very good game.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have my love for Gradius, especially Gradius 2, don't get me wrong, but R-Type.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your classic game of the week is R-Type, which you can check out a version of that on the virtual console if you are so inclined.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I believe that's available in all the different regions.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do believe so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just remember, if you were in Japan, you have to pay for two of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyhow, that's going to wrap it up for tonight's short show, although it wasn't much of a short show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been here for over two hours, so it was almost like just doing one long show and no break.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can't say you got ripped off this week, but I am definitely spent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm ready to go rest.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to wrap it up and go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going home and hopefully going to be able to play some Lost Odyssey since everything tonight reruns, except for the Food Network.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have new stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Medication, menthol, cough drops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's have tea will kill me if I don't say it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and downloading and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your guys' support that keeps us going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much week after week for your support.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's all there is until next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!