[SPEAKER_10]: Guy, and Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi How are you, DarkSakura or Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm okay You're okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Been better I think you and I are kind of in the same boat right now We are recovering from the plague Yes, we both have been a bit plague-ish this past weekend Although I don't think it's the same plague, or maybe it is, I don't know But I don't think I gave you cooties I don't think you gave me cooties I wasn't very, very sick But I've just been tired and worn down, so
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I got it from Becky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or from Dan getting it at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been sitting here rolling my eyes for a solid month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because seriously, this isn't cold and it's not humid, so you don't get cold with wet wind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's a funny piece of that puzzle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's not here tonight in studio, although he's been joining us on and off for the past month, not here tonight is Jason, our announcer.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has the night off, and would you like to guess why he has the night off?
[SPEAKER_02]: He has the plague.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has the plague!
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm fairly certain that the whole reason why I haven't been as sick as everybody else has been is because I practically live at the gym now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't you not supposed to work out when you're sick, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was like a big no-no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading lately that for people who spend regular, like at least two or three days at the gym a week, tend to have a stronger immune system.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if anything, that would explain why I've only been sick for like a day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but like Extrovert from Horde House is a big old gym guy now and he still gets sick a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not a lot, but like as sick as often as I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I haven't gotten sick nearly as often as I used to before this became a regular thing, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: TechMasterLoki
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What day did you have your wisdom teeth out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is only like three days later.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, it's so different for different people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like some people are better like the next day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like go right back to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people are out for like two weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weren't you one of the ones that was out for like a frickin' two months or something insane?
[SPEAKER_05]: Four months.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, what happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: The holes never filled in on the bottom teeth.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I basically had swelling and bruising for at least two of those months.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the pain didn't... I was on antibiotics for... I was on five different antibiotics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that pre-OLR though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't remember that affecting the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: The show's been on too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's... Around 2004.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, then I guess we would have had the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, Loki's moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I saw the swelling, um, and I can't really chew food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I can sort of chew food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I've been slowly getting into more solid stuff, you know, because before it was smoothies and soup.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, today, I tried to do french fries from McDonald's and it sort of works.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sort of works.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're making it work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and then, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so I'm not, like pain medication, I'm not really taking any unless, you know, sometimes during the night just because it makes the swelling, the feeling of the swelling go down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like right now, like today, I don't feel as swollen, but it feels like it's all swollen on the inside.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like sometimes like if I sleep on my side or something, I feel like I bite my cheek or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I kind of get that feeling right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I already had one of the stitches come out, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, you know, sitting there talking, I was like, pfft.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a string here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not get too detailed.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want people to keep listening before we get to the video game talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm glad to see you're doing much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like you're one of those people that made a quick recovery, so good for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently I metabolize the anesthesia medicine really fast too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to say, what happened to the Loki goes to the dentist or whatever video that was going to be planned?
[SPEAKER_07]: I wasn't really out of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I was a little tired and stuff at first because they gave me Valium to take before I went there, which is good because I have all sorts of unnecessary phobias about all sorts of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Surgical, probably because I haven't really done any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never had any experience with having surgery or being put under.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really go to the doctor that often, so I get a little nervous around needles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that there's no real danger to it, but it still makes me uneasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Valium helped.
[SPEAKER_04]: They wouldn't let me stay awake and listen to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so glad that shit knocks me the hell out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I woke up and they're all trying to help me out, help me sit down.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, no, I'm not dizzy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can walk just fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not a problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so we went out to the car.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, I'm not really, I'm tired, but I'm not really dizzy or anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, unfortunately I wasn't loopy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nellie said I said weird things, but all of those were intentional weird things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, you always say weird things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was making bad jokes, and she's like, well, you said this joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, yeah, but I remember saying that, and I meant that on purpose, so that's not just me saying weird things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let me go to the chat room because we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com and if you are listening live on this Sunday night, come on down to the chat room live.vognetwork.com We often read comments from chat on the show because it is the show where every gamer has a voice YYR starting us off tonight saying, come for the video game talk stay for the gross medical drama Yes
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like an episode of VR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, if I start talking about my hernia surgery that I had a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was not fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was way worse than this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was awake through that.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt saying, don't have rice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say popcorn either way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not chewing anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty much all liquid stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ate a lot of pudding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stuff that I can... Eggs, you know, like I had eggs last night and those are dull.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like the best eggs ever because, you know, after having just smoothies and, you know, tomato bisque soup.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you like pudding?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say because you can mix protein powder and pudding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, my wife wanted me to have like... She got... Well, she meant to get rice pudding but it ended up being tapioca.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome Unicorn is in our chatroom saying, man, when I had all four wisdom teeth out, I agreed to fill in for dinner theater the same night.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's hardcore, because having to sing, I would assume dinner theater means you sing, and just all that vibration would, oh, that's not fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That must have been some non-impacted easy peasy teeth coming out there, because that's too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I was just thinking back to... I wanted to stay awake so I could watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted them to put a mirror so I could watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they wouldn't let me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they wouldn't let me watch my hand surgery either because it was too small.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they had to give me laughing gas to make my veins dilate so that they could get the IV in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that hand stayed bruised for like a week and a half.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_02]: some more comments from our chat room at live.vognetwork.com Zebediah the Messiah saying long time listener on iTunes first live show well welcome, welcome to the show yeah we've been getting some new listeners lately just thanks to, well I know he said he's a long time listener but just thanks to Stitcher, he's doing very well
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't recognize that name either.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Awesome Unicorn as well, who I don't recognize.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that a little redundant?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, aren't all unicorns awesome?
[SPEAKER_07]: All unicorns are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: The girl at Starbucks, when I told her that I wanted a unicorn when she asked if I wanted anything else, she drew a unicorn farting rainbows on my cup.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the little sticker that goes on my reusable cup.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kept it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then DarkTetsuya in chat says, I was wondering if there was going to be a show or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hearing everyone's sick and then Loki having his wisdom teeth out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we had to be here because otherwise Zebediah the Messiah would not have had a live show to listen to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And honestly, I didn't know how it... I mean, I didn't know how... Everyone was saying, oh, you're going to be out for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And hopefully nothing... I mean, so far, I think everything's healing just fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows, like a week from now, you know, oh, sorry, that just...
[SPEAKER_07]: Infection, lol So they give you Keflex?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Amoxicillin, and then I have the, because I can't swallow pills, yet somehow, thank goodness that that volume was really small, because I couldn't drink water with it, because normally I just, I down a little water and salt and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Druggie lounge radio, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, this is legal if you've been prescribed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no, I have whatever, it's like Tylenol with codeine or whatever, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_05]: They gave me Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when those stopped working, they gave me horse pill Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the one that's pure, pure hydrocodone and no other crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just... When I had my gallbladder out, I slept for like a week straight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just what I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I did?
[SPEAKER_02]: The first time I left the house after gallbladder surgery, do you know what I went to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had my gallbladder surgery like two days before Halloween because it was my ex's birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the first time I left the house after that was to go vote against Prop 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the first time I left the house after my gallbladder surgery.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a worthy cause.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a very worthy cause.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you didn't vote absentee.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I never vote absentee.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm one of those people where I'm like, I think absentee, for me, I realize tons of people vote absentee and that's cool, at least you're voting.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, absentee takes the magic out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I like to go in the little booth, click the, I don't know, there's just something about that whole process.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I vote, I take my absentee, well, the voting place is actually, I could walk there in five minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I fill out my absentee ballot at home with the internet in front of me and then I go take it and drop it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That works.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I've gone to the place, but I voted in a very comfortable manner.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, before we get into argument weeks and the things we've been playing this week, some other topics here at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a whole lot in regards to kickoff topics, but we are entering the holiday period.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although we here at OLR, as far as I know, we're going to be doing shows every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not taking any time off for the holidays because everybody kind of lucks out this year with Christmas and New Year's being on, what, Wednesdays?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Christmas and New Year's are both on Wednesday this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sunday happens to be the 29th, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be here those days.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of us are traveling anywhere major.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will be here through the holidays, but since we're starting to ramp up toward that season, I don't know about you guys, but
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to have a lot of time off where I'm doing nothing for like a week and a half at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you guys going to be catching up on any games or do you have any gaming plans through the holidays?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a wish list of things you got to get through in the next month?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I still have to beat Skullgirls with everybody, which I just started it last night and beat it with Parasol.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not last night, but the other day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I do want to get at least up to a 35 and finish that stupid quest that I'm stuck on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's in 14.
[SPEAKER_02]: 14, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm still trying to do the play a new game every week thing, so like this past one with Skullgirls, I'm going to start Deadpool next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's my goal is just to do something different.
[SPEAKER_02]: One new game a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they'll be going to Washington later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, good luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snowpocalypse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get lots of pictures of the snow on the way up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say thank you very much, Loki, before the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you don't mind me saying this on air, but Loki gave some Christmas presents out before the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a Steam gift card from Loki, and I believe DarkSakura got one as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm armed and ready for the winter sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: When does that start, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: The winter sale for Steam?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought the winter sale was already done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or is it the fall sale?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't keep track of these sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's going to be a Christmas New Year's sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: There always is, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: But they don't call it Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: They call it holiday sale, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think what we just saw was the winter sale, and now there will be the Christmas sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody in chat set us straight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The winter festival sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the fall sale that they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's fall-spring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fall-spring because the thing was upside down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It said spring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think the winter sale is coming right up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just saying yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what about your projects?
[SPEAKER_02]: You love to start projects that you never finish.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's that tablet going?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, because I was actually thinking about that the other day because I got some more stuff for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Originally, I was going to use...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's similar to how they did the crossplane thing where they had individual circuit boards for each controller and it would have hooked up almost like a cartridge that you'd plug in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I bought a Sonic 2 and Sonic & Knuckles Genesis thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to rip the whole thing apart and use the...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, connectors on there for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's too damn small for what I want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm going to need to add stuff to it later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm like, okay, that's not the way to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the way to go is actually buying this... It's like a USB thumbstick that you plug into your system.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forget what they call it now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it basically allows you to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Use almost any controller on any system, including keyboard and mouse, on Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, Xbox One, PC, and it just works.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That simplifies wiring everything a lot more than it was before, because now I don't have to worry about having to switch between multiple different systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can just wire up one controller to it, and then just run it through that, and it would work on multiple systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: instead of having to do all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no, I'm still consciously working on all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just have to get the parts and figure out the feasibility and stuff to get it working.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mainly right now is I'm trying to figure out how to make the actual case for all of it because that's going to be difficult since I've never done vacuum forming before and I have to design the case and...
[SPEAKER_07]: But before that, I was kind of distracted by, okay, how am I going to get this so that I can wire up different controllers, configurations and stuff to one system?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now I don't do that anymore, so that makes it a lot easier in the design process.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm still going to make it, eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what's your plan while you... Because I know you probably have a little time off of work.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your plan during that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have any time off of work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, you know, like... The days, but... The days, oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I will have time off of work a few weeks after that, but... Well, that's for the baby, so... Well, actually, right now, I've been kind of in the, you know, what do I want to play and stuff, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, DeepSilverInvolition, for wasting 40 fucking hours of my time playing that game and basically making my save completely useless.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's apparently a widespread problem where not only is it not a save thing...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like people that bought the DLC, their game's just not fucking working anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so frustrating.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, you know what, I just want to play something stupid today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to play some Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_02]: After losing 40 hours in a game, how would you have the motivation to play again?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to cheat like a motherfucker is how I would do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even want to grind through, even cheating like crazy to make it super easy so I can just get through all of it fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why should I even put myself through the effort to play this game when it's so obviously broken that...
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, I can't, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's just, it's not gonna be worth it for these DLC missions, which, let me be honest, they're probably about 30 minutes long each, if I'm lucky.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so, I just don't know if I want to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I would like to go back and do it, but I wish my save would work just fine, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it was fun and it's definitely not mods because I've uninstalled, I deleted the whole game off my computer, redownloaded everything, no mods are in there it still fucking doesn't work so it's just something with their game and it's disappointing
[SPEAKER_02]: but yeah, I don't know I try to figure something else to play for me, I kind of want to do the Jamie thing and try to do some new games although with Final Fantasy XIV getting a patch this week I'm obviously going to dump a lot of my time into that but I'm trying not to spend my entire vacation because my work actually shuts down between Christmas and New Year's we have to take the time off so I have lots of time off to do very little because my family doesn't do an awful lot of holidays you can hang out with me
[SPEAKER_02]: We can absolutely hang out and do stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to Ikea every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, things should hopefully slow down a couple days after Christmas, which is the period that I've got all this time and nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might finally crack and get the PlayStation 4 because the finances are looking pretty good now, so this might be the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, and I understand if you're still hesitant about picking up the PlayStation 4 because there aren't a lot of games out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is one game that's on current gen systems that would take up a good portion of your time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it start with grand and end with a five?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I was looking to see if it was on sale at Target when I was on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thirty nine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I might jump on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really might jump on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying, just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not knocking the system, but it's just like, you know, there's not a lot I would play on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even like the PlayStation 4, like either of the systems, there's not a lot I would really... We have no reason to look at either right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't need a PlayStation 4 right now, but, you know, knowing that after seeing the Final Fantasy XIV footage with the remote play, I'm like, oh, God, I want... At least you know a date now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: and by the way, we just picked up Star Fox 3DS last night because we had coupons and Dan's all over that one so we've got plenty to play right now and Dan has a villager in Normandy you can go run by his tent now that Normandy is open
[SPEAKER_02]: the other big games I have to beat are Mario 3D World and Zelda Link Between Two Worlds because I do love both those games a lot probably my best of the year for sure but I keep getting distracted with all these other games I'm trying to play too so I definitely want to play those games and beat them probably inevitably during the winter sale Bioshock Infinite will be on sale and I can finally play and beat that and I'm hoping I can get I think it's still on sale now it's been like dirt cheap like 10 bucks I bought mine ages ago for dirt cheap
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hoping I can get The Last of Us and Beyond Two Souls from the rental company over the holidays as well that would be fantastic or Zelda Wind Waker is on my list too because I gotta catch up with that
[SPEAKER_05]: We've actually got Ocarina for 3DS on our list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan and I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go into our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome Unicorn says, Resogun make the PS4 purchase worth it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's one of the games I'm really eyeing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I definitely want to get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fifth Dream said, PlayStation 4 is worth it for Doki Doki Universe right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know a lot about that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: YYR says, a friend who works at GameStop said today that PS4s were sold out in 10 minutes, but Xbox Ones were in stock all day and didn't sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had no idea why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm hoping that if I do want to get a PlayStation 4, I can actually get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be really great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ragenator says, Sky, technically no one actually needs any games or system.
[SPEAKER_02]: People need food, water, shelter, oxygen, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: The question is, do you want the system?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, starting us off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not playing Animal Crossing right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you lying to the listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't lie to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Normandy's open.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody come hang out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing Zelda, A Link Between Two Worlds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your hubby made a house in Normandy, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucker.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that asshole I'm also playing Zelda I uh
[SPEAKER_05]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I played Skullgirls, which I really like, and finally got to, for some reason it doesn't work very well with the Capcom fighting controller, but it works just fine with the regular Xbox 360 controller, so that's what I'm using.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loaded the Shiva, and then I stopped playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've probably done five more playthroughs of the Stanley Parable, and I got the Portal ending.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to play more Bus to Move Universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is not very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to like it so much because playing it on my phone is freaking awesome, but playing it on the 3DS is not awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, oh yeah, I've been playing a lot of Bejeweled on my phone because that's my I really need to get sleepy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like the music in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does kind of have like new agey Philip Glass type of soundtrack to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I love Philip Glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, but the one on the phone, it's like this epic type music.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of almost like whenever you see ancient Mesopotamia, that type of music, you know, like you're watching Ben-Hur or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Epic movie trailer of epicness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Epic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's epic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I played more of Fractal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have Fractal?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm getting you Fractal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're going to live with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fractal is a great game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free games rule.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm ruining one of your presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have Fractal yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to play Fractal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fractal is like the best puzzle game in the universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes me super happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, for anyone who just showed up, Normandy's open.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's probably about it because I didn't play any Final Fantasy this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played last week, which is how I got harassed for my name.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everybody go on the VOG website and read my article.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Grand Theft Auto Online.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ended up in a lobby with, I guess, a modder or hacker or whatever you want to call him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever the case may be, I ended up level 40 and I have $13 million now, so that ain't bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I messed around with the content creator a little bit and tried to make a race and it turned out okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you can stack objects.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's like a trick where you can stack objects and make them float in the air, which is kind of what I wanted it to do in the first place, but they made it so damn difficult to do that, so I just kind of didn't mess with that part too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the way it integrates in your game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You see the waypoints on there, but they're orange instead of blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can go on Social Club and basically bookmark any stuff that you like on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will show up in your game and you can play it and do all sorts of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So right now they have just the race and deathmatch creator, but I guess more stuff is coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, what else did they play this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: Some other strange stuff, or a little unusual, I guess, for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, we were bored, and I was trying to occupy Josh, so I tried to get him to play Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_07]: That didn't work, because he didn't want to play it, and he wanted to watch me play it, so I showed him bullying.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I played a little Wii Sports this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Also played a little bit of Rabbids Go Home.
[SPEAKER_07]: He thought that game was a little bit funnier because the rabbits are being stupid and gathering trash.
[SPEAKER_07]: He still didn't understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those games are kind of made for kids, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: He didn't understand why the rabbit was screaming at people and their clothes were falling off and they were collecting clothes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he was worrying that their shopping cart was going to tip over because it was stacked really tall with all sorts of weird things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like, you've got to be careful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't turn so fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I played a little bit of Just Cause Multiplayer just getting in the last little bit of their beta that should be launching actually tomorrow so I'm looking for that I'll be coming out on Steam worthwhile investment if I say so myself and then what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh... A little Call of Duty, I guess, at work.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing really else to play there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um... That's pretty much it for right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, uh... Hopefully... Hopefully we'll get into some Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I want to go back.
[SPEAKER_07]: It... It...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're just frustrated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rabble, rabble, rabble.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously, it's sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games like Saints Row 2 and stuff, I really liked going back into those and playing them again and stuff, but it's just the last couple of games they put out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even Saints Row 3rd, I think I played through that at least two or three times.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't want to do it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to go through all the hassle because it's like, I've already seen that joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe, maybe if a certain other host that was on this network, you know, that would pick up a copy, then it might be worth it since I have to start from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_07]: We could go through together and play through a co-op campaign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I can also get those extra achievements I don't have yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Travis Donovan, hope you're listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Bobby Okay, my gaming week I actually played a lot of random shit this week I powered on my 360 I've never heard of a lot of random shit, Rob It's a new game, it's by Random Shit Co So I powered on my 360 this week Which is like the first time in like four months Like I turned it on and it had to do a Like I seriously think the last time I played my 360 was When the Mass Effect DLC came out Sure it wasn't Forza Horizon
[SPEAKER_02]: Jack shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do your friends list expand on 360 now, too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Xbox supports a thousand friends?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because all I see... I don't see what you're playing on Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I see is that you're on Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is kind of weird, because you could do that on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember I used to see what people were playing on PC, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they integrated there, so no, I don't have more than 100 people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have 99 friends right now, so find my username if you want to be the 100th person.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have 99 friends, but so-and-so ain't one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, somebody dropped me this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know who, because it won't tell me.
[SPEAKER_02]: and BlackWolf confirms no it doesn't well that sucks I was hoping for that expansion but oh well I admittedly haven't played a lot of 360 I'm not being a hater it's just nothing new I've really bought on 360 lately but I went back and visited some of my classics because I have a shit ton of downloads especially from like Xbox Live Arcade when Xbox first came out I know there's all that free stuff still although yeah I've been checking some of that out
[SPEAKER_02]: And they love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blessings be upon you for the mucus coming from your nose
[SPEAKER_02]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was one of those, like, you're going to sneeze, you're going to sneeze.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Radio host's worst enemy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing I can do about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine being in customer service and having that happen when you're trying to... Oh, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in customer service for seven years.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're trying to explain one's mortgage interest to them while they're yelling at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You see where this spot is right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's where...
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was playing Spelunky on now PlayStation Network, which literally it is the exact same game as it is on PC, so there's not a lot I can report on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play it on Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks great, although it's so tiny and it's hard to read things, but it worked well enough, so I'm cool with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played one other game, and this game...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I'm gonna get shit for my opinion because I didn't really get it and I have a lot of friends that are really really into this game but I'm gonna be completely honest I loved the presentation of this game I loved the way things looked and I was really cracking up but when it came down to the game itself I just really didn't have a lot of fun with the wonderful 101 on Wii U and I know I'm gonna get crap for that but it is what it is
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: so like the gist of it is that you control like an entire group of people and you pick up more people as you're running along and those people can be in different patterns like they can be in a circle to turn your main guy into having a giant like punching glove type of thing or it can be a straight line for a sword and then at some point when your group gets big enough you can kind of have both going on at once and then you also draw lines to get from place to place but a
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and I guess the game is supposed to be very challenging which you know I can respect it for that but it was a lot of um just kind of slash slash like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles arcade game with this interesting mechanic so mash and slash and hope you get it right yeah kinda that's what I felt when I was playing the game and so I feel kind of bad for razzing it because again it had a great setup and everything was in this really cool like package and the presentation was awesome and it looked great um
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, the game itself, I just didn't really have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like this is one of those games that if I revisit it in a month or two, maybe I'll enjoy it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I didn't really care for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you are entitled to your opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know I'm going to get emails telling me I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it looked like Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beautiful Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I might try to get into that game like one more time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, that was the game I played when I was sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that could have been like kind of, but I'll try it one more time after I feel better.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I still don't care for it, I'm probably going to send that one on back and get something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, that's really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anybody else?
[SPEAKER_02]: pizza pizza pizza you bringing me pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: no alright
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, some quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, you better bring out your DS so that I can get the last piece of the puzzle I need for the Rhythm Heaven puzzle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your thing hasn't street passed with me yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh, weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so don't forget to follow us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR, and we're also on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio, and Google+, google.com slash plus Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as far as shows off over the next few weeks, we don't have any planned.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will be here Sundays.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: You get an entry into the raffle, but you do have to opt into the raffle.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not just entered by default.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you actually need to go to vognetwork.com, click on raffles, and actually enter the raffle.
[SPEAKER_02]: This month we are giving away a $20 gift card to an online source of your choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meaning, I think the options are...
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox, PlayStation, Steam, Wii U, and regular Wii because those are still separate.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I know iTunes is in there too for people who don't even have any gaming consoles whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Google Play probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Google Play was one of the options, but it probably should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure if you came in and said, I really don't want any of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Google Play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure we can make that happen for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that is over at vognetwork.com slash raffle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you you can either check in live and you get five points just for listening to the show or there's a if you're listening on the podcast feed there's a passphrase hidden somewhere in the show and you've probably heard it before Jason interrupts the show at some point and says to register participation for this week's episode and then he gives you a little passphrase you go to vognetwork.com you type that in the front page and you will get your points but make sure you opt into the raffle if you want to win your $20 card that's not Google Play
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Bobby in chat?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby, can they have Google Play?
[SPEAKER_02]: If they really want that more than anything, can they have Google Play?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll need to hear back from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: VOG Master Bobby in just a minute here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other thing I want to promote.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's award season for things that you like, movies and so forth, and podcasts are no different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, we didn't get nominated for the podcast awards, although I appreciate those of you guys that tried.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know many of you were trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: We weren't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, we didn't get nominated, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we did not get nominated for the Podcast Awards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of indie shows did, though, so I can't be mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have a pretty good feeling I know which one of them is going to win.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if they do win it, they totally deserve it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I won't say it because I don't want to make a boobie of myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah, Podcast Awards, unfortunately, we're not there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do have a chance to do the Stitcher Awards are going on right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I love Stitcher because Apple's podcast app right now,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I know some of the other VOG Network shows like Bobby's going for games and hobbies as well so a lot of our listeners are kind of voting for us one day and voting for him another day which is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Under Station Live I think is making a push for Most Original which can't think of a better title for what they do over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that would be awesome if they got that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out again.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's part of Stitcher Radio at Stitcher.com and we would appreciate
[SPEAKER_02]: your consideration during award season just you know it the exposure helps grow our family as I say at the end of every show we don't ask for your money we don't ask for anything just help spread the word about just your soul yeah just your eternal soul all right let's get into gaming news though that's what you really came here for you didn't come here to hear me promo all this stuff you want to hear about gaming news and us riffing on it so uh Loki oh wait wait
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we have a... Okay, BlackWolf has the determination.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was like, do Google Play cards exist?
[SPEAKER_02]: They do.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I've seen them too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And BlackWolf says, then I guess they can has.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Add it into the raffle this month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Google Play if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now let's get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, so this week everybody was up in arms because Content ID started going crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It became self-aware.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, it started flagging a ton of videos, even more so than normal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is mainly because they opened it up from just, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, YouTube made a comment on it and basically said, nothing illustrates the incredible growth and evolution of YouTube better than the enterprise class.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this is all PR speak, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to interrupt that.
[SPEAKER_07]: As these networks grow, we are making products and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is part of our commitment to ensure that all enterprise partners can continue to thrive and be successful on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's a whole bunch of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, they said that, yes, those content ID things that went out were not a mistake.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are real.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a lot of the problem is, you know, these videos, you know, for those not aware of the Content ID service, you know, I'm sure you'll probably hear from, you know, anybody that you follow on YouTube or, you know, a ton of people, you know, especially in the blogs recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically this way of automating the process of finding, you know, videos out there that inflict or that...
[SPEAKER_07]: have copyrighted material within them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so the way it works is they have a 30-second sample or sample of their song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's like the first 30 seconds or video.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it can be submitted to this service.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it basically checks the waveforms or whatever to see if they match this ID.
[SPEAKER_07]: Think of it like an MD5 tag or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It checks to make sure that this is what this is.
[SPEAKER_02]: some of our just to give some perspective some of our videos on the Orange Lounge Radio YouTube account have been flagged like old videos like things I don't really care about that were us playing DDR at E3 and like the song that's being played in DDR content matches
[SPEAKER_02]: so even though we're filming off it because you know E3 is loud and has that background noise and even though we're filming off the TV it's still content matches which you know whatever like I really don't you know care I mean to be fair we were showing video of someone else's game not trying to really like monetize that or whatever but it's just kind of one of those eye roll things you know yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and, you know, the other thing, well, like I said, it's automated because before this content ID, you know, thing existed, it would be up to the content holders, you know, like Warner Brothers or whoever, you know, to actually go and find those videos and flag them manually.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a very manual process and they bitched and moaned at saying, oh, look at all this stuff's getting, you know, copyrighted, there's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Full episodes of shows and stuff on YouTube and this needs to be taken care of or else we're going to sue you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so that's where they came up with this content ID thing and now everyone's getting flagged.
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is though it's automated.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not necessarily done by these companies.
[SPEAKER_07]: So for example, say Capcom or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, they probably have their materials in there because they don't want someone infringing upon that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: but they may be okay with you putting that stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which Capcom is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, which they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so there's still, you know, you have to go through the whole process of, you know, basically contesting it and then, you know, it gets sent to the Capcom or their legal team and they have to either say, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we agree this is an error or no, this really is infringing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it can lead to copyright flags or copyright strikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three strikes and, of course, you're gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your videos are gone and you're not going to be using that YouTube account anymore to make money.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, personally, I've had to deal with some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a video that I made that was just some tutorial for Grand Theft Auto map editing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't have any music in the background, but there was no audio there.
[SPEAKER_07]: YouTube said, hey, here's some pre-approved tracks that you can use.
[SPEAKER_07]: Using their own service, I picked one of those tracks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It got flagged.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a huge... This really irritates the piss out of me.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's going on with that where other people are putting in their content ID and it's not even stuff that they really own.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what needs to be come down hard on.
[SPEAKER_02]: These companies that put in these content claims for things they don't really own.
[SPEAKER_02]: that that needs to stop and YouTube needs to come down hard and fast on that but they won't and that's that's gonna be this is gonna be a very interesting turning point because you've got a lot of very angry people about this because you know there's people that make their living off of YouTube videos and you know as much as you might want to say get a real job or things like that video editing is a bitch
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a reason I don't really like to put OLR on video, and I'm very thankful to our own VXJasonXV because he's the sucker that signed up and said, sure, I'll edit the videos to put it up on YouTube or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you, Jason, because ain't nobody got time for that as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got other things I want to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's such a pain to edit videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: So these people that do edit video and do work on it, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're going to watch it,
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the author can make like a tenth of a cent or whatever they get from the ad that shows in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of the people who have been making their money that way, like Classic Game Room, I think the Cine Massacre stuff, they've already left YouTube for other places.
[SPEAKER_05]: And SF Debris, I think, went to Vimeo or this other one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Vimeo allows gaming content.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not for gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the guy who does the Star Trek and Doctor Who reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he went to Vimeo or he went to one other one, but he's been off of YouTube for a while now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not good though because I mean, yeah, we're talking about the gaming portion of it, but I'm sure that not just gaming is affected by it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a ton of people are affected by it, you know, especially just all sorts of content producers and that's not good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's not sending them a good message.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically saying you're... And it's bad enough that once they do, you know, content ID you or whatever, they flag your video.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not making revenue on that video anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: The person who ever flagged it, they just assume that, whatever, they're making money off of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo does that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're so generous, and they allow you to keep your video up so that they can make money off of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I monetize the videos on my channel, Rob Roberts Plays.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sign up for the monetization and whatever, and I realize it's kind of shaky ground with copyright because I am playing...
[SPEAKER_02]: Other people's games, but they're old games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like to think I'm kind of educating and bringing light to it, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: The amount of money, trust me, the amount of money is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also don't have any disillusions that I'm going to make a shit ton of money off this and quit my job.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's not going to happen, and I'm totally fine with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's the kind of thing where I'm like, hey, if maybe one of the videos were to end up going viral and I can get money to afford a new microphone, then great.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do spend money out of our own pockets to do this show and VOG and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I told you how much I spend on my own money on this shit, you'd probably be surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not trying to yield anybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my hobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people spend money on their hobbies.
[SPEAKER_02]: If your hobby is remote control car racing, you probably drop a lot of money into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Stan does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my hobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I drop money into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same with pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I can recoup a little bit of that, then great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I realized too with the Let's Plays, this is a slippery slope.
[SPEAKER_02]: I recently did a Let's Remember video for The Legend of Zelda on NES, and you know that shit got flagged.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was just kind of one of those, I just rolled my eyes and like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever, fine, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh no, 30 cents lost, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, one thing, Bobby just linked in chat about Jonathan Blow being flagged for posting his own game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, see that's really not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shows a real problem with the content ID matching system though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And GameGuru pointed out that it was SF Debris went to blip.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew it was one of those other ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those comments from live.vognetwork.com SSJ100Matt saying there is going to be and should be a great exodus from YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are going to start getting fed up with their flagging and content policies.
[SPEAKER_02]: If many of the big time YouTube channels started leaving, people will follow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's be honest, YouTube is not a particularly difficult to steal technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's tons of other companies that do the whole video embedding thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it just kind of takes somebody stepping up and saying, yes, we welcome the gaming content.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people assuming that Twitch would jump on that real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would make sense because they already have ways that you can highlight and create a video on demand thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just don't have a way where you can upload your own videos that I know of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you can, and I just haven't really looked at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: but needless to say the focus on Twitch TV certainly isn't video on demand but this is a huge opportunity for them if a competitor wanted to come in for Twitch TV this is a great way to get their foot in the door but I think the problem is and this is I don't
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get me wrong, I understand if I take a track from some CD or something and blatantly put that up there in CD quality on YouTube, okay, that is infringing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is weird because I see that shit all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could go find a top 40 hit, bring up the YouTube and play it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although now I know we're putting our shows on YouTube, I better not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I see videos all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or full-length movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched The Flight of the Navigator the other day on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get the fuck out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That video's on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That movie was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I watch documentaries all the time on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Freakin' Addictin'
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is the system is just not... I think a good compromise, and even still this isn't perfect, it would be... Let's say that a video comes out and... Let's just use an example of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_07]: doesn't like the fact that you're using their video or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to monetize it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that you should be able to split the revenue between what you've done and them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's a perfectly acceptable solution.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gets a little complicated when you're talking music and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The music one is a real tricky slope though, because to some extent I think the artists licensed their music for that game, they did not expect all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is maybe how music needs to be licensed going forward, but I can kind of see a little bit more where these games with these very AAA soundtracks, it's a really slippery slope.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of get that.
[SPEAKER_07]: um the other thing I was gonna say is you know just because a lot of these companies or and I don't necessarily like that I don't blame those companies because a lot of them were like dude we don't know what's going on either I mean we just you know started to hear about this you know let us know if your video got flagged and you know or you know go ahead and you know object to it and we'll uh you know we'll go ahead and you know flag it and let it go through and stuff we we want you to have that stuff out there but um
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say, there are lists out there of actual games that people will let you play and they want you to play at different publishers.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blizzard games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's a Wikia, for example.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wikia called letsplaylist.wikia.com
[SPEAKER_07]: and they even have a whole you know hashtag on Twitter who who lets play and those are all companies that will let you basically play their games and they're fine with you monetizing it usually and it will I think it will even let you know if if they you know allow that and stuff and
[SPEAKER_07]: and I mean like you know like for example like Minecraft you can do that I want to say even I was surprised you know Rockstar they're fine with you doing Grand Theft Auto and you know that kind of stuff in there so there are companies out there and I think if that's going to be if they're going to really if these I
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: CodeMan in chat, speaking of live streaming and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: CodeMan over at live.vognetwork.com says, Twitch will eventually be in the same boat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's becoming more popular and copyright laws will hit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sad that these things were made to share experiences with people and a few rotten apples screwed up for the bunch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he meant to say it's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's interesting though, because now Twitch is in this really interesting boat where, well, but they're a part, they are literally integrated into PlayStation 4 now, and will be soon on Xbox One, or at least they certainly have that channel already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo, not so much, but Nintendo kind of does their own thing with online, you know, they're not looking to get Twitch on there anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but because now that Twitch is integrated into the consoles, it's going to make that kind of, it makes it a really weird thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I can't see gaming companies suddenly coming after Twitch when Twitch is a part of the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like if you put a game out on the PlayStation 4, you know that that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, from my understanding is, of course, game companies can turn it on and off, but who's going to be that dick company to turn it off?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think anybody's in a rush to be the first to have that notorious distinction of you can't stream it on PlayStation 4 granted I guess Playroom's already in that boat but for other reasons completely
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else on the YouTube dramas you want to share, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm just more interested to see how this is going to fall out, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, see the reaction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it only happened late last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know if we've really heard a lot from publishers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, YouTube's kind of said their thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be interesting to see what...
[SPEAKER_07]: What steps are going to be taken if people are planning on moving elsewhere?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of PlayStation 4 streaming, BlackWolf says, I believe NBA 2K14 turns off the sound on the streams and captures, so it's all silent.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that probably has to do with, you know, because a game like that's got a huge soundtrack behind it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those EA sports games always do.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that wouldn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you'd think that they would still be able to do game audio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the game audio you think would be there.
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah alright, anyhow going to another story really what they should do and this is the appropriate solution for NBA 2K14 is to really just substitute all the music in the game with Space Jam Space Jam the entire time that would be the perfect solution or I believe I can fly or I believe I can fly amazing
[SPEAKER_08]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase SHELL.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to some games that won't be showing up on PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: They probably won't show up anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 38 Studios, the big studio that went bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was one of the baseball player guy owned, and then they made Kingdoms of Amalur, and then they shut down, and it left the state of Rhode Island with a big...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the auction happened this week to sell off some of their IPs and the trademarks and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: And get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: No buyer found for Project Copernicus, which was the MMO project they were working on.
[SPEAKER_02]: No buyer found for the sequel rights to Kingdoms of Amalur Reckoning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody wanted to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I think you have to have what they call a reasonable price.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to be a reasonable... Two dollars?
[SPEAKER_02]: Two dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I've got some peanuts too.
[SPEAKER_02]: 38 Studios had their own social media platform called Helios.
[SPEAKER_02]: No buyer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Intellectual Property Rights for Catan.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the big huge game engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: No buyer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they sell anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They sold a lot that included Rise of Nations and Rise of Legends, those games and the associated intellectual properties.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the other one that they sold was for the Big Huge Games trademark itself, which is kind of a catchy name for a game studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Catan would have been fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Catan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they already had Catan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was for the rights for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, apparently there were, I guess, five parties that were actually participating in the auction, but over 20 parties had expressed interest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, what did sell went for $320,000, which might not sound too bad, but apparently Rhode Island, the debt they owe Rhode Island, $100 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's...
[SPEAKER_02]: practically pennies on the debt that they actually owe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the state will continue to negotiate with interested parties to try to sell that which was unsold thus far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe the state of Rhode Island could turn into Big Huge Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, just... Big Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big Island games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Big Island?
[SPEAKER_04]: Big?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it really an island?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: And its name wasn't really Rhode Island either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rhode Island's short for its full name, which is... Oh, God, I'm going to make myself look stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rocky Rhode Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's Rhode Island and something plantations.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about we just move on?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because I don't want to look stupid here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just going on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm from California, all right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the crap it means.
[SPEAKER_02]: The State of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the full name of the state.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have to sell the state to get out of debt for that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have to get a triple mortgage on their state.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: This just in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rhode Island is now a part of New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that they'd stoop that low.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love you, New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's kidding, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how about terrorism?
[SPEAKER_02]: The state of Rhode Island and New Jersey plantations.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about terrorism?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the NSA has a new bestie.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know who it is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: The NSA is going on World of Warcraft and other online games to look for terrorists.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because this is America and we're afraid of terrorists.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not just American agencies as well, it's British agencies too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently it's this whole Anglo-Saxon descent stupidity thing, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the NSA and the Government Communications Headquarters in the UK have been monitoring activity and harvesting data from World of Warcraft and Second Life.
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently some other games that they're trying to see if they're I guess if terrorists are trying to fish for information through MMOs just by posing as a regular player.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's the dumbest thing I've ever heard of in my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that our tax money could be spent on better things and I want to know if they worked out anything with Blizzard to actually set that up or any of these other ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Blizzard came out and said they didn't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just seems to me that they are really just picking anything that they can.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they said that basically where they got the legal ability to do that was because of a 1981 executive order signed by Ronald Reagan.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, not only did he ruin our economy, he also did that too, that gave it authority to collect the data.
[SPEAKER_05]: So privacy groups are basically, you know, stepping in and what?
[SPEAKER_07]: He was a real forward thinker.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the ability to spy on World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what World of Warcraft is, but someday this will mean something.
[SPEAKER_05]: At any rate, and I'm just going to read this line in this article here from Computer World.
[SPEAKER_05]: In one document from around that time, the NSA talked about how it was able to gather information on user accounts, characters, and guilds related to known Islamic extremist groups by monitoring World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't
[SPEAKER_05]: Well said, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think part of this is overblown.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think part of this is overblown because I don't think the NSA was necessarily paying a whole bunch of people to sit around in cubicles and play World of Warcraft all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that was quite what they were doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dream job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were they trying to hack into it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's probably more what's going on with our gold farms.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said they were taking data feeds and whatnot and user logs.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, it wouldn't be out of the question that they would have people who are actually trying to communicate with groups that were
[SPEAKER_05]: are flagged with a certain name.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't hear me out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I'm saying it's not as bad as you think, I'm not saying it's appropriate because I kind of don't agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's like, well, what good did it do?
[SPEAKER_02]: What did we stop?
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know there's those people out there that are like, lol, let's do a controversial name for our guild.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are, you know, Pony Jihad or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's tons of trolls online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good luck if they were, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: Spying on Xbox Live, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody's a terrorist on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a difference between a terrorist and an asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've heard of people that have committed hideous crimes that happen to be World of Warcraft players.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an unfortunate coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I believe, I really hope I'm not misspeaking here, but there's unfortunately so many crappy people in the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: That question is not being answered.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not even the Warcraft transcripts, assumably, that they subpoenaed were able to answer that question.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my point is that they're able to get that information when they need it, when the police has it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as prevention stuff goes, we're not seeing that anything was prevented.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that guy did what he did.
[SPEAKER_05]: His chat log would be like, LFR sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably not very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dot's running out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: This tank sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he'll please.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'll please, yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah, it's just... But... I don't know where I was going with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole thing's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I remembered what it was I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing you should be aware of is that your conversations that you have in these MMOs, they're not private.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are being tracked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if something ever happened to you or you did something, they will get the records and look at every chat you've had.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that could be whether you were cybering with somebody or what.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the stuff you do when you put that information on a server, it's not private.
[SPEAKER_02]: emails not private really in that regard I mean you could go and subpoena those companies too and so forth so you know just be aware if you think you're having these ultra private conversations on these websites you're not nope so alright however I do have a resource for people who want to stay hidden on the internet and it's actually a tumblr called we are hidden well you could also just take that plug that's in the back of your computer that attaches to the internet and you can unplug it and there you go
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, for people who are paranoid about that, there's a resource out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're really paranoid about being on the internet, don't be on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do or don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But with the world we live in today, you really can't not be on the internet and participate in modern society.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, don't have a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know plenty of people that don't use Facebook or any of that stuff, you know, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook is its own can of worms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear that thing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know if it's true or not, but that Facebook actually can see, like, if you type a status and you delete it, they still track, like, what you were going to post.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they were doing some type of weird, like, tracking thing behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear I saw some article on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a lot of me bitching about people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, and I'm thinking like, wow, mine's going to be really awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I write a lot of very angry things that I delete and don't post on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a good little vent.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I need to go back to LiveJournal if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_05]: LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's all go back to LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_05]: LiveJournal is going to be like, what the hell are all these people?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Facebook, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwolf, our pal in chat at live.vognetwork.com says, sure you can participate in modern society without the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Old people do it all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even my mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hardly modern society, Bob.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mom's on Twitter, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, I want to see what Ellen is tweeting about, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do I join the Twitters?
[SPEAKER_05]: I love your mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk a little bit about... I just lost... What happened here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Something moved.
[SPEAKER_07]: The NSA.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn you, NSA.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, let's talk a little bit about SteamOS.
[SPEAKER_07]: That just came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, at least they have the beta test out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they also shipped out those 300 steam machines sadly not to my house I am disappointed but yes you can actually check it out if you don't have a steam machine to test out on you can download it now and yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, one of the things about the Steam OS is they're not trying to be a replacement for your own OS that you have right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is a good, I guess, alternative for gaming or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: But check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they even have... Those Steam machines out there, they sound pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they came in like a wooden crate and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so fucking disappointed that I didn't get one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Second to use a new computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was really sad I didn't get one either, but it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have we heard anything about people that are actually using SteamOS?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know it's out there, but I'm not hearing a lot of reviews on it or anything, like how it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't heard anything yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess a lot of people are just hesitant to use it because it's like, well, I'm not going to exactly overwrite Windows with SteamOS.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you don't have a second computer for it, then what can you do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not necessarily because I think you can multi-boot into that stuff and do it that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: but I'm not really sure how I haven't messed with Steam or I haven't messed with Linux in a long time last time I tried to mess with Linux is when I heard that Linux would allow me to somehow mount the file system on some DDR disk I don't remember, something had to do with Dance Dance Revolution hacking that but uh yeah that was that um
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm going to try to move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: For our live listeners, the podcasts only will hear this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our live stream just dropped completely.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't connect to our streaming server.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not even my internet because I still see IRC and everything and everybody's freaking out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I can't even connect.
[SPEAKER_03]: The NSA shut us down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, would you mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to flip the script a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you go to your story next?
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose I could do such a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I try to fix what's going on here, even though it might be out of my control.
[SPEAKER_05]: Firefly Online is going to be a thing and it is launching in summer 2014 by developer QMX and it's going to be on iOS and Android but they are going to be expanding onto PC and Mac and may include other platforms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there's not a lot of information out other than soon, but basically it's going to be you get your ship, you get your crew, you have to keep them happy, you have to trade, craft, collect, fly around the verse, and you also have a freeform flight simulator built into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and uh they're basically uh saying that it's going to be uh you know when you start off you're basically going to be kind of another version of the Firefly crew you play as a brown coat captain and then you get other factions through later DLC releases but um it sounds kind of fun I'm looking forward to it I might play it because I love Firefly it's the Joss
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really cool news for those that were, because, you know, obviously, that show had a huge cult to it, and people want to see it come back, and they want to see, you know, what's... The comic's coming out, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's based after the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, what a nice way to kind of at least continue the story, because we all know, like, the show can't come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: All those actors are on to new things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it just, it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't Marina Baccarin, like, super pregnant right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think she's super pregnant right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although her hair grew back.
[SPEAKER_05]: She had long hair in the last picture I saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think this is a great way for people to at least continue that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird to me that an MMO for Firefly didn't happen sooner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why you're nothing but firefly pieces of pudding sitting on a plate.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're custard!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but for people who are really into doing things in that universe, there actually is a tabletop game that I want to say, well, the former White Wolf put out, because I think it's the same type of gameplay system as Werewolf and Vampire, those ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like I said, there's a comic going to be coming out that's based on the Fallout after the Serenity movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it seems that that universe is getting a lot of love lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: You think the fact that the Avengers is doing well and all that helps kind of bump up Whedon's properties?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Joss.
[SPEAKER_05]: People who love Joss love Joss regardless.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for the record, I was never a big Buffy fan and I didn't like Angel until its last season because that was when the writers stopped giving a fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was when we had the Puppet Time episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: but I loved Firefly I didn't watch Dollhouse but I've liked Joss's writing when he wrote for Astonishing X-Men that's probably the most I've enjoyed any X-Men title like since the Dark Phoenix stuff when I was a little kid so our stream did come back for the live listeners welcome back apparently it was not our fault I don't know what's up with that but anyway going to some comments in our chat room SSJ100 Matt says this still seems like an April Fool's joke is it a joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: ESGN ESPN
[SPEAKER_02]: ESGN, ESports Global Network
[SPEAKER_02]: E-sports, of course, is a lot of the head-to-head combat.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see some of the big games that support this right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: League of Legends, Dota 2, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those MOBAs are huge for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: StarCraft 2, World of Warcraft Arena.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see a lot of this being e-sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked a little bit about this on my other show, Horde House, as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're seeing now people are getting visas to come into the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just had a guy for StarCraft II got a visa to come in on that game this week to play that, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, ESGN will be launching at ESGN.com, and ESGNTV.com is the video site for its dedicated 24-hour channel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, it is not something that's planned to be on standard television, quote-unquote, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: What is standard TV anymore in the world of Netflix and Hulu and YouTube and all that?
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is going to be a very interesting experiment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we don't talk a lot about StarCraft 2 and League of Legends on this show, but if y'all need three fun and fabulous commentators on a Sunday night, we might be available.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just say if the money's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the money's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All joking aside, let's get to the release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Travel the world and check out what's coming out in a gaming store near you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not a lot, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or not a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a thing, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are done for the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the US, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: In the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, aside from, you know, digital stuff obviously coming out, but nothing at retail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Dragoon 3
[SPEAKER_02]: A brand new DualShock controller in crystal color comes out, as well as FIFA 14 World Class Soccer Bonus Edition, and Shin Gundam Musou comes out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's still some heavy hitters in Japan the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: The day after Christmas, Boxing Day, if you will, for Canada, in Japan they're getting Final Fantasy X and X-2's remasters are out on December 26th, so just barely making it this year, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Still plenty to come over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Xbox 360, Band Fused, Rock Legends is there as well, as well as Shooting Love Collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: And going over to the Vita, on the PlayStation Vita this week, Amnesia V Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that the same Amnesia that is the scary game that we have here?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is more based off an anime, I believe, with a lot of cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like this guy...
[SPEAKER_07]: Where did all my cards go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where did these come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a crap ton on the Vita this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead or Alive 5 gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Diabolic Lovers Limited V Edition comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Geki Johan Mahou Shoujo Madoka That's Magica The Battle Pentagram comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a big anime series that half my friends on Tumblr are losing their shit over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hakoyuki Kuyokoroku Injustice Kudwafter Kudwafter
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck Yes Madoka
[SPEAKER_02]: Shin Gundam Musou comes out this week on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, Gundam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Busy, busy week on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Wii U, nothing, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Nintendo 3DS, however, High School D x D, Koneku no Album, My Little Cat comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a kiddie game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to see what this is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am flailing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need this in my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone get me a Japanese 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like... It's kitties in fancy hats.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like real pictures of cats in like sailor suits and pink hats and like orange Halloween sweaters.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they don't even look like they're going to murder you.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, this is what it comes to.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is why Swapnil was removed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to link that to our chatters right now so they can take a look at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room is harassing me into watching Madoka.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need this in my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that means that's going to be the next thing I have to marathon since I marathoned all of Shingeki no Kyojin so far and Claymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who makes this game?
[SPEAKER_02]: MTO.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't recognize that name.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking on the box art.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody loves MTO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they have a Twitter or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I want this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to petition for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh my god, thank you for posting a picture of Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to harass them like we did for President Cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I still want to play that game too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I want that in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Koneko no Album, My Little Cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Koneko means kitten.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like, I wonder if it's just like you take pictures of your own cat and then this program helps you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Putting Midna in outfits!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, that's gonna be great!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what to do with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, did you know that A Legend of Zelda The Link Between Worlds is still not out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: They will not be getting that until December 26th.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to put Midna in a frilly little dress.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to murder the shit out of me in my sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's not going to drop this all night.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to be Midna.
Mom!
[SPEAKER_05]: Mom!
[SPEAKER_05]: This sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's how she talks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is AkumaJP helping us out here?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's this link he just gave us?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I know AkumaJP is over there and maybe can... Are... Is this... Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_05]: They're ID pictures and you can make one look like a Bosozoku.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is outstanding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, somebody get me a Japanese 3DS and this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has to do with cats being adorable.
[SPEAKER_02]: The internet would eat this shit up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at that picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like they're dressed up as Bosozoku.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Horrible radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe what I can do, I can beg Jason to maybe take some of these links and put some of the pictures in the YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: And put them on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_02]: or just look it up again for yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look it up for yourself, the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's out there on your favorite import gaming website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I gotta get through some PSP games though.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I'm inspired to dress up Midna on her Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some PSP games, as if the Vita wasn't enough, you also have After School, Colorful Step, Undou Yubu comes out this week, Lovely Quest Unlimited, Nobunaga no Yabu Sosensoku with a power-up kit comes out this week, that's a price reduction actually, and Ore no Kanojo no Uro Omote, Pure Sweetheart comes out on the PSP this week, still kicking in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need the kiddie game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 18th, we have Zen Pinball 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the 19th, Colossatron, Massive World Threat.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a cool name, Colossatron.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then on Wii U, we have Knit Underground, K-N-Y-T-T.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Ridge Racer Slipstream for the Android, iPad, and iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: And nothing else until... Xmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we should call it Extifermas and worship Extifer.
[SPEAKER_02]: We might do that on Horde House this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are having a holiday special on Horde House this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to be on a holiday special.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: At school.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys in the classic game of the week, which may or may not have to do with cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Sony has patented a brand new, looks like a Move controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: The difference being that instead of having an analog stick on that one side, the main difference is it's going to have a touchpad, kind of like how they have on the Vita and on the front of the PlayStation 4 controllers.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe, it makes sense if you think about it, because now they will need some sort of extra input, you know, to cover, you know, PlayStation 4 games that use the move controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe this is what this is about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really do a lot of games use the move controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are they going to start bringing it back like how they did with Resistance and Killzone and stuff where they have a giant fucking gun that looked ridiculous with the move controllers in there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I kind of got the feeling they were trying to kind of get rid of the move, kind of shove that under the rug or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the impression I was getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm trying to do a little research on this game company that makes this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found their websites and I'm trying to see if they have a Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's a Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to find a Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a dog one too!
[SPEAKER_02]: yes there's dress your oh my gosh but the kitty one's the best okay but this is good because now I can give out this URL so the podcast listeners can be like what the hell are they freaking out about so I'm gonna I'm gonna just totally give them a free plug here on the show because they're they make games to dress up your kitties and doggies mto-power.com that's mto-power.com is the maker of these games and there's got to be a way to to send them a message and let them know we want these games in America I have hiccups now
[SPEAKER_02]: Did the cute kitties give you...
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't burp on the microphone!
[SPEAKER_05]: Burping is a good way to get rid of hiccups.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never, ever said I was ladylike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Tigerclaw, for linking it in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one of those gaming good news stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank heavens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gaming exercise games, whether you love them or you're sick of hearing about them, they do a lot of good for our community.
[SPEAKER_02]: and a new study is out this week about Nintendo's Wii Fit Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, Wii Fit Plus was available on the Nintendo Wii and now they have the newer version that's on the Wii U. I believe the demo's done, but you can check that out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they say that Nintendo's Wii Fit Plus improves the lives of patients with type 2 diabetes and helps control their blood sugar levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is by BMC and Doctrine Disorders who carried out the trial with 220 participants for a period of 12 weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Half were asked to use Wii Fit Plus for half an hour a day and the second half were under routine care and just, you know, got everything 12 weeks later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those that actually got the fitness game lost weight and improved their blood sugar levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: because guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: They were doing exercise.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of the thing is I kind of look at this and go, well, duh, exercise leads to good things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, of course, this is what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you give the people the stuff for free, I guess there's more incentive to play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyhow, experts noted that the daily physical activity increased, mental health and subjective well-being increased as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The number of patients suffering from depression decreased.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, interesting, a third of the patients dropped out of the trial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meaning that people retaining the same level of enthusiasm over a sustained period of time was difficult.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to Dr. Richard Elliott, who's with Diabetes UK, So,
[SPEAKER_02]: you know what whatever gets people motivated right
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, the biggest thing is exercise and cutting out the sugar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because guess what diabetes is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Problem with insulin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although if you have type 1 diabetes, cutting out the extra sugar is not always good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, moving on to a more simple time when we weren't really able to interact with our games, unless it was Dance Aerobics.
[SPEAKER_05]: When Diabetes was Wilford Brimley.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week, DarkSakura goes into the Classic Gaming Vault and finds one game that she thinks, hey, you guys should be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead of eating all that candy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Write the F now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what is the Classic Game of the Week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Poll position.
[SPEAKER_02]: A very true classic indeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, it's an arcade racer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out in 1982.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that intro music because that's the only music in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much the only music in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The rest of it is just squeaky noises.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll keep it really low in the background just in case.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was manufactured by Atari.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, worldwide by Namco.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the U.S., it was done by Atari.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was actually the most popular coin-op game in 1983.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it has an upright cabinet or an environmental cockpit cabinet, which my Chuck E. Cheese's slash Showbiz Pizza in Mobile, Alabama had one forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: They still fucking have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The same one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just surprised it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically you have the accelerator, you have a brake pedal, and you have your wheel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was the highest-grossing arcade game in North America in 1983, and it sold 21,000 machines for $61 million, equivalent to 2012's $140 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just put it in modern money.
[SPEAKER_05]: The most successful racing game of its time, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it had a Saturday morning cartoon, which I watched the hell out of, and have every episode of downloaded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus it had a cool intro.
[SPEAKER_05]: um it uh basically pole position I think was the big inspiration for most of the modern driving games that we have now so basically in the game you have a formula one race car and you do a time trial lap to qualify for um the Fuji racetrack and uh
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and it also was had it was in full color and had scaling sprites including your race cars and your signs to give you perspective it was for the US release Namco actually approached Bally Midway to either and said okay one of you can get one of these games and so Bally took Mappy and Atari took Pole Position and
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, so basically, it's been probably one of the most ported systems, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been put out by Atari Soft and a lot of the home computers and consoles in the early 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the 90s, there was a pole position on PC that came back in Microsoft's return of arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been on PlayStation, N64, and Dreamcast in the Namco Museum.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's also been on PS2, GameCube, GBA and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuji Speedway was renamed Namco Speedway in the Museum series and for the Plug and Play series that were part of the Namco Museum Virtual Arcade it was called Blue Speedway.
[SPEAKER_05]: and there's also a version to work with the Puffer Exercise Bike Controller and it has been put out on iPod back in the day and now we have iOS versions with Pole Position Remix and Pole Position 2, which was the sequel, has also been re-released as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, Pole Position 2 being the sequel, it came out in 1983 and let me see...
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate my iPad sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as that, a lot of people are saying that Final Lap is the unofficial Pole Position 3, which is sort of a racing RPG spinoff that came out on the TurboGrafx-16, also known as the PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: That version was called Final Lap Twin.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I mentioned earlier, there was Pole Position Remix for iPhone and it had the courses for Pole Position 2 and a new course.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was also a cartoon of the same name, like I said, that I watched a bunch of times.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Pole Position showed up in the movie Daryl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the movie Daryl?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: The boy who was an android.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he won a very high score in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, Pole Position Remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_02]: Available like 11 billion different places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just because it was the most popular arcade game that year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We built our old main cabinet out of a pole position.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie lived in it for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was her cat condo, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great use for a pole position machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: My cat is, you know how fat Shermie was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, how the crap did she get in it?
[SPEAKER_05]: She found a little door where the pedal was, and she would just live, we had this pole position machine sitting in our apartment for a year it had to be, or at least half a year, and Shermie lived in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cats are amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break, but don't go anywhere because when we come back there is plenty more Orange Lounge Radio to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: More news, the Fuku Question of the Week, your calls, and much more when we come back after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I live in an interfaith home.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are a Christmaka family.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is fair.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we taught Julian about Hanukkah because he had to study for school.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a really good little gambler now with the dreidel.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he loves guilt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_05]: And he was going around going...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Becky and I determined that there's not a we call it the phlegm sound because there's no real translation for phlegm sound from Hebrew to English other than Chanukah
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, whatever it is you celebrate.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Kwanzaa's the 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kwanzaa, Festivus, if you have a Festivus pull-up, enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yule.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yule, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance naked around the tree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just a big thank you from all of us to you guys who are such a great support for the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had a really good year this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: and just additional exposure through Stitcher and podcasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know personally I've met a lot of other great podcasts through GamerX was a great way to connect with a lot of other podcasters.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just want to say thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had a great year.
[SPEAKER_02]: VOG has continued to grow, which has been great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brought on one or two new shows this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know Electric Sisterhood was this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember if there was one other one this year, if that was last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, that hopefully continuing to grow into next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just, yeah, lots of great things happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you guys are all to thank for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next year looks to be awesome as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cannot wait for DragonCon 2014.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby and Travis Donovan done gone and got me addicted to DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm counting down the days.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I go back to Atlanta for 2014.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be very exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: GamerX2 going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't even think I can handle how amazing that weekend's going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever else I end up doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really hoping to get that New York City trip in this year that I've been needing to take for the past six years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to go to GamerX.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a great OLR family in New York City.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure we can make GamerX happen for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get into some more gaming news, some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to buy Loki a little time because he's taking care of what he has to do for his wisdom teeth.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, alright Gotta do your salt water rinse, yep Don't want to get an infection, that's fine, I understand Is shoving all those salted french fries in your mouth Isn't the same effect?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't remember having to do that But I remember them giving me Two different mouthwashes
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: and
[SPEAKER_07]: To celebrate that, I'm not sure if they're releasing on any more platforms here anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it is on its way to Vita, PlayStation 3, and PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be even more copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Elder Scrolls Online.
[SPEAKER_07]: They finally announced the launch date of April 4th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Man, that is going to be a busy month for MMOs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gotta say.
[SPEAKER_07]: PC... Well, that's for PC and Mac.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next-gen version not coming until June...
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you're hoping to get on the PlayStation 4 or Xbox One, you're going to be waiting a little bit longer.
[SPEAKER_07]: And last but not least, this is kind of surprising because I remember this game from a while ago when Atari released it, but Mark Echo's Getting Up, contents under pressure, the kind of weird graffiti slash futuristic...
[SPEAKER_07]: um government totalitarian game um originally like I said put out by Atari and now though the rights have actually been um snatched up and um it's been released onto Steam so you can check it out um thanks to Devolver Digital for publishing that and that's available on Steam and I think it's actually at least it was on sale so um
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's still on sale for 50% off, so $7.49 if you want to check out the game if you may have missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on in music gaming news that isn't so happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Max Technica 2 and Technica 3 had this online thing called Platinum Crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to be confused with the Vita version of DJ Max Technica, which I know a lot of you have, but the arcade versions had the Platinum Crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, that is shutting down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will no longer be available as of December 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: SADNESS TO DJ MAXX
[SPEAKER_02]: All but dead now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, pretty much, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: It got pulled due to an intellectual property dispute.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who closed it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Submitted a request on November 19th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phantasm was trying to get a developer's license for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have reimagined a lot of the Ghost and Goblin stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: If for whatever reason they did not get the rights, they were going to rename it King Arthur.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they were just going to call it.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it got shut down because I guess Capcom didn't really... It was one of those things where it sounded like they were... Just getting the impression again.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were going to do that after the fact, not before the fact.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Capcom didn't want the name of the game being used like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can kind of see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: In happier news, our track record for helping out Kickstarters improves this week as read-only memories did get funded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to admit, they were really close.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really down to the wire, but they did make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So congratulations to Matt Kahn, who was on the show a couple weeks ago, as well as everybody over at MidBossGames that helps them out because they did reach beyond their goal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They hit a final tally, 64,378, and they were trying to make 62,000 to get matched by Ouya.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the good news is now they will be matched by Ouya.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, that game is happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we're hoping that will be playable at GamerX, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, congrats to those guys over there at MidBoss Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Totally cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look forward to playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see the screen capture that Bob Coffee just put in chat?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yours don't load, do they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, what am I looking at here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, I'm Wayne Brady from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wayne Brady.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that a gold shirt wearing you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's a gold letterbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, there is a Fable anniversary set coming out on February 4th, 2014.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the 1080p HD version of the original Fable.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, actually, it will be a good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it will also have launch day weapons and outfits pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you get a loot weapon that is supposed to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The core version is the 25th anniversary with nine figures, four of Witcher Mega Man, four Robot Masters, and one Dr. Wily.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's a $70 packet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then for $140 you get a deluxe version that adds Time Man and Oil Man and 40 card player decks and individual Robot Master game boards and dozens of token pieces.
[SPEAKER_05]: So good for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: and another cool thing and this is actually thanks to my hubby who gave me this bit of news while I was trying to work last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ultra Street Fighter 4 is going to have online training and 3 vs 3 matches like King of Fighters so you can get your Street Fighter 4 on KOF style.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am just looking forward to doing my final fight team of Andorre or Hugo, sorry Poison and
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when they released Final Fight Guy on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was such a big-ass deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what I have?
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fight Guy in the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, in retro... I'm sorry, not on NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super NES was Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a Blockbuster exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um... What's that other... God, fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mighty Final Fight was the... Mighty Final Fight was the Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of shit, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those things everybody's like, yeah, Mighty Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when they play it, they're like, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun for being shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, I'd have to say that Final Fight Guy was always my... I had a copy of it that I had borrowed from someone who stole it from Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I was in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're poor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I gave it back and I moved out here with my friend's Chrono Trigger that he just let me keep.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Dan and I looked into Final Fight Guy loose and then we looked into the box separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now we have Final Fight Guy in the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, let's just cut to the chase and do a Capcom versus SNK 3 already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hands in the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: Testify.
[SPEAKER_02]: Preach it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Preach.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I tell you?
[SPEAKER_02]: This needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, one of the other games that we bought last night was Tekken Cross Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we had to buy one, get one, and we couldn't find another freebie game.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you had nothing better to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also got Metal Gear Rising.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we could play around as pretty boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week on our Facebook and Google Plus communities, we ask a question and you guys answer it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it is the holiday season and I'm feeling awfully charitable, I think I'm going to read all the answers tonight, of which there are an awful lot of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: So heads up, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's only what?
[SPEAKER_02]: How many answers are on Facebook?
17.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the Fugu question of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, oh God, this was a moment in history on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: The internet just exploded and the gifts were priceless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm sure you've all heard by now the bombshell that was dropped on the music industry when Beyonce just released a new album with no promotion or fanfare.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the whole internet went to the Church of Beezus Christ.
[SPEAKER_02]: and was like, Breach, honey.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on top of that, it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a great album.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just like, I think my favorite thing that came out of the whole thing is that gif where she just, like Beyonce goes to the table and she just swipes all the albums of like Katy Perry and Gaga and Miley and everything just right off the table.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I will say this quickly, tangent, sorry, apologies, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're so awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: VH1 had that whole Divas thing for a while, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when they would all come together at the end and sing like an Aretha song?
[SPEAKER_05]: And they brought out Carole King at the end, and everyone tried to out-Diva Carole King, and you don't out-Diva Carole King.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: On her song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, Beyonce just fucking out-Diva'd them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: She just walked into the room, dropped the mic, and left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I get it, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because she's bejesus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we should support all talented artists.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I also just like that her album is called Beyonce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So all that aside, Shane is blowing up in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so sick of her.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, so sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a fucking huge album.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went back to check how many... What she did though, what she did was unprecedented.
[SPEAKER_02]: 400,000 copies sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like Gaga and Britney combined.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's like, not just all the music, but she's got videos out for half the stuff on the album.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and that's on... And they're good videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, alright, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're like, what the fuck does this have to do with gaming, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't Beyonce sue a video game company?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was just like, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, she did, but here's the point.
[SPEAKER_02]: The gaming community is, this is no stranger to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, we see this all the time, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: They come out in E3 and say, hey, if you want to get this today, you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to stop all this woman-on-woman fighting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need woman-on-man fighting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to see Beyonce take out Nickelback for good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think everybody wants to see Beyonce take out Nickelback for good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see it like freaking I don't know Celine Dion can take out Nickelback for good for all I care alright anyway so the gaming industry is no surprise this we see these it's out today announcements a lot what if you could in the gaming community have one I said realistic stealth announcement because I didn't want people to be like hologram gaming out today like okay if you could get a realistic stealth announcement this holiday season what bombshell do you want to see drop this holiday season so here we go
[SPEAKER_02]: um coming up first from Jimmy B who I think honestly he got five likes on this post so I think he kind of has the winning answer here but Jimmy B over on Facebook says Half-Life 3 pops up on Steam on Christmas morning internet explodes we're praying everybody prayer circle let's all form one Half-Life 3 that would be the bombshell I'd like that would melt steam that would melt the internet are you kidding
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is ironic, steam melting Alright, Jeremy J, our buddy from Koopa Club Hey Jeremy J, says I'd love to see Game Boy Advance games appear on the Wii U, eShop, OS, all stealth-like Specifically Metroid Zero Mission But yeah, that's a good realistic prediction Nintendo making more money off of old games, absolutely
[SPEAKER_02]: Degenerate Johnny says, I want Rockstar to announce that Grand Theft Auto 5 is out now for the Wii U. It's current gen, so making a port shouldn't be a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, you can use the touchpad screen to help navigate throughout the city as well as play around with the iFruit app while playing GTA 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Loki, but I had to speak my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did he have to apologize?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you be offended by Grand Theft Auto 5 on the Wii U, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole integration with the app would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the record, back to the Beyonce versus Nickelback thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: While I think Beyonce could take Nickelback, I think Rush could take Beyonce.
[SPEAKER_05]: All they have to do is have Neil Peart drum on her head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our buddy from PodCulture, Brad, says, PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 emulation on the new consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't think that's going to happen, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the PlayStation 3 would be a lot closer because of the Gaikai technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Microsoft will do it maybe if they can, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fabrice A replies and says, Easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega launches a new console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not stick to the classics?
[SPEAKER_02]: Robert K said the rumored to be finished Shenmue HD is released on Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network in time for the in-game Christmas festivities because sailors and I need hope Robert K taking a game of lucky hit on his his gander there so good luck Codeman says I would like Nintendo to announce a new Mario Galaxy I literally went crazy when I played the game for the first time I think a lot of people would like to see a new Mario Galaxy
[SPEAKER_02]: FifthDream says, is Fallout 4 realistic enough?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 15?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it would be cool if Sony suddenly updated the PlayStation 4 with CD, MP3, and streaming media support.
[SPEAKER_02]: A firmware update.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could definitely happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elliot B says, I could ask for a new Metroid Prime or Guitar Room Man, but I'll go with something a little more realistic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heists in GTA 5 Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Launching the online mode without a decent selection of co-op missions was very silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even the fighter jet death matches are getting stale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rockstar, throw us a bone already.
[SPEAKER_02]: You agree with Elliot?
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to see some heists?
[SPEAKER_07]: Heists would be fun, but I don't think it's necessarily getting stale.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now that they have all these content creator things, it'd be cool to do your own missions or make custom game types and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sial responds and says Capcom releases a new good Mega Man or a new 2D Metroid from Nintendo Daniel T says the announcement of virtual console cross buy followed by a one more thing announcing the availability of as Jeremy said select Game Boy Advance titles or in my dreams DS and GameCube titles would make me fanboy so hard
[SPEAKER_02]: John from Critical Myth, our pals over there, Mondays 4 o'clock Pacific on VOG, says Final Fantasy XI free to play on PS Vita 24th December 2013.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Loki would like that very much as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: BloodDrunk replies and says Steam Holiday Sale Day 1 Half-Life 3 status available now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like that response should have been read to like, duh, duh, duh.
[SPEAKER_05]: or in the Howard Cosell voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, but don't expect me to do that when I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all know my impressions are not very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jennifer L says, I would love the next generation of Pokemon to come out all stealthily.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kids around the world would panic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Pokemon games are capable of coming out without hype But that would be really funny to see happen Ragenator says As totally unrealistic as it may be I'd say that for the Steam Winter Sale Everything is completely and utterly free For a certain period within the sale It's a pipe dream, yeah, but one can dream, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly on Facebook, our pal Delvin from Video Game Realness, which is a really fun podcast out of Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Delvin replies and says, Some kind of major Wii U release that none of us saw coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Star Fox or Metroid-like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something no one is expecting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spanish Inquisition the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we might have a bit more restored faith in Wii U and say they knew what they were doing all along.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, I think Wii U needs the fanfare to kind of get their investors rallied up a little more, but I'm going to hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to form a prayer circle with you because I would love to see that happen on Wii U as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And shut them haters down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut them haters down.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, a few comments from Google+.
[SPEAKER_02]: Redertainment says, price drop on everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox One, PlayStation 4, Wii U, PS3, 360, games, accessories, everything reduced in price.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I'd like a pony.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to reply to something Ranma said about PC will never become the master race for gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: All games will be nerfed to console standards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not quite so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's some people that refuse to leave Mac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't forget that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, as far as Xbox One and PlayStation 4 and all that goes, 2014, it'll be a belated Christmas gift for Entertainment Belated.
[SPEAKER_02]: uh Actdeft says a secret Nintendo Direct this week before we sign off we would like to gladly announce that we're releasing F-Zero Universe a new installment on the beloved F-Zero franchise with HD graphics online play in a new customization mode so you can change your machine however you like when's it going to be released you asked right after this Nintendo Direct is over on the Wii U eShop and a retail version in January how's that for a bombshell announcement well I came
[SPEAKER_02]: That's exactly what I'd like to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I came over to the computer to place my pre-order.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to call your mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam H. Please don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam H. says Uncharted 4 available today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Colin M. says Shenmue 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chalk another Shenmue answer up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly but not leastly, Tech2030 replies and says, A new all-hand-drawn 2D Metroid game for Wii U or 3DS would make me the most excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love those answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys over on Google Plus and Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our Fugo Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did read them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in the holiday spirit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to read them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like hearing people's fanboy dreams.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about you guys?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything you would love to see the stealth announcement comes out?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was replying to chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, really, right now, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I would go with the Half-Life thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Half-Life!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we're done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: the one thing I want more than anything dear Jesus for your birthday I would really like more than anything to see after all these years and all this hoping and all this praying dear Beyonce may I please have the Guardian Legend on virtual console can I get an amen or a true sequel
[SPEAKER_02]: I will take what I can get.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need a Guardian Legend variety game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Compile needs to rise from their grave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rise from your grave!
[SPEAKER_05]: And not do any more Puyo Pop.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need more Guardian Legend and more Compile shooters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, and Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I'd go for a new DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just keeping it simple.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted a new TDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that would be shocking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, we're going to do a new TDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only shocking if it's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would like for our Roosevelt Golf Land to magically have a 2DX machine again and not get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Scandia is going to get a 2DX machine, probably.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you may remember the guy that runs Seanigan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Seanigan, he has this wonderful arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: In his garage?
[SPEAKER_07]: In his garage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's also at the drive-in, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I ran into, he works at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he's picking three of his machines to bring in there, one of which is a 2DX20, I guess, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually randomly met while I was playing some game over there, one of the shooting games, and we just started talking about his machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to get that guy on this show if he's here locally.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's on my Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, get him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send him a message.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get him on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Shane is sending me a private message in chat because apparently I skipped his answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's because you answered late, you jerk.
[SPEAKER_02]: But our buddy Shane from Horde House says, I want a stealth announcement for F-Zero for Wii U and 3DS in the same style as the ACGX versions, and then unlockable GX versions in both the Wii U and 3DS, and Jack Levin's theme making a comeback because it was the best in GX.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an awfully tall order, but I would love to see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you first.
[SPEAKER_07]: The current votes for machines that they are going to bring is top three machines will go to the location.
[SPEAKER_07]: Top three so far, 2DX Linkle, upgraded to Tricoro, PoppyMusic20, upgraded to Sunny Park, and DGMAX Technica 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, Other is number three, but who knows how Other is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree with all of these selections.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I forgot what I was going to say, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then let's get back into some news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the Xbox One, let's talk a little bit more about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of surprised that they kind of went back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess it never really worked for retail games, but they're not requiring demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's up to the devs to basically decide whether they're going to put out a demo for their game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, originally, you had to have a demo for any Xbox Live Arcade game that was out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now I guess they're kind of going the route of like the retail games where it doesn't necessarily have to have a demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of think that's a little lame because games are expensive and sometimes the demos get you to buy the game or in some cases I guess get you not to buy the game if you can't beat the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is one, I guess one of the demos that they're actually putting out, and I really hate, I think Nintendo was the one that kind of started this, but those demos that have a certain number of playthroughs you can do on them before they lock you out of them completely, like Dead Rising 3, they're going to let you play it for 20 minutes, and then you can play it for two more times other than that, and then it's done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, what the hell, man?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that different from what PlayStation Plus has you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play the first hour, but still.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but I remember back when they had the timed demos for Saints Row, and I played that demo over and over and over again, and it just got me hyped about the game, and I bought it immediately when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's how I killed my time until it came out, was by playing that demo over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess just...
[SPEAKER_07]: um whatever do you have to download the whole stinking thing just to play 20 minutes or does it do like the streaming thing i think it's the i think it's probably a shorter demo it's that's good but it's apparently the map i mean but it's just 20 minutes of it so maybe we have to download the whole thing i don't know um and they've also hit the 2 million sales mark as of um
[SPEAKER_07]: as of the 11th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, everybody's doing well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Selling lots of consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's spinning it like they're winning, but at the end of the day, they're both doing well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony and Microsoft, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that I'm worried about any of these companies, but I'm seeing a pattern emerge here, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: so it gets me worried that maybe they aren't flying off shelves not to say that they're doing bad I mean they sold 2 million units worldwide so that's not bad but it may be slowing down a lot faster and I think a lot of that has to do probably with the launch lineup there's just not a lot to drive people to buy them so that's my concern I guess it would go with Playstation 2 because maybe they're just not producing a ton of units I think they're about neck and neck as far as sales go
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be said as well, even though maybe Nintendo's not having the best luck with Wii U, and it doesn't seem like their fortune's turning around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're selling more of them, but it's not in the same league as these other consoles right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3DS still continues to sell like wildfires.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's a huge success story for Nintendo, so at least there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they won't be going out of business.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, speaking of sales, let's go over to the MPD numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki, you might have to help me out here a little bit because you read into more of the stuff than I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But video game sales for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: in November up 7% from last year, which you would hope is going to happen when you have new consoles out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hardware jumped up 58% again with two new consoles out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You would hope those numbers go up.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 4, the top-selling console in November, and PlayStation was number one in sales overall for home consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: My fans will be quick to tell you that, well, they had an additional week to sell those consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, they're both doing very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: 909,132 Xbox One units sold in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: in the first nine days, meaning over 100,000 a day.
[SPEAKER_02]: The top-selling games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the top 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty Ghosts 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Battlefield 4 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Assassin's Creed 4 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Madden 25 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto 5 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: NBA 2K14 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skylanders Swap Force 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just Dance 2014 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disney Infinity 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: FIFA 14 No surprise at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got your typical big sellers, the Call of Duty and the Battlefield, your Assassin's Creed, the Sports Balls,
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto is still in there and then the kiddie toy games with Skylanders and Disney Affinity rounding out your top 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of surprises in there, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about some of those Nintendo numbers because we do have some numbers about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: 770,000 Nintendo 3DSs sold in November.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the 3DS has been out for a couple years, and they sold almost as many of those as they did Xbox Ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Wii U hardware sales, they say up by 340%, but I think we all know that's kind of a spin because three times a little number is still not probably going to be a huge number.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it is what it is but Super Mario 3D World 215,000 digital and physical units in the first 8 days not too shabby especially in light of the article from Japan that didn't have quite the impressive number last week but it should be noted that didn't allow it to crack the top 10 but considering that Super Mario 3D World is on one console and one console that hasn't really cracked through as well as every single one of those games in the top 10 that I read off multiple formats
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I would assume I'm looking right here to set some of the weekly charts for hardware.
[SPEAKER_07]: Trying to see if I can pull up older stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's not helping.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, for hardware though, like for example, the week of the 7th, that would have been a week ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii U moved 72,000 units in North America and the 3DS 244,000.
[SPEAKER_07]: So kind of give you an idea, you know, when they're saying 700,000, you're probably looking at maybe 150,000 units of Wii U, which is not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, it's one of those things where it's like, it's not going to bankrupt the company, but it's going to be very interesting to see what they do in 2014.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, is Nintendo going to stick with it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I kind of think they're stubborn enough and they believe in it enough that I think they're going to stick with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what they're going to do to sell more, but I think they believe enough in Bayonetta and Smash Brothers and whatever Zelda or Mario game they have hidden up their sleeve for holiday 2014.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Kart next year is going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they believe enough in those that they're going to still try.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope it turns it around for them, because if Mario Kart or Smash Brothers can't move units, then they're going to be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some people saying that Nintendo will announce a new console at this E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's way too soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Internally, are they having that dialogue?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be very interesting to see what happens at E3 this year for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: They seem to be pushing themselves into that outside of the regular release stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's just disappointing not seeing the third-party support just not there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, they're going to be showing stuff on screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're always going to say that they have the third-party support, but they don't have full third-party support, and that's what's really hurting them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, 3DS does.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no EA 3DS games anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they've completely cut them off.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, they have plenty of stuff on 3DS keeping it going, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty of stuff on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's when they speak about Nintendo partners and not just 3DS and Wii U separately, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because EA's not supporting them on any of the platforms right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zebediah the Messiah in our chatroom says Mario Kart Wii U bundle and I'm in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a guaranteed from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: If not, you know Costco and Best Buy and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have their bundles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: YYR says Smash Brothers usually sells consoles, but I think the biggest threat to Smash selling Wii U consoles is Smash for 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the other thing too is a lot of people already bought the Wii U for Smash Brothers, so you can't really count a lot of new sales from that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who
[SPEAKER_02]: Who buys a console for a game two years out from now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: We kind of considered.
[SPEAKER_02]: You considered, but you didn't?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: so you know anyway I would say if you're gonna get a Wii U get a fucking Wii U because the Mario 3D World is one of the best games you're gonna play this year period especially if you have people in your house to play games with or people over frequently you will not find a better party multiplayer game experience than you will with Mario 3D World that's what you're missing but you know again do you want to pay three what would that be about $300 system plus game just wait the price will come down do you want to pay $300 to be the coolest kid on the block
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: More news.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I do have another bit of news.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this actually came to me by means of one of my friends who I met through Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have to give you the story of how I met her later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trading porn pics?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just here for the gifts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was at the Russian market and saw one of their free publications with someone's Homestuck fan art on it on the cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the article that it was advertising had nothing to do with Homestuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I found out who did it, messaged her, and mailed her the magazine in Australia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's something.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been chatting off and on back.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a really good artist.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's done a thank you pic for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a really, really good artist.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she linked me this story about how the South Australian government is doing an anti-gaming campaign that has a little girl with shades on at a poker table looking at her iPad saying, gambling starts with games.
[SPEAKER_05]: and basically what they're trying to do is I think it has more to do with the Facebook style and casual games, the online poker and the microtransaction type games but they have a site that's called nogame.sa.gov.au which I hate giving it anything but go look at it and laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: so basically it's supposed to say it's wanting to add an MA 15 plus to any game that includes simulated gambling meaning slot machines a card mechanics even what was the last Pokemon games Diamond and Pearl had like a slot machine thing in them didn't they I don't remember
[SPEAKER_05]: or, you know, any game that has some kind of variety of anything that could be, you know, construed as gambling.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're trying to get this bit of a... Is Pachinko considered gambling?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Nintendo Land has the Pachinko in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's totally gambling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, Pachinko technically is gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... Final Fantasy X-2 has, like, Casino Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, look at Sonic the Hedgehog 2 Casino Night Zone Which was like the best zone in the whole game I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: MM2K in chat at live.vognetwork.com says Australian government hates games It sure seems that way
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Ron Curry, who is the CEO of Interactive Games and Entertainment Association, has gone out saying that the view is supported by the fact that there was no consultation with an industry lead in the lead up to this policy announcement and the subsequent awareness campaign, meaning that they haven't even reached out to work with the companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just going on a broad generalization.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, the way that this was linked to me is, have you seen this fuckery?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's not exactly what, you know, how she said it, but it was pretty much the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she was going on to explain how there's a lot of revenue in South Australia comes from slot machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a big problem with gambling because, and I believe they're called pokies there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're blaming games for that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just, out of curiosity, I wanted to know, because you know, right here in the States right now, everybody's talking about mega millions, because the lottery is up to like $500 million, and even I'm buying a lotto ticket, that says something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I usually don't pay the idiot tax, as my mom calls it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gonna pay the idiot tax, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, when you buy the lottery tickets, you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, she wouldn't be saying that if you won.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I win, and we see what home she gets put in, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let her retire in Boca.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, as she also says, it costs a dollar to dream these days, doesn't it, Rab?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, the reason why I bring that up is I was curious, does Australia have the lottery?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't know much about the culture there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does Australia have lottery?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe some chatters can set me straight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if we have any Aussies in chat tonight, but I'm looking at Wikipedia, which I always love to go to to look up information.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like there's some different types of Australian lotteries, kind of depending about where you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's
[SPEAKER_02]: Tats has a lottery in Victoria, Tasmania, and the Australian Capital Territory in the Northern Territory.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's some state-owned, including the South Australian lotteries.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the reason why I bring that up is like, well, okay, wait a minute, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: The government has a sanctioned lottery system, yet we're going to pinpoint video games as don't play games because it'll lead to gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's caused, you know, there have been political parties formed to, you know, to get rid of the legalized gambling.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so if people are having such a big problem with it to the point that they're trying to censor games to...
[SPEAKER_05]: to prevent that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't they just pass the legislation and get rid of the machines or else regulate them a lot harder than they are now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the other side of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They get a lot of money from those machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like in Mississippi after Katrina because they didn't want the casinos on Mississippi soil so they were on barges.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then right after Katrina hit and the casinos were like we're going to leave because we're not going to build them on barges for the next hurricane to knock us over Mississippi changed their laws really quickly so that they could keep that source of revenue and keep all those jobs in Biloxi
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, yeah, it's, it's obviously if you know somebody that's addicted to gambling, you know, that's a real thing, but there's lots of, you can get addicted to anything, you know, you can get addicted to video games and that's dangerous too, you know, but I just don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's excessive compulsive behavior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, if you're gonna, I like gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did video games cause that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate gambling I also put a limit on my gambling like if I go to Reno or something I usually say okay $100 in fun money that's how much I would spend on a concert ticket to go see a AAA concert or you know a night out with drinks for Alan and I you know see
[SPEAKER_05]: Your limit is about 10 times more than my limit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the only times I have ever gone gambling with a purpose is when I had 50 cents and needed cab money and made myself $15.
[SPEAKER_02]: YYR in chat says, Gambling video games might cause gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just weird for me to say that, oh, because they played it in the game, they got addicted to gambling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if they were wired for that anyway, wouldn't just playing gambling kind of get them into that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It has to do with... I kind of have a problem with calling certain behaviors an addiction, except they do give that same sort of chemical response.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in that case, you're creating your own drug by performing the action.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so it comes, the only way to break that is to either remove the ability to do the action or remove the positive sensation that comes from the action.
[SPEAKER_05]: But even with losing money, losing friends, suffering financial difficulties because of the reward, the behavior, it doesn't stop that feeling of pleasure that somebody gets from participating in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is why you have people that are addicted to gambling.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have people that are addicted to gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have people who are pathological house cleaners.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all the same kind of pleasure response that comes from continued action.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my mother.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mother will follow you in the house with a vacuum cleaner.
[SPEAKER_02]: She will.
[SPEAKER_02]: No joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have literally caught her doing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a cup of coffee and I sat it on her counter or whatever and I was talking and talking and then I picked it up and put the cup away in the sink and she came in right behind me and wiped down the counter.
[SPEAKER_05]: but it's I'm trying to there's and for a lot of people you know I'm trying to get back to what I was trying to say with this too is that instead of treating the enabler being the gambling or the gateway as they're calling it the games that have the gambling element they need to treat the the behavior addiction
[SPEAKER_05]: You shouldn't penalize a whole group for something that's a problem of a handful of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you or someone you know got addicted to gambling and video games are to blame for it, we'd love to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Meanwhile, back into the news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds like one of those advertisements for like Ricky Lake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call 1-877-GO-RICKY Did your drag queen dad beat you when you were a child?
[SPEAKER_07]: If so, call us now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That show is such a fucking train wreck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'd be like, oh my god, I'm not getting into this.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'd just stand back and watch like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was always that look of her hand pressed against her face and her jaw dropped like, I can't control what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Ricky, go back to doing Waters movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: The legit best weave pulling of all time came from the Ricky Lake show too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just Google it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ricky Lake weave pulling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fascinating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt says Australian PSA, don't gamble or a dingo will eat your baby I'm sure the Australians that listen to this show greatly appreciate that SSJ100 Matt
[SPEAKER_07]: So what do you expect?
[SPEAKER_07]: When a game service doesn't exactly work like it's supposed to, what are you to do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, you should go on the internet and complain.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, the lawyers come and decide, hey, let's make this into a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_07]: In which case, that's what's happening now with a law firm investigating EA and Battlefield 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Law firm Holzer Holzer and Holzer Holzer and Fistel.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that name, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: LLC is investigating whether EA, I guess they claim that regarding the development and sales of Battlefield 4 and its impact on EA's revenue and projects moving forward, complied with federal security laws.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even know what the hell that means.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I know is people are bitching about Battlefield 4 and that I'm guessing that they're smelling money somewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: That
[SPEAKER_07]: hmm that whole SimCity thing was really fucked up and people were really pissed by that hmm maybe we can get some of the money out of that EA's got money right?
[SPEAKER_07]: EA's got a bit of money I think
[SPEAKER_02]: because they charge us for everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking, though, that this may not necessarily be... If the internet wins this class action lawsuit, we lose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not necessarily for people that are playing the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's for investors basically saying that they misled investors that they knew that Battlefield 4 was going to be a fucked up thing and that they knew that they were going to lose money and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Clever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, seriously, it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Money.
[SPEAKER_07]: They smell money, they're gonna go for the money.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like blood and sharks.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you gonna do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shark is delicious, but you can't eat people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, I know I would eat this game right up if it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who doesn't love the Second Densetsu series?
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you don't know it by that name, perhaps if I said Secret of Mana, remember that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a classic, classic Super Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is sad, because Legend of Mana was kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Mana was pretty balls, but Second Densetsu 3, really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hardcore awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Secret of Evermore, Underrated, I realized it wasn't really part of the same series because it was Square America's game, but Underrated, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Time was really mean to that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, the Of Mana series, I think a lot of us would love to play a new game in that again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there are hints that an unannounced title in the series could be brewing, and this is because of a Christmas album that featured a song from an as-of-yet-unreleased game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The official page for Xmas Collections 2 includes a mention of Second Detsetsu, the series' Japanese name, labeled as Future Project.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, could this be Circle of Mana?
[SPEAKER_02]: Circle of Mana was a Japanese release on iOS and Android devices, which I'm...
[SPEAKER_02]: which is very strange that we don't have that here yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure it's only a matter of time before that's translated and comes out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie instantly picked up her phone and started searching.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only in Japan, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can look and bookmark it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why you jailbreak your devices.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyhow, I know I would love to see a new of Mana game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really hope that is something that's in the pipeline for oh, wouldn't that be an awesome PlayStation 4 game?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think there could be any truth here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it's just circle of mana?
[SPEAKER_05]: I need new pants.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, unfortunately, will have to put her phone down to find the game that she's not going to be able to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week, you guys email us mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura is going to dive into the mailbag head first and find an email that she thinks, hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one's twitching.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one should be read on air because if I don't read it, we'll get another email next week chewing me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only a couple emails this week, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just one or two, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, three, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let me get this straight.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys do a video game podcast, but you couldn't be bothered to actually watch a video game's award show.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you were able to do a little Monday morning quarterbacking and bash the show none of you watched.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I didn't bash anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I watched the live stream and it was better than the usual schtick you see in award shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead of making a big deal about the subjective superlatives of best this and that, the show is bringing gamers the previews of upcoming games, something all gamers are normally excited to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: And bashing Joel is just mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was hired to do a job and I thought he earned his pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Calling him transphobic was unfairly judgmental considering you didn't watch the show and everything you heard about it was taken out of context.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, you do have a right to your opinion, but next time do your homework.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems a little odd and disappointing that not one of you took the time to watch the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sincerely, Narc.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember saying anything about the guy because I didn't watch it and I didn't have anything to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't watch it, and I was recanting things that I read across the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that people were offended at some of the things that Joel McHale said, whether you weren't or not, other people were.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I thought I was defending him, but that was me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, this guy's welcome to his opinion, but I kind of have a problem with the... He says, because you guys have a video game podcast, you should watch this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's something I don't care about watching, I don't have to watch anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I listen to other independent podcasts that do their award shows, and I'm curious what they have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: People like you and me that do their own shows, and I read websites.
[SPEAKER_02]: What makes this any more or less of a deal than those?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was not proven to me in the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I heard in there was, oh, they have previews of new games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did look at all of those on YouTube after.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if Joel was so great, why did they excise him completely from the TV version?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I watched part of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't watch the whole thing because I had things to do that day, but I did catch part of it and I commented on the part I saw as well as the recaps I saw on YouTube, which I know were cleverly edited together.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I was going to be perfectly honest about it, I've been so busy with school and other stuff, I actually didn't even know it was on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, like I said, I have my feelings about what I've heard from that, but I don't care either way.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you play a musical instrument, are you required to watch the Grammys?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you make home movies, are you required to watch the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kind of throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm challenging because obviously this guy puts VGX up on a pedestal, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're allowed to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe we were too harsh on things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think his criticism is that we're criticizing the show, yet we didn't watch the entire show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my God, if I had to watch that entire show, I'd be tearing my hair out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was very slow paced.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to explain two things last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: One, what I heard everybody else saying because, yeah, of course I'm going to say, oh, this is the feeling I was getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I read this person's blog that was very upset over the joke that Joel McHale said because this was a transgender person themselves that was very upset at the joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, I was going to communicate that I heard some people were pretty pissed off at this joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm telling you why I don't watch it because I don't see the reason to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not like I can sit here on a video game show and just flat out say, which is the honest truth, that I didn't care about the fact that there was an award show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't care who won and I didn't care about watching it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't make good radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love video games You, the emailer, love video games The chatters that are here love video games DarkSakura and Loki love video games That is why we do a video game podcast End For the record, I really didn't care
[SPEAKER_02]: No, and I don't want to sound combative or anything, although this email was pretty pointed, because everybody does have a right to their opinion, and I can get where you're kind of like, well, don't shut your yap if you're going to comment on something you didn't even watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's what's going on out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to comment on it somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is a big human nature kind of thing, at least amongst the average neurotypical human being.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one likes to hear when someone does not like something that they like.
[SPEAKER_02]: A very good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: however, it must be understood that sometimes you may like something and other people either will not like it or don't give a shit about it you have to live with that
[SPEAKER_02]: You wrote that article on VOG this week all about Homestuck, which is something... Well, but to be fair, that's something plenty of people have judged without really looking at it themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would that be accurate to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd say so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that could be plenty because some of the cosplayers have been boneheads, and you touched on that in the article.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, you know, sometimes it's people giving it a bad image and so forth, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: When I was looking for graphics, because I wanted a good background to do the banner from, I actually found a write-up by a mother who had just thought it was the crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: She wasn't interested in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She thought it was corrupting her kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then actually took the time to sit and go through the entire thing and ended up loving the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, a mom probably in her 50s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ended up really liking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, already a sci-fi fan found things that she could relate to in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that, you know, maybe if I had sat down and watched it, then maybe I would have liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I didn't care enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I didn't bash it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I bashed it, did I?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chris109 in our chatroom says, Video games rule.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games rule.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Chris109 says, Opinions.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are awesome, yet cause issues because people misunderstand it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to say thank you for the email, and I think if people think we need to be called out on something, then do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tone is going to be very important in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we get an email that says, Fuck you, you fucking fuck, then we're probably not going to respond to that in kind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's probably one of my emails.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, well, it goes back to that Facebook comment from a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, as long as you do it respectfully, we'll give you, you know, we'll have a respectful dialogue.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then at the end of the day, have a beer and play some games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that the email was disrespectful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a little bit pointed, but I understand why there's anger.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I also think that at the same time, just because, and this is something I kind of wished I'd put in my article too, and I do understand that if you're not going to watch something, it doesn't put you in a position to bash it.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it doesn't mean that you can't take a community-wide opinion and report on it, which is what we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: well okay let's be real though yes I have heard plenty of Nickelback unfortunately and all that's just I think we can all agree Nickelback sucks all right next email sorry
[SPEAKER_05]: Seasons Greetings and Salutations, OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love when people say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what movie that line came from?
[SPEAKER_05]: Heathers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Greetings and Salutations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Heathers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That movie is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to watch that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Had Shannon Doherty in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So was Winona Ryder.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Winona Ryder.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want her to be my sister or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: When Winona Ryder showed up... My dream family is like George Takei as my daddy and Winona Ryder as like my cool older sister.
[SPEAKER_02]: Betty White as your grandma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Betty White is my grandmother.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: When Winona Ryder showed up in Star Trek, I was so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, and then they cut like half her scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Firstly, I hope Rob is recovering from the VOG plague.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, I heard it affect Jess from USL, then Shane from Horde House, now Alan and Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: To prevent yourselves from getting the plague, all VOG members should perform the anti-VOG plague ritual.
[SPEAKER_05]: It involves a dead hippo, burnt out TV tubes, short bits of string, and fire-breathing squirrel.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel a lot better today than I did yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a temperature and I'm not congested in the head.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just I have stuffiness.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll be back to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just sucks to be sick on a weekend when I had social stuff planned.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love everybody in the chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chris1 and I know they really suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, the reason I am emailing you all is because this week has been a significant week for my mobile gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the past few months, I've been playing a mobile game called Jurassic Park Builder.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically your run-of-the-mill sim game involving filling your park with dinosaurs and leveling them to create cash.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: With that being said, have you ever encountered an update on a non-MMO game that changed the very nature of the original game?
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you feel about those changes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not so sincerely, Degenerate Johnny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a really tough question because in this day and age, I mean, we're used to the whole patching and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, like, you know, that's something new in the past 10 years where games are updated like that and changed like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's only new since iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly can't think of anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mortal Kombat 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: From the beta versions to the new ones because you lost your infinite combos as they tweak stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luminous on the iPhone actually made it playable because the first version was awful but then they actually changed the control scheme and it's actually playable that was a big one let me say this though, I'll answer the question with this so I'm going to take it a slightly different direction, sorry about it but back in the day I remember when sequels would go in really random directions
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Zelda 2 Right, Zelda 2 for better or worse I did a Let's Remember this week, plug plug On my YouTube channel, Rob Roberts Plays YouTube.com slash Rob Roberts Plays, plug plug But I did a Let's Remember for the game Donkey Kong 3 Yes, that one was bizarre Wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was very bizarre Because it was such a departure And I even talked about this in the video Such a departure from Donkey Kong and Donkey Kong Jr.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because those two were platformers Although I think it had more in common with Jr.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Donkey Kong 3 was a fucking shooter game
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but... Disguised as Donkey, with the Donkey Kong skin on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the otherwise look of the game, I think, had more in common with Junior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for the fact that... The aesthetic was the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stanley disappeared, never to be seen again, except in obscure references in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think was in a Game & Watch game but that's really it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think about like back in the NES games sometimes sequels were really radical departures from the original games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even like Castlevania 2 really played I mean sure it was still the whole like jump and whip and all that type of stuff that the first game had.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what a terrible night for a curse.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the first game was more of an arcade game where the second game was more of an adventure you know backdrop.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was more of an annoying game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the sequel though.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3 was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, that's the best we can do with the answers there.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, SSJ100 Matt says that Heathers is going to be an off-Broadway show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was going to say in chat as well, Ragenator talking about Heathers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ragenator in chat says, Heathers also gave us the line, Well, fuck me gently with a chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: It also gave us the line, Big fun was one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I love my dead gay son.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a fan of Orange Launch Radio, you do need to watch the movie Heathers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you seen the movie Heathers, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Please tell me you've seen Heathers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're killing me!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the best movie!
[SPEAKER_05]: It also was like
[SPEAKER_02]: They used to play it on Comedy Central like every other day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great pate, but I really must dash if I'm going to meet that funeral.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Watch Heathers this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll thank us later.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's the movie that got Que Sera Sera stuck in my head every time someone says the name Heather.
[SPEAKER_05]: Que Sera Sera Anyway, last email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear Orange Lounge Radio, with the release of some less than stellar Wii U and Super Mario 3D World sales figures this week, this past week, sorry, it has been provided yet another excuse for doom and gloom for the console.
[SPEAKER_05]: this led me to wonder when exactly sales figures started mattering to people who aren't investors more than liking the games of the systems that were being played I myself have loved my Wii U since release date and it has absolutely changed how gaming has fit into my life my boyfriend has become an avid gamer due to a mixture of first party titles and indie releases that he would never have bothered playing elsewhere the system never fails to create memories at parties and Nintendo's mastery of the couch co-op style of gameplay is still as evident as ever
[SPEAKER_05]: but even loving the system as much as I do I am still given pause to doubt myself when I hear people focus so heavily on something as impersonal as sales data as something that should speak to the quality of a system
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: so my question to you is this now that companies make such public displays of game sales and sales data for gaming related products are so easy to locate is liking a product enough I'm always willing to speak well for titles I enjoy never to the exclusion of others whenever the topic arises but is there something else that can be done to improve the image of products such as Super Mario 3D World which will likely have its spectacular reviews overshadowed by being one of the lowest selling 3D Mario titles ever
[SPEAKER_02]: was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: thank you for the entertainment you provide each week and Daniel because I don't say last names on there I think that was a good email and thank you for that and thank you for your masterful grammar sales shouldn't matter to your enjoyment of the game
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think, don't we all, I mean, Oh, for fuck's sake, I like Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_02]: But haven't we talked about this on a previous show as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's those cult games that maybe not everybody necessarily played, but you love, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I talked about, there's a great card game called Cold Sept that's like Monopoly meets Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But like, they don't sell beans here.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I think they didn't even come out with a 3DS version here because those games didn't sell very well, which was a tragedy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, yeah, you should like what you're going to like.
[SPEAKER_05]: There should be no shame in your game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love bad movies better than some of the top rated Oscar winning movies ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked up Barbarella recently and I fucking love that movie because Jane Fonda was hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: It shouldn't be a guilty pleasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It should just be a pleasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you love it, fucking love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter how well or how niche or how many copies is sold or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like what you like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's a lot of... Well, it's the whole thing about some people feel that theirs has to be the best, that theirs is better than everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that whole fanboyism.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, in the chat?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that awesome...
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you, Awesome Unicorn, because I also read grammar and etymology books for fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should change your nick to Awesome Emailing Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: You made me lose my tangent with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lose my thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Barbarella, Psychedella.
[SPEAKER_02]: But people should play whatever they want and like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, the fanboyism.
[SPEAKER_02]: People will use sales figures and wield it as a weapon as something like, look at what's going on with PlayStation 4 and Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're both selling well.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still the fanboys are going to say, oh, well, but it's because the number of regions this is selling in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's because of, you know, such and such.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be fair, we've asked those same questions on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's because we know there's spin going into this from Microsoft and Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we are kind of curious, like, which one is selling a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that doesn't make the other system worse necessarily.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a Wii U owner.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like my Wii U an awful lot even though I didn't necessarily care for the wonderful 101 and I'm gonna hear shit about that non-stop this week but I love Mario 3D World it is one of my top five games of the year for sure and I know Nintendo's gonna put out some great stuff for it in 2014 and there are more reasons to buy a Wii U right now than there are to buy a PlayStation 4 or Xbox One
[SPEAKER_02]: Will that be the same story in 2014?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm a little worried about for Nintendo's sake.
[SPEAKER_02]: But 3DS will keep them afloat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like whatever you're going to like.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's lots of great games to justify a Wii U purchase.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love is not wrong, but it can sometimes be really gross and sticky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yerp.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is it for emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com And by the way, I would like to go back and still thank NARP for the email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for being honest with us and making your opinion known.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said thank you for that email as well, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_05]: But I didn't say thank you and I'm saying thank you so he doesn't think I'm a total bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm only a 95% bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you to Jenner and Johnny too because I don't think we thanked him for the email either.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank you Unicorn Friend with the great grammar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, thank you to everybody who takes the time out of the week to say hello to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank you to anybody else who loves Xanadu and Barbarella because those are the two best movies ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: You watched them at my bachelorette party.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we were eating jello shots.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is this fuckery?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was awesome because I fucking love those movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, then again, I love showgirls and that's my Halloween tradition is to watch showgirls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which we did at my house and drank wine and watched showgirls and it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Miss Monet was with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is she a gamer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we need to get her on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think she is.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we should have her on the show anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should.
[SPEAKER_02]: She can teach a pole dancing class during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our friend Monet is a pole dancer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to work with Monet, which I knew Monet before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew Rob, and I knew Monet separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I found out that they knew each other.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like my circle of Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's Kat and... Yeah, Kat through Rocky.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you guys know Mystique.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: For my birthday party last year, Monet had a pole dancing class.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about this on Horde House because Extifer came to the pole dancing class and he was really good at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was so random.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently him and Monet ran into each other at a postal service concert and they remembered each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: The world is such a small, funny place sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was mention on my Facebook about doing a Cards Against Humanity session.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been getting my 12 days of Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, this is too much talking about people that our listeners don't know, so we need to get into the F- We need to introduce our listeners to these people.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to get into the F-U's of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, F-U's of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_05]: F-U to the sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: F-U to the plague.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will follow her because I have the exact same FU FU to the fact that I got sick especially when I had a weekend where I actually had a bunch of stuff planned I was supposed to go wine tasting with friends this weekend who drove up from out of town and I couldn't fucking go but they did the most adorable thing for me and I just love friends hugs and kisses if you guys are out there listening
[SPEAKER_02]: and I was supposed to go to a big holiday party with some of my friends here locally and that was supposed to be Friday night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Couldn't go because I was sick and it's rude to go to a dinner party when you're sick and cough on all the food.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, boo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just F'ed to the fact that I still have to heal up for a while before I can actually eat real food.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's giving FUs tonight to Conditions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a theme tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should puree some turkey.
[SPEAKER_07]: And why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's give an FU to Volition and Deep Silver for their fucking broken-ass game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I have another FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it goes to you and Victoria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: For Frivalo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's great wine, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I bought a bottle, and normally I'm not a sweet wine person.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I described this to Victoria, it tastes like angels pissed in my cup.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frivolo's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That winery should pay me money for that endorsement.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the record, don't buy it at Whole Foods.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go to Total Wine because it's four bucks cheaper.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or just go to the winery.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you live here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've never taken me.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to take me, Rob, next time you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else do I want to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Twitter topics and the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR and our username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I've got to admit, I'm a little bit worried.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby didn't have a single caller tonight on his show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we going to get people to call into Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming up in a moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, some quick stories here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Oculus Rift is moving along.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just received $75 million in funding from the venture capital firm Andresen Horowitz, led by Mark Anderson Horowitz.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why does it seem like there's too many, or Andreessen?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's too many letters in these words.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like they have extra E's in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, and he's the founder of Netscape.
[SPEAKER_07]: Man, I remember Netscape.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the browser to go to before Firefox.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Netscape was the bomb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dial into Prodigy, then fire up Netscape.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what we used to call it back when I was on AOL because there was a big rivalry?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nutscape.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Prodigy, I mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: We called it Buttigy.
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew,
[SPEAKER_07]: uh yes my first website was designed in Netscape that shit was the bomb um so anyways so they um apparently they liked what they saw and you know I'm sure 75 million dollars in funding can only help um they've already secured I guess previously 16 million dollars in the first round of funding in June so I'm very uh very curious to see what happens hopefully one day I will have an Oculus Rift myself but uh
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting closer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting closer to this total immersion future or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwolf in our chat room says, On Prodigy, we just called AOL, AOL because that was insulting enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I remember AOL when it was DOS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when it was free because they kept sending you those 30 day trials No, I remember having a phish account I didn't phish it either I remember when AOL was Quantum Link on the Commodore 64 and yeah, I used to dial into BBSs on my 300 baud modem It's hardcore, bitches, hardcore
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I still have my same, when they went to where you could have your free accounts, I actually still have the same username on my AIM from that account.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I hide so no one can find me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, wait a minute, now you're going to get tons of AOL instant messages.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who uses instant messenger anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Me and Becky and Victoria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: A few people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never use it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of the people are people I've been friends with from my old AOL days.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't use Facebook Messenger either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a messenger that I prefer but even then I only talk to like two people on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only keep AIM up because there's maybe like a handful of people and sometimes some of my friends from Alabama are on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all text messages now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of where people went.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's easier to type.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, one more story for you guys, and don't read too much into this, but it's very exciting to know that Nintendo has renewed the trademark for Metroid Prime.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of people are doing, you know, shaking and crying because, ooh, this means there's going to be a new Metroid Prime on Wii U.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there might be.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it would certainly make a lot of sense for Retro to go and do another Metroid Prime game for the Wii U. But we do know that the trademark was renewed on August 13, 2013, probably just to protect, you know, the games that already exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: because you know Nintendo loves to package up its old shit eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on the next Nintendo console, we'll probably have GameCube games and Wii games downloadable.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, they just want to keep that trademark out there for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: But wouldn't it be nice to have another Metroid Prime game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that will be their ace in the hole at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's open.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use your name on Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can give us a call right now if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's anything you want to share or talk about maybe that we didn't bring up or something we did bring up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Give us a call and we will talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, I'm going to go to Twitter topics and see if Loki has any last minute stories or Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't really have anything at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, good thing the phone is ringing and we can actually go to some calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: The only one with the fastest internet finger in the whole wide internet chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're very good at this, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I do try.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are some topics I do want to cover real quick, and I got to be on my merry little way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I feel with Loki, with the whole dentist thing, because once I went to, I have my
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 Impacted Teeth Pulled Out Before I Had To Do An 8 Hour Shift At Work Oh God I'm Thinking Okay Get It Done Drop Off The Meds Go To Work Won't Be That Big Of A Deal 20 Minutes Into My Shift I'm Like It Hurts It Hurts
[SPEAKER_06]: Take my break, grab the meds.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was pretty much floating on cloud nine for the next eight hours after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my, how did you even work a shift on those?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe you didn't just somehow get the day off or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a high tolerance for pain.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was that time that I dislocated my knee and they gave me Tylenol 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: They gave me a weak prescription.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only needed it for one day.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole YouTube debacle about them flagging videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel those users' pains because some of my videos get flagged as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of our OLR episodes that have been posted on YouTube are getting flagged, and it's making me question if we should continue to do it, to be honest, because it was all a kind of experiment anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's been a couple people who have been very vocal about their support of the YouTube posting, so I am trying to stick it out for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so very nice that they welcome us with open arms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, you fucking stole that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you make that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how I feel, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, sorry, Rama.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool, it's cool, because the issue is...
[SPEAKER_06]: With my videos, the Japanese come to make the albums of Sony, EMI, and them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They will have the videos flagged because us videographers who record masquerades, they realize we didn't get permission to use their music in the video, and I'm like,
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't put the song there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was part of the skit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was part of the musical or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just put back, I just, under fair use, leave me alone, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Worst case scenario, some countries can't see my videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still, that's so irritating to even have to go through that, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole 38 Studios bid, I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will give 38 Studios...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair value for all their franchises.
$20.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe I'm being more than fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not even the price of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe it is now, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be the price of the game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just thinking there's not a lot of call out there for a sequel to Kingdoms of Amalur.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I know some people really liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like I heard nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like it was a crap game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was decent from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm actually kind of surprised no one wants the sequel rights.
[SPEAKER_02]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and last thing before I get out of here, I am returning to my Pokemon roots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you going back to red and blue, or what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing the game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked up a copy of Y. You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The new 3DS games are really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you having fun with it so far?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's still sealed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I told myself I am not unwrapping Y till I finish A Link Between Worlds.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fair, because I was going to say, if you're going to sit there with an unopened copy of the game, I will sick Shane Alinko on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he will use his powers.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I'm fairly certain that Dan's gifting me that for a holiday mess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting X. I told him I wanted X. So you'll have somebody to trade Pokemans with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only bought the game for one reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toys R Us had it on sale last week for $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got Best Buy to price match it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a steal for that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I did with my Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got it for $10 cheaper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then everyone on my Facebook is like, can I get it for X?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I get it for X?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take it in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ask them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple of people have said...
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Buy was able to price match it for X as well because they're practically the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they are the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Ranma, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: An anime jam session.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tuesday nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, one more thing before I get out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next week, I do believe, is the 24th for our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be our final show of the holiday before we take a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be doing the anime jam session or getting crunked Christmas Eve special.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are going live on Christmas Eve?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's impressive.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are hardcore.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because we'd rather get drunk with our friends and guests than our own families because if we're with our families, we're going to drink anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I have plans with my own family on Christmas Eve, but if I get back in time, I'll join y'all for a round.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm probably going to have to drink to make it through our Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't want to spend Christmas with your family, spend Christmas with the drunken bastards at Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have a great show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you still have one more show before that because this week coming up is the 17th.
[SPEAKER_06]: This week, yeah, we have a lot of stuff coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then that following week, all bets are off.
[SPEAKER_02]: All bets are off.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: This week is the Horde House holiday special, and I'm going to tell you it's a doozy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on to your butts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I only have one thing to say about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: May the fierce be with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a Beyonce day.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma doesn't like Beyonce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: May be Jesus be with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or use your name on Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, that's 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we have another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey Ragenator, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, two things.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was going to do a rant about the whole YouTube group I have, but since that's going to take a little while, I just want to get the quick thing out of the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Since I'm feeling a little generous, I'm going to do a little game giveaway, a Steam game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, in fact, this weekend, since it was a steam sale on DinoDA, where the game was basically $2 for a single copy or a four-pack for $6, I can't figure what the hell.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pick up the four-pack, keep a copy for myself, give away $8.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's Santinator tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight he's Santinator.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I can't figure what the hell.
[SPEAKER_00]: Give away one of the copies of the game tonight on OR.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what we'll do is, well, I'm going to ask a question directly in chat, that way you guys don't get an unfair advantage because of the delay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now the first person that answers the question directly, go ahead and shout the answer out in
[SPEAKER_00]: No, in text, in chat, who will get the game?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm posting it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to let the chatters have it, but I'm almost positive I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it have to do with cards?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't say.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's your hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you wanted to rant a little bit on the YouTube thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I'm going to ask you to try to keep it a little bit concise because we do want to end the show at a reasonable hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's your thoughts on the YouTube thing?
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: On one hand, I know that companies be it Nintendo or Valve or Microsoft, whoever, yeah, they would like to protect their IPs.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's understandable, but at the same time, you know, fans being Bobby Blackwell, yourself, me, whoever, we like these games, we want to support games, and we want to promote the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And what we do is show off these games, and
[SPEAKER_00]: We're effectively giving these games free publicity.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're doing PR for these games and the game manufacturers are not paying us one red cent for this promotion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me ask you this though, Rachel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to interrupt you real quick just to ask a tough question because, you know, yes, we're giving the games free publicity, but doesn't a game maker have a right to say, I don't want that publicity?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's one way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't look at it that way or consider it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time, I can't figure out why a company wouldn't want free publicity for the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I already mentioned that assuming that the game isn't crap, they want publicity for the games because usually they'll get extra sales.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like Casey Point earlier this year, Bobby Blackwell,
[SPEAKER_00]: On Twitch, he had showed off Sacred Citadel, which is the Go Force and Conquer game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I saw his stream and I liked the game, bought the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, what was it, Deep Silver that put the game out?
[SPEAKER_00]: They made $15 off of me because of their stream.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it's when you have these other websites like 4Gamer or Machinima or whatever and they're the ones that I get content ID matched with.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not right because it wasn't their stuff to content match in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't their game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rage Leader, I got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let us know though in chat who ends up winning that code and we will talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, have a nice night
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to some of the tweets that we got tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Redertainment sent us a tweet that we did touch on earlier in the show, but just to mention it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Read Only Memories Kickstarter got funded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I noticed MidBoss Games even retweeted our tweet that we were going live tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're supporting us just like we supported.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys rule!
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling the love.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am feeling the love.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just you wait for Gamer X 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole lot of you are getting glomped.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: If I get to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll make it work out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Rob, you have to cosplay with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, if I lose 20 pounds, then I will cosplay with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you with something hard and sandpapery.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would invite you to go to the gym with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: you know I go to the other gym I know you do but I can get you into my gym alright anyway we'll talk later about that meanwhile we got some tweets if my fat ass could lose 20 pounds you could do it easy no fat shaming we shouldn't fat shame but I can say I'm fat if I want to but I saw that video this week but anyway you know what I feel for health reasons I feel I know I can be better have a better body than the one I'm at you know what as long as you love you
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I can do I do love me but I know I can do better all right anyway um moving on awkward talk moving on uh we have some tweets SSU and Hunter Matt guy trollingly applies to a college football coaching job citing his years of Madden and NCAAF playing do you do you think that do you think that we would be eligible for a job at a gaming company just because we did this podcast
[SPEAKER_02]: I will actually, I will say, and I think I've talked about this on the show, I'm not going to tell you who, but twice I've applied for positions with gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them I actually was really close with and I decided to, because I would have had to relocate and I would have had to stop doing the show and everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I decided to not go forward with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to tell you what it was, but you guys know I am a corporate teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I do during the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a corporate teaching job with a video game company.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it would have been really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was just the relocation kind of like I couldn't do it because of where they wanted me to go, you know, would have been tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: but um yeah so um but yeah I mean like you know but but does the fact that we do a podcast mean we should work for video game companies not necessarily yes well I mean if it's graphic design then that for you that's good yeah Loki does sales you know so you know maybe that type of stuff would be good for him I would love to do design for like digital manuals and that type of thing
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt says, I've cited OLR in a job interview once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't get the job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've used people for references, though, as people have listed Orange Lounge Radio as jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't you do that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: You put OLR down and me as a professional contact?
[SPEAKER_05]: I put OLR down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you were already one of my references.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I put OLR down as a client for freelance design.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I put myself down as art director for VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have used it as an example of management skills, doing this show and keeping you two in line.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: We all help each other out, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had one other tweet here I wanted to read.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was from Eric RPG sent us a tweet, and it was just a link over to a Kickstarter for Grapple Knight is another Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm assuming this is a Kickstarter he's behind.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get her back on the show for sure at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you remember our buddy?
[SPEAKER_02]: She came on the show right after it was announced she was going to be on the Tester 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our buddy Asuka was on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, funny enough, we didn't know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: She called in just out of the blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't arrange the interview or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: She knew a listener of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope Stan's still listening if he's out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for hooking that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she called into the show one night and it happened to be the week before she got kicked off the Tester 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, she was very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she was very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a lot of fun with her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's on the King of the Nerds season two.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, girl, I know you can't talk about if you won or lost the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm like, win or lose, you have been on the Tester and King of Nerds.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are the nerdiest reality show contestant of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, I just thought that was hilarious that she's on that show now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll have her back to talk about that, which sounds like Ranma saying, fuck King of the Nerds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he'll be really excited for that interview then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Redertainment says she's on actual TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other stuff I wanted to mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peeker Uno tweeted the show and said, I missed last week's topic, but one of my favorite TV programs was Nightmare, a virtual reality RPG game show in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, I don't think we're getting any other calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL, bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm going to go ahead and close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one last bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead, and then we'll close up shop for tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been actually waiting for this to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duke Nukem 3D Megaton Edition has now added Steam Workshop support.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a level editor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, does it have multiplayer play yet online?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm assuming if it has the level.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm surprised it doesn't if it already.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a bombshell announcement I could use.
[SPEAKER_07]: 60 maps for download already.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're adding their own rating system and mini forum.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the game's also 75% off until tomorrow, which means I'm going to have to buy it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I just realized something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to check Drunken Robot Pornography.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: To see if they've updated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because remember, I've still been playing the alpha.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me too with Audio Surf 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been getting little updates here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I've got my Steam card so I can buy... Yeah, I think you're going to have to buy the game being it's only $2.49.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's only $2.49.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shadow Warrior and Duke Nukem 3D together, $3.74.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tempting, tempting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys so much for listening to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay in here for the whole show, the whole way through for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope we could entertain you during your day with our chatter about video games wherever you're listening to us, whether you're here live Sunday night just chilling with our show or if you're listening to us on your commute or at your workday on Monday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much for taking the time out to listen to Orange Launch Radio and supporting the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Support independent broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's so many hardworking people like us out there that do this just for the love of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please go forth and download lots of indie podcasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, word of mouth is key to the success of this show because there's so many of these big corporate podcasts that have much money in their pockets that can buy the promotion and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So all we ask, if you enjoy the show, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not as cute as us.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're very pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're super adorable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are the most prettiest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys once again for checking out the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave a nice review.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you wouldn't mind saying a nice word on iTunes reviews, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Stitcher reviews are hugely helpful too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I directly attribute the increase we've had in our exposure on Stitcher to those of you that are taking the time to write reviews.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I don't know what else to say thank you guys again for listening you guys are great and have a great holiday season let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts Loki your final thought for tonight you have another game to play now
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that, Duke Nukem?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it's two games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duke Nukem and Shadow Warrior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we'll work on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought for tonight is I may just have to get that Grand Theft Auto 5 on sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Loki might have finally broke me.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wouldn't let me buy you a fractal on my Steam app, so I have to do it when I get home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, shucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you're worth the $7.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's always... I love you more than Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: He only spent $3 on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I spent $7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, what?
$3?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to spend $3 on me?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have gotten you fractal if you didn't already have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave us reviews that are nice and sweet because we're cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: To paraphrase, we're OLR and we're pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: all right well thank you guys again and Bobby too have a wonderful week Bobby is especially pretty all the VOG shows damn it we're all pretty and all your all the indie shows you listen to I mean there's there's lots of great ones out there I know a lot of you support various indie shows I know a lot of you listen to the shows over on all games they would love to have your support with Stitcher Reviews as well I know a lot of you maybe like Gamer Tag Radio and some of these shows that have been on like ages like we have they all appreciate the support
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I'm just throwing it out there, I'm actually planning on doing a Let's Draw series.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what would that be?
[SPEAKER_02]: You just draw?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, pretty much, I get votes for a character that someone wants to see me draw, and I will do one once a month and give it away as a freebie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little community.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gather round.
[SPEAKER_05]: So instead of a let's play, it's a let's draw.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't have to worry about people breathing on my shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's just like Bob Ross, but they're bitchy little clouds.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: That came up in my oil painting class last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, I can't be like Bob Ross.
[SPEAKER_05]: My clouds are a little angrier than his.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, so are they fussy little clouds?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're fussy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we hope you and your bitchy little clouds have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same bat time, same bat channel here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next week!