[SPEAKER_04]: It's a videotape!
[SPEAKER_04]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_14]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Our live talk program begins now.
Boring!
[SPEAKER_03]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hide Orange Lounge radio for the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_13]: My kind of people, and assholes.
[SPEAKER_13]: One.
[SPEAKER_13]: Disco.
[SPEAKER_10]: Misfit by that much.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's Dr. Evil's cat.
[SPEAKER_13]: How can you tell?
[SPEAKER_02]: I never forget a pussy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like, if I may, to take you on a strange journey.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, I hate nature, I just wish the world would explode, and then I could take over hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sky, do I look like the weather girl?
[SPEAKER_17]: Really?
[SPEAKER_17]: Everything alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, two corpses, everything's fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are live, and this is episode number 19 for November the Tenured, is the way I wrote it on the script here, whoops, November Tenured.
[SPEAKER_08]: November 10th of 2002.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hee hee, time for a dive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's been a long-ass weekend, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're tuned into the Bimani Scene's most shafted radio station of all things Bimani.
[SPEAKER_08]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm more on the funny part.
[SPEAKER_08]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're coming to take me away, ha-ha, they're coming to take me away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say hello also to our newest co-host.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although he has been here since the beginning, he's still the noob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say hello to Loki, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the three of us tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dave couldn't get a ride here.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was begging me for one about an hour before the show started.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, he's probably at home with my copy of the freaking sign, that bastard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, do you have some hate mail for Dave?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's wait until the FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be talking to everybody else a little bit more later, but first we're going to take a really quick break.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's as if we didn't talk to tons of people before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you can't tell, my throat's slightly going today.
[SPEAKER_08]: And no, it's not from anything dirty.
[SPEAKER_08]: You sick bastards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, we've got a lot of big announcements.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got local news about the big tournament we had yesterday, but that includes, like everything, we've got some show news, including big changes coming next week, coming to our website, I think, tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: As long as that song doesn't play, we can talk about changes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we won't play the song changes.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have nothing to worry about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, and then an F you to myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: is also coming up later, because I did something very, very bad yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very, very bad and naughty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was a naughty boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not by you, honey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dave is claiming he hasn't taken my sign, so I will have to find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then Dave's off the hook.
[SPEAKER_08]: He just got the blame because he left, and he was easy to blame.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, it was all DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_11]: He blamed you.
[SPEAKER_11]: He pointed the finger at you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which sign?
[SPEAKER_19]: Was it the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Movie, Signs, Signs, Noel Gibson, M. Night Shyamalan Cause Loki gets the hook up and gets the promo stuff So he has a promo of Signs Anyway, let's take a quick break We're gonna play the full remix version of one of the new Max USA License tunes This is a speed remix of Venus with You Leave Me Alone here on Orange Lounge Radio
VOG Network VOG Network
Now tell me why
[SPEAKER_00]: Why don't you wanna try me?
[SPEAKER_00]: Give me a chance I still need you
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio with the Ping Pong Balls.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_20]: Mel cracking up in the car today because I pointed out something to him that I noticed from day one.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one and only Mel B, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or are we talking Melody?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mel B. All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: The QQQ sounds like ducks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you're one of the breaks, we'll play it during the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_20]: But QQQ.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want me to pull up QQQ for the folks?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's listen to some QQQ.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, we're going to pull this up, and I want to take a survey from the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_20]: Tell me if this does or does not sound like ducks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Down to the laughter in the background.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Does it sound like a... See?
[SPEAKER_20]: It sounds like ducks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, it sounds like the music that they play in the electric parade at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like a spiced up version of the chicken dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think it sounds like ducks, but it doesn't sound like chickens.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sharon, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not like ducks, am I right?
[SPEAKER_20]: Say yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: They said work, work, work.
[SPEAKER_18]: They must be a little bit behind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, there is the clown.
[SPEAKER_08]: Demon child laughter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our chat room always full of clowns.
[SPEAKER_08]: or they're comparing it to the dying giraffe noise.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the Ultimate Tack pre-show, by the way, that you heard before we went live just now with every, I think, just damn near every Tack song from DDR and 2DX and then some.
[SPEAKER_20]: I took out Stoic on purpose.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you have against Stoic?
[SPEAKER_20]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stoic isn't a highlight for me either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of a boring video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a stripped down holic.
[SPEAKER_20]: And holic is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take everything good out of holic and then you get stoic.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, that's your expression after listening to it.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're like, just flat and stoic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, lots of big news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Today is just one big sigh, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_20]: I slept 13 and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_20]: Did you really?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_20]: I came home and took Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's fill everyone in that may have missed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we are an international show, Orange Lounge Radio, for the international Bomani community.
[SPEAKER_19]: Konnichiwa!
[SPEAKER_08]: But here in Sacramento, where we're based, as you probably may or may not know, in Northern California, we're based out of Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a huge tournament yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shaft.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we were all a big part of this, and we're all tired as fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if any of you guys might have been tuned in for our live broadcast, Orange Lounge did broadcast the whole day live from Shaft.
[SPEAKER_08]: We cut it off around Improv Freestyle because it was starting to, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's only so much you can talk about at a tournament.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to apologize for all those who did listen to the live broadcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope you never have to be subjected to something that horrible ever again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to get some clips of Loki going insane, but there were some great moments.
[SPEAKER_08]: All I know is that I was standing on the Max 2 machine, and I looked over in the corner, and they'd taken the microphone, some of the folks that were helping us out, and drug it out the window.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was Evan that did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm definitely going to talk about Evan a little bit here, too, because he did a great job.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the microphone was out the window, and Jahi was holding onto it, and I know this isn't going to translate well to radio, but he was standing there, and he's just going like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking like he's ranting about something and I'm like, there's quality radio going on in the corner right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, I so wish I could be there right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yes, a big, big thank you to everybody that helped out with that live broadcast yesterday because Jamie was so busy with tournament things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was so busy with tournament things.
[SPEAKER_08]: We let the noob, Loki, kind of take the brunt of a lot of that towards the beginning.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was all over the place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Towards the beginning.
[SPEAKER_20]: But he did a fabulous job.
[SPEAKER_20]: I kept going in the back room and...
[SPEAKER_20]: Capt, just hearing the interviews going one after another, interviewing practically everybody who did an accuracy attack, and I just remember seeing a microphone in my face a few times going, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, we're live.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to go over here now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just especially a big thank you to everybody that helped out with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brad, Irene, JB, 23M, Jahi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just everybody that helped out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a big, big thank you to Evan because he got really creative with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Evan was born for Internet Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can we have some Flyboys over here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Evan is a fucking riot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got judged.
[SPEAKER_08]: He sat at the table for a little while and saw some forms.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one contributing factor to how you guys ran out during Improv Freestyle, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He judged me, and he wrote down on this thing, Nice flaming blue shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just all this funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Evan cracks me up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish he could have been there the whole day, just to kind of ease the tension.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to have to get him on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's not...
[SPEAKER_08]: He plays Bomani, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's kind of a closet Bomani fan, but he's maybe played it once or twice, but he wouldn't be able to talk about it like we do.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he's still funny, so I'll have to get him on here sometime.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think he might be listening, so hello, Evan, if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_11]: He had to kind of play relief because I was very sick yesterday at the same time doing the radio show, as anyone that listened realized.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um, I was losing my voice.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, I had pretty much lost my voice by the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so, I was talking on the radio, trying to think of... It was pretty much me being sick and all, like, just miserable.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just ranting on about whatever came to mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though it probably wasn't incoherent at parts, but, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Go Donut!
[SPEAKER_20]: Have you ever seen a beautiful, beautiful sunset?
[SPEAKER_20]: And a flamingo is flying across the sunset.
[SPEAKER_20]: Also, it's holding a rose in its beak and a painting in its paws.
[SPEAKER_20]: Or claws, I guess.
[SPEAKER_20]: Also, you're drunk.
[SPEAKER_20]: Another deep thought by Jack Handy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have had a cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had three of them somewhere and I lost them all because I suck.
[SPEAKER_20]: I remember one day we would go visit my Uncle Caveman.
[SPEAKER_20]: We called him Uncle Caveman because he lived in a cave.
[SPEAKER_20]: And one day he would eat one of us.
[SPEAKER_20]: Later on we found out he was a bear.
[SPEAKER_20]: The face of a child can say it all, especially the mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think my favorite deep thought of all time was, it's true that every time you hear a bell ring, an angel gets its wings.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what they don't tell you is, every time you hear a mousetrap snap, an angel gets set on fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, yes, Shaft, the big topic, it's weighing heavily on our minds.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, wait, you're sitting on my face.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, a funny thing to tell a child is that when it rains, God is crying, probably because of something you did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then there was one about how Disneyland burnt down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like to play jokes on my little cousins.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to play jokes on little children, so I took my leave.
[SPEAKER_20]: But it was getting pretty late.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we pieced it together in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Shaft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Deep fried Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: What DDR tournament ever has deep fried Twinkies?
[SPEAKER_20]: I just know that we had the whole RTF versus Step Squad Twinkie eat out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you just say the RTF Step Squad Twinkie eat out?
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't mean it that way.
[SPEAKER_20]: My apologies.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know, apparently there was some sort of little mini... I think it was just teasing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you use that, I'm going to kick you.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, but we were, basically it was just like, everyone was talking about the heart attack they were going to get, and then I hear something coming from a Kyoki saying, I just took one for Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_20]: Took one what?
[SPEAKER_20]: Twinkie?
[SPEAKER_20]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there was actually a guy there named Mr. Twinkie, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sir Twinkie, I'm sorry, Sir Twinkie.
[SPEAKER_20]: I met Sir Twinkie's mom, she was nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were some people that came in from out of town.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there was a caravan that came in from Reno, a bunch from the Bay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Biggest thanks to Fury for flying out from Omaha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my lord, Omaha in the house.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some SoCal, I believe there were some ER Maniacs folks from SoCal.
[SPEAKER_11]: And my apologies for constantly saying on the radio that he is from Kansas, because I was sick and out of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I heard Omaha saying, Kansas?
[SPEAKER_11]: Kansas?
[SPEAKER_20]: Nebraska!
[SPEAKER_06]: We're Californian, Warrior Grant, thank you.
[SPEAKER_20]: I ain't Californian, originally.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know my states, yo.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else about Shaft yesterday?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's so much to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk about the winning freestyle routines.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're all a freestyle, really.
[SPEAKER_20]: Which I saw three pieces of.
[SPEAKER_08]: You didn't get to see that much of Freestyle, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, I was working.
[SPEAKER_20]: Some of us don't get to be the MC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, dear.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you think about a lot of this stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: I definitely have my favorites.
[SPEAKER_08]: What were some of your favorites?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, you know, I'd have to, well, there's some really interesting ones and I'm sure we can go into a little bit later about how unorthodox a few of the, uh, rigs we had going there were.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, yes, we'll get into that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but definitely, um, I'd have to say my two favorites, you know, obviously first and second place, uh, Tranpower, you know, his routine was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I only got to see that from distance.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing Max 2 Guard during that time, so I only got to see it from distance.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were too many people blocking the way, so I only saw the top half of him, like his head bobbing up and down.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was very good.
[SPEAKER_20]: I did see it.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was so smooth.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was really nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was very good.
[SPEAKER_11]: He is an awesome freestyler.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even his improv was right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looked like a routine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then first place, you know, obviously went to Bruce Leroy and all I have to say is, man, that guy's got some funk in him.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have one thing to say about Wendell.
[SPEAKER_20]: Mm-mm, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was actually just about to say, and our chat room is going crazy about it right now, because Wendell and I can't remember the name of his partner.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember who it was?
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like an ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yes, Holland.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did this hilarious routine to a DDR song that usually annoys a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically what they did, and as the chat room's going, roast beef, roast beef, hot, hot, hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically they did this routine to this song where basically Wendell was fighting for a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_08]: The other guy had a sandwich, Holland had a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just the way they were choreographed to the words was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I loved that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was one of the better routines I saw all day, I thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, really...
[SPEAKER_08]: Every routine, I mean, I didn't, now, keep in mind I didn't get to stick around for Improv Freestyle, but every routine I saw that day was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, to point out some of the more hilarious routines, or I don't even know if we can call them routines, there was one that's, I don't even know who was doing it because there ended up being like six or seven people on the stage when it happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's for Twilight Zone where they're doing the Mortal Kombat rendition there.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Goro made that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Goro thing, when they were stomping on the ground, that was the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, notably, probably the most eyebrow-raising routine of the evening was about ten people all in the routine area doing It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Irene, the rice princess, is a frequent contributor to this show, and also I think one of the world's only holders of an Orange Lounge t-shirt, which we don't even have, as host of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: She just was up there singing, and she had her Flyboys on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yes, DDRholic, Anita, was up there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Anita was doing the actual dancing so they wouldn't fail.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Irene was just singing, and then they had Flyboys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you'd heard Evan saying earlier in the evening, I need some Flyboys!
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to get some Flyboys!
[SPEAKER_08]: And, of course, the first two people to speak up, Sunia and Rai Rai, two cute younger girls, are all, We'll do it!
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you're not a boy!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay!
[SPEAKER_08]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that was kind of a very eyebrow-raising routine where a lot of people were just like... I just remember walking by the machine and seeing Bruce Leroy with his hands in the air doing the swish.
[SPEAKER_20]: Swish.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like he shot the perfect free throw.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was... Bruce's routine, really, was swish.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that guy has come a long way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did see a routine... He was wearing orange.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one...
[SPEAKER_08]: The one tournament I ever was a freestyle judge at was an old Sac State tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this was before, like, Hypnotix and Bruce Lee were really well known as freestylers throughout the scene, and they were both there, and they did excellent jobs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_20]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_20]: I did see a little bit of the improv, and there was a little bit of what I saw was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Improv, by the way, was a last minute addition to Shaft because we just wanted to keep it going.
[SPEAKER_20]: We had a few hiccups with the tourney, which we'll come to in my fuckies of the week.
[SPEAKER_20]: But everything seemed to go pretty good.
[SPEAKER_20]: And by the way, I have to say right now, a big congratulations to Orange Beanie.
[SPEAKER_20]: for making, in his first tournament, fourth place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and we're probably playing favorites because he's a Sacramento kid, but you know, we gotta show some Sacto love.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, even so, to come in fourth place in your first tournament is quite a... You know, Jessica and I were talking a few weeks ago about how he came up and said, oh my god, how can you perfect attack so well?
[SPEAKER_20]: And to have him come up and do that well when only not too long ago he was looking at all of us, that right there, he gets a big pass from me.
[SPEAKER_11]: All I've got to say is yesterday some of the most unorthodox things happened at that tournament.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's start off with the setup.
[SPEAKER_11]: Obviously we had fourth mix down that day.
[SPEAKER_20]: Which I need to give a little bit of background on.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_20]: The security card...
[SPEAKER_20]: I know how many people know about how a DDR machine works.
[SPEAKER_20]: We have a CD that links up to a security card.
[SPEAKER_20]: And the security card basically makes you able to play the disc.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, what it is is they needed a cartridge that will sync the security card to the disc.
[SPEAKER_20]: And their fourth mix came pre-loaded, so they didn't have that cartridge.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because Melody was telling me that her solo did the same thing when it had damage done to it.
[SPEAKER_20]: So we got the card in, but they weren't synced.
[SPEAKER_20]: So the fourth mix stayed down, so...
[SPEAKER_20]: And another big thanks to Maple and Iguana Girl for going and modding those pads for us during the tournament so that we could have them to put on the stage instead of the fourth mix pads.
[SPEAKER_20]: And we were going to hook up a fourth mix on the PS2, but we didn't have third mix because of transfer team.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I was just going to say a big congratulations to everybody that was involved getting the fourth mix situation to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think this is, it's probably not the first time PlayStation has been used in a big tournament like this, because I know a while back they were going to do something with the Club of Pens and OHA or something like that, and I don't know if that ever happened or not.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was supposed to be at the last two next tournaments.
[SPEAKER_08]: But certainly the simulator, ending up having to use Step Mania to do a third mix song just because there was just no options left.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was downright innovative.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let's give Matt the applause.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, me and my stupid sim, you know, I just happened to have my computer with me because I was using it for, well actually it was for the after party, you know, I had my sim with me and everything and I have all the setup to, you know, rig everything together.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we went ahead and rigged it with my TV out onto the TV and we had the pads going through my inputs and it worked great.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had a third mix after the Game of Love working there and, you know, come to find out, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: Fury, his only routine was on 4th
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, and look at this, you've got two guys, you've got one guy who came all the way from Omaha for the tournament, and then you've got Tran, who hasn't really been very active in the scene for the past four months or so, you know, he hasn't been very active, he kind of, he took a little hiatus, you know, whatever the reason be, personal, whatever, but it was good, it was great to see him back and doing a freestyle again, and it would have been so awful to have to turn these guys away, but it was really a situation that was just out of our hands, there's nothing we could do.
[SPEAKER_20]: Turned out to work out
[SPEAKER_08]: and it worked out awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so happy that all worked out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So big props to the Fourth Mix Repair people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess we'll call them that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_20]: It took a major hiccup and made it more of a productive burp.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a big thank you, I believe too, and I apologize if I get this wrong, I believe it was JM3P that brought the metal pad for Match USA?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I think so too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big thanks to the folks that helped that get set up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a thank you to the DDR Spot staff that was there doing the videos.
[SPEAKER_20]: Big thanks to Mike Noe and AJ for taking care of filming all that for us.
[SPEAKER_20]: Also, one of the biggest thanks goes to, of course, Konami and Jason Enos for donating DVR Max and a few t-shirts to give out for prizes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hopefully, maybe we'll see Jason in a tournament in the future, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we can swing it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing, after a tournament, it's probably not the best idea to have a party, honestly, because everybody is so dead and so tired, especially amongst the staff.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we weren't all local people, maybe we'd have more energy in us, but we were just so dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just all kind of sat here and watched movies and played video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I do have one thing I have to say about last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the Power Glove.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, well, uh, just keep your power gloves off for a pat, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I was exhausted after, you know, we were supposed to be having fun stuff and I had a major headache, you know, being sick and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I came back and I set up my metal pads and all that and, of course, every time I set up my metal pads and they never worked the first time and I ended up having to dissect these damn things to get them to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Baby Bush Baby
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, so I'm getting the sense in the chat room, and if you want to join our chat room, you're just going to join any other side IRC server, and you're going to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm getting the sense that some of the people who weren't here in town are kind of left here with question marks over their head right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's talk about something a little more adaptable to folks that are listening to us international.
[SPEAKER_08]: What were some things that we learned from the tournament that other people can take to their tournaments?
[SPEAKER_20]: Make sure that you have backups for everything that you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make sure that you have plenty of paper for the printers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make sure that you have one cash box.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Make sure...
[SPEAKER_20]: It's better to have a big staff because things will run a lot smoothly if you've got everything coordinated.
[SPEAKER_08]: The staff this year was probably three times as big as last year and it helped immensely.
[SPEAKER_20]: This made me feel very good to hear that lots of people came up and said that we had a very efficient staff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh good, that's a very good compliment.
[SPEAKER_20]: Make sure, you know, I thought it was a great idea that we had ElectroTal as our backup MC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am especially glad because after you guys added that other tournament and my voice was already starting to go, I was like, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Tal took the reins on that and, from what I understand, did a fabulous job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, I had to get to the house before anybody else did to get the party started, but...
[SPEAKER_20]: Make sure that if you're going to introduce another portion of the tournament the day of the tournament, that you have backup judges, because our judges did look pretty tired.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry, guys, but thank you for sticking it out like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, we kind of expected it would be that long anyway, but a team, unfortunately, with a fourth mixed problems didn't catch on, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to have to just do it again.
[SPEAKER_20]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And when the judges are not just giving scores, they're giving comments and suggestions on how to better the freestyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that all takes a little bit of time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we tried best we could to kind of get people up there and interview them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we had some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had some great in-between stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bran got up there and did a hilarious imitation of... I don't know what you'd call him, but it was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Bruce Leroy... Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bruce Leroy did a great improv little...
[SPEAKER_08]: Beatbox thing, which is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did hear that, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they did that on Orange Lounge a little later too, so that was cool too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, great stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: I, as frazzled as I was, I had a good time and I got hugged a lot.
[SPEAKER_20]: People just grabbed me and started hugging me.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the best part of a tournament, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that the best part of a tournament is just drive-by huggings?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, it was nice.
[SPEAKER_20]: It made me feel happy.
[SPEAKER_20]: But the best comments that I could have heard the whole time that I kept hearing is that we had a good time and just hearing we had a good time and when's the next one, that made me feel really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: The whole tournament set up actually reminded me of sort of an anime convention, because we had like, you know, it was just kind of crazy, and you had people doing their own thing everywhere, like watching movies on their laptops.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had, you know, I was kind of bored at certain points, you know, before we actually got the tournament running, and so we had people playing DDR Max on Metal Pad, we had someone else playing Step Mania on a sim,
[SPEAKER_11]: I had, you know, people were playing the DDR Max 2 on free play and I had my sim sitting there because we were using my computer for the PA system and I was playing through there too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and of course, because what tournament would be, you know, without Tanook Tanook, we went ahead and played that too during one of the big breaks and also played one of those, ah shit, I can't remember the artist's,
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, we played B4U.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who?
[SPEAKER_11]: Kutu, I forget what it's called.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Kutimu.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kutimu, yeah, we played the Kutimu B4U.
[SPEAKER_20]: The vocal B4U.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which people are kind of going, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: And then there were the people, it's like, what was it that, um, that, uh,
[SPEAKER_20]: was it Margaret Cho that said it?
[SPEAKER_20]: it's like some of you laugh and some of you just smile and nod but yes, the biggest advice we could give from Sacramento to the rest of the world from what we learned this weekend make your tournament fun that's the number one priority you need to have when scheduling a tournament fun, fun, fun keep drama away from your tournament if you've got something going on behind the scenes you don't need to let the rest of the people know it as far as they need to see, things are running fine yep
[SPEAKER_08]: and really, it wasn't, I mean, there were, sure there were things falling apart behind the scenes, I wouldn't say falling apart, but you know, just problems, but they were solved, and there was no drama, there really wasn't, at least not that I really saw, so maybe I'm just ignorant, but I didn't see any drama, which is great, so.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think there almost was with some people that were there, but we won't make comments on those people, you know, and on any of that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just that I want to thank people who kept their patience, you know, with certain situations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Poopy on drama.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, poopoo.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Piles of feces.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are going to take a quick break, and when we come back, I'm being told that around 8 o'clock-ish...
[SPEAKER_08]: That DSCS SoCal kicks our buddy down in SoCal who is being our HTML whore basically Because I can't seem to get our old website updated anymore because it's just over my head So he said, okay, you suck, I'm going to just do the damn site So I'm like, cool!
[SPEAKER_08]: So he's been working very hard on it and I believe he's going to have it done tonight And we're going to look at the site on the very show And we're going to peruse it and give our feedback, our instant feedback
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure we're all going to love them forever so we'll be talking about some show stuff right after the break things that you'll want to hear if you're a fan of Orange Lounge and we thank you for listening we're going to start this off with a song we heard a lot of yesterday and we just still can't get enough of it not Sugaru, don't worry no, not Sugaru, not the Accuracy Attack song how about the Freestyle song of the day, shall we?
[SPEAKER_08]: alright, here we go
Metagame, Dirt Dirt
[SPEAKER_16]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_16]: For an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_16]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, our buddy Mel B, who was...
[SPEAKER_08]: In the studio, literally minutes before we went on Arabidive, but unfortunately they have a long trip ahead of them and couldn't really stick around.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we thank them for being here this weekend because I know they both were helping out immensely with the tournament this weekend.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're fun house guests.
[SPEAKER_20]: Lots of fun to hang out with.
[SPEAKER_08]: How'd that go?
[SPEAKER_08]: We went to the same Mongolian barbecue place, though, I believe Friday and today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, they just ended up crashing out last night while I was making a special banner for Wendell in a tribute to his roast beefy goodness routine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Roast beef!
[SPEAKER_20]: Roast beef!
[SPEAKER_20]: Hot!
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, it was pretty good, and now I'm going to go get my taquitos.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can go get your taquitos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you enjoy those taquitos.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at what the chat room's talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're talking about Orange Lounge Forums, which we're going to try and have on the new site eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not going to be there right away, but soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they're a pyro man, our resident comedian's back, talking about how he was locked in his room masturbating to a glue stick inserted into a CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Great, that's very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And how he's currently expanding his pornography collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's always a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotta keep a variety.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray for pornography.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of pornography, they were watching yesterday at the tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're talking about pornography, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: You missed all the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, Dave's, Dave's getting pissed in the chat room, cause he brought those taquitos for the party last night, but we were so dead that nobody thought to cook them.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you for my dinner, Dave.
[SPEAKER_08]: First we don't give him a ride here, and then we eat his food.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are such assholes.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not an asshole, I'm a bitch, get it right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, where the fuck was I?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were talking about... Shaft?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we were talking about... Oh, porn!
[SPEAKER_08]: We were talking about porn!
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear God, how could I forget?
[SPEAKER_08]: We were talking about pornography.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the tournament yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the tournament yesterday, on the little iMac, they were watching the Dirty video by Christina Aguilera.
[SPEAKER_08]: In between... The Titanium Power Book, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watching Christina Aguilera with Dirty.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they were watching, I believe, the Girls Gone Wild videos.
[SPEAKER_20]: I missed the... She made the disc for Islander.
[SPEAKER_20]: and then Mike No took it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh man, I miss the Girls Gone Wild videos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, I miss all the good shit at tournaments.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do agree though that next time we do an Orange Lounge live broadcast from a tournament, we're going to actually go to the tournament as participants and not staff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we're going to demand that we be allowed to SportsCenter.
[SPEAKER_08]: in the back of the room.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't have to be in front of the machine, but in the back of the room so we can actually see the machine instead of being... See, you know, to add to the whole porn thing, I could have brought about, you know, a couple hundred tapes of Playboy videos to pass out along with the DVDs, but I thought that wouldn't be family-oriented.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's not a family fun center function, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, uh, you know, maybe at a, uh, different kind of, maybe it's for the next edit contest?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it could, that should be your next edit contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki's edit contest of pornography.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make edit get porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_08]: That should be like a, that should be an international thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I, I, that should, I would, I think Orange Lounge needs to sponsor that contest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make edit get porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you heard it here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will do this that you ask.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: The make, edit, get porn contest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Details coming soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: To get those details...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: To get those details, you'll want to log on to our website, which is currently being reinvented as we speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your HP is tasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm waiting for the word from SoCalKicks to... Oh, you've already got a pre-registration.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just waiting for the words to SoCalKicks and everything's finished.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, we'll go look at the new site.
[SPEAKER_20]: And we'll, uh... Save me some boy porn and I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have any boy porn?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, not really, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But maybe there's, like, you know, guy on girl porn that actually, like, shows the guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, well, we've got...
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know for a fact they can get a hold of a ton of Playboy videos, I mean, shit, man, I, from, like, for, like, the last eight months, I have every single video that's been released, and they're all crap, I mean, they're great, but, um, no, it's just, I don't know, they have their own, like, series that's, uh, called Playboy Exposed, it's actually, like, Girls Gone Wild, except, you know, kind of even more ridiculous, but, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Completely...
[SPEAKER_08]: Off Topic from Imani Anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard they're making a movie out of Girls Gone Wild.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, like, it's gonna be, like, actual actresses who portray these sorority girls that end up participating in the videos.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds like Porky's 3 or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, shit, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be bigger than Jackass, I guarantee it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is inside news for everyone.
[SPEAKER_11]: I read today on Weekly World News, okay, that Nostradamus predicted that Britney Spears is going to convert to Islam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nostradamus predicted it, then it must be true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: You might want to have to dispute this rumor going on in the chat room here, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what you have to say about this, but you need to set something straight, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_11]: I prefer his Playgirl.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never even seen Playgirl.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: SoCalKicks just being a jerk.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm just not turned on about the fact that they don't really do anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the movies are exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_11]: They all put them in situations where they start feeling themselves up for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: They appear to try to have sex, but for some reason just...
[SPEAKER_11]: Get Nowhere Near Having Sex
[SPEAKER_11]: And this one's actually pretty sweet, but... No, we're fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no Bomani Talk tonight, just porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come back later.
[SPEAKER_11]: This one's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've got Julia Strains in it, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's pretty famous.
[SPEAKER_11]: And actually, Sexcore TV is a really live show that they have on Playboy TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, my girlfriend doesn't let me go down on her.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, your punishment is you let him go down on you.
[SPEAKER_11]: In my courtroom on the show right now!
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's what happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of stupid, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have to add, I forget what their booth is or whatever, but it's this giant seashell bed thing that looks like something out of a Little Mermaid porno sequence or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the weirdest thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's definitely a good movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Plus I have a couple other ones that are really strange.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just had to get it because I saw the poster for it and it was just funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Playmate of the Apes.
[SPEAKER_20]: I've only ever seen two porn.
[SPEAKER_20]: One of them was the boneheads, like the coneheads with collapsible tops.
[SPEAKER_20]: As in inwardly collapsible, so they could use them.
[SPEAKER_20]: And Final Thug X.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fuck X's winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, okay, I have to add that these aren't true pornos, these are softcore porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Skinamax porn!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Skinamax porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, now, if you want to get some good porn, you need to definitely go with the Vivid DVDs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Vivid DVDs are awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, the extras on them are worth another movie right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Plus, a lot of them are like a twofer.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get one movie plus bonus features, plus another movie with bonus features, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I know, in the Sacramento area.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, in Sacramento area, I know that you can go to Video Clearance Center.
[SPEAKER_11]: They got porn as cheap as like two bucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: So go there and check it out, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are pretty much being worshipped in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: And another bit money news.
[SPEAKER_08]: That Loki knows his porno and remind me when I go to NorCal to go to Loki's.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Loki is pornified.
[SPEAKER_08]: And porn on talk on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never thought I would see the day.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have a taquito.
[SPEAKER_20]: Do you have a taquito?
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we have a comment, Porn and Orange Chicken, which, you know, yesterday at the tournament, take this back to Mamani a little bit, you brought over some Boston Market and you got a half chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a half chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were that damn hungry, but you gave a hunk of it to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's Loki there sitting eating some chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, you know what goes great with chicken?
[SPEAKER_08]: I said grape soda, but then somebody else said porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm just so professional during this.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm having a meeting of all the judges while I'm eating chicken.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was hilarious because they were trying to pass me a demo of the scorecard sheet thing and my hands were all greasy and sticky from, you know, WHOA!
[SPEAKER_11]: From the chicken!
[SPEAKER_11]: From the goddamn chicken, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: The chicken was damn good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get him a Norelco for those palms.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, but the chicken was very greasy, so, you know, obviously I was just, you know, going, uh, don't hand me that, because I don't want to touch that, and, you know, get all these grease marks all over it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, good chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: The answer that nobody did give, though, we got grape soda, we got porn, nobody said waffles.
[SPEAKER_20]: Chicken and Waffle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nobody said waffles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_08]: I flog you all.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was Dave who said porn and chicken.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I don't give him credit, he'll cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, I have to add, since we were going to originally talk about, I believe, Showgirls that we watched last night, I have to say that Showgirls is a complete waste of time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure, it's got, you know, T&A, but it's three hours long and it's got, like, a plot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will cut you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Showgirls is like the greatest movie ever because it is so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I like watching trainwreck cinema.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like watching her bump and grind on people, so that was all worth it for me.
[SPEAKER_20]: And in other Bimani news, I like DDR.
[SPEAKER_20]: I like Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_20]: Apparently, other people like Beat It Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDRholic.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDRholic says, I may not be a guy, but I like porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amen, sister.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need more porn freaks in this world.
[SPEAKER_20]: Porn is funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: An ideal woman.
[SPEAKER_11]: She likes porn more than I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_20]: I like boy porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is a yaoi fanatic as she shoves her iron fist of justice into the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: Iron fisting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, and then I have to also add that, as well as my hentai collection, we're not going to go there either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, just when we're starving to get a new topic, I have SoCalKicks in his typical IRC way telling me 40 times in the chatroom, line after line, that he has finished.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, let's see what we get if we go to our website right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, not just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: At orangelounge.skie.cx.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go to it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: We're gonna go browsing, we're gonna go browsing
[SPEAKER_08]: This is pretty sick that, you know, here we are, the host of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't know a damn thing about our own website.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we go to the website, we can click right here on the main page.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see what we get.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome to the newly redesigned Orange Lounge site.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks to me, SoCalKick.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, thanks to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: This site will be very easy to run to the point Rob can even update it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now, all pages are very under construction as Sky himself goes in and makes this site his own.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, Jamie and Loki might want to participate too.
[SPEAKER_20]: We're going to have pictures.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we'll have new pictures.
[SPEAKER_20]: It actually looks like my nose.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't want to be supermodels anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're just going to jump in a garbage can.
[SPEAKER_20]: I will no longer look like Barbra Streisand.
[SPEAKER_08]: You did not look like Barbra Streisand.
[SPEAKER_20]: The nose was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it looked cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: The nose was not like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll take new pics just because people want updated pictures of ourselves.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Of ourselves in the singular.
[SPEAKER_20]: Rob, is there something you're not telling us?
[SPEAKER_20]: How many of you live in there?
[SPEAKER_20]: Knock, knock!
[SPEAKER_08]: Forty.
[SPEAKER_08]: In a row.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thirty-seven.
[SPEAKER_18]: Try not to get any more personalities on your way out to the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh... Let's see, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now, be sure to listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be sure to listen.
[SPEAKER_20]: Always.
[SPEAKER_20]: Every day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every second.
[SPEAKER_08]: Visit the Live 365 page for more info, and a direct link goes to the station site.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now, if you know me well, you know I like whoring out SCK, so here goes nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then he whores out, continues to whore out, the Friday, November 15th launch date of SoCalKicks.com version 5.0.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if we have anything on these different pages yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no, it just says under construction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under construction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, here's what it says for chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now, I just won't make it pretty and just say what's needed.
[SPEAKER_08]: The channel is Orange Lounge and can be found on any other irc.otherside.net server such as irc.acons.org and others.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under Construction, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: CAST!
[SPEAKER_08]: Under Construction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, come on, SoCalKicks, I know you know who's on CAST.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: It looks very pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Links.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under Construction, but here's your first link.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, Sackbit Monty needs to be on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's the link to SoCalKicks.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the upcoming, we will have... Might I add, that's one giant link banner.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll just have to make, like, one's just as big.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's huge!
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like an orange dropped on a toothpick!
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, so the site is very pretty, and we appreciate DSCS and all his hard work.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, a big kisses from all of us to DSCS.
And, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be sure you're involved in any future Twinkie eating competitions.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, you two can eat out of Twinkie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I have to scream out his slogan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Should we scream it out in agony, ecstasy, pain?
[SPEAKER_08]: How should we scream out his slogan?
[SPEAKER_18]: S-C-K-A-R-B-L-I-S-H-I-S Ultimate Tack!
[SPEAKER_20]: Evolution just now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: SCK accomplishes ultimate evolution just now.
[SPEAKER_20]: That was very ingrishy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was the natural gift of love.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, in rave style.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's say his slogan in rave style.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to go find my glow sticks real fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I can come back and do this in rave style.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't want to know where your glow sticks are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, man, oh, did you hear, man?
[SPEAKER_07]: SDK accomplished his ultimate evolution just now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blur!
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just out of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, all your base style.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, all your base style.
[SPEAKER_08]: SCK accomplishes ultimate evolution just now.
[SPEAKER_08]: RS.
[SPEAKER_18]: For great justice.
[SPEAKER_20]: Move, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, let's take another quick break.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, so Rob can go put his glow sticks away.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we're going to come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're just going to be a quick break, and we're going to come back, and we're going to talk about... We're going to do Happy Hopper in this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do Silhouette of My Mind in this break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going from extremes here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're going from very happy to very wrist-slitting-ish.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, we're going to go the other way around.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go from wrist-slitting to happy.
[SPEAKER_20]: I look as the blood splashes upon the...
[SPEAKER_10]: Blackness of my soul.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome to Goth Talk.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm Asriel the Prince of Sorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go sad to happy and then we will come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is the time when you're going to want to send me your FUs of the week if you're in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we're going to talk about those when we come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enjoy, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on a train to die How can I find my way to you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep reaching for my life Seeking the secrets of my heart I keep reaching for my life
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, tune in to hear live train wreck radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch all your favorite monster hosts, DarkSakura, Skye, and Loki engage in the Bomani Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_05]: This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, at 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pacific Time, heads will roll and arrows will scroll.
[SPEAKER_08]: And be suitable for children under 6, pregnant women, retards, and residents of Baltimore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ready for the race, are you ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio and we're back and we're live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_19]: Is he a resident of Omaha?
[SPEAKER_08]: Resident of Baltimore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, remember that the reason why I said F you to Baltimore was because they were the lowest ranked on the list of what cities are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they had a whopping, like, second.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing that's being said in the chatroom, we have a new face in the chatroom, Tank.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't recognize this person, new person.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's saying, wow, the musical variety is making me feel like a teen girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that just made me think, I'm as happy as a little girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: A big welcome to all our new chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see Orange Beanie's in the chatroom, too.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hi, Beanie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Beanie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Great job at chat yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're proud of you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all of our chatters, our chatroom's been picking up lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our cutesy, girly girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got EOSFVB's a new person, too, I think, that came in last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And VidPower started chatting here last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: All of our regulars.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat room.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think during our next break we need to do our tribute to one of our famous people in our chat room, DJ Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I think that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Konami needs a good tribute.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get to the FUs of the week, shall we?
[SPEAKER_08]: We just talked about the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, we're going to talk about the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talked about how we don't play... Well, I'm sorry, Jamie has to kick it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll reference what I said later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me don't play that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you've got to start it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's your baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's your little crack-infested baby.
[SPEAKER_20]: Crack-infested baby?
[SPEAKER_20]: Never do a drug named after part of your own ass.
[SPEAKER_20]: Waka Laka gives you wings, what?
[SPEAKER_20]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_08]: It is that time of the show, ladies and gentlemen, where Jamie and the rest of us all get pissed off as hell, and we give our FUs of the week!
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm pissed as hell, and I'm not gonna take it anymore!
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, first one is gonna go, and this wasn't anything anyone could control, so I'm saying fuck you to fate for fucking with us in the fourth mix machine yesterday at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_20]: Damn you all to hell!
[SPEAKER_20]: Another one goes toward... Fuck you to hurting at the end of the day and thank you to Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you to sleeping for 13 and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sleep feels good, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck you, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I really am not filled with that in the shakes today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you really Jamie, or are you an imposter?
[SPEAKER_19]: I feel good.
[SPEAKER_20]: That fucking sucks!
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you to my good mood, dammit, because I can't be angsty enough to go off without something enough to just be super pissed.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I have to be super pissed to be ready to kill people, too.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, I can't do that either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so much for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, after 19 weeks of being pissed off, it's time for Jamie to be in a loving, sharing mood, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck that!
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: That pisses me the hell... Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's talk to Loki and see what his fuck you of the week is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you of the week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, fuck you of the week, that's definitely for sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: First one goes to my cold.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like having a cold, and it snuck up on me on Friday, and that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably all the rain's fault, so F you to the rain, even though I like rain.
[SPEAKER_11]: And F you for my battery being dead this morning in my car.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least it works now, I think, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to Cigaru, because I hate that song, and they played it way too many times at the tournament yesterday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, a big cute FU to something we're going to be covering in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to Super Eurobeat, the new song that's going to be on GDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of the most evil things on the face of the earth.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you add Naoki with B4U...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm very scared and concerned about that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I show great concern for this new song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, let's see what else we got here.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to my pads for being faulty sometimes and me constantly having to prepare them.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you for myself for getting shocked by my stereo numerous times while I was putting wires to it because I'm an idiot and I was tired and didn't unplug it when I was hooking up wires and just kept going, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: FU for people not talking in chatrooms enough because I'm bored at work and I read the forums too fast and I go through about eight forums and no one's talking about anything new.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm running out of things.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm probably still tired from yesterday.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU for me being tired.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure there's something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thinking there's something I remember seeing yesterday that I was going to do an FU about, but I can't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dammit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll come back to you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU of the week goes to myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yesterday during the Orange Lounge broadcast, yesterday during the Orange Lounge live broadcast we were doing live from Shaft, we did some music breaks so that Loki and whoever was on air could actually have a break to get up and go out and do something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of the CDs that I used during the break was Dance Mania 20.
[SPEAKER_08]: So unfortunately yesterday I unknowingly played Bye Bye Baby Balloon on this station.
[SPEAKER_20]: You bitch!
[SPEAKER_08]: So a big fuck you to me for breaking that rule that I put down weeks and weeks ago when Bye Bye Baby Balloon was voted by the listless process as the worst Bomani song next to Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not only did I play it, I played the full version.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play Dirty yesterday, however I have in the past.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we have to go back to your music.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_20]: My fuck you goes toward that damn song for finally growing on me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_20]: I found myself at work with that song stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: What song?
[SPEAKER_20]: Fucking Dirty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pointing at you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: Stop pointing at me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Everybody yell at Rob.
[SPEAKER_20]: Nini.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_20]: Did Loki, oh, Loki, you thought he'd rep you?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, this is a general FU.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU do speed mixes.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're the dumbest things in the face of the earth.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate everybody that does speed mixes of any sort.
[SPEAKER_11]: This goes with Jenny Rom and the Zippers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: JB is walking here right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's going to walk a lock on your ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they've done some slower stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I hate... I hate...
[SPEAKER_11]: B-Mixes, I hate them to death!
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, now, okay, I'll give credit to, you know, Jenny Ranma's stuff because some of her stuff is good, I do like it, you know, but I dislike, for instance, we just heard the Venus, um, what was it, uh, you can leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we just heard it like an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: So we heard it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds like shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just, just like, okay, I've heard one more time.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds like shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've heard, like, I don't know, there's a bunch of stuff I've heard.
[SPEAKER_11]: All of it sounds like crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just speed it up and have some guy cover it because you can't pay the artist royalty fees, and it sounds like shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then the comic goes, whew, it's fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's put it in our next New York Stream Super Duper Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, you know, people play it and go, damn, this is tiring.
[SPEAKER_11]: I dislike it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And living in America sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Remember, DDR isn't just a power, it's a super-duper power.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ugh, God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stupid, freaking... Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: And F you to Naoki, because... I don't want to say that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And F you to freaking Naoki Jules, because he's not putting anything good in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is he just speaking Japanese?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is he Japanese or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: He can't speak English like everybody else in the face here.
[SPEAKER_18]: So find out what this fuck is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, oh, oh, and here's another one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, since I'm going off on the EDR extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the Loki show, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell kind of... They need to come up with some better names for the songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's have Paranoia Survivor Max.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, come on, name it something else.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is the deal with milk?
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm finished.
[SPEAKER_08]: The chat room is yelling at you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're half with you and half against you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Half of them are with you and half of them are against you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we ever going to get to the chat rooms?
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck the chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_20]: I love you guys, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_20]: First of all, speak mixes are okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Some of them suck ass.
[SPEAKER_20]: Major fuckers go to Politary for still being alive.
[SPEAKER_20]: Woman, I've been listening to Politary now, unfortunately, for days.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because it keeps coming up.
[SPEAKER_20]: I say that we have a one-week ban of Politary from our radio show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we're going to ban Politary from the radio show?
[SPEAKER_19]: Just for a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just for a week?
[SPEAKER_19]: There are some songs that have good music in them that are just ruined by her voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting tomorrow, Orange Lounge has banned Politary from its playlist completely.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have another proposition.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am offering a $500 bounty for Politary.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dead.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, no, you can't kill her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just killing is wrong.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, how about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: $500 for her to go mute.
[SPEAKER_20]: Shove, like, acid down her throat?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shove a Twinkie down her throat.
[SPEAKER_20]: A fried Twinkie.
[SPEAKER_08]: $500 for a super hot fried Twinkie shoved down Voluntary's throat.
[SPEAKER_20]: To dissolve her larynx.
[SPEAKER_20]: And she can't sing anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want her tongue sent to me in a plastic baggie through the mail.
[SPEAKER_20]: Make sure that you vacuum seal it so that it stays fresh so we can see it still twitch.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_10]: We've had sex, we've had violence.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've had sex in the first hour of this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have violence right now and probably drugs before it's all over.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had my Vicodin already.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge goes to hell tonight.
[SPEAKER_20]: We're going to hell in a hat and basket and you're all coming with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I get to the chatroom FUs?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_20]: We're going to give the chatroom special music today.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to give them something to yell about.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now they can all do an FU to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-oh, Orange Beanie's a little mad about Politary.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what music do you need?
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, I'm going to have to say that, um... Oh, shoot, what else was one of my, uh...
[SPEAKER_11]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_11]: to Scandia for having their party room window covered up by blue paint or something because I couldn't see the freaking machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Scandia rules, so we'll forgive them this one time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, yes, Orange Lounge Vice City tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what we're being called.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, oh, F.U.
[SPEAKER_11]: to Vice City because I can't for the life of me get the hooker to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: She gets in my car, she takes money.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's your sound clip from now on.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the life of me, I can't get the hooker to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is now chat room fuck you time, so Rob, go at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I had special music for them, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: This one's all nice and fast and angsty.
[SPEAKER_20]: Speed mixy, if you will.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, okay, I like KOGG3, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: They kick ass, and so does RedMonsterHyper, or whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, um, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: DSCS SoCalKick says, F you to the rain and cold that made them almost sick-ass Loki sounds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you, Owen, for not wanting to go to the movies on Monday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you, Char Plus Parents, these are all people we don't know, for not letting me go over this weekend in FU time, because there isn't enough of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to beta test STK Max 5.0 in the next two to three days, finish my special art project by Wednesday, or get an F on it, and make an avid side of my ass before December 7th.
[SPEAKER_08]: And F you to Loki, tell him to get him on fucking AIM, because I'm home all effing day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dave, I have to give Dave special music.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember what Dave's FU song was, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does anybody remember Dave's FU song?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just going to play this song for Dave.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dave says, F you Tigger for being so freaking good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you have to own every song?
[SPEAKER_08]: He beat me in the quarterfinals on the Can't Stop Falling in Love speed mix by 31 greats.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got 40 out of 444.
[SPEAKER_08]: He got 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came in fifth though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Un-fuck the weekend for being three days long, but fuck RyRy's parents for not trusting her with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's a little intense there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I shouldn't have read that out loud.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm reading without thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope she's not listening with her speakers turned up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody's in trouble.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back to the rest of the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, he's got too many.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm only doing part of these.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you for not understanding a single word of the Shaft stuff tonight F every female on this planet F celebrate night for fucking me up on Oni F the entire CBS DDR coverage which we've got to talk about before the show's over F those stupid dancers who won PS2 and pads on that and F Loki because he asked for it
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus, F. Roulette, he expects something non-rave style when he does improv freestyle, or something like Sugaru for improv.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's for you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: In status, we all know he got Nori Nori Nori.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kill, I still should get an award for most incongruous routine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you, Nori Nori Nori.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Konami, F you to Kakumei Encore Stage because I failed on the 6th step.
[SPEAKER_08]: SoCalKicks, I missed a part and I closed the window.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Resend it to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll read it.
[SPEAKER_08]: JB says, F you to anyone who doesn't like Hello Panda cookies.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should be stabbed with sporks.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to hurting after the turning and burning myself in the deep fryer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Hello Panda cookies.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I say Politary can sing and Naoki can't compose.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd like to add that, JB, you know, kind of that was your fault since you're deep frying everything that you can get your hands on.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty entertaining watching him deep fry pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think one of the most popular things that was being deep fried yesterday, other than the Twinkies, had to have been the candy corn.
[SPEAKER_20]: By the way, you're very welcome.
[SPEAKER_20]: I hope you enjoyed your Hello Kitty Yang Yangs.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDRholic, oh, I love DDRholic, she's so cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU for there not being such anything as Guys Gone Wild videos.
[SPEAKER_20]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go on, girl.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, they did a thing, like, they did Guys Gone Wild, like a promo for that on the guy show, or the man show.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't make a real one.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU to Girls Gone Wild, there should be a Guys Gone Wild series.
[SPEAKER_08]: EOSFBB says, wow, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little, a little racist.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to read that on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: So he says China Power, so we'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fitpower says, my FU of the week goes to the official Animal Crossing site because they've taken down the Donkey Kong Jr.
[SPEAKER_08]: NES game and it's now replaced with Clu Clu Land D. Now I can't get Donkey Kong Jr.
[SPEAKER_08]: in my town now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also FU to Wrapping Paper because I like to keep my DVD covers in excellent condition and the Wrapping Paper took about 45 minutes to get off because of all the extra tape they put on it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have another FU.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've hit your quota for the night.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm the angsty happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_20]: My fuck you of the week goes to my fiancee, Dan, for hitting Mallory in the head with the bug net.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mallory is a bitch and she needs to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: She needs to burn in Animal Crossing hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to Animal Crossing hell and burn, Mallory.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_20]: And also to our town lesbian, Dina, because she went ahead and took care of her errand myself just because it was a day late.
[SPEAKER_20]: and, and, and, and, and Fuck You to, um, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_20]: I need people to play Phantasy Star with, so if anyone has Phantasy Star Online and a broadband thingy for the GameCube, let me know, or if not, then Fuck You.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because I want to play it with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: SoCalKick says F you to whoever hates on Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't get my music.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, you're right, he doesn't get your music.
[SPEAKER_08]: He gets something even better.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to whoever hates on Loki, because that was the best rant-a-thon I've heard in ages.
[SPEAKER_08]: 23rd Magus, Politaris, sounds like Yoko Ono with laryngitis.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gwen says F you to me because I wasn't supposed to say that female one on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: EOSFVB says F you to me for being quote unquote racist.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I just kind of used some kind of words I don't want to say on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And DDR, it's on a happy note.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for the kudos, Rob and Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: And F you to whoever took my signed tape, because I won the season 10 for a fourth time.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have to watch my bootleg DVD, which has really bad subtitles.
[SPEAKER_11]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: F that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck this song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, F this song.
[SPEAKER_20]: One, two, three, four, this song really sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, I need to find my copy of Instant Love, because I don't know where it is.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's on one of the old pre-shows, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey everyone, this is DJ Konami!
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you all know Beatmania, but I want to go back and teach you the basics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen carefully and try to follow.
[SPEAKER_04]: The object will come down from the top.
[SPEAKER_04]: When it hits the red line, push the button.
[SPEAKER_04]: When it hits the red line, turn the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's practice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's for all the keys and the turntable.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hard, but you can do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the ball, it's the ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the ball, it's the ball.
New Feat Media
[SPEAKER_04]: The Powerful Sound System will make everybody HOT!
Alright, gotta go!
Knock me out with your fabulous sounds on this very new version of your Beatmania!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight, I'll try to let you remember All the times that we were happy together Sing a song, you and me can be singing Tonight, it's such a pleasure tonight
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Over London, Rock Over Chicago, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a good place to listen to the music.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't know Wesley Willis, maybe you should.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where that little promo comes from.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a joke, and I don't even think it was really something I ever intended on putting into the station rotation, but we need a new promo, so what can I say?
[SPEAKER_20]: We'll make more then.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll make more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that tournament's over, we can sometime this week get you guys over and we'll work on more promos.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um,
[SPEAKER_08]: Bubble Bobble Techno Song
[SPEAKER_20]: It was one of the Overclocked remixes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So probably Overclocked.org?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: And search for... Should be Overclocked.org, it's gonna be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Search for Bubble Bobble and you'll probably find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All I gotta say is, you know, I've been, you know, especially nowadays, you know, I'm totally browsing the internet while I'm working.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Final Fantasy
[SPEAKER_11]: And he's actually done some stuff for Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_11]: He did this one that's called Strings Machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just an awesome trance.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, this guy should be doing professional stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I don't know why he's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: The ones to check out are definitely Strings Machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then there's also one that's a Geneva trance remix.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a few other ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Metalroid is another good one to check out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a Metroid-themed remix.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of hard rock, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that URL one more time?
[SPEAKER_11]: I believe it's remix.overclocked.org.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remix.overclocked.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you just do a web search for overclocked, you'll find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you might want to do Overclock Remix, otherwise you're going to get a bunch of sites.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't clock me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's talk about... We've got about 20 minutes left in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got about a bunch of Imani news to cram in.
[SPEAKER_08]: But speaking of time left in the show, this is an announcement we haven't made yet during the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We probably should have opened the show saying it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But starting next week with episode 20, Orange Lounge season number two debuts.
[SPEAKER_08]: A whole new season.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as I'm concerned, the past 21 shows or however many we did, because we had a couple half shows in there, they've all been leading up to next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: This has all been practice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because next week we're taking Orange Lounge to three hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: A three hour tour.
[SPEAKER_08]: 3-Hour Treatment
[SPEAKER_20]: Maybe we should be here when Rob makes the intro, or maybe someone should hook me up with a particular program that we need to let somebody else make an intro.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can hear it now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, for the life of me, I can't get the hookers to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for giving that to me once again nice and clear.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll make editing a lot easier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's how it's going to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to go 6.30 to 9.30 Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The replays will still be 7 o'clock on Monday and 2 o'clock on Thursday for the time being.
[SPEAKER_20]: As long as I get to be an angsty happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, as always.
[SPEAKER_20]: Happy, or angsty, or both.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty much all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: New season starts next week.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now you know, and knowing is half the battle.
[SPEAKER_20]: Go Joe!
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Bomani News this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Way back to Monday, day after we did this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: CBS, on the early show, did a little DDR promotion on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was basically one gigantic infomercial for DDR where everybody did not know shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be the best way to describe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like taking the audience members from an infomercial and having them do the infomercial.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's what they did, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: They got this local dance school to come down there, and they had these people that I guess were from some dance school, from what it looked like.
[SPEAKER_11]: A local school, everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they were playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Dance School of Jennifer Lopez.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, it was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, no one really knew what they were doing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Watching, like, newbie people playing DDR USA.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, they had three machines set up there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, speaking of the machine setup, this pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why I get angry about it, but I just find it kind of irritating.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had Max 2 machines with USA banners on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: That really strikes a bad chord with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like, Konami, why do you have to lie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you just give us a new mix?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you not notice that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did not notice that.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was freeze arrows, and one of the songs being played was Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had Max 2... Matsuri Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Matsuri Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the machines, the one in the middle was a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one that the CBS host played on, that was a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, the two side machines were Max 2 machines.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's kind of like, you kind of feel like, you know, obviously for Joe Q public, those that don't know DDR very well, you know, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: You're kind of like, why are you misrepresenting the product here?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, now the home version of Max is similar to Max 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got a lot of the cool things Max 2 does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why didn't we just have somebody demo the home version of Max?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did we have to invent these arcade machines that don't exist in the U.S.? ?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't sit well with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Konami deserves a big slap on the wrist for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, one of the highlights I thought that was pretty interesting... Or whoever made that decision.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Konami didn't make that decision.
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta love that they had a video game expert there who was talking about DDR and had no idea what the fuck he was talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: All I could think of during that whole thing was, that guy's really gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's really, really gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's saying gay things.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's kind of talking gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: This whole segment's kind of gay.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would have, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't see this.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I'm sounding vaguely glad that I didn't.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, I was asleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm being reminded that one reason they probably did the marquee switch was because imports are illegal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, true that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that doesn't get around the issue of you used an import machine, you just lied about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, I mean... It's like, you know, okay, so they had trouble importing USA machines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine, why didn't we promo Max USA?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a damn good product.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we should have been demoing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, if they had, you know, maybe put out a PlayStation, a couple ignition pads, could have whored out Red Octane, or the official Konami pads, if Konami wants to whore out their own product.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, what they ended up doing is they had a drawing throughout the show, which...
[SPEAKER_11]: Any, anyone watching the show really didn't give a rat's ass, it was only for the people actually at the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know, Super Contest, which has been pre-changed.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was, um, two, uh, pretty shitty-ass, um, third-party dance performance pads and a, uh, what was that, PlayStation 2 and a DDR Max, uh, USA, uh, game, which is pretty, I mean, obviously that's pretty cool, you know, I'd love, you know, to win that if I was there.
[SPEAKER_11]: The thing is, they didn't really plug the game that much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, they talked about, you know... No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they kind of didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were just kind of like, well, it's this new game that's sweeping the nation, and we're going to let these ignoramus dance students play it, and we're going to give one of them a fabulous prize of a home version game that we're going to just kind of show you.
[SPEAKER_08]: The box art of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is Konami...
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Max and Konomics
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, it might not have been Konami's fault.
[SPEAKER_08]: That whole switcheroo might not have been Konami's fault.
[SPEAKER_08]: It may have been CBS that made that decision, but F whoever did that, because that wasn't cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoever's decision it was, F them.
[SPEAKER_20]: I saw some pictures from it, and honestly, if you're going to show off something, it's like having a product.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you're going to show a product, you put it in the most positive light possible.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you don't do it by putting...
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: by a Catholic priest.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's the same difference.
[SPEAKER_20]: They have no idea how to do any of that, unless they've been reading confiscated material.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know about some of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand why they didn't interview the dance expert.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had all these DDR people in.
[SPEAKER_08]: They flew 8-Ball out there, or he flew out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what the hell the arrangement was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he was just kind of there in the background wearing a DDR Freak t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I... Didn't he make a comment during one of the clips?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sure, because I didn't exactly... I don't know what 8-Ball looks like, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I thought there was some guy that looked like he knew who he was talking about, and... He was the only guy wearing a DDR Freak shirt.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that might have been him, then.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know either.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, the dance school's kids should not have been there, and whoever that guy was wasn't Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: He shouldn't have been there either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me just put it this way, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any publicity is good publicity.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's very true, and you know, it's going to sell the game a little more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we will get an arcade machine in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: that's like Max 2, but... You know, we had the discussion about it, you know, it was me and... I don't remember who I was talking to about it, but we were making the discussion that now that the whole Endemiro suit's been settled, or is in process of settling, I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_20]: It should be, it's long over, whatever... It opens the door for a new mix, and I don't think that it's necessarily that Konami themselves have to do the work on it.
[SPEAKER_20]: If they're allowing third parties to do the arcade releases, they could just as easily have a team set aside.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, it's just kind of like... And it will make so much money.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we were just in the know a little more, if we knew a little bit more about how all that operation works, what goes on inside Konami's roof, inside Konami's Japan roof, inside Konami of America's roof, it would probably make a lot more sense to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We wouldn't be so bitter about this game that we've wasted so much money on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fact is, we don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: and so we're just confused and we don't get but luckily at least the home releases are moving in the right direction by far so if they do end up doing a Max 2 in the US which I don't see why they wouldn't it'll probably kick a lot of ass so
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, CBS, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, well, I guess we can talk about other, you know, smaller stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, any other news you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we've got, of course, you know, the eighth release of Characters for DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that anyone ever plays that game anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'm sure there are certain people that play that game, but I know for me... I did see this morning.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did not, I did not play this, I don't play this game anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: It crashes on my computer and whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is there a new character to be released?
[SPEAKER_11]: The newest characters that we have, we've got two Latin people, I don't remember their names are, it doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the most important one is Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, Jason Enos is a playable character in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which we all pretty much knew about ever since the game came out that he would be released at some point.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly what I said, his head is smaller than the rest of his body.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some graphic artist really fucked up on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And his shirt looks like your shoes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dude, I love the shirt.
[SPEAKER_20]: I want that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The shirt was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he has a shrunken head.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a real bummer.
[SPEAKER_20]: But it's still pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't play it in-game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't played it in-game yet, so he probably looks okay there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that little preview picture of him?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's still really cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know that you've made it when you are in DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Konami's hoping that they release Kyle Snyder as a hidden character at some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a Sky character, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky and DarkSakura should be a team that comes up.
[SPEAKER_20]: But we'd have to have orange bats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, if they gave us orange bats, would you be a DDRPC character?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I would.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, you know, someone let us know if you can, you know, make skins for the characters or something.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let us know if anyone's figured out how to hack it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Loki can be in DDRPC, too, and he'll kind of have that big trench coat of his on doing that whole Keanu Reeves thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoa, I know DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoa, I forgot my steps.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little insight there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other than that, some stuff that's probably going to be announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not positive it's going to be announced next week, but that's when it's scheduled to be announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tourney Mix 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Tourney Mix 3 is coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, this would be the sim news portion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, sim news, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tourney Mix 3 is going to be started, so we're going to see a lot more sim files.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, this time around, I'm expecting Vimani really not to enter, you know, unless, of course, you know, almost all of his files are out there except for one, and that's the return.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so, well, if he is going to enter, it would probably be that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki gets on the soapbox.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, okay, off my soapbox here.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, Tournament Mix 3, they're talking about actually having prizes.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was going to be some DVDs provided by myself, but they never took me up on that, and now it's too late.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, oh well, screw that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to have to buy their own prizes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there's probably going to be prizes this time around.
[SPEAKER_11]: There might be a section where you actually have to pay to enter, so that's kind of crap, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: This time...
[SPEAKER_11]: This time, unlike the last two times that I said I was going to enter, this time I will enter because I'm actually making sim files now.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you'll see something from me in there if it's not something that I've already made.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we'll see something from me in the tournament this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess I can plug my site a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, everyone knows about www.leachfromloki.tk.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to be uploading, probably tonight, my finished copy of Outer Limits.
[SPEAKER_11]: I finished that, no, actually, yesterday.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: How did you have any time to finish that yesterday?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, technically yesterday, if you consider, like, 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: yesterday.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so, I finished that yesterday, so it's almost, it's, no, all ready to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just need to upload it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of fun, pretty difficult.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tried playing it on the pad today, and I just realized I can't do 10-footers on a pad, so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other than that, just keep watching DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've got their user sim file section updated to where people can submit files now and you'll see a bunch of cool stuff come on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, DDR UK, if you're not a member of that site, I recommend becoming one because...
[SPEAKER_11]: Lawrence there, who also you might know him from his Bantu originals and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: He actually is doing synced sets for DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's got synced sets for Euromix and Euromix 2 full sets with MP3s and everything that you can download in one huge zip or by themselves.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also he has Disney's Rave done and he's working on Club Mix and he's going to do the rest.
[SPEAKER_11]: And actually if you find his site, which I can't remember the URL by itself, he's got sync sets for Max 2 and DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think he had at one point all the other original, you know, 1 through, you know, 5th, but, you know, I have them, but they're not on the site anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you'll have to find them somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they're out there, so just, you know, keep looking.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other than that, I don't think there's any more updates with Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't heard anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: The final just got released.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some tumbleweed rolled by.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: The final got released a couple weeks ago, so not too much going on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know there's a few people still trying to find out a way to crack the max...
[SPEAKER_11]: The DDR Max 2 edit machine code thing there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Something I've been working on for months and kind of given up on because I don't play the arcade machines anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe we'll crack that and then I'll go play again and make some more edits.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm supposed to make some edits to be on SoCalKicks' site, so look for those.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_11]: Love is the Power, which is the ending theme from DDR Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's going to be in there, another Naoki track.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, as I mentioned earlier in my FUs of the Week, Super Eurobeat, which is going to be done by Naoki featuring the DDR All-Stars, which is Paul Terry, B4U, and some other chick, I can't remember the name.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, you'll have to listen for that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure it's going to sound like a train wreck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, a few more Oni courses.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a really particular evil one that's got a bunch of slow songs like Bag and Orion 78 played at half speed, so it's going to look like one giant mass of arrows coming up the screen that you can't read, so that'll be fun, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Check Aaron in Japan's site.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's got a really cool comprehensive list on there, and his stuff's pretty updated really frequently, so go check that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, we've got a few more minutes left in the show, and I thought what I'd do is open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to open up the email mailbag right now on the station.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's get some mailbagging music, shall we?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm... I'll tell you, let me go ahead and make a mention of something while you're... Yes, please do.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm working on a little something now that I have some spare time.
[SPEAKER_20]: Again, this tournament's over, thank God.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um...
[SPEAKER_20]: Basically, go ahead and send in an email to orangechallengeradio.com with what your favorite joke of the show is.
[SPEAKER_20]: That would be whether it's Malky's Diary, maybe, or maybe our hatred of Paul Terry, or your favorite segment, or maybe even our listless segment.
[SPEAKER_20]: What is your favorite...
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, staple discussion of our show.
[SPEAKER_20]: And go ahead and send that and just put attention DS for the subject.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you may see something come of that within the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That email address is orangeloungeradio, all one word, at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to go check the mailbag right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to the mailbag, going to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we're opening up the mailbag right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, I see this entire week we've gotten one new email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, that's one more than we got last week.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, and a lengthy one it is, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, this is a great email.
[SPEAKER_08]: This comes to us from somebody who refers to themselves as Mask Kun of Suspenseful on behalf of the entire Closet Poppers Society.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, when I first read this, I thought, Closet Poppers, that sounds kind of like a rave thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Read the letter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's read the letter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is three of us now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is located between the paint cans at his hardware store, which he is not at one of our meetings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your 24-hour Bomani words of wisdom inspire us all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love people that can kiss some ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we try our best to play every game that they make.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, we feel that there may be major bias within those divine offices, and it is starting to get on the Coalition's nerves just a tiny bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are we talking about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, we've chalked up numerous hours of listen time, many thanks to Danny of Surf Punk and Yamye of Asian Ska, who took the time to set up the player.
[SPEAKER_08]: and on most occasions felt that each of the great Konami's honorable franchises has been fairly represented in regards to each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: If the collection of 2DX music began to eclipse that of Guitar Freaks or Keyboard Mania, the system would quickly be brought back into relative balance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I think we have more 2DX music than any of those, but... I'm pretty sure we do, but I don't know if...
[SPEAKER_20]: But we do have a good selection of the others.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do have a good selection of most Bomani music.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, our society is mainly composed of poppin' music 1 through 8 fans, and out of the many times we have tuned in, we have only heard maybe two or three songs out of the well over 350 that exist, and we feel that you're not doing the license any justice.
[SPEAKER_20]: If I could find poppin' music songs...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I think I know a place where I can find some.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will make it my mission to download plenty of pop music stuff for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jean-Marc of Arty Pop has been especially traumatized by the imbalance and keeps running into walls, rambling about buttons that never were.
[SPEAKER_08]: To make a long story short, we've come to beg you to add more poppin' music tracks to the lineup.
[SPEAKER_08]: All we ask is maybe two to three a month until the series catches up to its brethren and its long-lived potential.
[SPEAKER_08]: We repeat, give the poppers the representation they deserve.
[SPEAKER_20]: You asked for it, you got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You asked for it, you got it.
[SPEAKER_20]: We've got the space for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This week on Orange Lounge, Politary is out, Poppin' Music is in.
[SPEAKER_20]: But my personal request, we need Poppin' Music and a Melo stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to have the Cutie Honey theme on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will make it our mission to go find ourselves some Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, here on Orange Lounge, we always go out and buy the legit soundtracks before we put songs into rotation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to go right now and order soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_18]: We will order them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as soon as those ordered soundtracks are in our possession, we will rip them and play them for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, I will have mine rushed overnight so that they get here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will have them rushed overnight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, we shall do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a fabulous idea.
[SPEAKER_20]: We will make sure that they are sent by a special electronic courier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, electronic courier.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I'll repeat my comment.
[SPEAKER_18]: End the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, we're going to end the show, but I need to cue up the music real fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: So is this tonight's fortune for you right there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so I need to ask really fast, though, if you guys have any final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, do you have any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_20]: Those taquitos were good, I have to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, enjoy the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, any final thoughts from you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I just looked up one of the older games I used to play, which was One Must Fall, and they're making a sequel to it, so just go check out onemustfall.com, or omf.com, and check out One Must Fall Battlegrounds, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that the old school epic game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, the old school epic game they're turning into a 16 player deathmatch giant robot fighting game that's going to be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: So go check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: OMF.com Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I don't really have one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need a date still.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We at the end of the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're back.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to hear the fortune cookie
[SPEAKER_12]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as Dark Sakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Prepare for trouble!
[SPEAKER_02]: And make it double-double!
[SPEAKER_02]: Quit imitating us!
[SPEAKER_02]: To protect the world from devastation!
[SPEAKER_02]: To ignite all peoples within our nation!
[SPEAKER_02]: This is insulting!
[SPEAKER_02]: To denounce the evils of truth and love!
[SPEAKER_02]: To extend our reach to the stars above!
[SPEAKER_02]: Ash!
[SPEAKER_02]: Misty!
[SPEAKER_02]: And Brock!
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.