[SPEAKER_00]: It's a videotape!
[SPEAKER_00]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_08]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our live talk program begins now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boring!
[SPEAKER_08]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hide Orange Lounge radio from the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_05]: My kind of people, and assholes.
[SPEAKER_05]: One.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mischief by that much.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's Dr. Evil's cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: How can you tell?
[SPEAKER_00]: I never forget a pussy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would like, if I may, to take you on a strange journey.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Sky, Orange Lounge Radio We are live and this is episode number 18 for November the 3rd of 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny, during the intro in here, if you sit in the studio, when it comes to that part where it goes, My girlfriend's got 37 dicks, everybody in the room all at once goes, Try not to suck any dick on the way to the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tuned in to the Bomani Scene's most wonderful radio station of all things Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello as well to our newest co-host.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not really, because he's been here since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's our sim god, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with us tonight in studio is always our most special guest in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to Dave.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's our pet brownie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave brought us brownies tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are buying us crap tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting pizza from Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got spongy brownies from Dave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does life get any better than this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I have Propella.
[SPEAKER_07]: Life is good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except that stupid fly needs to get the hell out of here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know a lady who swallowed a fly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why she swallowed a fly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's doing this whole karate kid thing here, trying to catch the fly.
[SPEAKER_07]: For our listeners, a fly has made it into the studio and it's going to die sometime during the duration of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll be talking to everybody more a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, we're going to take an opening break, and we're going to play a bunch of stuff from Max USA, because that is the big news this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Max USA finally hits shelves this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of surprises in there, including a lot of really great new tunes, and we're going to play some of those for you right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go on Orange Lounge Radio, a whole block of Max USA songs, and we'll be right back to talk about Max USA.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a long way to go, honey.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm afraid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are we going?
[SPEAKER_14]: Into the dark, black forest.
[SPEAKER_07]: We interrupt this music for a special announcement.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki has killed the fly.
He has dropped the bomb.
The Closest Diner, what it takes is a service call, we make a few mistakes, what we gotta do is so momentum, if we need the right tools and best, it's right the way, it's not copy the rhythm of the market, it's just we gotta get with it, the rain is setting on my car, you can do it now, you're not the mango collar, yes I already hate that ball, I'm using it to call the rock and ball, yeah, rock and ball, rock and ball.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, tune in to hear live train wreck radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Watch all your favorite monster hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki, engage in the Bomani Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_03]: This Sunday, Sunday, Sunday, at 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pacific Time, heads will roll and arrows will scroll.
[SPEAKER_03]: May I be suitable for children under six, pregnant women, retards, and residents of all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_00]: Ready for the race, are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're already listening to Orange Lounge Live Radio, but I hadn't played that promo yet during the live show, so I thought I would.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do six-year-olds and retards have to do with it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just decided I'd be random.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you listen very carefully, it also says residents of Baltimore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're picking on Baltimore because when I pulled up the stats for what cities listen to us the most, Baltimore was in last place.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're picking on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is a bummer because Baltimore is where all the John Waters films are set.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you know me, I love John Waters, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I hope you enjoyed the Max USA crap that we just played for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't crap, it was more like diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max USA just came out this week and we're all happy happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was really special.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed we have a lot of new people listening tonight, so I thought I'd point out some things for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to join our chat room, just go to any Other Side IRC server.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to just put in your server as irc.eggheads.org, or you're going to put in karma.othersideirc.net, either one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where all the big Mamani chat rooms are, and you're just going to join Channel Pound, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's where the cool kids hang out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're too lazy to get on IRC, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're making an effort to keep our Yahoo box online while we're doing the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can just shoot us an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio at Yahoo.com and we'll check that box throughout the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's for all the cool kids in the email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to be a cool kid, don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: While we're talking about, you know, station news and events, as you noticed in the beginning of the show, we have decided to make Loki an official co-host now.
[SPEAKER_07]: May as well, he's here all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, this guy shows up, he sits over here, he gives commentary, we give him a segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't even let him sit in a chair.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here, ask it over.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like last week, there's people outside the studio here fucking honking at the neighbors.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't care!
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my gun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, now... This is my boomstick!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that... God damn!
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody fell asleep on the horn out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me.
We realize that your horn works, but we don't need to hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I'm very happy to be the... Oh yeah, speech, speech, speech, speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for all the little people.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the little people that support me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it just me or did the horn get quieter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it died.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it was a pathetic horn.
[SPEAKER_07]: I put a fear of DS into them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my bat?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have neighbors, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have neighbors.
[SPEAKER_07]: That horn gets a fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do the fuck you's of the week a bit later.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it stopped.
[SPEAKER_04]: It stopped.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's fine now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, Jamie can be polite, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, did you have anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: I could have said, thank you, bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They started up again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish we had a microphone outside, but we don't, so the whole listening public out there is going, what the hell are they talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Live on the horn, Mike.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie finally shut the window.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, right now I'm having Dave play my DDR Max save game so he can beat my Onis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you suck at the Oni.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate Onis, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I incredibly hate Onis, and when I found out that you have to play the Oni courses to unlock songs, that really pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you don't have to, but if you want to get them like this month... I unlocked a song by failing one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something, that was the first thing that made me think, gosh, this game really is for Americans.
[SPEAKER_04]: That you get unlocks by failing things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, good effort.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just got Gradius Cyber today, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song was Zinkonomics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love getting unlocks from games I already own.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my one bitch about Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, don't get me wrong, great game, pretty kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the best home releases they've done yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really haven't decided if I like Fifth Mix more or if I like this one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's definitely, by far, better than either of the other two games we've got so far in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have been cool if they had a databank with saved edits.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what makes Fifth stand out for me, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only problem is they would be all Konomics or DDR USA edits, which would be totally pointless because, I mean, you can't play them on the arcade machine, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, I don't know, it's pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Oni courses are alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't like them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Playing them off heads sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just like being able to see them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if I wanted to play Oni, I could.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want them to be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe have, like, one song unlocked with an Oni instead of, like, you know, the two last songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The songs you want most of all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I can't possibly, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Steal the steps and put them in sim files if, you know, I can't play them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now can I?
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of which, you want to give a plug for your big contribution to the scene this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I would say I was helping NMR and those people, the crew of people that were supposedly making Max USA sim files.
[SPEAKER_02]: This crew seemed to have pulled out two files, while myself, in like two days, pulled out 11 files.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we time you last night?
[SPEAKER_04]: It took you about a half hour to get out, you leave me alone, like all six difficulties, single and double?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, singles and doubles, it took me 34 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I went to bed before you finished, but... Yeah, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also finished last night, you know, the other five.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, everything's up except for Drop the Bomb, System FX, FX Mix, and... System SF.
[SPEAKER_02]: SF, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: System San Francisco Mix, and the... Come on, girls, it's time to drop the bomb!
[SPEAKER_02]: and the Do It Right two-step harmonized mix or whatever the hell that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: The decent version of Do It Right, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You like the original?
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the original.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a fan of the original.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the bass in it better.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm entitled to.
[SPEAKER_07]: So deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can like whatever you want, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except let them move.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one's allowed to like that song except Gwen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I say so.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the chick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're the chick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look, the horn drove off.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you looking at, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki's... The fly is still... Oh, he's looking to see if the pizza guy's here.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the fly, by the way, which we left twitching on the windowsill, has managed to slide off and is stuck to the edge of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have prop... Now the fly is actually dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was the fly's last moment on this earth.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you in hell, fly.
[SPEAKER_07]: The fly is now splattered against a propel bottle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave's back in the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Dave.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say about Max USA, Dave?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Black Forest is really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I do like about Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what they did right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't just do it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did it fucking better than right.
[SPEAKER_04]: The licensed USA tracks fucking rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Black Forest is one of the best Bomani songs ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I will cut you if you think any different.
[SPEAKER_04]: and You Leave Me Alone is something, it sounds like it's right off like a Dance Mania album, but better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know who thought to license those songs, because I certainly never heard them before, Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know anybody that did know those songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you said you thought you'd heard Dark Black Forest before, or somebody on this show said they heard that before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'd never heard it before.
[SPEAKER_02]: They announced it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very hard song to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm very concerned because the trucker there looks like a guy walked out with a bag of something and went to that other house.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably cocaine, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I swear, that's the one thing they did right, was those license tracks, Rule, I don't know who thought to pick those.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were cool, except for I Like To Move It, which that song sucks!
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hate that song!
[SPEAKER_02]: I Like To Move It, reel to reel.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to say that that Move It song, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I just want to say that they could have done better on making the songs harder, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Sandstorm, I wanted it to be hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like Freeze Arrows, they went overboard on the Freeze Arrows way too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, if SCK was here right now, which he's not, so he can't bitch at us whenever we make fun of Max USA, he'd say, that's what edit mode's for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I know, but they went way overboard on the freeze era.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're like, hey, we've got a new mode that we can use.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me make you steps.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sandstorm is a cool song, but they made shitty-ass steps for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They needed to do the do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead, they were like, freeze, freeze, note, note, note, freeze.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the thing I was disappointed in is there's no new katas.
[SPEAKER_02]: None at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was kind of weird that there's no new katas, but I guess, you know, that's to be gentle to us, you know, stupid Americans.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the fucking horn again.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I beat the adrenaline honey for Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's the pizza guy honking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki ran to get his pizza.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then we'll get our pizza and then shoot him.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get our pizza and throw it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll pull a Braveheart on him.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll throw artichoke hearts at the... I'm going to eat those.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about the old... What do you think about getting old Dance Mania tracks and tracks that were licensed for Japan and getting some of those on USA?
[SPEAKER_04]: I must admit...
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was fucking cool that Captain Jack was on Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the coolest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was feeling really crappy when I started playing my game, so I only thumb-bumped it and didn't get very far into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, Brilliant to You, Orchestra Groove was on there, so that made me instantly a happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_07]: And me being the only person who likes to love that feeling, I was ecstatic to have that song in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dave has just unlocked it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Two-step harmonized.
[SPEAKER_02]: How'd he do it?
[SPEAKER_02]: He beat the adrenaline, Oni.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he really?
[SPEAKER_02]: So guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to see a sim file for that on my site tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You heard it here first, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy, happy, joy, joy, happy, happy, joy, joy, happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you notice the interesting use of some of the recycled videos, like how Love This Feelin' has the Let's Groove video in it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you looked into it that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just happy it was there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan was there, and I didn't want to torture him with the multi-genre, multi-tempo song, even though I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twin says he loves Love This Feelin', and he made me play it on Wednesday's little thing, which is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what to think about that, because he also likes Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I actually, you know, you've got good taste, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you were missing it, this is one of the reasons why you want to listen to Orange Lounge, you know, throughout the week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: On Wednesday night, when we picked up the game, I came in here and had this elaborate setup in here, and unfortunately, Jamie was at home playing it herself, and Loki wasn't here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie was at home sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie was at home sick and playing it for yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just got on the stream, fired up the Orange Lounge stream, and just started playing it on air and playing all the new tracks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you listen during the week, sometimes you get little surprises like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So listen to Orange Lounge all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would still like to say that I'm still having an open commission, I guess, for someone to make me Dynamite R5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that JB made you that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... In the way that you imagined it in your head.
[SPEAKER_07]: A professionally styled mixed one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't like JB's version?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was special.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, JB.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was special.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not quite the way I envisioned it to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we actually play that on a show?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, then maybe we ought to play that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know if I still have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: You made JB cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no, I, look, it was good, but it's not how I envisioned it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you'd have to sort of read my mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: New one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, a new one.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's a good one that will work?
[SPEAKER_07]: How about mixing Holic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holic.
[SPEAKER_07]: With...
[SPEAKER_07]: Stoic.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not stoic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Missholic with, Mixholic with, um, um, um, um, um, Gentle Stress.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holic doesn't really mix, though, because it's, uh, different measures.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on seven.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two, it's seven, eight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Era with Gentle Stress.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gentle Era.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Era-sensual mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: If someone can make me a good mix of era and gentle stress, I'll give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we can't use the word sexual in a game, we have to use sensual.
[SPEAKER_04]: That pisses me off, because that's why they can't license any erotic songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember saying on DDR Freak a while back, why not just call him exotic?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think somebody ran with that, I've heard that used again lately, but you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really would want to see something like Kiss Me or Temple of Love in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we've already seen those songs in DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: A year and a half before I had even heard of DDR, there was a song that my friend sent me called Don't Talk Dirty, which was the very first erotic song I ever heard.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I would like that to be in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song owns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll play that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would make me a happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to put Lollipop in DDR Lollipop, Lollipop No, not that No, the DJ Alligator Project Lollipop Suck on my lollipop, I wanna lick it Last week on Orange Lounge Hunters I'll bring that song, it's awesome Black Lab has announced he'd like to see Dr. Dick in DDR Help me, Dr. Dick
[SPEAKER_02]: Max, don't have sex with your ex.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, they have the 2003 one or 2002 version of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, on the new Dance Mania Red, or not Red, uh, EX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Mania EX one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Dance Mania Extreme!
[SPEAKER_07]: I still fear that, you know, I hope what Dan said doesn't come to pass for DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, once they release a series of games, then add Extreme to the end of the most recent release, that means the series is about to die.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if it's coming, it's gotta be the final.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it had to be like, you know, DDR extreme, super duper extreme, fun, dance party, final mix, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or something like that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, DDR happy crack mix, and have it all happy hardcore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's play some Tetris, motherfucker
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, could that mean that they're going to be starting over with some new kind of dance game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God's 8-panel DDR or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR 2DX?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, then we'd have Technomotion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, is the pizza here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was a false alarm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dick with the horn.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Dick with the horn.
[SPEAKER_04]: He hasn't honked in a while, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but if he does it next week, I swear I'm going to go over there and cut off his hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then if he uses his head, I'll just cut that off too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we'll make him eat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, we hear a yes from the other room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I wonder what Dave got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave might unlock something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other thoughts you have on Max Rosen?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, I have to give a big pile, you know, a big six-bar box of kudos to Jason Enos for those funny little blurbs whenever you unlock a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whenever you play a song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, some it works with the unlocks, but I think that it's mainly when you actually play the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to read one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this is for when you unlock So In Love.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, You have unlocked the song So In Love by Caramel S, oozing with stories of love just like melted caramel over a hot flame.
[SPEAKER_04]: This down-tempo song has elements of 70s pop, smooth jazz, and lounge all rolled into every bite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yum!
[SPEAKER_04]: That is so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just that they have yum.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three little letters add so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there another one I have here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, this is another one that's very popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is already posted on some message boards.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have failed game mode for the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a result, you have unlocked the song Celebrate by JJ Company.
Celebrate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you can celebrate your first failure in style, but don't give up on your dream to be the ultimate dancer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, by the way, is one of the most god-awful songs I've ever heard in DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Celebrate!
[SPEAKER_14]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this is information mode when you... Oh, anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll play that later, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll play Celebrate just to torture everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he just beat Candy on quarter stage, so I unlocked Candy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now he's playing home base, the Oni, the 17 song Oni.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you get when you beat that, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you get a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's, um... Is there anything else you haven't unlocked yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Spin the Disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Spin the Disc, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Spin the Disc, and the last one's Drop the Bomb.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it's Drop the Bomb, you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drop the Bomb is in this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's been confirmed online.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to beat the 21 song order to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it starts off with a three-footer, and the highest thing is, uh... The hardest song in there is gonna be Midnight Blaze, Maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tal says that failing an Oni gets you gentle stress.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a really funny information that says, like, Oni mode can be so stressful, but, you know, smooth out with a sensual song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I remember that one because, of course, I failed my Oni on the first song because I don't like Onis.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: The ferret hates them, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Arrgh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anything that you wish you would have seen on Max USA that didn't end up making it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nemesis?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what happened to those songs?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember on an early list, we had Nemesis, we had a remix of Superstar, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am not at all unhappy that the Superstar remix is not there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you hate that remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the one, the M2 step from Six Style?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was an M2 step, I believe that was supposed to be in there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder what happened to those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I think More Deep was on there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, let's see what else was supposed to be on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: My guess, if anything, since, you know, they probably did have some data for those, Max too, that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe somebody can go into the disc and see if they can find images for Nemesis and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised nobody's thought to go in and see if those are in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure people have thought about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they're working on it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a guy that I talked to on DDR Maniacs that was doing, like, hex editing on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was, like, a cracker at one time, so he's, you know... Cracker!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he's supposed to be going in there to rip the high quality backgrounds and stuff and the videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we'll see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be cool if they could find that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because didn't somebody go into USA Mix and actually found a bad girl's background without the gun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also, with the aid of GameShark with Konomics, they found modes that were in the fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because they basically ripped a fourth mix, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but they found all of the challenge mode and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was kind of sad that Challenge Mode didn't make it into Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Challenge Mode was evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's what they kind of called Oni Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was always fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a challenging mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just love the picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to cry about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And remember, there's STDs in DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you notice though that when you're actually playing the game that it still has the little characters, the Asian ones?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, whoops, somebody got lazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also on the high score screens it says DDR6.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it's kind of so subtle because it kind of goes with the whole little theme, the modernization theme they had going with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't really notice it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's still cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get us wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just glad that, you know, they would have had to put it on a DVD for as much crap as they put in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is on DVD.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I mean crap in a positive sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it was nice crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it fertilizes your, you know, music addiction.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only other thing, the thing that kind of also disappointed me about Max USA is that the box, the back of the box says something like it links up with Konomics for special stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically what it means, and when you read it in the manual, you can load your edits from Konomics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: You could, but they just wouldn't show up.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing I was kind of laughing at the whole time while playing DDR Max was how much they're advertising for Konomics.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the information screen, it's like, Go buy!
[SPEAKER_02]: Go buy Konomics!
[SPEAKER_02]: Go buy it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_02]: Go!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Konomics is probably down to $19.99 by now, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think most of the PS1 games are.
[SPEAKER_07]: At last check, Konomics was at $29.99 at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would imagine eventually it'll probably go down to $19.99 though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: As most of the PS1 games probably will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eventually, but it still sells.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I'm sure it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: No question about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're hooking new people onto DDR, I suppose why not let them know that Konomics is out there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, they didn't try to sell any copies of USA Mix, but that's okay because USA Mix was kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was better than I would have expected for a first release.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, if you keep in mind, they were testing the waters.
[SPEAKER_07]: From what I understand, Konami had little faith.
[SPEAKER_07]: The DDR was going to be that big as it is now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you've noticed each release has been progressively better.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now we have exactly just about the same copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a better one that was released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree to an extent about the first mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they kind of should have already known from success in the arcades, from rabid followings such as DDR Freak, things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact that import machines are more popular than the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: machines, I kind of would have expected a little bit more faith.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they really didn't have that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the fact of the matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: It took convincing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we have it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney Mix, on the other hand, was an improvement over the Japanese one, I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was missing some of the good songs, but it had Maniac Mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really liked playing the oldies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I loved playing Mr. Bassman.
[SPEAKER_07]: I loved playing Surfing USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate the Macarena, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sort of understand, you know, why they couldn't license them, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: They took out Fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping that they do... Not Fire, they took out Electric Light Parade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they took out the Electric Light Parade, which is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the one I liked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of hope if they do do a Disney mix, too, that we'll get the catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never.
[SPEAKER_07]: I miss battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss dance battles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Battle, Dance Battle from Second Mix, Dance Magic I actually almost missed couple steps Having couple steps, like Second Mix was the last one to happen that I understand Didn't Third?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, maybe not Well, I mean, you can always do couples edits But it's not the same You know, I miss going up to a DDR machine and having to tell it to do verses
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember going up to the 1.5 and holding my buttons down so I could play in versus mode so that we could have the same nifty little steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of miss it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost miss having to stomp around and do a code to put in Maniac.
[SPEAKER_07]: I miss being totally messed up when USA came out because I was so used to playing on flat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, we're going to take a real quick break, and then we're going to come back, we'll talk a little bit more about MaxUSA, we'll talk about some other stuff, you know, while MaxUSA has been kind of taking all the news, kind of taking everyone's attention lately, there's been other news going on too, so we'll get to that, and a whole lot more, we've got a listless segment for you guys tonight, so do stay tuned, and we will be right back for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to start this off with a song that we kind of referenced a little bit during this last break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Touch me with your love and give me satisfaction When we get into action but don't talk dirty Take me in your arms and go for my obsession Give me all your passion, don't talk dirty to me Oh touch me, don't talk dirty to me
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: I need your satisfaction Touch me with your love and give me satisfaction When we get into action But don't come dirty Take me in your arms and go for my obsession Give me all your passion But don't come dirty
[SPEAKER_14]: Dope, Maya, Sash, Gimme
[SPEAKER_04]: Rockover London, Rockover Chicago, Orange Lounge Radio It's a good place to listen to the music That's not going to make sense to anybody unless you were listening that one Friday night Anyway, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_04]: And we've been talking about Max USA, and I believe Dave's in the other room right now trying to get through with the 17 song Oni.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's on home base, the 17 song Oni.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's on song 11 at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's passed all the hard stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing that I would be iffy on, because I haven't actually seen him in play yet, is the Do It Right, Two Step Harmonize, and the very last one, the Drop the Bomb System FX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, has he not even played that Do It Right mix yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Big news for us locally.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a tournament Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huge NorCal tournament this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you want to talk about this Saturday's tourney?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are having Sack the Money host another fabulous tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be, the festivities begin at 10 o'clock at the Scandia on Hillsdale.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hillsdale and I-80.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's Madison and I-80.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can find Madison and I-80, you can find Scandia.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's right off the freeway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Registration starts at 10 o'clock right when the place opens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Accuracy attack starts at 11.15.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not perfect attack, accuracy attack.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're having two lines.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are having plenty of prizes, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, tell us about everybody who shows up has a chance to win huge prizes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm estimating already I'm bringing in at least 300 or 400 DVDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least, and probably even more than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So why don't we have an opening stipulation for the first, say, 20 people who pre-register?
[SPEAKER_07]: They get a DVD?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or something, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so, yeah, as you heard, about 300 to 400 various DVDs that we're going to be giving away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, we're not going to lie, they're not like cream-of-the-crop type DVDs, but they are good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's great good stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot of anime stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's not all anime though we know not everybody who's into DDR is an anime fan like I don't know shit about a lot of animes but there's some other stuff in there too there's some great sci-fi stuff bling bling and things like that just tons and tons of DVDs are given away so just show up because you might win something I mean there's a very good chance you're going to walk out of there with something first 20 people who end up pre-registering are going to walk away with a DVD as well
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, at least for $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we register, we'll get a DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, going to be tons of prizes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we want to talk about what kind of prizes are going to be given away?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the special things that have been donated?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or are we going to talk about that later?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's still going to be secret with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, there's going to be secret.
[SPEAKER_07]: You will find out day of turning.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, we are going to make, as Orange Lounge, we are going to be making a donation of a prize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Orange Pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Orange Pack will be donated as a prize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is going to be donating an Orange Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we've already bought one of the things for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and... Is that the pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: That wasn't the pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll take another break pretty soon then.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for those that cannot make Shaft, because we know that we're an international show at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have lots of listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks a lot for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Canada as well, got a lot of listeners, eh?
[SPEAKER_04]: And where else do we have a lot of listeners I've been noticing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Australia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Australia, yes Australia, Australia, we love you A place I am dying to visit someday Australia, we have a lot of listeners there And all over the globe, thanks to you guys for listening If you guys can't be there, that's okay We will bring Shaft to your living room
[SPEAKER_04]: or your computer room or wherever you have your computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are going to be broadcasting live from Shaft all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: The stream will start probably before the doors even open sometime at 9 or 10 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_07]: We might get bored once we have everything set up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we might get bored once everything's set up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll sing a little song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's going to pretty much be in charge of this because Jamie's kind of the queen of the tournament so she's going to be running around like a chicken with her head cut off making sure everything's in order.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the empress, what you talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm going to be kind of emceeing the tournament with my buddy Tal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be up there doing the emcee duties.
[SPEAKER_04]: So when Tal's doing the emcee stuff though, I'll be in the back helping Loki out with interviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: But pretty much it's all going to be on Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So welcome aboard as co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now do eight hours of radio all by yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotta catch up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, anybody who wants to, as you come off the stage from Perfect Attack, from Freestyle, whatever... What?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Accuracy Attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta get in the habit, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, this ain't your mama's Perfect Attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: As they come off the stage from Accuracy Attack, or Freestyle, or A-Team Freestyle... You just so sounded like Cartman.
[SPEAKER_04]: A-Team.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm calling it Perfect Attack if I want to, bitch!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jeez, Carmen!
[SPEAKER_04]: As you guys finish, you can just walk right into the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be escorted into the office and get the shit beaten out of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll be able to be interviewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forge Lounge will tell all your friends to listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you are there at the event, you can't listen, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll rebroadcast it probably at least twice on the station at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I can get it to archive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't guarantee it'll be rebroadcasted, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might not be able to get it to archive.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've just got to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Get you guys all to listen on Saturday if you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I burped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to add about Shaft, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be there judging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you're doing the A-Team stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we got to plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to do interviews while you're judging for A-Team?
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got Rice Princess and Brad, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have them helping out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, BR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Raving Reporters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have lots of people helping out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if you want to pre-reg, that's open right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: The address for pre-registration is ShaftStaff at Yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make sure, though, that you actually look at the webpage first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to SacPayMoney.com slash...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sack09 Just go to SackBomani and follow the links.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is the actual site.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is the actual address that the pre-reg information is on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, you can just go to SackBomani.com click the link, click on Shaft and look there too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I always like going directly to the site because that's just me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, go ahead and have a look at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make sure, though, that you do not leave any information out if you do not know what song you want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, the songs are located under the rules section.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, accuracy attack songs are up.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at, or AA in this case, I'm looking at the blink of an arrow a lot of the time to get the tempo, so I would kind of be fucked in that aspect, so it makes it a little more difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I would love to see you try to do something in Dark Reverse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, sucks that I'm going to be up there doing, I can't participate because I already know all the songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to be at Scandia before then.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to see you take the shaft challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I can handle shafts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see if you can get the shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I might like getting, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whale.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whale.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that special?
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Accuracy Attack, very game show.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way we've got the brackets set up, very suspenseful, at least as much as a DDR tournament can be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't rely on what we've named the categories.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got category names are starting to float around out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say three people, I believe, on the planet know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Literally three people know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Literally three people know what are in those envelopes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And only two of us actually have them written down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and only two of us actually were there to write them down.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Scandia doesn't know what's in those envelopes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: The best PA-ers in the nation don't know what's in those envelopes?
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't be told either.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can try bribing me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It ain't gonna work.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm like, let one song out for $90.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to wear a big sequined jacket to do the MC.
[SPEAKER_07]: You totally need to do the Rod Roddy outfit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on down!
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on down!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're gonna take a really quick break because there's food here and we want to get some food.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're gonna play some Groovalicious 70s tune to get everybody in the mood for a shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we'll come back and we're gonna talk some more about some other DDR things going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hope you guys can tune in on Saturday
[SPEAKER_04]: Saturday, starting at around 9 to 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: for the Big Shaft livestream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: And now DJ, let's start rocking it, rocking it, rocking it
Whoa, hello, sorry gang, that's a bad mp3, so we're gonna just go right into the next song, sorry about that
DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_14]: And when you wake up late thinking it's a dream The best thing for you, no, you can count on me, believe me There's a lovin' lady, you know what you found in me
[SPEAKER_08]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were just talking about Sak Bamani hosting another fabulous tournament, also known as Shapt, which is going to happen this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty soon already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe it's already here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Max USA DDR Max USA
[SPEAKER_02]: All that they did was, Max 2 has been announced for the Japanese system, so we know that for a fact.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now where people are getting their information is from GameFacts.com, and they said that it's been announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be honest, I don't think it's credible at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, yeah, there probably will be one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it hasn't been announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling the angst in this room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking it's about time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, we're going to do some FUs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's do some FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the part where Jamie likes to go off and F something.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I had to go off and say, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck them right in their nose, because their ear and their ass aren't good enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and if you want to send your FUs of the week, just send them to me over in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can PM me over in the chat room, and we already had some people do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can alternatively send us an email, but you've got to do it right now, because we only do this segment for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio, that's all one word, at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, my first one of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's the fly, but the fly's dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's the asshole with his horn, and I hope he dies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said what mine was going to be in the car, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_07]: On the way over here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, license plate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan comes home last night and proceeds to tell me that our license plate is missing off of our car.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's nowhere to be found in the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the whole plate around...
[SPEAKER_07]: The license plate is missing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, we're thinking it's either been stolen or has just fallen off, although it's kind of funny that two screws would fall off at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, this actually, my fucker of the week is in, you know, for my man's benefit, that he has to spend however many hours at the DMV tomorrow to get that replaced.
[SPEAKER_07]: My poor sweetheart.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm going to hear about it all back tomorrow, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the worst part, is that now you have to deal with the bitching.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drive your ass to work, and then go to the DMV, and then come back and work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some days that we don't let the line move at all, we call those weekdays.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, another fuck you of the week goes to this cold that just seems to be refusing to leave me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm at the dead tail end of it and I'm still getting all I want to do is sleep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm taking a nap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, um, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they're not very big, powerful, evil fuck yous, but they are, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of those things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, thank you for people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that all your FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hear it from Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got any FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a new song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, I called this actually before the show, so for people that were recommending it during the show, I beat you to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, first FU of the week goes to Konami and DDR Max USA.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate Onis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, people like Onis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like Onis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like the fact I have to play Onis to unlock songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just play the game for months on end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got other games that came out the same week, like Grand Theft Auto Vice City.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're beckoning my attention and not playing this stupid game constantly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've double-a'd almost everything on Heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need to fucking double-a everything in this whole game and still be playing and songs are still not unlocked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dave just beat, you know, the home base, you know, course, and the new Hardcore 21 still hasn't been unlocked.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess I gotta play some more songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't unlock Hardcore 21?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it didn't unlock that at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess I gotta play about 500 more songs before that fucking thing gets undone.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you got to see the Drop the Bomb remix, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me add that the Drop the Bomb remix, while the song is cool to step, suck ass, and the backgrounds, they took no time whatsoever to make that background.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, yellow stick, you'll drop the bomb, background, and put System SF Remix on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoop-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's my complaint.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember Brilliant to You, when they put out the orchestra groove, they just made it in pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they changed colors, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, shit, they didn't do anything for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, yeah, that's my complaint there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Onis, you know... Oh, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Part 421.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took a 40-minute Oni, so if I fuck it up like 30 minutes into it, I gotta play it again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not gonna do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one should have to play a 40-minute Oni, and that and the fact, who's actually gonna have a homepad responsive enough to actually play a 40-minute Oni on a homepad?
[SPEAKER_09]: You probably have to go through a couple of homepads while playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like you've burned out a whole new one just from playing that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would feel bad for anybody trying to do that, like, not on a controller or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even on a controller, your freaking hands are going to cramp up, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, F Konami for their... I mean, I like the fact that they put Onis in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what the hell are you thinking, putting 21-song Onis and 17-song Onis?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like my 100-minute-long Oni.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, does Dave have an FU?
[SPEAKER_09]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, this is better.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, my FU also goes to Max USA, even though I've just played it like half an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also towards the Onis, but for a different reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like them, but damn, I've got like Carpal Tunnel now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not just that, it's the fact that the backgrounds are really bright and really flashy, and so my eyes are really... You can turn that down in the options screen, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't know that after like three minutes, and I'm not going to go start over again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, to start over I have to play all the other songs again, I'm not going to do that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, FU, Oni, on Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: And how do you unlock Hardcore 21?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to basically give head to DDR Max USA.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially since it doesn't have either.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a few, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: My first FU of the week goes to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: For getting me addicted to Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I have to go spend money on a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so I can have those annoying little assholes move into my neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob lives in my neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_04]: And an F you to Belle the cow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bitch, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did Belle do to you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Belle's the nice one, Petunia's the bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, an F you to Petunia, she sucks too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And an F you to Mallory because she won't move out of our town.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, Rob sent me fruit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I mailed... He sent me an apple.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mailed Jamie some fruit, and I mailed Dan some fruit, which he got.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan sent you clothes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Dan sent me clothes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I sent you rags.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, F Jamie for getting me hooked on that crack rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: My other F you goes to Psychos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Psycho is online that want me to do dirty things on my webcam.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop messaging me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop mailing me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to stalkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now there's a difference between showing a little attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like attention, but stalking, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop stalking, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate when I get runs in my stalkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's all my FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I really have anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll think of something later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, FU to myself for sleeping through half of Halloween.
[SPEAKER_04]: And FU, FU just like last week, FU to all my friends who get drunk while I have to drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: My god, Twen, you've got too damn many.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only reading your last three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twen says, F you, uh, from the manager to a dumbass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to be hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's seventh mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twen says, F you to another dumbass.
[SPEAKER_04]: To me, I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every song he picks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, F you to Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to release more PS1 DDR titles in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: BlackLapSaga
[SPEAKER_04]: F his roommate and his now girlfriend for once again getting naughty while he was in the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: They went a bit further this time because moaning was heard, even over his headphones, and they ignored him when he threw a bottle at them to get them to stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that was my suggestion last night in the chatroom, to throw a bottle or poke him with a stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going for more of the poking with a stick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next time, set them on fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: See if they notice.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, F everything that contributed to his inability to go to Shaft this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead, he will be paintballing for his birthday, and he will not be able to listen to the broadcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's your choice, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck his left side shift key for sticking so much lately, and fuck the fact that I still have no car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of you know what I mean by that, and if you don't, too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should hang out in the channel more.
[SPEAKER_04]: More Than Jay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that slash emote sex doesn't work in real life.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never used a slash emote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's... No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that an AOL thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: And being sick and depressed sucks hard, so fuck that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what sucks worse than that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Get back to my music for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Having the flu and PMS at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucks more than anything has sucked before.
[SPEAKER_14]: La la la la la la la.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, this is the DJ... I just had to say that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mine tops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Women in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twin also says F you for not owning a PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just wants to clear that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then get one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Conundrum, a new person listening to the show, says, fuck you to the damn commies in the sky that watch me in DDR because DDR sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to me for consistently changing names in the chat room because it was flipping back and forth between DarkSakura and Sky, so fuck that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's because I'm not at home.
[SPEAKER_07]: When?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, our buddy, who's sometimes here during the live shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder why she's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes me cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to people who bring their babies to the 11pm showing of the movie The Ring last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're hurting your child's ears as well as pissing off everyone who wants to enjoy the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I have something along those lines too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my music?
[SPEAKER_04]: You and your music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Dan and I were at Fresh Choice today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoying our lovely salads and soups.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had really good acorn squash soup.
[SPEAKER_04]: French Choice is a rip-off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: They charge something like nine bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to get my fuck you, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me have my fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This woman was... Do you still have that PMS thing going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is fucking weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Girl, I'm going to drop the bomb on your ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, um, this little kid makes a mess.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, little kids make messes.
[SPEAKER_07]: This woman comes up, her mom comes up to her and goes, Oh my God, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: In the middle of a damn restaurant?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Dan and I look over.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: And the thing is, is that you know who Dan and I are blaming for?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is not the little girl we're blaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her mom for being such a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, fuck you, whoever you were, woman.
[SPEAKER_07]: She didn't even look like a bitch, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that weird when, like, people just look like a bitch?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you can just tell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Some people should not breed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jerry, Jerry, Jerry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I get back to the chatroom FUs now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have another new person here, hello to you, it's EOSFVB.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's some kind of acronym, I don't know though.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, fuck you to AMD for making a 2.7 gigahertz.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I get it, it's going to have this huge heat sink and fan, which is going to make a lot of noise, making him crazy, and also will exhaust a lot of heat, which will fuck over the whole global warming thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't run the heater.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really have a choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone else gets cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do.
[SPEAKER_04]: On Halloween, Dan and I were taking his dad out to dinner for his birthday, so that was more important.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I was watching Friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we were at Red Lobster.
[SPEAKER_04]: IT vote Survivor, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get to watch Survivor until the next day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to Sukjai for voting out Sheehan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that means nothing to the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: JB says, um, F you to the little kid at RVGL who likes to grab asses.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joe Mama, I think this is a good one to end on.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, my fuck you is to school because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I don't go.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that don't know, I graduated high school several years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish you were that simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm too old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too old for DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the fact that I have to go to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I've had a whole week off.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, F you to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't had a week at all and I still don't want to go tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had Friday off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was so nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could sleep until like 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was supposed to meet Loki at like 9 and whoops, I slept.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that we've gotten those 5Qs out of the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I need to check the mail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if we got any over email.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to give them the courtesy, because not everybody loves the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: No 5Qs over mail, so... Fuck you to the listeners for not emailing us.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't think of anything that rhymed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I brought up in one of the FUs, Survivor, a popular program on CBS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of CBS, segue, segue, we have the early show finally happening tomorrow from what we're being told.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been delayed not once, but twice now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to happen on Halloween and I had the whole TiVo set up to tape it and lo and behold, it didn't even happen because I guess it rained or something so they couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The early show is like CBS's answer to Today, you know the Today show?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this like a brand new show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you know Good Morning America?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's like, you know, the early new show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, yes, you're right, Loki, they just re-tailored the show recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got rid of Brian, well, Brian Gumbel quit, I think, and the other chick got let go, and they have like a panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the hell, but they're turning it into The View.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically, now it's the early show, but it's The View.
[SPEAKER_04]: But with men.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, for our listeners who are unfamiliar with my habits of watching TV, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, just thought I'd clarify that for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if somebody brings up a show to me, I'm usually going to go, what's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or a commercial, I'm going to go, what's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing I keep up with is Buffy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I haven't watched Buffy since the season started.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I have to watch Buffy because I need to see James Marsters naked, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need Spike.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, CBS, early show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been delayed, but I guess it's finally going to happen Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you guys are up early tomorrow, you should watch this, provided it doesn't get delayed again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps I should check some of the big news sites and make sure it didn't get delayed again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess there's going to be some folks just out there playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what arcade machine they're going to be playing or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the best dance!
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so we have the early show tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet you it's going to be like, it's going to be one of those things they show in like cutting the commercials and then maybe they'll just kind of briefly mention it for two minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll probably interview DJ 8-Ball or something and then, you know, we'll get to hear about it for weeks and weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, did you see that DDR was on CBS?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God, it was to DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, oh my god, they played Oops I Did It Again on MTV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomani on TV, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what MTV needs to play?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Hot Limit video.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, that video is so much ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, you know what, we need to set aside a little bit of space and put the Hot Limit video up on the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think at some point we're going to need to, because that video is like the fruitiest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.
That's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think I got one more FU coming, and it's for somebody that I like, Vandalus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he'll have to PM that to me, so send that over, and I'll get that FU in there before we go to another segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving along, would you like to do a sim update, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: But no, keep your eyes on your TV people who are inclined to do so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, for anybody who actually posts on the Sackman Money Board, if you go to the Leading Cyber Forum, there is a link to this commercial so you can download it for yourself and watch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's absolutely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as cool though as the Gacked one, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: For one of the other Metal Gear games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember if it was Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just going, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Gacked commercial was so funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll make that available somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll make that available.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gacked is the hottest woman.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have to say while we're on the topic of commercials, the one with Donald Trump and Grimace for McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm clueless.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I'm clueless too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't watch enough TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever since I got TiVo, I fast forward through commercials.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know... I'm a whore for TiVo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That shit is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know... I have this theory, and I posted this on DDR Freak a while back.
[SPEAKER_07]: That the McDonaldland characters represent different factions of the franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ronald represents the company itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: The all-encompassing whole.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have the early bird, who represents breakfast.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have the fry guys, who represent the fries.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got Mayor McCheese, who's the cheeseburger, and Big Mac, the cop, and the Hamburglar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ronald isn't the crazy psycho who likes to lure children into his playlands.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan and I have been trying to think of what the Grimace represented, and we finally realized it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what McDonald's wants its consumers to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big, purple blobby things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this like trying to compare the Wizard of Oz to the Dust Bowl, that whole thing in history class?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that where you're going with this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, kind of, but no.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other thing is, you know, the McDonald's franchise wants us all to be dim-witted, slow, and fat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And live off of their food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where, you know what my impression of the Grimace is?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the expression you make after eating there.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but like, it's Donald Trump and Grimace.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't get a better couple.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's too cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Donald Trump.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe Ivana and Grimace.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Grimace.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, Grimace is what you get after eating a Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm making a gift!
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, I got Vandalus' FU, and since we like Vandalus, we'll let him in a little late, because we didn't get it before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vandalus says FU to politicians for filling his mailbox the past week with snail mail spam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vandalus!
[SPEAKER_02]: and for all those stupid fucking poster things that are out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear to God, there's like so many of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, it's like being in high school and seeing all the posters around campus, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, hello people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vote Jamie for class president.
[SPEAKER_02]: She rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the number of posters that wins you the votes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a clue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your vote going to be based on something different there, Dave?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm going to go around and tabulate how many posters are up, and then I'll vote for the person who spent the most time putting them all up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God you're not 18 and can't vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember how that was in high school.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one year, I put up a poster that says, vote for me because I wasn't nominated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a late response to your commercial about the Metal Gear Solid commercial from 23rd Magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The truck has started to move!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, I love that!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, the Treadcafts started to move.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to take a really quick break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to come back and we're going to do a listless segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now you can participate through email as well, but we like it if you're in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead and join the chat room, any other side IRC server.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can join irc.egheads.org as your server.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can join karma.othersideirc.net.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're just going to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge is what you're going to join.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tonight, the list list is going to be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_04]: We decided we're selling out this week since Max USA just came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to pretty much suck Konami's dick tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what we're going to do... The views expressed by Rob are not necessarily those views expressed by the cast members.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much tonight what we're doing, we're doing best Konami game, not the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: So best Konami game that wasn't Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going old school.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or we're possibly going new school.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be damn near anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're being specific with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to start this off.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have an old school Beatmania song and a really old school DDR song in this mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to start it off with one more new school Max USA track.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Do It Right here on Orange Lounge Radio.
DMT is a tab, don't think what I suck, and T to bring something, don't sleep on the end, you see something like brother, it don't take time for me to blow your mind, it take a second to record because you dumb and block, so just laugh, but you're an empty cloud under the sun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: I like to move it, move it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You like to move it.
You like to move it.
I like to move it, move it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've been all over the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: And when you move your body, wanna move it nicer
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, letter A, and the number B9.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_04]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi-ho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cut it, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as promised, here we go with...
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight's list list segment, yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: This particular list list is non-Beinami Konami games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whether it be stuff that's been in the arcade, whether it's been in America, whether it was only released in Japan, whether it's super obscure, we're talking about them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh god, I love you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Freakin' press your luck.
[SPEAKER_07]: No whammy, no whammy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's so old school, this is cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're teasing you in the chatroom for saying Ben-Mommy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said Ben-Mommy.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you flubbed it up, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, my analysis is full of snot.
[SPEAKER_07]: You try talking with a stuffed up head like mine...
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we'll see, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I love you anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, best, and this can be as old school or as new school as you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave, your number three choice for best Konami, not a Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, my number three choice is an arcade game, Police 9-1-1-2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that game is cool, and it kind of defeats the purpose of having the game be called 9-1-1-2.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Police!
[SPEAKER_07]: If you think about it, the Japanese name was Keisatsu-kan, so... It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what's your number three choice for Konami thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally old school arcade game here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Ninja Turtles arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to plug so many quarters in that machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not even fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember one night being at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was, by the way, the same day my brother got hit by a car and was in the hospital.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, these guys paid me to play as Leonardo.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we got to the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had freaking... What was the name?
[SPEAKER_07]: Crane?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we had Shredder beaten and the other guy, and then they turned off the machines at Lab's Castle because they were kicking us out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only multiplayer game that I liked more than the Ninja Turtles was the X-Men six-player game that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that was Konami, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, my number three... Jamie's number three.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by the way, I picked games that I own because I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost said Gradius II, because everybody knows how much I love Gradius II.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burning Heat?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, instead what I picked for my number three was Kid Dracula on Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you play as Super TV Alucard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn, that's old school.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, and you know, the thing is, is like, if you look on the old Funkoland lists, you know, when they used to have the prices on those pages like that, the game is a $30 game, even used.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's really hard to find.
[SPEAKER_07]: If anyone can find the game, you can get ROMs, though, for the Famicom, the Famicom ROM, online.
[SPEAKER_07]: If no one's ever played it, check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number three pick is Castlevania II, Simon's Quest.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game was the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you if you don't like that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two was the bomb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they completely fucked up the first one in the best ways possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the music owned and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Castlevania II it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number two pick is Gradius, the original.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: From newest of school to oldest of school, Gradius for what, Nintendo Arcade?
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter, I'm not putting systems down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: The reason why I'm specifying systems on mine is because a couple of games on here did have variations from system to system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, we'll be okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess arcade is... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, is there any particular reason, Gradius?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, number two?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, number two... I'm gonna have to go with Dracula X.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, Dracula X, which one, the one that they put on what, TurboGrafx, or which one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one, the number, Castlevania 5, or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's on PlayStation, I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, okay, that'll work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dracula X, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well... Dracula X...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that was my number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a duplicate, so what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, Loki's going to change it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that then?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll just go with Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metal Gear Solid, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Switching gears and putting Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you're number two big.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number two, Sexy Parodius for Saturn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sexy Parodius.
[SPEAKER_07]: I came close to saying Olshaberry Parodius, but Sexy Parodius just kicks its ass because you can play as Winby and Twinby and the guys on the paper airplane and the little bunny girls riding the rockets.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game is so cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what other game can you totally destroy a Las Vegas showgirl in?
[SPEAKER_07]: And a pirate ship with a kitty cat face on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see in the chat room, I see Guardian Legend being mentioned.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should point out that's not Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guardian Legend was made by Irem.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's made by Irem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Broderbund.
[SPEAKER_04]: Released by Broderbund.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who were the same people that made Lode Runner.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you remember Lode Runner, you're cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number two pick is Life Force.
[SPEAKER_07]: Life Force is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Salamander series.
[SPEAKER_04]: The honky version of Gradius II.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it wasn't really Gradius II, it was Salamander.
[SPEAKER_04]: Life Force was Salamander.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But they called it Gradius II here, in America at least, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was Life Force.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember they kind of... The reason why I know this is because I found my Nintendo cartridge of it last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, for my number one pick, I had Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, good pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would have been on my list if I didn't already know you were picking that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I had trouble coming up with some Konami games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I just really love that game and the music owned, and the fact that you can play as Alucard and I think Richter and the girl, I forget.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can only play as Maria on the Saturn version, and the Saturn version had two extra levels.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can play as Maria after you... Well, that was a rumor, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it ever really was possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing about it is that Maria was supposed to be playable on the original, plus they had the other two levels done.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you notice, there's a little trick you can do when you first run into the corridor.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you go back to that first corridor and stomp on this trapdoor, you can go down the trapdoor to a save room, but that save room leads to the underground garden on the Saturn version.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, a little bit of trivia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Strider is Capcom, we should point out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frogger is a Konami game, but I think... I think somebody else put it out and then Konami distributed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Atari?
[SPEAKER_04]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's one that Konami distributed a version of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they were just the distributors of it or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: It hasn't showed up on the list yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm torn, but I'm going to have to go with Contra.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go with Contra Shattered Soldier because that's the brand new one and it's everything Contra should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except very, very, very, very hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess Contra's supposed to be very, very, very, very, very hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number one is Dracula X, Rondo of Blood for the PC Engine Duo
[SPEAKER_07]: Game was not released in America.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, for all of you who own the Super Nintendo version, I feel so sorry for you because it's totally butchered.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dracula X Rondo of Blood has the best music ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: The best levels ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is like... And I actually... My friend had to pay Dan and I back for...
[SPEAKER_07]: DRACULAX
[SPEAKER_04]: Very popular series in Japan, but they didn't do much with it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They released a couple games, I think, but I swear this is... I'm naming the American version of this because this is the one I remember playing as a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: This version was the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had Gradius in it, you might remember, in one little part.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is The Legend of the Mystical Ninja.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Legend of the Mystical Ninja was like the best Super Nintendo game they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe next to like Actraiser, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do have to offer an honorable mention to a series.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Konami World series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami World.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were released in Japan on the Famicom.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were basically, you play as two generic characters who could go to different Konami games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had a Castlevania world.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had a Gradius world.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Kingdom Hearts Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was kind of like that, but it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, that's also one that you probably will have to find in a ROM now because it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami!
[SPEAKER_04]: Police 911 Part 2, Ninja Turtles Arcade Game, Kid Dracula, Castlevania 2 Simon's Quest, Gradius Arcade, Metal Gear Solid, Sexy Proteus, Life Force Slash Salamander, Castlevania Symphony of the Night, Contra's Shattered Soldier, Dracula X, The PC Engine Version, and The Legend of the Mystical Ninja.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but you get to start it off, Dave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still live for Castlevania 3, or Super Castlevania 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, Loki...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm never really a fan of a game where the bullets travel like 20 miles an hour, so I'm going to have to take off Police 911 too, because bullets are supposed to travel at bullet speed and not at fly, slow paper airplane speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the one I was going to eliminate, Daniel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you not mention, did you forget to remember that you're Superman, you're faster than a speeding bullet, so everything moves like slow motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: bullet time alright, Jamie, your turn god life force is so freaking hard you know, I'm thinking about see, I have memories attached to all of these games that's the sad thing
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to leave Lifeforce on there, just because even though that game is harder than hell, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Symphony of the Night is awesome, even though the Saturn version is great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra has the turtle with the fetus ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never really played the Goemon game, so I had to give it a boot.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I really... I'm just being picked on tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I've always wanted to, but because I have no experience attached to that game, I'm taking it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay, because I can get a little revenge, because this one was my next pick to go off the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: So my apologies to Jamie, but Kid Dracula, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Boy, I just don't have much sentiment attached to that game, and as Dave mentioned earlier, if you're going to have a Castlevania game on the list, it needs to be Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Dracula X is a good choice, too, but not Kid Dracula.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Chibi-Alo card with the spiky dragon ball hair.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it once, and didn't need to play it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when you hit them, they go, poof!
[SPEAKER_04]: I was considering Contra Shattered Soldier, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is so disgustingly beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so here's the final list you guys have to vote on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can send me your votes over a private message in the channel during the next song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Random note right there for you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm closing out all my windows so you guys can send me your votes.
[SPEAKER_04]: As soon as I post the list in the chat room, you guys can send me your votes over private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send them over to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can send them over email.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to do it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadioYahoo.com Jamie's going to read for you all the final list here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once it's posted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, go for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: As soon as you put those back up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the Ninja Turtles Arcade Game, we have Gradius Arcade, we have Metal Gear Solid, we have Sexy Proteus, we have Life Force Salamander, we have Castlevania Symphony of the Night, Contra Shattered Soldier, and Dracula X PC Engine Duo version.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we're going to play a quick song for you guys, and then we'll come back and... What, we're going to do Burning Heat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's kind of a cute one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me pull it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go ahead and do the one from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't usually play this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: We usually play the one from DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll do the one from 2DX, and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you guys have about two minutes to vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do two songs, and then we'll come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: See ya!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio or we will kill you.
[SPEAKER_07]: and your firstborn.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have the final list all prepared for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: The winners are, for the best non-Bamani, best burp goes to Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Jamie had the best burp two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: That one was really weak.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now they're fighting over this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before I get to the list, we'll answer this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're fighting over how many options you can have in Gradius.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're pretty convinced it's four?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can have four options in Gradius.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the Nintendo versions, you think there might have been only two?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think in the Nintendo version you can only have two, and I think in Life Force you can only have two.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in Gradius, you could have four options, because I know that there are some bosses that you cannot beat unless you do the straight line.
[SPEAKER_07]: I seem to... You are up, and you have your options trailing behind you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: Life Force was two.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Gradius.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know for a fact that Gradius was four.
[SPEAKER_04]: Life Force is a fucking car.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to my house and plug them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Eurobeat No. 1!
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, here we have our winners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we have our winners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jenny, in third place, what is our third place winner?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sexy Parodius.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is so freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like for the reasons I mentioned before, just because I like blowing up a Las Vegas showgirl and killing her to death.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Killing her to death.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, there's redundancy for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number three, we have Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, for those of us who imported it, it would be Dracula X2 Nocturne in the Moonlight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was officially in the Dracula X series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is a travesty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should have been number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You people have no taste, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drumroll, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ninja Turtles arcade game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have such fond memories of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: By somewhat of a landslide, might I add.
[SPEAKER_07]: My God, it got like, what, 65 votes, something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot for Turtles, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an okay first choice, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Symphony of the Night still should have been your number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for that, I reprimand all of you in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was so addicted to Symphony of the Night when it came out, but when the Saturn version came out, I blew through the whole game with Maria.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, she kicks Alucard's ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maria is so powerful in that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's very few places that she can't get to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um... There's also, though, I mean... What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just laughing at chat things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, you saw something I pulled in the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll let Jamie finish her thought, and then we'll go on to the other tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: My thought just got deflated, so you go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go on your tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: See if I care.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have my propel to keep me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pardon me while I eat on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nom, nom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: What other game could you get Castlevania with Metroid-style gameplay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you can't forget the cliche Ninja Turtles thing, which had, well, two things, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the pseudo-3D, it had the diagonal walking down part, you know, where you had, like, sort of, you're going towards the camera, but not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you also had the jet hover skateboard things, for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's always going to be the Turtles people versus the Castlevania people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Turtles in Time was cool, and fuck RVGL for getting rid of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually before... They need a Castlevania arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was close between Ninja Turtles and the Simpsons arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Simpsons arcade game was one I'm surprised didn't make the list, but it's the same engine as Turtles, so it's pretty much... I think a lot of people maybe are thinking Simpsons when they vote for TMNT.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Propel, Ghetto Kool-Aid, but not
[SPEAKER_04]: Propel, the orange lounge choice of drink while playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another random note.
[SPEAKER_04]: A new test version of Max Extreme, or Max Extreme, DDR Extreme came out this week, and apparently Sakura has been removed as the extra stage replaced with another paranoia, and Black Lab would like me to take a minute to tease Loki about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tease, tease, tease.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your response.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, the machine's not done yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if they've had the song done and completed, and it's a Konami original...
[SPEAKER_02]: Why wouldn't they put it in there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, there's going to be 200 fucking songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be in the goddamn machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might not be an extra stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, guaranteed it's probably not going to be an extra stage because that would be kind of redundant.
[SPEAKER_02]: You play Max and you play Max again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that would be kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's going to be in the goddamn machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revenge, the song's done.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Konami original.
[SPEAKER_02]: What more do you need?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's Loki's official response.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dave has another random note he wants to bring up before the show's over.
[SPEAKER_09]: On a side note, I AAA'd the Remember Me or Remember You, what is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: And nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You obtained the highest dance level.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't get shit for AAAing anything, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you get one of the earlier unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something you've already unlocked by playing enough songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and one more random note, because I promised you guys I would mention this in the chat room, I talked about this at the beginning of the show, somebody asked, when is Orange Lounge going three hours?
[SPEAKER_07]: We've been discussing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been discussing this, and we are going to up the show to three hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to start... Eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to tell them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's tell them.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will start that with episode number 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 20 will be the first three-hour show, and that is, by the way, in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week, we're going to be just too fucking exhausting after Shaft, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have a lot of Shaft wrap-up, a lot of interviews, a lot of out-of-towners next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be a big show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the first three-hour show will be in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, what do you want?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit, man, we're doing an eight-hour show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and Jamie's got some things she's talking about for the afterbirth here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, for the afterbirth we'll go a little bit old school so I can, you know, let you know about one of the greatest and least appreciated systems ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and give me some more, everybody go around and give us your final thought, because I'm still trying to get the show, end of show wrap-up in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, final thought, actually, I didn't get to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really not too much going on other than the DDR Max USA DWI is coming out, thanks to me, and Team Guilo Max, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, speaking of Team Guilo, they're gone again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where they went.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's news to me, so they're just bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: And X-Step Release Candidate 4 is out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also probably going to be version 1, so go check that out if you use it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And see, other than that, I'm going to be getting back onto the 2DX project, so I'll have more of those 2DX sim files coming out for you guys to play on StepMania.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Dave, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_09]: Homework blows ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: MaxUSA, if anyone knows how to get the Hardcore 21 unlock, tell Rob, or post it, so I can look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides your random coughing fits.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of you people, go play Kid Dracula.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll love me for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play Kid Dracula in Konami World.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go obscure, because I say so.
[SPEAKER_07]: And drink Propel.
[SPEAKER_07]: And come to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought of the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come to Shaft, and I need a date.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to be playing more music for you after the show's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned with us on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks a lot for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Y'all be going on vacation?
[SPEAKER_06]: See, the thing is, if you about to be up off this bitch, check it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Peep Delta.
[SPEAKER_06]: We be flying all over this bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me ask you something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You fin to raise up and get your travel on?
[SPEAKER_06]: From the interior to the exterior, you've got to get your posterior in one of these big-ass planes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark, you lay in the cut straight sitting on your ass and getting your drink on and your snack on while we floss and fly this mofo all over this bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: East Coast, West Coast, it don't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nia will get you to your hoe and back lickety splits.
[SPEAKER_06]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'll be back at your crib chillin' with a flat spliff, thinkin' we was some crazy-ass angel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, these fat, round, thick-ass vessels run up in the sky so deep, it be cryin'.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you thought it was rain.
[SPEAKER_06]: So bring a towel, cause at Delta, it's laid out like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call one of these fly-ass Delta coochies, and make all them punk-ass co-workers of yours catch the vapors as you be off and about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.