[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki Tonight, December 19th, 2010, Cataclysm sells oodles and oodles, a crime victim calls for the ban of Mafia 2, and K'nex's first sex game gets the smackdown from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet, and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: December 19th, 2010, episode 394.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Join us live in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be with you over the next few hours with my co-host, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing well and energized and electrified.
[SPEAKER_02]: Electrified.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, you sound, I don't know, like you've just been to Xanadu or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I saw Tron twice this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wasn't Tron amazing?
I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'll get into that in a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have to introduce, of course, the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, fine You know, I remember a time when you really hated all things Apple And now it's funny, because at the start of the show I'm always having to tear you away from that new little eye touch you have Or you've had for a couple months now No, you see, I hate all things Mac, not Apple Oh, my bad Because Apple, too, was a pretty awesome computer back in the day It's true, it's what we all played Oregon Trail But I'm sorry, all those Mac computers are way too damn overpriced
[SPEAKER_02]: Making friends, and we're not even five minutes into the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the three of us here in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, no guests joining us, but it is our last show of the year, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to be here because of the holiday next week, sadly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, but some of us are going out of town, so we're not going to be able to get everybody together to do the show next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's our last show of 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, don't worry guys, we'll be back, of course, in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have plenty of show to go to tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we always like to start things off with, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: But, can I just say, OMG Tron, like, wasn't it great?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you got to go see it, what, Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_02]: How'd you swing that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Jessica Harper had an extra ticket.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, she was on the show a few weeks ago, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and she let me have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so we all went.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oomph.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the best part?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, without spoiling, because keep in mind there's a lot of people that are like, OMG, you don't want spoilers, so is there a way you can kind of say the best part of the new Tron movie without ruining anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I like how everything flowed together.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'd have to say that I have a favorite line.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: As we've discussed earlier, but I'll go ahead and repeat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The cycles haven't been good, have they?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice, very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you got to see the Trons as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was Tron for you?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just everything I was hoping it would be.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I would definitely see it again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And everybody here saw it in 3D, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, this is a movie that it is totally beneficial to see it in 3D because I'll just say Wizard of Oz Treatment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's not all in 3D, but it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, I would just say my favorite part was how they upgraded some things from the old movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can I say this without spoiling too much?
[SPEAKER_02]: But okay, y'all know there's going to be a light cycle sequence in it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And when they did the whole light cycles, but some of the new stuff they did with it, like I'm doing hand motions here in studio, I was just like, oh, that is so cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so fucking badass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, but I'm trying to be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you actually go look on the Tron Wiki, they do explain that they're all different models.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the interesting though, just kind of tie it back to what we're all about here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made me want to play the game like really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the game has not been kindly treated by the critics out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been getting like average reviews.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when I say average, I mean like a six, which I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually when a game gets a six, that means it's really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: The movie is only getting like a 40% or something on Rotten Tomatoes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not a movie for critics.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to win Oscars.
[SPEAKER_02]: The dialogue and story are all nerd service.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I honestly think like I walked out of that theater.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just like mind blown.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a movie worthy of like Star Wars, Star Trek, nerd opus, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on top of that, if you have seen the first movie several times and know it very well, and if you've kept up with some of the roundabout stuff, even some of the old deleted scenes, there is a lot in this that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, I actually went back and was listening to the soundtrack a bit, because keep in mind, I have the original soundtrack for the original Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, but the new soundtrack also.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I went back and gave it a solid listen, some of the elements, especially for character theme songs, were incorporated from the original into the new.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have to say Daft Punk did an astounding job.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I realize when people listen to the soundtrack the first time, they're like, this isn't like a Daft
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not meant to be
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm not being a fanboy it would be a crime if Daft Punk didn't get nominated for the score because it adds that much to the movie like we don't need some artsy fartsy film stealing one of the nominations for score you know that's kind of like the same old same old that you always hear in a period piece this is something like really new and different I really hope it gets acknowledged I'm gonna spoil one thing there's nothing after the credits oh yeah okay that's not much of a spoiler
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but you know what else I really like too is how they gave the Disney castle the Tron treatment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really want to go see the Disney electronica thing, which I still haven't seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have friends there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were supposed to go this weekend, but it just didn't work out, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm glad we didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: It rained the whole damn weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: It got rained.
[SPEAKER_07]: They shut most of it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had friends that went down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They still had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm bummed I didn't go.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, I had a great time at the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just awesome time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went and saw it at the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They think that's what it was and I walked by.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still an arcade in the movie theater and there was an arcade upstairs, the Tilt Arcade, which is right by the Walk of Game, which is still there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they've updated it in a while, but it's still there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of sad because they're selling all these arcade machines, but seriously, some awesome deals.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Marvel vs. Capcom machine for $300 on sale right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Beatmania 5th Mix, which is like the old school Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't tell anybody because I'm going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: for $5,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a total rip-off.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm totally lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really this much.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but Jamie wants it, so I'm not allowed to tell the listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this was the funniest thing of all, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: going to the little claw or what not the claw machine you ever seen the ticket redemption machine where the light kind of goes around the marquee and you have to hit the stop button at a certain time and if you hit a stop button then you win a prize okay i posted this to my twitter do you know what one of the prizes was in there still in a sealed box a game boy advance e-reader machine with cards
[SPEAKER_02]: I lolled so hard seeing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think everybody, after going to see the movie that I went and saw it with yesterday, went online and started reading about Tron and who the actors were in the movie and how it tied into the 80s version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that nerd-tastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, how was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actual video games outside of Tron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not because I'm still playing Star Trek Online and you can call me an addict for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Double addict.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not addicted.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I said I'd give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was like, I was seriously this close, again, to just going, forget it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, by this close, I mean like holding my fingers, you know, a half an inch apart.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, stupid goat people, world sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though I like playing goat people.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm leveling faster, so I don't know what's up with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's cool chatting with everyone in the guild and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It still seems more of the same to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm giving it a chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm somewhere new.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob gave me some stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to play for a good month now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well... And it still looks the same, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, I didn't make it there last time I played.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what's the name of the stupid... Darnassus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Darnassus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it still looks like Night Elf stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Darnassus wasn't touched by Deathwing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to... He didn't take a big poop on it?
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But once you take the boat to the ruins of Albertine, which used to be Albertine, you'll start to see some of the damage and some of the better stuff, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I figured that I'm going to do that when I get, like, 20 and I'm, like, what, 14 now and I've been playing three days?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah you've been doing very well
[SPEAKER_07]: 2 weeks to get to 20 last time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm gonna keep going with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'll try.
[SPEAKER_07]: But like I said, you know, it's not something that I can keep doing consistently.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm keeping my attachment to Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, by the way, Episode 3 of Star Trek Online came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gorgeous, gorgeous, gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once Cataclysm settles down a little bit, I still want to go back and check out Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully DC Universe isn't out by that point and derails everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still want to go check it out a little bit, especially since they've changed so much since the beta that I originally had played.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to try out the new stuff, but I'm not going to buy two boxes of upgrades unless I'm sure I'm going to play a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_07]: And even then, if I play, it's going to have to be in the form of month cards or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still ridiculous that they're charging so much for Wrath of the Lich King, and I think that will come down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kind of have to wait it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably after the Christmas rush or something, it'll come down to try and woo new players into the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's kind of what I'm hoping for.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'm not going to give up on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, like I said, if I keep playing it, it's going to be, well, I'll buy a month card to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm not getting rid of my Star Trek Online subscription unless STO just starts getting ridiculously crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: and right now though my frustration with Star Trek Online is that there's really not a whole lot of new stuff for new characters and I want new factions.
[SPEAKER_07]: They sort of teased that we're supposed to be getting Cardassian faction so I can keep up with the Cardassians.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's a bad joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not the first one to think of it either.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to play the Romulan stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're doing a lot of big stories for the Romulan factions.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really, really like what they're doing with the story because they're putting something in it for everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's like...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll say, oh, and by the way, they did this in Star Trek Online and this, this, and it led to this story and this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And she's like, sounds like you're talking like, you know, well, she hasn't said right out, but I feel like I'm talking about an episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when they actually, when they bring everything up, it's like the way everything flows is like an episode of the show just without acting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good because just as someone who is a fan of the Star Trek series, not counting Enterprise, I really wish they would have another show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really want there to be another TV show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that right now it's all about the movies and that new movie was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I would just love there to be a new show in the next-gen Voyager canon, Deep Space Nine canon, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like... Well, you know, and I've been going back and reading the books.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the continuation books, which is really where... And this is going to be kind of a... I'm going to try not to veer too off the point.
[SPEAKER_07]: The book universe is very different than the game universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: The book universe is sort of like it's its own tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: What I like about the game universe is that it incorporated the first movie by saying that this is what happened in the prime timeline.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the movie, as I said, is a new timeline.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they can keep going with all these characters that you love and, you know, history that you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'd really like to see, you know, even them do like a comic series or new series, you know, involving the Star Trek Online universe or maybe the stuff that happened in between.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they've incorporated some of the Enterprise stuff in there too, you know, even though I think it's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been very, very happy with Star Trek Online, but like I said, I'm giving World of Warcraft a try.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like my goat girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's dressed like a hoochie right now, but she can burn things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do like, and I think this is new, the arcane missile thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not new, but you... It's new for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything is at different levels now, so you might be getting it sooner than you would have before, because they rearranged everything when they did Cataclysm, and some people get talents at a really early level that they wouldn't have seen until level 40 before.
[SPEAKER_07]: This Arcane Missile thing, they're just like, here, have this for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: And you don't have to, it's just random.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can randomly cast it and it doesn't cost anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's instant.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can kill lots of stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thinking you specced for it somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of, yeah, usually those free things are usually some type of speccing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, that's spending talent points.
[SPEAKER_02]: You spent your talent points.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I had it before I got my talent points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play a mage, so I have no idea how it works.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll double check my stuff real quick because it's not going to show anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did pick Arcane Path, but I had everything before that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's important.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to veer off the path too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I lost my pet, I don't know how to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do think it's important for WoW veterans to hear how newbies approach WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I think sometimes the WoW veterans just assume people come into WoW and they know everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think it's important that if you're a veteran of WoW, you sometimes kind of hear what the new people are really thinking and some of the challenges and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me look at chat room really quick because we want to get some questions out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quick question from Breakman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are the Star Trek cartoons canon?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, the animated series is considered canon.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breakman is also asking, do newbies still have to go find that wife in the Barrens?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play Horde, so I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still have to get the stupid mushrooms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hate the mushrooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Due to the shift of Burning Crusade, or I'm sorry, due to the shift of Southern Barrens being its own zone now, I don't believe that quest is there anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stupid, stupid mushrooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: But see, that hasn't changed, but you'll get there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and then someone had to start in Badger, Badger, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was already in my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, is there any games you've been playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you don't play any MMOs right now, so what have you been up to?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been just playing Grand Theft Auto and Sword and Poker 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Playing lots of Sword and Poker 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and I did actually play a little bit of... Now, it's a little confusing because I have both Tron games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have the Tron Legacy game and then also the Tron game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I played Tron Legacy a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You race around in light cycles and the recognizers.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't like tilt steering.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate tilt steering in everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, it's not, it doesn't feel natural.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you must be playing it on PS3 with the six axis or what?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, on the iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought these were the retail games.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just tilt steering on the iPod to steer the bike.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I prefer my finger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's pretty much it, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't play a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's too busy yelling at Comcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the internet's been down for still, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You were down last week and you're still down, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're dumb, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll just put it that way and no, Comcast really doesn't care despite the fact, you know, what certain Twitter people will say and how they may seem concerned and ask you to email them and then they don't give a shit once you've emailed them, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just slightly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be canceling TV with them, actually, because I'm pretty pissed off.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's not working all the way, too, because I can't use any of the on-demand stuff, because the signal's not strong enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thankfully, thank you to my new Virgin mobile phone, though, that I have rooted.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can now tie into the Wi-Fi on that to connect to 3G networks, so that has been a lifesaver, I tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: my gaming week has been mostly dominated with World of Warcraft Cataclysm I won't kind of go all the way back into it but I hit level 85 which is the new max level this week so shut so that's and I've been just trying to gear for heroics and I am geared for heroics now so I'll be doing that soon
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as other games go, not anything new.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just some of the same old standbys like Rock Band 3, Super Meat Boy, and some of those games I've just been playing gradually over the past month.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, with the holidays coming up and everything, my gaming time has been kind of thin.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the good news is, with the huge break coming up, I don't know about some of you out there, but I have been given at work, basically, the entire time between Christmas and New Year's off.
[SPEAKER_02]: our company does this whole like closure thing where we have to take time off basically which is you know I'm not gonna lie I kind of welcome it so it's gonna be a nice break but I don't know what to do with myself for like nine days off in a row I can't really afford to take any major trips right now so uh I guess I'll sit at home and play some games so that's good though because I really need to just catch up on some things so hopefully I'll get some gift cards for Christmas or something and go buy myself a couple new games and beat them that'd be great
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkCircuitry Internet equals Warcraft equals Rob's life at least
[SPEAKER_02]: Not totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, I spend a lot of my free time playing Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let's not forget, it just had a major expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Its third expansion just came out like last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So of course, you know, that's kind of the focus right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, that'll die down once I've really experienced a lot of the new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really plan on rolling in alts or, you know, getting through all that and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll have time to play a new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, I know how to go outdoors.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in the city all weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I do more than just sit on the computer and play WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that is a lot of what I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm growing in my netbook there you go stay connected and yeah I will just you know Loki and I will just be taking some time off for the holidays so we won't be here but we will be back the week after in the new year with a new show otherwise if you want to follow us on Twitter for all the updates about our show twitter.com slash OLR also be taking your Twitter topics there facebook.com slash orange lounge radio as well
[SPEAKER_02]: More comments from our chat room, chat.orangelongestradio.com Tigerclaw says, Sky will just play Cataclypse for nine days.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not going to play for nine days straight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to play a lot with the time off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to play the whole time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides, I have Knights of the Clicky on Facebook I've got to be playing too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone sent me an invite to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a real time waster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jim Sally in our chatroom says, if you're bored next week, Rob, do a show every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's three hours taken care of.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'd run out of things to talk about and then it would get kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would the listeners help me do a show?
[SPEAKER_10]: You can talk about all the stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's already a bunch of live shows at All Games Radio where we do our show, and obviously we wouldn't want to bump any of those shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have the right to.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty of fine shows on the network, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let them do their thing and we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: William Murderface in our chatroom says, I love that name by the way, Rob, you need a drunken Rocky marathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been doing Rocky for so long now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I need to marathon it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And JV Mon in our chatroom says, Oh yeah, more people need to play Pinball FX2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pinball FX2 is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Believe it or not, there is still some going on this week, even though it is the holiday period.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So apparently Microsoft is wanting, obviously, to improve upon what they've already created.
[SPEAKER_10]: They want to quadruple the Kinect's accuracy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the way they're going to do that is by unrestricting the camera from the 320x240 pixel resolution range
[SPEAKER_10]: to unlock it to 640x480 and unfortunately they can't do that right now because of the limitations put on by the console's USB controller interface which has to keep open enough to support other USB based peripherals like batteries and rechargers but if they somehow enable it to where you know they
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: so that's kind of cool and they said that can all be accomplished with a firmware update so um that is kind of cool and kind of makes you wonder why it wasn't there in the first place well they said right there it's because of the limitations of the console because right now they have to you know they have to play nice with all the other peripherals on there um I don't under well I mean I guess the USB controller so I was gonna say I don't understand why they couldn't just unrestrict the one port for the Kinect but um I don't know it would be difficult to do that uh
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as whatever they do doesn't impact the older consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that's my fear is that, you know, as they keep talking about, we're going to upgrade all this stuff for firmware.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to do all these upgrades.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, but if you have the old white Xboxes, then you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only going to work with the 360s.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just need the adapter that comes with it, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's just for power.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just have more power coming through there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess what they could do is say, when running the Kinect, you can only hook up one device or two devices or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that's the way they could get around it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little tricky, but I could see them doing it, especially if it's going to make things that much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time...
[SPEAKER_10]: We really need the games to be four times better anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not convinced that even if you make the technology better that there's enough games with really new ideas there yet to substantiate it, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Central is awesome, but as far as a lot of those other adventures and those sorts of games go, the fitness games, I'm kind of over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Show me...
[SPEAKER_02]: How Kinect is going to make my life as a gamer even more awesomer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, that's a term, more awesomer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, show me how Kinect's going to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kinect is still kind of a flashy...
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen it really truly integrated into the hardcore games that I'm used to.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: So at one point I'm kind of like, don't waste your time with this upgrade to the technology unless you have the games to kind of back that up that aren't just more exercise games and more dance games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I think they're just working on having that available for when they do get to that point as far as game development goes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, yeah, some of the stuff that is available right now, it's very basic with what they have you doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Central is a pretty good example of what it can do, but some other games that kind of just have these modes tacked on, like Harry Potter and stuff, where it's just an on-rails thing that you... It's very unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need less fitness games, less snowboarding-esque games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just some better ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dara Gage wants to give a cheap plug to connectable.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games are only scratching the surface.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at some of the stuff here that they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, I've been kind of reading about the hacks on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this website, connectable.net, seems to be kind of a collection of the different sorts of hacks that are out there, like lots of YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm seeing things like an air piano where you can use your hand to play the piano.
[SPEAKER_02]: on Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not exactly like a real piano, but still, it's an impressive little thing that they're doing with the technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta wonder if Microsoft's kind of letting this hack thing go a little bit just to see what people are coming up with so they can steal it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I want?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Kinect's theremin.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is me being serious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I really want a theremin.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe Kinect music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Since there was Wii music, let's have Kinect music.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually have it be good?
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's not, because once again we figured out that porting stuff over from the Wii or basically copying the ideas that you've done on the Wii is not exactly a great plan, because then a lot of these games just come out very cheesy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, even some of the games are just... I mean, like DECA Sports and Game Party.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's just...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's stuff that they have on the Wii right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need a ton of minigame collections and little sports compilations and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just come up with something cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And something that doesn't even necessarily need to use your whole body, like head tracking in a first-person shooter would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be actually really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's completely optional.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like to duck, you have to duck.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can like do that on your couch.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not even.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not even the ducking thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm saying like you can poke your head a little bit to the side to kind of get a different perspective.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a little bit more immersive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't take that much technology.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could you imagine time crisis done with head tracking?
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be cool, but I'm kind of sick of time crisis.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'm just saying, I'm taking that concept to where, you know, say that you duck under, you know, a divider and you can peek over it and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm just trying to think of a solution for, like, you know, people that want to play with controllers on a, you know, on a couch or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they can make everything very minimal and optional.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you don't have to have...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting comment because, yeah, Police 911 used a dance games technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically Para Para Paradise, the setup, to kind of do this different sort of game.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the, like, mo-cap boxing and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the whole mo-cap thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the same theory, but I'm saying that now with the Kinect, something like that is actually really possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, just like, you know, Para Para is possible in the home.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's that Dance Masters game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I need to get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I forgot to mention that for my thing, but I got a Kinect for Decemberween.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Festivus?
[SPEAKER_02]: Decemberween.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what you call it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to call it Decemberween.
[SPEAKER_02]: Decemberween.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to lend your own comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of comments there just kind of on that story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's go back to talking about WoW for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, guys, but I know some of you are WoW haters, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are going to like what they like, but you can't ignore this.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft shatters a record this week yet again, and probably to no one's surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cataclysm is sold...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm wondering, well, has Cataclysm launched in every country?
[SPEAKER_02]: But certainly there's a gap there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's only day one, I think, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, some people, you know, couldn't make it over the day or waited a little bit or they're getting as a gift.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think some people are honestly having to wait like a month because, you know, the economy the way it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's certain people in my guild that are like, I'm not going to be doing Cataclysm until the new year at least because just can't afford it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, I think there's a lot of people that just...
[SPEAKER_10]: Or is Cataclysm like a lot of that stuff like Endgame?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I could see maybe some people starting off there saying, eh, I don't need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of it is because the stuff that affected the pre-Endgame, you know, the 0-60 experience, you don't need this expansion to experience any of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was all a free upgrade basically because they destroyed the old world and ushered in this new one.
[SPEAKER_02]: However...
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole Worgen and Goblin experience, which are really well done starting areas, just as far as immersing in story and everything, you can't do unless you have Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can't do those new races.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can still roll a Draenei like DarkSakura is and at level 15 or whatever, head over to the other continent and experience some of the Cataclysm stuff without really needing the Cataclysm expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other important news out of Blizzard, and this isn't about WoW, but this could be about what ends up killing WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blizzard might actually be making the game that is going to kill WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're making their own WoW killer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frank Pierce, in an interview with Destructoid, confirmed that the earlier rumor was true that the next MMO that they are making is called Titan.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least right now, that's a code name.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, take a lot of that with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, more quote here in the interview with Destructoid, quote, The media is not supposed to know anything about Titan.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's our next-gen MMO, and we've only started... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, I'm kind of curious as to what this is, but they probably won't even do an announcement until like BlizzCon 2012 or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a ways out there, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's interesting to know that that part of the rumor was true, because I think I passed it off on Horde House's fan wank, so sometimes I can be wrong about things.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pac-Man Fever nah you remember that song don't you yes I do of course I remember that song well so do the folks that song's older than most of our listeners you know
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, so the folks at Rock Band, they remember it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, it came out the same year as Tron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the Pac-Man Fever album will be on Rock Band Download Content.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's supposed to be early 2001.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will have, as I said, Pac-Man Fever and Do the Donkey Kong and Froggy's Lament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just so you guys know, these songs were actually kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But pull up Pac-Man Fever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was popular when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember skating at the roller rink to this song.
[SPEAKER_02]: So do I. I'm totally dating myself, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: This song was really just written.
[SPEAKER_02]: This whole album was just little video game tie-in songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really just written to cash in on the whole craze.
[SPEAKER_02]: One-hit wonder band.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want me to find the 7-Up commercial.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've shown you the 7-Up commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, yes, a long time ago on this show, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't mind having some Pac-Man fever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skullcrusher Mountain Skullcrusher Mountain So there you go
[SPEAKER_10]: The other songs on the album sound kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't really heard any of those other ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been ages since I've listened to any of the other ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually did have that on vinyl back in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a collector's album.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, let me pull it up here so you can hear a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a little bit of Do the Donkey Kong if you want to know what this song's about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Pac-Man fever Alright, there you go
[SPEAKER_10]: So when the whole ESPN streaming was announced for, or actually I'd say when it came out as part of the November dashboard update for the Xbox 360, some people unfortunately were unable to participate in that streaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: And those would be folks that had Bright House, which is owned by Time Warner.
[SPEAKER_10]: as their cable provider.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, those people were unable to actually get the ESPN app to work correctly.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now it says, apparently...
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is coming from the ESPN website.
[SPEAKER_10]: The way it works, I guess, is when a Time Warner or Bright House user turns on their Xbox 360 and tries to access the ESPN app...
[SPEAKER_10]: it'll direct them to the ESPN activation page where they have to authenticate their account with Bright House or Time Warner then it'll be given an access code once you have that you would I guess you're going to be able to actually use the streaming service now so that's kind of neat that they're not locked out of it anymore I guess some money exchanged hands or something like that
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I always thought it was kind of weird that the whole Comcast logo was in the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, it knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's aware.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I know it's just reading my IP and so it can tell and probably the gateway I'm going through and what have you, but it always kind of struck me as interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I want to open this can of worms and make me sound even more ignorant, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to ask this question.
[SPEAKER_02]: is the reason how Time Warner and all these companies are able to block this because of the fact that net neutrality didn't actually work out or was like they they found that it's not in the courts or whatever that it's not actually exists that that neutrality shouldn't exist because part of me says well how can Time Warner block this when it's on the internet
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like how they go in the squabbles with Fox or whatever will be all of a sudden blacked out on a certain cable provider because they don't want to pay certain royalties or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it may have been that these, like Time Warner Bright House, didn't want to pay ESPN or whatever or...
[SPEAKER_10]: Something to that effect, I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, right, but that's also not the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it always kind of fascinated me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's TV content.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how that exactly works with streaming on the web and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you can get to it... Because I know some places you can't...
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't stream certain games on the web depending on your location or something like that because of blackouts.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a Time Warner user, would you be able to get around this just by spoofing your IP?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet there's websites out of there with more devious information than things I've read.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not really going to pay attention to this whole streaming app until they have ESPN8, the Ocho.
[SPEAKER_10]: with all sorts of extreme sports and Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, actually, I did try to watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember when Dodgeball came out and stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then shortly after that, they actually did have Dodgeball on one of the ESPNs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was boring.
[SPEAKER_10]: Goes to show you, it's just a movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not exciting in real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's an awesome 8-bit NES video game, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a Game Boy Advance launch title.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like if someone, you know, if for whatever reason they decide, hey, you know what, it'd be awesome if we have some people running around an arena throwing frisbees with little lights on the outside of them and playing tag, you know, kind of like Tron, but, you know, Disc Wars and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would not be fun to watch more than once.
[SPEAKER_02]: JV Mon in our chatroom asks, but Sky, why would you go out of your way to do that for ESPN?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're that into ESPN, you probably already have all their channels.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, but I'm going by that hacker mentality of because I can, and I'm not going to be told no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, isn't that kind of why people install Linux on toasters?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they can, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can't is not a suitable answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I consider that as I'm a power user.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, if I want Linux to be on my toast, then that would be kind of cool to put Linux on a toaster and then have it print stuff on your toast.
[SPEAKER_10]: If that were possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: They make a coffee printer.
[SPEAKER_10]: ESPN3 is a paid service that the ISP has to buy, so spoofing your IP won't matter because the content can't get through the Time Warner routers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucks!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, Rama in our chatroom says, Sky getting into ESPN, he loses 20 gay points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's lots of gay guys that are into sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, one of my best friends I'm taking to this game with me because he likes sports a lot and he likes basketballs and he happens to be too gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: More news going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation app on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not here yet, but here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: A PlayStation app has been announced for phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Sony Computer Entertainment Europe is releasing this, the official PlayStation app in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to be doing some PlayStation Network interaction through your iPhone or Android device.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could that be buying games and spending money and my points through the phone?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's got to be one of it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you're not going to be playing games on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: One would hope so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then again, we are sort of the red-headed stepchild of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is interesting that with all these rumors we've had lately of the Sony phone and the photos of it in action and all that, that they are acknowledging at least that the iPhone still has a huge-ass market share, so they ought to put something official on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they need to stop wasting their time with this crap and actually deliver on the stuff that they promised way back in the day before all this stuff was coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, for example, we would have trophy rooms in home where we can show off our trophies and they would be really cool interactive things and people could walk through and do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still not there.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do what you promised and stop wasting the damn time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki's a little bitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not that it matters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never go in the home again anyways, because it's a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll bag on Apple for a little bit for a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's why Game Center sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's so much trash out there in the App Store, especially stuff that is free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I kid you not, I downloaded a free app the other day, and the game itself is alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you want to unlock, here's how you get quote-unquote achievements in Game Center.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: there needs to be some type of quality control I feel like Microsoft's put a little bit more quality control in achievements granted there's some pretty asinine achievements out there too and some of them have to do with download content and things like that but I don't know I just look at Game Center and I go sometimes leaving this stuff wide open is a little too open but maybe that's just me
[SPEAKER_02]: sometimes I just go lolz going back to ESPN3 for a little bit because I find this conversation in our chat room humorous at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Derek H says oh my god I'm checking out ESPN3 right now World Badminton Championships enough said but I like Breakman's follow up they could have at least called it the shuttlecock tournament nice there you go chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to chat with these folks I know right
[SPEAKER_05]: How about something that has nothing to do with cocks?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boring!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, no, we can do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's been a call to ban Mafia 2 by the daughter of a Sicilian journalist who was murdered by the Mafia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the journalist was murdered, of course, not she was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her name is Sonia Alfano.
[SPEAKER_07]: She is a member of the European Parliament and president of Italy's Association for the Family of Mafia Victims.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think she, basically, she's still grieving.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it happened in 93.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her father, Beppe, was murdered in January 93.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically, it's dealing with the American Mafia.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, sort of like the Godfather and Sopranos, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that they, you know, were trying to make it sort of a more realistic type thing, yet still be entertaining.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily to glorify the violence in real life things, but to take the sort of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Fictional world of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: To take the fictional world of it, not necessarily glamorize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, I think this is a little bit too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't ban an entire video game just because something unfortunate happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't get me wrong, I'm not trying to disrespect what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's terrible that she lost her father in a crime like that so many years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I imagine that's something that you never get over, even though it's like 17 years later.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's letting one bad apple ruin the barrel, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_02]: At the same time, though, Take-Two's argument of, well, it's not the European mafia, it's the American mafia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's... I don't think that's specifically their argument, just that they're saying that it's set, you know, the whole Godfather Sopranos slash kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why I'm reminded of this completely random conversation I was having last night on the train.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Alan and I took Bart into the city to go to the Metreon to see Tron, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And while we were going down into the Bart Tunnel, I was commenting, wow, I have 3G signal in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't had 3G signal in Bart Tunnel, I don't remember when.
[SPEAKER_02]: They must have put a tower down here, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And he said, yeah, I think they put a cell tower down in the Bart stations a couple years ago, you know, so people could still use their phone when they're down here.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it met with a lot of resistance for a while they didn't want to put it in I was like oh is that just San Francisco being hippies again they don't want more cell towers no apparently it had to do with the fact that when the UK bombings happened back in oh...
[SPEAKER_02]: 405, sorry if I'm misstating that, but back when those happened, when those buses went off, that was all triggered via internet and Wi-Fi or what have you, wireless signals.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they didn't want something similar happening in the San Francisco BART tunnels.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I said, well, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, obviously...
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not arguing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just telling me the fact of the matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my response is, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: If somebody's going to do something stupid, they don't need 3G signal in order to be able to do it or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is my thing too.
[SPEAKER_07]: My granddaddy died of cancer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a problem with house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Must be lupus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just know that they also I've just picked something hospital related so
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have problems with people that smoke other than that they usually stink.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's how my granddaddy got cancer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the other thing I think this gal needs to take into consideration is that if she's upset about this mafia video game, is she upset at the movie that comes out once every three months at least that also glamorizes the mafia and the crime and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's an awful lot of movies...
[SPEAKER_02]: Books
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of books.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Godfather was a book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I think she's sensitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: She has a right to be sensitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand she's sensitive, but at the same time, you don't take that out on everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't mean you ban a game from an entire country because you have that whole response to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that it's people taking their personal... Honestly, this goes back to one of the biggest things that I think is wrong with the world in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes back to that...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very selfish, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm not trying to belittle her grief.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's like, especially with the whole political correctness thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: People spend so many time because one or two people are offended for something, but not the entire population.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orangeontradio.com, Frisbee says, Remember, 3G and Wi-Fi didn't cause those buses to explode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Explosives did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was kind of my point, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jvmon in our chatroom says, Does that mean Facebook will be taking off mafia wars?
[SPEAKER_02]: William Murderface says, Is she mad at Jersey Shore for making Italians look like asses?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a whole nother topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is my thing, okay, for example, and I actually get a lot of this living in California.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to pick something neutral and something light.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get the whole, oh, Alabama's full of rednecks thing, which I know for a fact it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm from there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I a redneck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Rob, you do get awfully excited over Chick-fil-A.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chick-fil-A's delicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, I'm kidding, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put the angry emails down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, you know, a lot of people in the South are uber conservative, Bush loving, you know, gun-toting rednecks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the stereotypes exist for a reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, I don't get offended because I know they're not talking about me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now if they said all people from Alabama are freaking rednecks and all that, I'd be like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Allow me to educate you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm saying that people, and I understand the concept behind wanting to make things better for other people, wanting to try to decrease opportunity for hate, if that makes sense, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same time, I think that people are a little too sensitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really like this comment and I think this is a good one to end it on and move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breakman in our chat room says people have the right to their opinions but they don't have the right to enforce their opinions on others.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the world just needs to be a little thicker skinned.
[SPEAKER_02]: chat.orangeloungeradio.com or you can always email us if you have an opinion on that mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com I'd actually be really curious about this and this might be a dangerous place to go but that's okay we'll be a little bit dangerous here on OLR I kind of want to know if there's a game out there that has ever made someone
[SPEAKER_02]: that has ever kind of offended someone in this similar type of manner?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not necessarily like, I don't want to hear your really upsetting story about something that happened in the family or whatever, but has there ever been something in a video game where you were just kind of like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They really shouldn't have done that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kind of curious if people can think of a case like that and email it to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm saying that now we should know what the warning signs are, know what to stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: There should be no legislation that forces one person.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something different when it's something that's beyond your control.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, now that we can learn from history, I think that that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think that people do need to understand that there's just assholes in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people are, haters gonna hate, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my favorite saying in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just gotta be a little bit better than them, but you know, ready to put the stop when it actually is something that you can do something about.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't change minds.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't change the way people feel.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can change how you respond to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of a comment here along those lines from Derek H in our chat room says, I did not like the airport scene in Call of Duty 4 at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was really fucked up and had no reason being there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat.orangeaudrey.com or our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was really offended when Rockstar Games decided, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: For the Ballad of Gay Tony, we're going to make all the deathmatch multiplayer into smaller closed-knit locations.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead, the open-world Grand Theft Auto... Oops, dropped my iPod.
[SPEAKER_10]: Closed-knit deathmatch locations, not the big old expansive open-world stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was very offensive to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure we're on the same page, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure you're quite seeing the same thing out of this topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some more games are coming out, and I don't know if there's anything offensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's the holiday week after all, but let's travel the world and see what releases are coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll start with the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a whole lot coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mostly download stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I shouldn't say mostly.
[SPEAKER_10]: All of it download stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're just going to talk about some download stuff instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: The normal console releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Monday you're going to get Cosmo Fighters on DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_10]: Darklight Dungeon on PC, FroBot on WiiWare, Mario Party 2 on Virtual Console, and Paul's Monster Adventure on DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_10]: December 21st, Battlefield Bad Company 2 Vietnam will be coming out on PlayStation Network and Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then finally on December 22nd, A World of Keflins and this is awesome, Back to the Future of the Game on iPhone, Mac, PC and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully Steam is having another Uber sale this holiday too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So keep an eye on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, if that's it for the US, let's travel to Japan and look at the Japanese releases and what's coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 22nd of December, Cybertroopers Virtual on Force comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a regular and a box set edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Twin Stick EX coming out in support of that game as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's all coming out on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since there's no show next week, I'll also mention on the 30th, Dream Club Zero on the Xbox 360 from Tamsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobunaga no Yabu Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shinsei no Shuo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if this is the first expansion for Nobunaga.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they have Nobunaga's, like they turned Nobunaga's Ambition into like an online game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not sure if this is the online game itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that had already come out or if this is like the first expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that is coming out in Japan on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, the description is in Japanese, so I can't read if that's a regular one or expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also coming out on the 23rd of December, Mugen Kairo Hikari to Kage no Hako comes out as well in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this looks like... Oh, it's Echo Chrome 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what this game is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like Echo Chrome, but with colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sure enough, it is Echo Chrome 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a download title.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is actually going to be out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It supports the PlayStation Move.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is coming out on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to the Wii in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Momochan Diet Wii Figurobics by Chon Dayon comes out this week on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's another diet game, but get this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to see the box art for this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to copy that little picture, and I'm going to post that in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you kids tell me if you're going to buy that fitness game based on the artwork or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: What does this fitness game have in the box art that most fitness games don't usually have?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot Asian chick on the front?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: In a bikini, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's not only in a bikini, she's kind of peeling down the bottom of her bikini.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What a hoe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jillian Michaels tried that on the cover of her game, and I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not the same effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, no, I don't want to see your penis.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Milestone Shooting Collection 2 comes out on the Wii, but who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're all going to be looking at your unopened boxes of Momochan Diet.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the DS, not a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: There really isn't anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do get to Saga 3, Jikunohasha, Shadow or Light comes out on January 6th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe this is another game in the Saga series, like it's a remake of one of the Saga games, which was what, Final Fantasy Legend here?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, going to the PSP, Beyond the Milky Way comes out this week on the PSP, as well as Starry Sky in Autumn, and a big release this week, The Third Birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that doesn't sound familiar to you, that's the new Parasite Eve game coming on PSP, The Third Birthday this week, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll go ahead and mention the 31st.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have EA Sports Grand Slam Tennis because kids like tennis.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for the release dates this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go back into some news and we have the classic game of the week just a few minutes ahead of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, a story from Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, you may remember that they just released the pretty awesome Infinity Blade on the iPhone and iOS App Store.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there's going to be other games supporting the Unreal Development Kit, and it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the demos that they were showing off the Unreal Development Kit for was...
[SPEAKER_10]: None other than the long, hopefully not forgotten, epic game, Jazz the Jackrabbit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now updated in 3D graphics and fun stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's actually some other epic, well, other Unreal Engine games that are coming to the store.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, I think there's actually one, and I don't remember what it was called, but it kind of looked a little bit like World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: on um but it was like a tower defense game or something like that or like a hack and slash game with the name dungeon and the title I don't remember exactly what it was but uh it looked pretty cool so um
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I mean, more games supporting the Unreal Engine would be pretty awesome because they can do some pretty sweet looking stuff just even with the limited resources of the iOS and the iPhones and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like when I hear that there might be a new Jazz Jackrabbit or whatever, I'm like, oh my God, is it 1994?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else that is new and exciting, I guess, depends what kind of games you play.
[SPEAKER_02]: SingStar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, remember SingStar, the karaoke game?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also a dance game now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played your ABBA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, SingStar.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to see if there's any really, really big songs in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a shit ton of Lady Gaga songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're into Lady Gaga, there's quite a few songs from her first album that are there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bad Romance, because you know you want to make your friends sing Bad Romance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Songs from the Jackson 5 are now there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take That.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an old school band that I think is getting back together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know that the New Kids on the Block and the Backstreet Boys are going out on tour together?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and I actually did see that performance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of it being the 90s all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody asked me if I wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, no, I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, no, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can do some dancing to Tiffany, I Think We're Alone Now and Aha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Take On Me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, I still like the Birthday Massacre version better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is, some SingStar stuff for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, let's go to the classics video games and talk about an old school game that DarkSakura thinks, hey, you kids ought to be playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura's gonna step into the vault, find a game that she says, hey, you got two weeks because of the holiday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can tell you people are going to have a hard time finding this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Space Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Space Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Fantasy Zone, but Space Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically what this game is is that it is a mix of Space Harrier and Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: and even the music is a little remix of the themes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually, with the particular game, it never came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was never released.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a prototype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, you actually can find the disc image online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aha, so the kiddies are going to have to resort to more scandalous means to play this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't necessarily say it's scandalous, given that, you know, I don't really think there's any kind of restriction on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is really pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's still got the same kind of Space Harrier scaling issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty minimalist, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: The other thing that actually I didn't really care for in it, too, is that it is a little bit harder to hit stuff, but it's still so freaking cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because the game Space Harrier is set in the Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, welcome to Fantasy Zone, get ready.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it takes two of the best things and just puts them together.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, your bosses are some of your classic Fantasy Zone bosses.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just really neat, and it's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is just, it's something for people who love Space Harrier or Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's really all that it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's eye candy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and you can go into your little shops and buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got the same lady from the shops in Fantasy Zone and get all kinds of goodies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that's really all I can say about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's got the Opa Opa and his little feet sticking out going, I'm the Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to throw the two together.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, oddly enough, I wouldn't exactly... I don't really classify Space Fantasy Zone on some... You see, the other reason why I'm bringing it up for the classic game is that it is... You can play the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, you know, a nice waste of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not... There usually are a few issues with the disc, too, and burning, so you have to be really careful when you do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But... Like, see, there's the wood face thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I like how the bosses in this game kind of look like the bosses from the original Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they are the bosses.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're in that whole 3D environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I really had to just throw it out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's a game that I think any fan of Fantasy Zone and Space Harrier should at least give a look at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, there's some listeners that aren't going to know, so I have to ask.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just said your second favorite game ever is Fantasy Zone and your third favorite ever is Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's number one?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amen, sister.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guardian Legend, most underrated NES game ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is so great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely astounding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not as good any of those games as Super Metroid, but they're all still really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's your favorite game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I mean, so really, I know it's not an official released game, and yeah, I've got a few prototypes of other stuff, but this is one prototype that you can get the full version of out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not unavailable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, you can't find an official printing of it or something without spending the bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, and I don't think there's any real reason about why it wasn't released.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might have been something about licensing issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not even really the greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is something that's worth playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something that's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And at least, you know, watch the video.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I still love the PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's going to do it for Part A here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty more to come in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your Twitters at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be sure to get those in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, your phone calls will be coming up later in the program, as well as some rapid-fire news, some really quick news stories of what's going on, and some other game-related news stories, including one about sex.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you better stay tuned for more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a mic off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk about sex.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a George Michael song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that that was Salt-N-Pepa.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Salt-N-Pepa.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: They both had songs about sex, among many others.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, George Michael was the one that got busted for, well, it wasn't really sex, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just going to go to break.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back in a minute with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live on this Sunday evening, December the 19th of 2010 with the 394th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are taping live at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com if you've ever wanted to join us for a live show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tune in at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not next week because we won't be here next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But tune in in early January when we will be back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over the break, we were playing some music from Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, we can't play it on the podcast because it's copyright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, Loki, you were saying something about the whole Space Invaders on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were not a fan, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, Infinity Gene is terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah, I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not nearly as good as Extreme.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you play Extreme, it's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Infinity Gene was just, no, not cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, during the break, I also got a present from Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: He bought me something on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dungeon Raider 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Dungeon Hunter 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it's very much like Diablo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I love me some Diablo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jamie has something coming her way, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: presence in studio good times speaking of presence we should actually let the I gave you guys your presence before the show uh-huh oh yes I forgot we didn't talk about those on air yeah DarkSakura got me a World of Warcraft trivia calendar because she knows I'm an addict and so now I have a little desk calendar for work that I can tear off each day and then like I can mark things a little post-it notes like e3 and some of the big events during the years I can see how long it is till e3
[SPEAKER_07]: When I was working, I actually had three different calendars like that on my desk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had the Redneck Dictionary, which I just thought was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I had the Yiddish Word of the Day.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I had another one that was, oh yeah, like random facts that they won't tell you about or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I got Loki Family Guy Calendar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm definitely going to put this up on my desk because all I have is... What was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Axis Game Localization gave me a calendar.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's tiny.
[SPEAKER_10]: And not Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because this has quotes on it that I can actually put on my marquee.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you do a show as well, and you're running some year-end specials right now, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we do one called Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on Infamous.net.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's with no I in front of the N. And it's me and Mar and Marvel and Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we talk about comics.
[SPEAKER_07]: and we talk about Shadow's hatred of Hulk people and the love-hate relationship of Marvel and Matt Fraction who's writing Iron Man and my cluelessness about just about anything DC Comics related.
[SPEAKER_07]: So.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want links to those, both those shows now available at OrangeLawnRadio.com right on the left-hand side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little links to both those shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: How cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: So awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And remember, don't mention Jeff Loeb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may have to go into the archive a little bit to see this, but our buddies over at Under Sedation Live are doing their annual Madness tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was March Madness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's just Madness, I think, because it doesn't have a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's USLOLR Madness version 2011.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should submit your top 25 lists to uslmadness at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the top 25 games listed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever!
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if you are a huge fan of Super Metroid, I'm gonna send my number one to Super Metroid to uslmadness at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you already know, DarkSakura's list is gonna be one, Guardian Legend, two, I'm writing her damn list for her, Fantasy Zone, three, Space Harrier, and continue on through 25.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the nominees to get the most points will be entered into an elimination 64 bracket.
[SPEAKER_02]: uslmadness at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: More information available on our website.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to scroll back in the news a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All that information at orangelaunchradio.com, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Tigerclaw is letting us know that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry, I thought that was about rebroadcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's something else I'll have to chat with him offline about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's get into some rapid-fire news, some quick news, some stories that we just don't have the full time to talk about, but we wanted to bring them to your attention nonetheless, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this is neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Super Meat Boy, a game we've actually been talking about on the show for a few weeks now and is very awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you happen to have the PC version, apparently they figured out a way to uncover the dev mode located in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course it was discovered by the modding community.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I believe it allows you to customize your game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: and of course this is only in the PC version it gives you the keys to the kingdom as they put it and some very user friendly tools in which Team Meat created the game with including the original batch of levels and actually it was kind of cool Team Meat the creators of the game were actually nice enough to post a few tutorial videos explaining how to access and use the tools
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: and of course if you're a fan of Dead Rising 2 you'll be happy to know that on December 27th Dead Rising 2 Case West will be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade it's the exclusive epilogue to the game and will cost you 800 Microsoft points or $10 do want
[SPEAKER_10]: So that looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, they're also going to have the photo part of the game coming back as well for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice little after Christmas gift there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then finally, Section 8, which was a first-person shooter, came out last August.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or I should say August 2009.
[SPEAKER_10]: That actually did okay at retail and was a full-price game when it came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's going to also include a single player campaign, support for up to 32 players in online multiplayer and a new four player co-op mode called Swarm.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says offline players will also be able to partake in multiplayer as the game can add bots in case you don't have friends or an internet connection to play against.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hamlet, The Game
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Hamlet's taking out the trash.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only it's not real.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that Hamlet 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that was from Last Action Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be or not to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you seen Hamlet 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the dumbest fucking movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there still kids here?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hoping not because the door is wide open.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are there still kids here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I swear?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the dumbest fucking movie ever made.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's so dumb, it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, that was Hamlet 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this actually is not really what you would think it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, there's this whole little trailer out there for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very stylized.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that style.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like that limbo-esque thing going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's all coming out January 2011.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing the trailer here in studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This does not look like Hamlet to play to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it is based on Shakespeare's Hamlet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have no idea how that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now we need the sassy gay friend to show up.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the rest of the Marvel vs. Capcom 3 roster has been revealed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been spoiled.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is, if you believe the dirty internet rumors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sienko from Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Akuma from Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hager from Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's awesome actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phoenix, the X-Men, Sentinel from the X-Men, Taskmaster, Avengers-ish, Galactus is the final boss in the Fantastic Four.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taskmaster would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently some other characters that were planned for the game, but they didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phoenix Wright, Mega Man, Venom, and Frank West were all planned for the game, but it just didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of sad that Frank West won't show up.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, he's not the central character in the new game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would have been an easy port since, you know, Tatsunoko vs. Capcom had him.
[SPEAKER_10]: You would think, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Taskmaster...
[SPEAKER_07]: Taskmaster actually makes sense because he was a regular in the older Deadpool comic for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hey, if you like RPGs and you own a PSP, and when I say RPGs, I mean old school RPGs, then seriously, there is an awesome, incredible must-have game that was announced for the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get the dust off the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Break them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squenix has announced that they are bringing Final Fantasy 4 to the PSP and this is not the 3D version that was on the DS but it's being redone in 2D with the graphics in HD a la the Final Fantasy 1 and 2 remakes but here's the thing it's not just Final Fantasy 4 it's
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also the After Years on one disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the mobile game that came out on WiiWare, and that is also being upgraded to the new treatment, so that is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy IV Complete Collection for the PSP was revealed by VJump Magazine in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, this has only officially been announced for Japan, but I can't see how this game isn't coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is just, oh man, this is just awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming out in Japan this spring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably the U.S., eh, what, summer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Next holiday?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the news I got.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Tactics The War on the Lions
[SPEAKER_02]: They were plugging that at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's sure taking them a while to get out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder what's going on with it, but it looks cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take the time to get it right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't release something buggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine by me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, and this should make people pretty happy, is that there's new Rock Band download content for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually is Happy Christmas Wars Over, which is John Lennon and Yoko Ono.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then Poutatre en Angine, I think, by Anais and Dix-Moi by B.B.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bruns and Verdamp Langhaire, which is by B.A.P.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nurenwort by Worsen Helden, Phantasma by Linnea, Proibito by Litfilba, I don't know who they are, Jerk It Out by Caesars.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of worldly music this week, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only one I care about is the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been a lot of John Lennon love in Rock Band 3, because he released one of his albums, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was also, well, all the Beatles stuff got released, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sure, of course, there was the Beatles game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there was the anniversary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, that's right, there was a re-release album, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dreamcast!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually been a confirmation of a Dreamcast collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameStop has a listing for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Supposedly out of Feptember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feptember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why am I saying Feptember?
[SPEAKER_02]: February.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like a holiday month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Faptember.
[SPEAKER_07]: February 15th for $30.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's really not a whole lot saying just that there is something by the Sega marketing VP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alan Pritchard says, and this is a quote, we actually have a Dreamcast collection coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: How descriptive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSO or GTFO, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll take Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Space Channel 5 I like just how completely emotionless she says it in the Japanese version whereas you got Apollo Smile who was the most annoying person in the universe being all fabulous and everything in the US one and then the Japanese one you have Space Channel 5
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I just have to point this out in our chat room at chat.orangesauntradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bochikawa says, Faptember sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's make it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Frisbee says, Jerkuary.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was trying to say Feptember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Faptember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob's dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know it wouldn't be hard to get people to participate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you have what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have NaNoWriMo, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: The writing month where everybody's supposed to write a novel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, how many people can actually write the whole damn novel, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: November, where you're supposed to be growing out a beard through the entire month.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think Faptember is something everybody can participate in.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should start making banners and buttons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still trying to find Deadpool on a moped.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're going to go to the Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't even like pulled up the Twitter at all yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you linking?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a picture of Deadpool with Taskmaster on a moped that's supposed to, it's done up like the bike from Nakira.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like all the, suddenly we are getting all these unsolicited names from, you know, Fat Timber.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Sex Timber and Cocktober.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Jessica Harper is quick to point out, women don't fap, we squick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that was the term for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've learned something new on this episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was click.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just, I always heard like clicking the mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what, we have Pokuary?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, we're getting all this bullshit spam coming from somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta block this user real quick because I seriously can't read our Twitter because it's so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate spammers on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all need to die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you think so?
[SPEAKER_07]: How about a boat fire?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read Twitter and filter that guy out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, there's like no tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is up with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well Spazinator sent us one.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two free vids on PlayStation Network again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh good, we like free vids.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting the free vid update from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two free vids on PSN again.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pilot to a new-ish anime series and a promo for Robot Chicken Star Wars 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, free promo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spazinator also wants to know, is WoW cataclysm Shermie approved?
[SPEAKER_02]: MolesJK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has, I don't know, has Shermie voiced an opinion on cataclysm?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but our overseas friend Rob sent me a card that says Merry fucking Christmas on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that card.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he said because of Shermie.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember hearing about this, although I thought I also did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, we'll read it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you got to be one of the top 32 virtual racers in the US if you are one of the top 32 you will compete in March 2011 to be one of 16 finalists and then you get to drive real Nissan racers that's according to the announcement the final winner will get to join the GT Academy they will train with professional drivers at tracks around the world and join a professional racing team
[SPEAKER_02]: and I guess it's all going to be televised like a reality show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you've ever wanted to be on a reality show and you're, I don't know, you're good at Gran Turismo 5 then go for it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's pretty good for being a $6 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They sold it over 286,000 times.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's the fastest grossing app ever, according to the website Appmodo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: The old record, I guess, was held by Cut the Rope, which was $1 million in 10 days.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize Cut the Rope had caught on so quickly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard of Cut the Rope, but I've never played it, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I thought it was one of those games that kind of slowly grew in popularity.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually, I'm standing corrected.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, Epic Mark Rain, he said that the Game Center numbers that are being reported are quite a bit lower than the actual sales, so more than 1.7 million.
[SPEAKER_10]: hmm um says uh the says i tweeted because i thought that it'd be obvious that the game center numbers are a subset of our overall sales and not the actual number but several of the reports i saw seem to be confused about that also infinity blade does not require a game center you can choose to cancel and still play the game however i recommend signing up for game center apple has done a great job it's
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, that's where I lost him right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, did you hear, speaking of like failed Apple launches, did you hear Ping got some new additions in the last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Ping?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know what Ping is?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, whatever happened to Pooping?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was that website one of our listeners made, the Pooping site.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, no, Ping has now, you can share playlists with your friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can share playlists of songs that you know you could go and then buy on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it's finally a feature of ping that Twitter doesn't have.
[SPEAKER_02]: However insignificant it may be.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Infinity Blade is getting an update next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to be adding some new enemies to face because from what I heard there's only like six that you face each time you play through the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're also going to be adding multiplayer soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Marrow Fiend
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's screenshots from a frickin' iPhone?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looks outstanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you played the game yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will have to show it to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: At some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not trying to do a radio show, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I meant later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: During our music break after the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about sex!
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that I have your attention, let's talk about this new thing that's on the thingy, that's on the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking earlier about Kinect hacks and, you know, people can play the piano and people can do, you know, whatever, these 3D dancing and all these sorts of things that Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it didn't take long for somebody to think of sex.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's from Thrix with three X's.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Thrixx.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Thrixx.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Kinect hardware is used, plus some of the open drivers in Windows 7 is how it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I would play the video for you, but it was removed from YouTube because some people reported it for nudity and sexual content.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Ruining all our fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like all the other sex games that they have out there, like all the anime ones and stuff where you use the mouse and stuff, but instead of using the mouse, you use your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's honestly not that exciting, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty much exactly what we said.
[SPEAKER_02]: You rub this magical floaty hand over boobs and the chick goes, you know, ooh, boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, you might be wondering when this is coming out for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're really wondering that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing, Microsoft has pretty much said, hell no.
[SPEAKER_02]: In an interview with IGN, they said, Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: IGN?
[SPEAKER_10]: You went and asked them?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like it wasn't completely obvious to begin with that this was A. First off, never going to come out on a console.
[SPEAKER_10]: B. It was just a PC game anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: And C. It wasn't that interesting of an idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, you had the spare time to go ask them this so you can get a comment so that you can get some more page hits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree, but at the same time... Maybe you should dedicate a podcast to that too, because they have like 80,000 podcasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of bullshit, because, you know, and I'm probably preaching to the choir here, but if somebody really wants to waste $60 on this, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_02]: How is this any worse than some of the Bang Bang Shoot'em Up games that are out there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't know, Mafia 2 that was brought up earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so sick of this double standard of sex versus violence.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a double standard, and I bet you anything that this will come out in Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball 3 where you can tickle them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's just tickling.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just a giant feather that's in your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not actually your hand, but it's a giant feather, and you can go tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, and they'll go hee, hee, hee.
[SPEAKER_02]: And their boobs will move, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, would you play Dead or Alive if it had booby-tickling connect mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should be able to unlock things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that they should have the dudes in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boobs are a lot more fun than junk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, for bounciness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm with you on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, there's people going, why don't they have one with dudes and speedos and everything?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm surprised they don't have, like, a beach, you know, beachwear mode in, like, Dead or Alive, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't there the whole volleyball game or whatever?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that was the volleyball.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm talking about, like, actual fighting, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how I feel about this at chat.orangelandrena.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long Sagat, I don't know, in our chat room says, poop should be cool in video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't think that's ever really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like some things, you know, again, if that's what somebody really wants to pay 60 bucks on is poop the game, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go play Conker's Bad Fur Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, you can poop for free like every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just eat more fiber, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: But tickling chicks with feathers, that's...
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't Shit Your Pants
[SPEAKER_02]: anything is possible on the PC and that's why folks PC gaming will never cease to exist and you think that poop is not in games yet or at least not enough in games just wait Duke Nukem Forever hasn't come out yet so I'm sure there will be plenty of poop in that I love this oh my god this is the best comment ever and I can't pronounce this name
[SPEAKER_02]: Kasson, Khan with an S, says to Long Sagat about his whole poop thing, fiber, uppercut.
[SPEAKER_02]: You win.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatter of the evening right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sound the bells and whistles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude whose name I can't pronounce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fiber, uppercut.
[SPEAKER_02]: You win.
[SPEAKER_02]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we could get away from the sex topic for a minute here, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have something maybe a little more legitimate for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Barf!
[SPEAKER_02]: Barf, barf, barf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, basically...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sega wanted to talk about why we got Shadow the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_07]: They thought it would work for US gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: The producer of Sonic Colors, Takashi Izuka, said, "...after Sonic Adventure, we had two studios, one in the US, one in Japan."
[SPEAKER_07]: "...and to continue the quote, the Japanese studio was to develop a Sonic game in the standard style, and the US was to develop something different which could contribute to the Sonic franchise."
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, he was made to work in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: because first and third person shooters were popular and they wanted someone who could work with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hence, we got Shadow the Gangsta Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what they haven't realized is that we like Sonic because it's not standard American fare.
[SPEAKER_02]: File this under the Americans are so stupid bin More like, don't try to guesstimate what a completely different culture is going to like Why is it that every time there's a game that's targeted at America, it usually really stinks?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, maybe I'm just doing an overall broad generalization I thought it was a cool looking character, really well designed But other than that, the concept was just crap
[SPEAKER_10]: Sonic Colors Sonic Colors
[SPEAKER_02]: It's out already.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, but I can't afford it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a game that was targeted for the US or whatever that wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Secret of Evermore was horribly underrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually was a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I had the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably still have the Super Nintendo cart in a bin somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, that was not as terrible as people made it out to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was no second to Setsu 3, but it was good in its own way.
[SPEAKER_02]: and wasn't that the first game that uh what's his name the guy who does all the music for like Guild Wars and Oblivion Jeremy Soleil he did that was like his first soundtrack I think with Secret of Evermore so I guess it's rare but it does happen occasionally let's move on yes um now I don't I'm gonna try to report this without sounding hateful
[SPEAKER_10]: We could use a Loki rant tonight, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gran Turismo 5's creator wants to add monthly updates.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plans premium car upgrades later on, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, they're saying that they don't consider their work complete yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: You think that that game wasn't
[SPEAKER_10]: Rush to market because it's been in development for years now and they really need to get it out this year because delaying it again, people would just kind of roll their eyes at them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I remember there's only about a fifth of the vehicles that are represented in the game right now with premium models, which feature higher resolution textures.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the models in the game aren't quite as finished as others.
[SPEAKER_10]: But don't worry, they're going to be adding patches later on to add some new items, including new premium cars available for download.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they haven't said yet whether those updates will be free.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great, so you can pay, or possibly pay more, for more of your game that you purchased that isn't quite done yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: But don't worry, they'll finish it someday.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll call it Gran Turismo 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think Gran Turismo 6 is going to come out for the PS3, or do you think we're going to wait for the next big system, next console?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about that whole 10-year life cycle thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're only, what, four years in?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gran Turismo 6 Prologue will be coming out, and it will be totally like the game was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Man, that's got to... Well, I don't know if it's got to suck for the people that bought Prologue.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I think that's a dumb idea to buy the game anyways, Prologue, because...
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_10]: You're like paying for a demo, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no, no, it's a full-featured game.
[SPEAKER_10]: With, like, you know, very few cars.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well... Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not a demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, coming also to the PlayStation 3 very soon, and a lot of people are excited about this, even though this game was already out some time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect 2 is coming out to the PlayStation 3, but there's some, you know, some tweaks and some upgrades and some new things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect 3, of course, is coming out in 2011.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you, of course, have this whole weird thing going on where Mass Effect 2 is coming out on the PlayStation 3, but Mass Effect 1 never came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if I don't own an Xbox, how do I get that experience of Mass Effect 1?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they've figured it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's an interactive comic that's going to come with Mass Effect 2 called Mass Effect Genesis.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what it does is a really quick...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to say it's a playthrough because it's a comic but it's a real quick summary I guess of the 360 and the PC game Mass Effect 1 but you also get to actually do some things in this comic that you did in the original game you get to make they're saying six decisions that you made in Mass Effect 1 that will now impact your Mass Effect 2 game
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope one of those decisions is making sweet, sweet love to the alien chick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, wasn't the whole lesbian thing in Mass Effect 1?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully that is one decision.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, apparently you will get to make some of the decisions and have your game impacted just like you could play Mass Effect 1 and have your game get impacted in Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a PlayStation 3 gamer will get to start the game...
[SPEAKER_02]: do the opening sequence and then they're going to go into this comic that I guess will then impact the game later on so that's kind of cool I like that
[SPEAKER_02]: so again that is coming out in January Mass Effect 1 they are saying is not going to come out for the Playstation 3 because they're going to move on to Mass Effect 3 so this is as close as you're ever going to get unless you happen to own a PC which you probably do if you're listening to this show and you can go play Mass Effect 1 I don't know if Mac has Mass Effect 1 if it does it's probably on Steam there you go
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go now to the mailbag where folks can send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and every week we read your emails live here on air and respond to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com Two emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi everyone, I have a question that can possibly be answered by the OLR gang and chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm an avid knitter and I'm looking for video game character garments that look like they were knitted.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only two examples I can think of are Riku's scarf from Final Fantasy X-2 and Nora's SCM sweater slash vest in Final Fantasy XIII Pictures Attached.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got no problems, no projects going on and I'm waiting to start Nora's Sweater Slash Vest as soon as I get patterns from someone to make them up for me because I don't know anything about sewing and patterns.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks so much, Stan.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last time I wrote in I was telling you about how a friend said I wasn't a gamer because I didn't like certain games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I confronted him and we're cool now.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, the other friend was with us when I brought it up and made them both listen to that episode of your show and now he's a fan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did I already share this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really awesome that we can make fun of your friend and he's still a fan of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm checking out this... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you're into the whole knitting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I crochet, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I always get the two confused.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, knitting...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you can do more with knitting, but I don't have the coordination for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, when I tried to learn again, it really made my hand hurt.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, crochet will do it to me after a while because I finished a hat for Becky that was really... Yeah, but you got that whole trigger finger thing still, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like residual stuff from when that was really bothering you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm sure there's also characters that wear hats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I would think like a lot of like, I don't know, for some reason I think of the Zelda world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also think of a game you should look up is Eternal Sonata.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't know if there was a lot, but I don't know why I just think of that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But something that could be like a creative idea, like if you're really looking for projects that, you know, I kind of see these things online once in a while, and I always thought they were kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, look up 8-bit sprites.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's a lot of websites around that have like 8-bit sprite repositories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I was going to say you could do, I mean, but still it kind of gives you an idea like how to knit, like if you want to make like a blanket or some other type of throw or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't believe I'm actually talking about knitting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get some ideas for patterns from like old school 8-bit sprites, I would think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you're not going to get clothed patterns, but.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to sit and draw it, but I did have a plan for a much later project of crocheting a Tetris blanket.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd crochet it actually in the blocks and then attach the box with yarn.
[SPEAKER_07]: But right now I don't have the time or patience for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about like a pillow front thing or is that more of a needle point type of thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: You could crochet a sham.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as like actual clothing, gosh, nothing really comes to mind for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the best place to go would be RPGs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know why, but I'm thinking of the characters from Eternal Sonata.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I've seen one that had a lot of knitting type stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does Dan know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan, do you know video game characters that wear knitted outfits?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did he give you the face?
[SPEAKER_02]: He just gave me this face of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Rob, I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance is Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ness's Sweat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Knitting advice from Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ness's Sweater could very well be knitted.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a wonderful idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance is Freddy Krueger.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, there's Nightmare on Elm Street.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan goes, a really bad game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, did he send pictures of his projects?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm seeing pictures of the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we need to see pictures of your work.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we'll be awaiting those pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a really... See, I think in a lot of games...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, last email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey guys!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_07]: For Festivus slash Decemberween, one of my friends gifted me with her PlayStation 2, which she no longer uses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice gift.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is extremely awesome considering that one of my evil exes took my old PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The downside is that the only PS2 game I still own is Final Fantasy X. How about helping me to rebuild my PS2 library by suggesting a few good games for me to buy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, Tiara.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, Rob, I want to be on Horde House 11DR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted her on last week, but it didn't work out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll talk to you offline, Tiara.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do want to have you on as a guest, so maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to find a Thursday that you're free.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any of the Silent Hills that came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely the Silent Hill games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I would say get Silent Hill 2 and 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Tiara owns Final Fantasy X, then I'm going to guess that she's a role-play game type fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So definitely X-2.
[SPEAKER_02]: XII was horrifically underrated because it came out right when the new consoles were coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll lend you mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the .hack games were always really underrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that whole simulated MMO thing, but they're a little more action-y.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think those are really good to look into.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember the name of the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's .hack, Volume 1, Infection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Magic Pen Gel was an underlooked RPG game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the one where you could draw wieners, and then they could go into battle and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a lot of fun on that with that game in the early days of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Graffiti Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course there are tons and tons of DDR games if you want to get your music game thing on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amplitude and Frequency are both very good games even though you can't play Amplitude online anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get the Space Channel 5 package.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Space Channel 5 Part 1 and 2 were released together combined.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm unwinding my thing and I'm going into the vault.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think of like other epic PS2 games that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura is actually taking her microphone into the vault to give TR suggestions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little stretch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some folks in chat, not fans of Final Fantasy XII, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: It won't reach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jessica Harper is suggesting Kingdom Hearts, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Solar Flare suggests Rez.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good one as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll show you Rez.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long Sagat suggests the Metal Slug Anthology.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's always a good one as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Metal Gear Solid games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a great one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good PS2 games you need to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Katamari Damacy from Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Dragon Quest VIII was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still awesome today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiara, that's like $200 worth of video games we just suggested to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, I will lend you my Final Fantasy XII if you're interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: As do I.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe someone might be bringing some of them in person.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: If one is not broke.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good suggestions, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: More.
[SPEAKER_02]: More of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just real quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: She actually sent me a message.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo, a zillion games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xena Saga 1 and 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yakuza.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Solid 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Tiara, but Zillion is actually on the Sega Master System.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for the emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send us some emails for next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jessica Harper is saying, I want to go to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take me too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you haven't heard that episode of the show, just make sure that Jessica doesn't run into any DDR freak people because you never know what freaky things might happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just messing because I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the part of the show where we get angsty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't have an FU, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually having a great week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I passed Algebra.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to say FU to the Photoshop Selection Tool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, do you have an FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, FU the Comcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, big surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, fuck them for not being able to hook up my cable correctly.
[SPEAKER_10]: It apparently takes them numerous crews to do something very simple like running a drop to the street.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently they have a crew that specializes in underground installations.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, but that crew doesn't know how to actually hook up anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I was about to install my own damn cable when I was like, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why the hell am I doing this?
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yes, they really need to, I don't know, get their shit straight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, gosh, I don't really have a strong FU to follow up to that, but I will say FU to traffic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to drive to the Bay Area on Friday night, and it took me like three and a half hours to get there thanks to a traffic jam on 880.
[SPEAKER_02]: So FU 880!
[SPEAKER_02]: You suck!
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan the Man's in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to give an FU?
[SPEAKER_00]: It should be on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you're there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd like to throw an FU to God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or at least the weather.
[SPEAKER_00]: For really sucking ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right before I have to drive for like 15 hours.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's real cute.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all real nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Real, real good.
[SPEAKER_00]: The week that I have to drive someplace, snow and rain and crap from the sky.
[SPEAKER_00]: And who else can I blame?
[SPEAKER_00]: God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Suck a dick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mother Nature.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was also really pissed at me because I was so drawn on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but Dan got over it because he saw it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to say this for the record.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know what my wife's problem is, but I'm a fair man.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got to go to the Tron sneak preview on IMAX and I didn't tell her a lot about it because she didn't want to hear about it because she was a little bitter so she got so she got to go to the Tron sneak preview and I was a little bitter but I wasn't going to be like no because I've gotten to go and it all worked out fine for me because thanks to the unstoppable pimp Matt I got to go see it for free and it was awesome it was awesome so I want to throw an F you to Jamie for going to see Tron early
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't elbow me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you, Dan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Black.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened to the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: One minute we're just giving our little FUs and reading emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now we're just giving out the hot dickings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, that's Dr. Tran.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jessica's in chat saying, I deserve that FU.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan's yelling from the other room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It ain't her fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta act on those opportunities.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's move on to... Where are we at?
[SPEAKER_02]: The skypline?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we got a couple more stories and then the skypline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan, get a mic or GTFO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR in just a little bit right after two more stories for you guys, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I first saw this headline, I was like, sweet, Xbox is finally getting all risque because they said goodbye, gal gun panties.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't think they would go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, I guess 79 days before the game's release in Japan, Microsoft called a meeting with the Gal Gun developer, Alchemist, and they basically said, you know what, we're going to have to censor the game and not put all these panty shots in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's the point.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you going to sell the game now?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're saying now...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, because I guess the game... I don't know if the game uses the Kinect or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that they're trying to gear it more towards a family game or now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they really should.
[SPEAKER_02]: A game that's fun for the whole family.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot chicks bending over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: X and A game, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: X and A. Here's something you can use the Kinect for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spanking.
[SPEAKER_02]: When those naughty girls bend over, you can spank them with the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, you know you want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spanking game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes or no, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not my forte, but who am I to judge other people?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: E was her head T was her cleavage M was her naked vagina censored obviously because it's classy
[SPEAKER_10]: and AO was tentacles sneaking up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Nellie's like, what is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, it's tentacle rape.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's something that's popular in Japan, you know, in anime.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm just like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says Maybe it's the game parents will use when kids ask them where do babies come from SolarFlare in our chatroom at chat.org.com says Rob, spanking teaches kids to hit
[SPEAKER_02]: One more story for you guys, and it has to do with indie games and the Humble Bundle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Humble Bundle 2 was released this past week, and in less than 24 hours after its release, it got over $500,000 in revenue.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is notable because this was one of those pay-what-you-want type of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five games for whatever you want to pay for it, DRM-free.
[SPEAKER_02]: The biggest payer was Marcus Persson
[SPEAKER_02]: Infinity Ward's Robert Bowling spent $500.
[SPEAKER_02]: on the pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: The average price that people are paying for this, $7 and change.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pack comes with Braid, Cortex Command, Machinarium, Osmos, and Revenge of the Titans.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can divide your payments between the developers, the Electronic Frontier Foundation, and Child's Play charity.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in other words, if you don't want to pay the developers, you want 100% of your donation to go to Child's Play, go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: that indeed is some developers being very humble in allowing that to be sold very cool twitter.com slash humble for more information on that
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go to the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me open it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have it open right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's open.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR if you want to give us a call or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, if you are going to give us a call on Skype, you do want to give Echo123 a call first to make sure your connection works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please, please do us all a favor.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're on Skype itself, Echo123.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 800 number is a lot easier because all you need for that is a phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's 877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: While we wait for some calls, because there's a little bit of a delay between when I ask for calls and when they start coming in, Loki, do you have any last-minute stories for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm starting a new trend by Tron-izing a picture of myself like people were doing with Avatar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's kind of cute what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised there's no, like, filter thingy on Photoshop or one of those programs that will kind of automatically do something-ish.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well let's go to the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: You forgot about one game series in particular for the PS2 and I'm quite upset at you for doing this, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Persona series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought somebody in chat said Persona, and I said it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, any title with Atlas is pretty much gold.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't come across really one game from Atlas that's really so terrible that I would not talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they have a really good game on PS3, Demon's Sword.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or no, what am I thinking?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, scratch that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Demon's Souls is the game that's out on PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great PS3 exclusive game.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I believe it was just given a price reduction because it's in the Greatest Hits series, and the servers,
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one of the stories that missed our show all this week, but I remember reading the servers are going to be open through at least March 2011, if not beyond.
[SPEAKER_01]: And definitely, if you're looking for a long series of playtime with a role-playing game, .hack series is really, really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was the four games, and then there was the...
[SPEAKER_01]: 3 for the GU, which was happening right after.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they keep the storyline pretty much intact throughout the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's really cool how you can take your save game from the first game, put in a second, save the second game into the third, the third game into the fourth.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you can carry it on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then if you take it and put it into the GU series, which happened a few years after,
[SPEAKER_02]: RayCraft in our chatroom is correcting me saying Demon's Souls isn't an Atlus game, they just published it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still, it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_01]: SSJ100 They don't put their name behind sucky games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And hopefully they'll get President Cat and everything will be well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt is also saying Disgaea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now there's a good suggestion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, if you happen to be in a Japanese region, Earth Defense Force 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, good thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very good thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what else is on your mind, X-Link?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else fun and exciting going on in your gaming world?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm kind of disappointed you haven't invited me onto your show yet either, considering that I was the number one achieving core in your guild for quite a while, if I remember correctly, before someone took my spot.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's quite okay, because I'm not going to be bitter or anything about that at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you shouldn't be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thankfully, there's been a lot of people that have wanted to be on, so we're trying to give everybody a shot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I'm playing around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess was only on because we kind of needed someone quickly, so she came back on twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're going to get lots of people on.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, I'm very much enjoying Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keeping up to the wee hours in the morning playing all the different stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many hours have you spent on your archaeology?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: It hasn't been that long.
[SPEAKER_01]: Believe it or not, I spent...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Deathwing showed up while I was doing archaeology.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you survive or did you actually die?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually survived.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to turn this into the WoW show, but I actually survived because what I did, I flew through the fire instead of getting on the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: The timing or something worked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got the achievement and didn't die.
[SPEAKER_01]: My friend, she was in Ratchet and she actually lived with like one hit point or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was weird, but she couldn't believe it.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's like, yeah, I actually got an achievement, but yet I lived.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she took an awesome screenshot of the town.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, just totally engulfed in flames everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you couldn't even really tell it was that for a bit because of the flames in the background.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was a really cool screenshot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, I should let you go before the WoW haters come out and start saying, you guys talk too much WoW.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too much WoW on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: And welcome to the guild, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's busy on her Tron pic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, no problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, 1877gameOLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you even hear that, DarkSarka?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, welcome to the guild.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has a pet in her mouth right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I heard, and thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Season four?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have your little Tron-y looking headband.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm working on the eyes.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: 877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we got a call coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This would be Miss Jessica Harper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Jessica Harper.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So glad to have you back on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's new?
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually came with an agenda tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that I believe you guys spoke about before as per my conversation with Jamie, but we have USOLR Madness.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are currently taking your top 25 lists, and unfortunately we haven't received as many as we would like.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're a bunch of procrastinators.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the deadline is coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since USL will be on hiatus just based on how the holidays fall, since we have Christmas on a Saturday and then New Year's Eve on a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yikes, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of puts us in a little bit of a hiatus.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I thought I'd come and be a pain in your ass and talk about it on your show instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: We think it's great what you guys do over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why USL OLR Madness?
[SPEAKER_04]: because it is the way that you, the gaming audience, can actually get your voice out there and be heard and show what the real games that people love are rather than those that are just being highly profitable because...
[SPEAKER_04]: People are spending way too much money on stupid shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it won't be rigged for Final Fantasy 7 like the GameFAQs contest for every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every year it's Final Fantasy 7 something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 7 could win.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has been in the top 16, but I don't believe it's won a Madness title yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: If anybody wants to get their top 25 list in and has not yet, just go ahead and formulate your top 25 list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send it to uslmadness at gmail.com We will tack it on in with the rest of the votes and deadline is January 3rd.
[SPEAKER_04]: So get your votes in and we will be starting right after the holidays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excited to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to pull up my list that I had actually sent to Brestle so I can give you a little taste of what I'm rooting for here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I'm trying to pull it up in my email archive here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I set my list on November 30th because I'm a very good boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you're a good boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you just a little taste.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one game, of course, was Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number two game this year was the Civilization series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think between five out this year and four being so epic and the original being so awesome, I think Civ is deserving of a spot that high up.
[SPEAKER_02]: With five this year, I was just like, oh, this is all amazeballs.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number three game...
[SPEAKER_02]: Castlevania, Symphony of the Night, Metroidvania, Final Fantasy 6, Plants vs. Zombies
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, maybe it'll make the top 64 then.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's the weird thing is that John has been keeping good track of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has not breached the top 25 recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: During the initial voting, it was one of the top 25 and it did get pushed out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even in the bubble zone right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you love Plants vs. Zombies, you better put it on your list.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think Plants vs. Zombies is the greatest game ever made, you better hurry the hell up and get in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else going on in your world, Jessica?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I got a new computer and I have a brand new video card that I'm ready to put into it, but it is a slim computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And while I did get a low profile card, I do not have the proper brackets for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm in a holding pattern once again and just waiting for my brackets so I can put my new video card in and actually start doing some decent PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually had something similar happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I bought a new video card, it was so Uber, it wouldn't fit in there with the power supply.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we had to get a new power supply as well to make it all work.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a very tight squeeze, and I'm not quite sure exactly how it's going to work, but I'll make it work, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when are you signing up for WoW?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have a feeling that I might end up with Star Trek Online somewhere in my mailbox at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm thinking STO is going to be the game of choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want a 10-day trial, let me know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I may still have another card.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura's recruiting.
[SPEAKER_07]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, Travis is a big fan of that, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disney.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't be surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well Jessica, good luck with the new PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it brings you lots of gaming joy this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already brought me Plants vs. Zombies, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best of luck with everything going on at Under Station Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear about the bad timing of the holidays this year, but hey, enjoy the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good night, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: You too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio on Skype or 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number to call We are taking some calls Hi, you are on Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow the Hedgehog was made for Americans, or whatever, or the, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's not get shadowed I already said my two cents about that in the chat room What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why'd you call?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, to satisfy Breslow, I finally sent out my 25 because I realized I didn't play enough games this year to qualify.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm sitting there for about an hour putting my list together and picking the brains of my roommates for what games did you like?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, keep in mind, it's not the top 25 of this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the top 25 of all time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, but still, I just feel like I don't really game enough for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I got my list together and I sent it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, good boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: and I did put on there Final Fantasy 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good man.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a great Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although Final Fantasy 4 I sometimes call my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave it a little bit of a backseat which is funny because I sent that list in before the news about the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will probably be back near the top of my list next year after I play the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what was at the top of your list?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I be nosy?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was your number one game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_11]: Scott Pilgrim vs. the World, the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Was your number one game of all time?
[SPEAKER_11]: I loved that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is one of the few games where I sat there and played it over and over and over.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is one of those games where, yeah, tap the bank for the crack.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what that game fell under for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where every gamer has a voice, even when those voices are insane.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: I like River City Ransom, I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm giving you shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I'm watching Loki in studios playing, I think the new version of Super Mario Crossover, like there was a brand new version that came out, but he is driving the Blaster Master car, and that made me think, oh man, Blaster Master should have been on my list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Blaster Master is in Mario Crossover?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they just added Sofia.
[SPEAKER_02]: The car from Blaster Master is now in Mario Crossover.
[SPEAKER_11]: I now have my reason to play the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to tell my roommate and he's going to fangasm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I need somebody to send in a top 25 list that has Blaster Master near the top to make up for the fact that I left it off my list.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, DarkSakura, it says she will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still haven't sent my list in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, good, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need some Blaster Master love because I forgot because I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_10]: When do we have to send those lists in?
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe the third was the deadline, but you're procrastinating, but you should do it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else on your mind tonight, Rama?
[SPEAKER_11]: The main reason why I called was I want to ask you guys this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think programmers purposely put code into games where you swear it cheats?
[SPEAKER_02]: um it depends on the type of game but like when you say games that cheat my mind automatically goes immediately goes to Super Mario Kart and the whole rubber banding and this is a very common thing you hear in racing games Mario Kart's not the only racing game that does it a lot of them do but yes that's basically programmed cheating is that if you are too far ahead of the other contestants they get to speed boost or whatever to catch up to you that's programmed to cheat to make it more exciting so
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like his team of four growing up with a team of eight.
[SPEAKER_11]: As soon as he walks into the area, that whole team just slaughters him under 15 minutes and he's screaming repeatedly that the game is cheating.
[SPEAKER_11]: Me personally, I don't think the game cheats.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that dates all the way back to the NES days when you would be playing a sports game or any type of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: RC Pro-Am was another racer that would just infuriate people.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's fucking cheating, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game fucking cheats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can understand if they actually put in purpose code for cheating compared to where your skills aren't good enough, Padawan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or it's just ramping up the difficulty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind a lot of those NES, and if you want to go way back, Atari 2600 games, were set to loop over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So of course the difficulty gets insane and harder than you're able to do at some point because that's just what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or take a game like Civilization.
[SPEAKER_02]: and at its highest difficulty level, I believe the computer opponents can build resources like 1.4 times as fast as you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to really think about how to use your resources.
[SPEAKER_02]: well I don't think that's really cheating the game is cheating per se that's just like advanced skill god mode it's like you know what you're getting yourself into when you walk into it yeah and if you can beat that then you're a fucking stud like you are but you know going into it okay I am playing an uphill battle here and if I beat this I'm awesome mhm
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's exactly what I was getting at.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Ranma, we're going to let you go to try to get some more calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_02]: But thank you so much for your call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay fabulous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will call.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got time for one more call if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Decemberween Decemberween
[SPEAKER_02]: or Festivus, whatever it is that you celebrate.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or his username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd usually be going around getting some last minute stories, but there aren't any.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's read them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's busy playing Super Mario Crossover and DarkSakura's working on her Tron art.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I am telling a monologue right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry for not participating.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you plan to do with your time off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have any time off from work, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have 3D weekends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to do anything special with them?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, hang out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just hang out, be with the baby?
[SPEAKER_02]: You taking the baby anywhere for the holidays?
[SPEAKER_02]: My mom's.
[SPEAKER_02]: But your mom's here are kind of local, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like you're having to go to the snow or anything?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, she's very close.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone in our chat room named Hi, I love that name, is saying a new Gorillaz album on Christmas, the fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you're the big Gorillaz fan, girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a whole new album for sale?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think like an EP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the phone's not ringing, so I guess that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks so much for those of you that did call, and if you didn't get through tonight but you wanted to, well, you had a chance, but you can always leave us an email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts of the night.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tron.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is this game is pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I blew up, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought of the night is this show is done early enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might have time for Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was a short show tonight, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a wonderful holiday, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, we will not be here next week, but we will be back in 2011 for the ninth year of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a great Christmas or whatever it is you celebrate over these next couple weeks and have a wonderful and safe New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't be stupid, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like what you hear here at Orange Lounge Radio, please tell a friend about the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also love reviews on iTunes or any resource where you can grab a podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Share the love of independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_08]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!