[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki Tonight, December 5th, 2010 Video evidence shows the PSP phone may be the real deal PETA parodies Super Meat Boy to a strong response And a video game song finally gets nominated for a Grammy
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are that show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live on this December 5th of 2010 at www.allgames.com for the 392nd episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a lot of shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games with my awesome co-host, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a little dreidel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it made out of clay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, mine was wood.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy Hanukkah, Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: How have you been celebrating Hanukkah?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you do anything besides light some fire?
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to temple.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan went with me.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: and they were loving some Rock Band and I was like, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really play much Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually, I'm not going to be doing a lot of gaming for the next week and a half because number one, Dan has Gran Turismo 5 and number two, finals.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, busy week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bummer on both counts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just kidding, I'm not hating on Gran Turismo 5 I am I'm not very good at the Uber driving games I'm angry I'm great at arcade racers How can the Veyron not be a premium car?
[SPEAKER_09]: IDK Bastards Also say hello to, we gotta introduce, Tech Master Loki Hello How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm doing fine Alrighty, good to hear it I know your wife celebrates Hanukkah, so have you been doing anything for that?
[SPEAKER_09]: No No?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe this is something I could do while I'm not working.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also do want to take a moment to poll our listeners and send us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: At mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com so Rob can read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, who would be interested in an Orange Lounge book?
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a text message about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to know more about your thoughts on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why you suddenly want to do a book.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm sure the not having a job right now has a lot to do with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: To commemorate our fans and talk how awesome we are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would it be a pop-up book?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm not good with writing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be a physical book to be ordered or...
[SPEAKER_02]: An e-book.
[SPEAKER_09]: An e-book.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can it be something I listen to on my iPod?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's a physical book with pictures and links to goodies.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the OLR yearbook.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Easter Eggs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Michelle on the Outsiders shows has a book deal, but I don't think it has anything to do with her shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the, what is that site?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh God, it's been everywhere, and it's her and her sister's site.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn you, autocorrect.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you seen that site?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's her site.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think she's got a book now going on about it, so you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: If all these other all games people can do a book, so can we.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ours just won't be as good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm designing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you see?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just got kicked in the face.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: All books aside, let's talk about video games and the games we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what types of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, Star Trek Online, because I'm updating the Tribble server right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: At, like, 1K.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I played some Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been very busy because the American River Review, which is the magazine that I've done some design for, goes to print on Monday.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is where the book idea is coming from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, I got the idea from the book I did for my client because we just published it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it'd be very easy for us to do a book.
[SPEAKER_02]: But back to this, the American River Review.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as soon as we have the order information up, I'll be linking it to everybody because you have to buy a copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: um but the American River Review is uh all of the uh literature the art digital physical media fashion and culinary for um American River College for 2011 we win tons of awards we beat out big schools we are amazing I did the culinary section I designed it anyway and um
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's definitely, you know, something that anybody should have a copy of because it really is an impressive product.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we had our proofs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got our proofs last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so that's what's been taking up my time instead of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you said the hubby's been playing Gran Turismo 5, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, we did have some Scott Pilgrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is Gran Turismo 5 pretty?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, except for the shadows are retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little early for that music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty as in that music.
[SPEAKER_09]: As in that music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is as pretty as that music?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the music in the game is very elevator-y.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's new My Chemical Romance in there that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura gave me a beer before tonight's show, so if things are a little bit off tonight like what just happened, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just roll with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's it off?
[SPEAKER_07]: This always happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at any rate, at any rate, it's got some stuff that needs to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still hate that all the people around the track are like, we're just standing here, we are stiff, we don't do anything but wave.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'd like to see more stuff going around, because the game can handle it, it's just not...
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to see some women flashing their titties as you drive by.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what the game needs.
[SPEAKER_02]: The cool thing in this game is that it has the Top Gear test track and the Stig.
[SPEAKER_02]: And your driver looks kind of like the Stig from Top Gear.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it doesn't have Rainbow Road, which is really disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does have go-karts.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be awesome if they just, you know, because, come on, it's Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_07]: They take themselves way too damn seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just throw in some wacky shit in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you know, we're driving in space now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because it's a realistic sim racing game, but just put it in some very unrealistic situations and have fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gran Turismo 6, In Space
[SPEAKER_02]: You're supposed to be doing a patch that's supposed to fix a lot of the problems, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just sit in there sometimes and listen to the elevator music and usually I fall asleep while Dan's playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's it's really like it's like a chibi role-playing game but the whole battle system not so much I mean kind of like puzzle quests I guess they you have a grid of um you start off with a grid of a five by five and then um in the middle there's a grid of uh three three by three uh poker cards and
[SPEAKER_07]: and the whole goal is to make up different poker hands and by doing that you do specific amounts of damage to the monster that you're attacking and then the monster does the same thing as well and you can charge up a wild card and stuff and then they have different magic that you can cast that rearranges some of the cards or does different things or shields that block certain damage and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually really fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it a free game or when you had to pay?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it does cost money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how much money, but it costs money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been playing that most of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, just probably Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com There's a little bit of chatter going on with our ever-present fourth guest on the show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of talk on Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw in our chat room says, Gran Turismo 5 looks so amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't help but be mesmerized by the graphics as I watch people play the game on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Justin.TV, from what I remember when we were doing our video feed on there in the old studio, it's not like it has the best quality.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if that still comes across really well, that's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, Loki just kind of did this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: It stinks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: By soon we mean six years.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: And some of the folks in chat are talking a little bit about Gran Turismo songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Dark Knight says, Need to kickstart my heart to the best Gran Turismo song ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Dark Tetsuya says, Actually, that's the first song on my Gran Turismo 3 playlist.
[SPEAKER_09]: So a lot of talk about the soundtrack of Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you noticed the soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I said earlier it has New My Chemical Romance in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You were talking about all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, once...
[SPEAKER_09]: One song that I do not believe is on the Gran Turismo 5 soundtrack, but is in a game we're going to be talking about a little later tonight is...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, that happy hardcore song from Techno Kitten Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Sea of Love by Frisco, if you wanted to know who it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might remember last week on the show, we got a tweet saying that we needed to check out this game called Techno Kitten Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we were laughing our ass off because it's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you know, laughing with them, not at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: to on-air interview in one week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's amazing what can happen here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to have Nick from Techno Kitten Adventure at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just over 30 minutes away.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you checked out Techno Kitten Adventure, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: You thought it was a little basic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I played it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's similar to, I guess, like the Robot Unicorn Attack games where the concept's very simple, but what draws you into the game is just the fact that
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so unusual, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, the gameplay itself, it's all one button.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just, you know, a button to control the thrust on a jetpack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I were to improve something upon the game, I would maybe tighten up the controls a little bit at level three.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also maybe, you know, make it a little harder.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to ask them if there's any plans for a sequel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because the game has shown up in the top games on Xbox Live Indie Games, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not like the number one game, but it's not number 500.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we definitely want to ask them about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I played the game as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even though it is as basic, let's say, as an Atari 2600 game...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think... In fact, I'm pretty sure I played a game like this on Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the environment that he created and just the, you know, absurdity, outside-the-box type of thinking he constructed the game around is clearly this... Wouldn't this be funny if I combined X with Y and made Z?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think it really works, especially for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear, please don't say combine X, Y, make Z. Y. Algebra hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you having flashbacks to school?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what my final is in.
[SPEAKER_09]: If 2X plus Y equals Z, solve for kitten.
[SPEAKER_01]: Meow.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're going to talk a little bit about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I want to know if he has any other games in the marketplace as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we have to ask him all those questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think it's worth it for one whole dollar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the type of game you're going to whip out a party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby's giving Loki a hard time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't get more tight than one flipping button.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, we were talking to Bobby, and of course Bobby Blackwolf is the gentleman that does the show before us at All Games Radio, the Bobby Blackwolf show every Sunday night at 5 Pacific, 8 Eastern.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he always has us on at the very end of the show, which is very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: He doesn't have to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we were talking about this game a little bit, and we were kind of talking about how
[SPEAKER_09]: We like that somebody went there and did this and didn't just try to make a clone of some other game because we're all about the whole kind of like absurd, outside-the-box sorts of ideas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember President Cat a year and a half ago?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why were we all excited about President Cat?
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't really the game itself, per se.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure the game itself was really just an average game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think a lot of the blogs who ultimately reported on, wow, there's this podcast trying to get this game called President Cat localized.
[SPEAKER_09]: What a bunch of weirdos!
[SPEAKER_09]: And don't forget playing the piano.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, and absolutely playing the piano.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why can't we get original shit like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, why do we have to get these games we know are subpar and below?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we're America!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything is mediocre.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, Majin Makon in our chatroom says, Muscle March.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a pretty unique Wii game, I will say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was at least that, so it's working.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, so we'll get to more talk on TechnoKitten Adventure in about 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: But in the meantime, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't talk about My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I mentioned TechnoKitten Adventure and I didn't play a whole lot else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played quite a bit of World of Warcraft because there's big changes going on this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I have the other show for that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: so not a whole lot I want to say here otherwise other games I played some more Super Meat Boy which I think is a great Xbox Live Arcade game and that was really about it I had a work trip this week so I didn't really get to play a whole lot of games at home so sorry guys I'll try to play more next week
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Join our Facebook.
[SPEAKER_09]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be taking Twitter topics later in the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: So definitely submit those topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: And email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Email our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura's going to read those in Part B a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: For now though, we're going to get into the news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki's going to start us off tonight with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, um, so, you know, it was funny because they were actually, um, quoting, uh, one of the quotes made about this device, allegedly, was that where there's smoke there's fire, well...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think you can get much more fire than this.
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation phone, of course, remember a while back they had some not so clear video of the device.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people were like, well, it's probably changed quite a bit since then and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now they have really clear video.
[SPEAKER_07]: showing this brand new device called the Sony Ericsson Zeus Z1 PlayStation phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it kind of shows some of the features that it has, the slide-out controls, the dual kind of touchpad thing on the front that simulates the analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, the shoulder buttons as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that looks like...
[SPEAKER_07]: They made possibly a front and back mounted camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of neat stuff though that you would expect in like a PlayStation phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they even had some video of course showing them going to like the actual PlayStation mode where you could play different games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course there's no games loaded on there so couldn't really do anything with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but it's very interesting to see all this stuff considering that they've kind of been denying, you know, oh yeah, we're not working on a PlayStation phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously something I would be willing to bet you'll see at CES because they've shown off this new hardware stuff and it seems right up their alley.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the question I've got to ask about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this the same thing as the PSP2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because we've heard rumors about a PSP phone and we've heard rumors about a PSP2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my question is, is it actually the same thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I thought the rumors about there being sliders on the back and all this other weird stuff that we're seeing in this video was for the PSP2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now that you mention it, that does make sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: The not-so-clear video or pictures that we saw before were of the PlayStation Portable 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, we've seen some pictures before of the PlayStation phone, but they're different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just in the design of how they are and stuff, they look different.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a little bit similar to the PSP Go, almost.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it does look like a phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the slide-out keyboard, you know, you could almost replace that with a keyboard and be it, you know, just a normal Sony Ericsson phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could it... Again, I hate to harp on this, but do you think that maybe the PSP2 is just this without the phone, like an iPod Touch is to an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly, and that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that would be... It would make sense, I would think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's going to be... I don't know if I really care for the idea that it has, like, a touchpad on the back of the device.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I think nowadays you kind of almost have to have everything as like a touch screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can pet it and caress it from the back.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can literally reach around your PSP and rub it a little.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it would be very awkward to have a touch pad on the back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because I don't think that would lend itself well to the games unless it's just some sort of, you know, context sensitive touch pad or something like that in addition to other things.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I got the guy that's Bit.Trip Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or whoever he is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have him.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's in one of the Warp Zones.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just saw some videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's PC only, though, of the Minecraft guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is PC only.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd heard about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk about cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, definitely...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: The Go kind of stopped, pun intended, the PSP chat for a little while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because The Go, no matter how Sony or the fans try to spin it, was a miserable failure.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not a lot of stuff coming out from Sony for the PSP anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than, the only thing I've seen was Podapon 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, so what?
[SPEAKER_07]: The second one that you were selling as a download title.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know if that's...
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that could be the very last game they have in development for the original PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be just all now PSP2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't know if this would actually be marketed as a PSP phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: To me, it happens to be... I mean, it's not branded as a Sony PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's branded as an Ericsson.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, it's a prototype.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it still strikes me as, oh, it's this phone that happens to have PSP playing capabilities.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like there was that GameCube that was marketed as a DVD player that happened to play GameCube games, but they didn't call it a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Panasonic Q?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Panasonic Q. Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSP-2
[SPEAKER_07]: And also possibly, you know, something that's also that little touch panel thing that's on the front of the PSP phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perhaps this is where this patent comes from.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that it uses a two-fingered touch gestures for data manipulation.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they specify that the touch interface may be separate from the main display.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very similar to what we saw with the PSP2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they also said that...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's interesting, though, that they're putting out the... I mean, just based off what we've seen, I guess it's not make... I would be willing to bet that this thing's going to have a touchpad on the back for the PSP 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to have a touchpad on the front for, you know, the PSP phone or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the stuff that we've heard over and over again and seen pictures of, I don't think this is going to change all of a sudden, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's probably what we're going to expect.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if they're going to announce this at CES, you only have a few more weeks to wait anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's mid-January, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: You gotta know they're pissed about this, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are pissed about this video.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every single secret that they've had just leaks out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony, man, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to do something about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to our chat room at chat.orangehauntradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt, responding to a comment I made a minute ago, says, Why would I give my PSP a reach around?
[SPEAKER_09]: It never did anything for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It never made me a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_09]: AlphaKananagram says, I don't think this phone is the graphical powerhouse the developers are saying the PSP 2 will be.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was that chatter, I think, that we covered on the show a few weeks ago from a developer saying, We've seen it, and it's a huge graphical powerhouse.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, which might explain how they plan to compete with the 3DS by presenting better quality graphics, perhaps, than what you're going to see in 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because maybe the 3D thing will get old real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: BlackWolf seems to think that the PSP 2 will be at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_09]: Might be the better place to debut it.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameDeveloperConference.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way, totally left that out of my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But on a listener's tip, I did try going into home this week and doing the whole DDR room or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I couldn't even get it to work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gave up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I threw my controller into fitterage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, and then some folks are saying that it was the Panasonic Q, or as Frisbee says, the Panasonic QQQ.
[SPEAKER_09]: And lastly, Tigerclaw says, the PSP phone is just Sony trying to get into the iPhone and Android market for an app gaming perspective.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe trying to expand the Sony App Store or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trying to get more PS1 game sales and the cross-platform PSN games you can buy and movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know this thing will do everything the PlayStation Portable already does.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trying to expand the marketplace potential, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, moving on to another story.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a little bit of a follow-up to something that had come up last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember when I mentioned that Harmonix is for sale?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sadly, I'm not reporting about a buyer tonight, but I am saying somebody has said they are out of the picture, and you might be surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came from an interview with Bloomberg at Bloomberg.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: The CEO of Electronic Arts, John Riccatello, actually has said that the company has no interest in pursuing more multi-million dollar acquisitions for now.
[SPEAKER_09]: The company is going to focus on better integrating some of the casual game developers, such as Playfish and some of the other casual gaming things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine Pogo is a part of that too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, the people asked, are you interested in harmonics?
[SPEAKER_09]: And Riccatello said, if we did that, it would, quote, look like I'm doubling down on yesterday.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure some smart investor will buy the business feeling they can catch a falling knife, but more people have been cut trying to catch falling knives that have benefited from getting the timing exactly right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_09]: This whole rock band phenomenon.
[SPEAKER_09]: They made the original Guitar Hero game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_09]: They were working with Activision back then and Red Octane and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: They made the original Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: They split off to do rock band ABC and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's to say Harmonix is not going to make the next big thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: That just seems, I mean, I realize you're taking a little bit of a gamble there, but if there's one thing, there's one thing I could say in the nine, ten years practically we've been doing Orange Lounge Radio, the developers that take risks are the ones that get the big payoffs.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ones that just sit there with their thumbs up their rear, making the same old crap year after year, Konami, don't usually get to have the big payoffs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami doesn't really do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, okay, with their dancing games.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as the music games go and the stuff this show started about, yes, they did for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And granted, they've got some other neat stuff coming out now and they still have Metal Gear, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as far as the music game goes, that's how I feel.
[SPEAKER_02]: To quote the 62nd Ferengi Rule of Acquisition, the riskier the road, the greater the profit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, maybe they should be putting the masters of business forward.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, BlackWolf in our chatroom is saying that the falling knife thing is actually a misquote and the whole thing is not quite... I'm trying to look at what part of the story this is in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: He just linked us to something here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess he actually came out and said, I think the music genre is going to recover.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know exactly how.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be based on some new innovation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it all becomes dance-based.
[SPEAKER_09]: He likes Harmonix, and he said,
[SPEAKER_09]: the nervous investor would be worried about the decline of the music sector feeling like a falling knife the only part of that conversation that got reported was the falling knife part so he's saying I was misquoted although I guess they did use a part that he gave him but whatever he didn't mean to come off as harsh as he did so
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, at least I like the fact that he acknowledges that, you know, harmonics could be also sitting on this big thing here with Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think that's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't frown as much as I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it doesn't change the fact that they aren't interested in acquiring harmonics at this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even though maybe Falling Knife might have been harsh, it seems to be that the motivation behind that is...
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't have that next big thing just right yet, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although it is a little weird because he says Dance Central seems to be a big deal, but I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair loss.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for the Doctor Who fans like myself, there will be the last episode for the Doctor Who The Adventure Games called Shadows of the Vashta Narada, which for anyone who doesn't remember that one, this was the episode where they were stuck in the library and these things were eating the people, and it was the first episode that River Song showed up in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where can you buy it here in the US?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would assume the BBC website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Underwater Christmas Adventure for Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think these... What I think is interesting about this, because the BBC is kind of paying for these games, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're paying for the development, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of like...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a very different... And you have to pardon my ignorance here a little bit, but I've never lived in another country.
[SPEAKER_09]: All I know is it's a very different setup here in America than it is in Britain, where it's a lot more... I guess you could say, to me, it seems like the BBC is sort of like their PBS.
[SPEAKER_09]: But over here in America, we think of PBS as the network that plays...
[SPEAKER_09]: Classic, Opera, Shows, Sesame Street, and occasionally Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think the BBC is... But what I'm saying over there, they're actually making this more cutting-edge programming.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, imagine if PBS was making the shows Fox was making.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how it strikes me.
[SPEAKER_09]: But my point is, it's interesting that now we have this whole gaming thing coming out of that that is part of the public broadcasting industry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yet here, we don't have anything like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: PBS doesn't really make games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think there's been stories on the show before about how there's kind of been a call for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like why do we have the public broadcasting system, but yet we don't have anything for making games outside of, I don't know, maybe like America's Army, although that's still the government contracting with somebody else to make that for recruitment purposes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the closest thing I can think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just to let you know, the Doctor Who games are actually up on direct2drive.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can just search for them there, but I'm going to put a link to the downloads in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the point that Tigerclaw is making in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's not forget PBS also plays British shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first time I heard Doctor Who was PBS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that was my introduction to Doctor Who, and when I was little...
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Star Trek now, don't get me wrong, but when I was little, I didn't like Star Trek at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was watching Doctor Who, which I thought was a lot cooler and a lot neater because the concept was neat and it was this crazy old man and all these people running around with him.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my first Doctor was the fourth Doctor with Sarah Jane.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's to this day my favorite companion.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's back in the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has her own series and that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Doctor Who is just awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Majinami... Majinamicon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say Maji.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maji.
[SPEAKER_09]: Namicon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Majinamicon in our chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that's what I said before and I got yelled at for mispronouncing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Says... Namicron.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yet some political extremists want to shut down all public broadcasts, radio, TV, etc.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I recall correctly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've heard that too.
[SPEAKER_09]: And... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because of NPR.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thought makes me sad because when I think of PBS, I think of Sesame Street and Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood and Bob Ross and shows like that that wouldn't exist without PBS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it just makes me very sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, granted, maybe I haven't yet developed an appreciation for some of the other stuff they show, like not in the morning or not for children, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it just would be very sad if that were to go away.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what else PBS gave us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fawlty Towers for our British television.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Dwarf.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Red Dwarf.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I watched Keeping Up Appearances and Are You Being Served and Monty Python's Flying Circus.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need more of this on the PBS, but now we have BBC America, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gamer Girl in our chatroom says, Wait, I'm lost.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do they want to shut down PBS?
[SPEAKER_09]: Without getting too political on the show, I think it just boils down to that whole, you're poisoning the public minds with these crazy liberal ideas that PBS gives or whatever, which is a little bit ludicrous to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think as DarkSakura referenced, a lot of it comes back to NPR.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when some people don't like what a public organization is saying, they want to shut it down, I guess is...
[SPEAKER_09]: The best way I can cut it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's a lot of reading between the lines that goes with that type of stuff too.
[SPEAKER_02]: NPR gets a lot of its funding too from the Democratic Party.
[SPEAKER_02]: And PBS gets funding from political sources.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that if people want to pay for it, let them pay for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not your problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just don't listen to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's people too busy being right and wanting others to think just like they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the bottom line.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm not going to go any further than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying people being too busy being right and wanting other people to think the way they do.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let's talk about something we can all appreciate, and that is sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, Black Friday always means lots of big sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: And with that, you know the game companies have to come out and start waving their cock around, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kinect, of course, sold very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they've reached 2.5 million units with the help of Black Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's worldwide, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, they break it down, that's 100,000 units a day.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that they're on track to meet their original goal of 5 million units sold this holiday.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty awesome, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think they've already bypassed the move sales from what I remember as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, of course, Nintendo, um, they're saying that they sold a lot of DS's and Wii's during Black Friday, uh, might help that they also had a lot of, uh, new colors, uh, for different stuff, uh, coming out, new DSi XL colors, uh, I still don't understand why people go crazy about the colors, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the 25th Anniversary Red systems with Mario Kart in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They also had the Red Weaves, which people are going crazy over for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Orange and Green systems with different games with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, they sold 900,000 DS units.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's DS, DS Lite, DS Lite XL, or DSi's, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then of course 600,000 Wii's were sold and that's during the week of November 21st through the 27th that's really interesting about especially the number of Kinect sales I mean I'm hearing more people in the kind of the mass media quote-unquote
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: and Nintendo did the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: We kind of think you're going to do the same thing with Kinect.
[SPEAKER_09]: It won't meet that goal, but it looks like the supply is actually meeting the demand a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: In certain markets, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: How so?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, because, you know, the smaller guys obviously aren't getting enough I'm sure as hell know we aren't getting enough shipments of that shit They're sending them all to retail, those fuckers So, yeah Well, they obviously are shipping them somewhere because they're selling those units, so I don't know They're still going for a pretty penny, though, on eBay, that's for sure
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: How much?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the reseller market look like on that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I remember with some of those things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually $50 to $100 over retail.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let's get into a big story from this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Loki asked me before the show, why are we reporting on this?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think the response to this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let me tell you what's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Peta decided to parody another game this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they've done some video game parodies.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had like, I think there was like a Super Mario Brothers parody and some other crap too.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Super Meat Boy was the last game they set their eyes on and they decided to make this parody called Super Tofu Boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: and SuperTofuBoy is, you know, you play a chunk of tofu instead of a chunk of meat.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've made Super Meat Boy the enemy in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quote, Meat Boy is a vengeful, bloody cube of rotting animal flesh and he smells.
[SPEAKER_09]: After a short-lived fling with Bandage Girl, he became enraged when he was dumped for the tasty and satisfying Tofu Boy, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the blabber setup from the PETA game website.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the gameplay is...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fairly similar to Super Meat Boy, but it's obviously a cheap hack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I shouldn't say a cheap hack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Considering how fast this must have turned around, it's a pretty decent hack, dare I say it?
[SPEAKER_09]: But whoever they've got programming the games at PETA seems to be pretty talented, like it or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Meat Boy, Super Tofu Boy,
[SPEAKER_09]: None.
[SPEAKER_09]: PETA can't change anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was pretty much their response to the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not quite just that, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you read some of the other follow-up tweets and so on, apparently the guy who made Super Meat Boy went on to the PETA forums and posted under some different names to try to call attention to the game to, I guess, basically get free promotion.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it worked!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the crazy part.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if he's making that up in retrospect, but I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's actually kind of a smart thing to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, oh my god, can you believe they're making this game out of a moving piece of meat and glamorizing meat and meat is murder?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tasty, tasty murder.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's really funny that it worked in so many ways.
[SPEAKER_09]: So anyway, now they've come out and said, well, since we were able to get basically free advertisement for Super Meat Boy, we're going to put Super Tofu Boy as an unlockable character in the PC version of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they came out and tweeted, if you type pedophile...
[SPEAKER_09]: P-E-T-A-P-H-I-L-E at the character select screen, you will be able to play as Super Tofu Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, and I even made that joke earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Omicron says in here, the funny thing is that by Super Meat Boy creator's own admission, Meat Boy is a normal person without skin, not a hunk of meat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Way to screw up, PETA!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a game, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, I love Super Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a great arcade game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really think its only drawback is this whole, like, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a piece of meat?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I don't... That's your mark... What?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the artwork?
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the name of your game, Super Meat Boy?
[SPEAKER_09]: But whatever, I didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_09]: People probably say the same thing about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why the hell do you call your video game show Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not about oranges.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not in Orange County.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frisbee makes a very good point and this is very true.
[SPEAKER_02]: PETA, we euthanize more animals than we take in even though we don't support euthanization.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they actually have to report all this stuff to the IRS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a matter of public record.
[SPEAKER_09]: by the way Edmund McMillan who is the co-creator of the game he admitted that he made fake usernames in PETA's forum pushing the game at them in hopes that something would happen PETA is 1000 times more well known than Super Meat Boy and the fact that they went out of their way to make a parody like this is beyond flattering and amazingly helpful
[SPEAKER_09]: Edmund McMillan has said he was once a vegetarian and has worked as an animal control officer and he disagrees with PETA's total stance against the lab testing of animals and this is so interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's saying that being against the lab testing of animals means you're against these medical discoveries and treatments that save lives like his mom who is diabetic and that's why he's against PETA.
[SPEAKER_02]: The person right under the PETA lady, Ingrid Newkirk, is a diabetic who is on insulin made from dog testing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun double standard, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, why is it that this show keeps coming back to politics tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, but I just found it very interesting that an author of a game trolled the PETA forums and got his way.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's outstanding to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I should try to sing it because it's much prettier than I'm giving it credit for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can play a little clip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been nominated for a Grammy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's under Best Instrumental Arrangement Accompanying Vocalist category from the composer's debut album Calling All Dawns.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a really pretty song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's been going around since they've included it with the Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I hope that they win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a little clip.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Civ 4 really did have this epic theme song to it, which obviously is this, and then Civ 5 just pales in comparison.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, Civ 5's a great game, don't get me wrong, but it doesn't really have quite the moving song that Civ 4 did, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm happy to see that a video game song gets acknowledged with a Grammy nomination but here's the weird thing to me Civ 4 didn't like come out this year so it is not getting nominated because it's from Civ 4 it's getting nominated because Christopher Tinn ended up making an album that happened to come out in the past year that has this song on it so you wonder well did it get nominated because people knew the song already but Civ 4 is what a 4 or 5 year old game it wasn't nominated for a Grammy 4 or 5 years ago 2005 was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah
[SPEAKER_09]: so it's it's kind of interesting that it took this long and you got to wonder that oh well maybe people knew about it from here who knows uh Black Wolf in our chat room wants to point out that Christopher Tinn the album was also nominated so no matter how people found it uh it's it's it and if you actually listen to the rest of the album itself it is a really good album you know it's not pop or rock it's very different it's a world kind of more um I don't want to say Enya but more of that it's PBS music
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, also, I like AkumaJP in our chatroom says, Lion King.
[SPEAKER_09]: It does kind of sound like the theme of the Lion King, doesn't it, a little bit?
[SPEAKER_09]: A little less Elton John, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like the freaking Avatar soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never really listened to the Avatar soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it that good?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it had really pretty music in it, but it's the same type of the same theme.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, I promised you guys that we were going to have an interview tonight, so we are going to give Nick a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: He is the creator of Techno Kitten Adventure, and I'm really excited to talk to him about the game and how we got him on the show and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're calling him right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is totally live and unscripted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything could happen, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have questions, post them in our chat room at chat.orangelunchradio.com while we wait for him to pick up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wouldn't it be funny if this went to voicemail?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, oops, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Our show was kind of founded on the games like Dance Dance Revolution and Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're definitely no stranger to happy hardcore.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course we love kittens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_09]: So this game kind of seemed to be almost the perfect game in a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we have to know, what inspired Techno Kitten Adventure, Nick?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I recently discovered happy hardcore, which is the greatest genre of all time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Robot Unicorn Attack a while ago, and that kind of gave the idea to incorporate music into a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Robot Unicorn Attack didn't really have everything going to the music, it was more like a background sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, I like kittens, as you said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I wanted to incorporate all three things into one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this the first game you've ever made or do you have other XNA games out there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or was this like your first adventure?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a few more games out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of them are not very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the better ones is Physics Sandbox 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like Crayon Physics Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you've played that.
[SPEAKER_09]: A summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't really spend too much time on it, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Most of the time when it's actually licensing the music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that was the next thing I had to ask you about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you didn't make or write a song specifically for this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You somehow licensed an existing song that's out there, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell me how you got the song and found the song and got the song in the game, ultimately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'd heard the song before, like a trance version.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I discovered the happy hardcore version, which is from a company in the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty popular over there, but non-existent in the USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just contacted them and paid a fee and got to use it for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that song, of course, is Frisco with Sea of Love is the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, DJ Hicks' remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, I don't know if you're allowed to tell us, so you can pass on this question if you want, but do they get a cut of the profits because you used the song?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'm going to have to pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if I can answer that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are the possibilities?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me back up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: How successful has this game been for you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I know you're only charging a dollar for it, but I also noticed it was in the top 50 indie games, which has got to be a hard place to get to.
[SPEAKER_09]: So has this game been pretty successful for you money-wise?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually been less successful than my other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think they were...
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot more appropriate for the audience that goes to indie games, which seems to be like 13-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so it hasn't been as successful as Share the Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really interesting, but definitely there's been an audience for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, do you plan to do anything else with this idea?
[SPEAKER_05]: We are going to port it to Windows Phone 7, iPhone, and Android probably within the next three months.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll get it on my phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say, not bad for a bunch of 13-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them's got their own company somewhere that's going to help you out.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about, you know, I've got to ask about a potential sequel to Techno Kitten Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a Techno Kitten Adventure 2 in the works?
[SPEAKER_09]: Electric Boogaloo?
[SPEAKER_05]: The company that contacted me said that depending on how well it does, they'll probably think about making a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it'll be the same genre of music.
[SPEAKER_05]: For me, I'd like it to be some more happy hardcore, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll probably be a different genre.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I started off just wanting to make
[SPEAKER_05]: and then have Happy Hardcore playing in the background kind of make it like Robot Unicorn Attack and then while I was doing that I made a few effects on accident that worked really well with the music and so I decided to have everything sync up with it which took like listening to the song a few hundred times unfortunately to get it right but you love Happy Hardcore so it's okay right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's actually still a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how great of a song it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you've got to be careful, Nick, not to jump the shark.
[SPEAKER_09]: So enjoy this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played the metal version.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucked pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you do a techno shark.
[SPEAKER_09]: Techno sharks with lasers adventures.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got a couple more questions for you, and that is, are you thinking, though, I know you've got the company that wants to do other things with this title and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think maybe you're going to do another game that really has nothing to do with this whatsoever?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just kind of a one-off thing, and you have other games you want to do, or do you want to kind of play this out and see where it goes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now I'm working on a music-based shoot-'em-up, which is going to be way more gameplay-based, rather than a simple one-button game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you can say about that right now, or is it all still in the works?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty much going to be a music visualizer going in the background, and then just really hardcore shoot-'em-ups.
[SPEAKER_05]: and a couple other bullet holes sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I look at it quite a bit, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and what do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of them just say that it looks like it was made in MS Paint.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really read anything that horrified me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haters to the left.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of think the art style, in a way, is kind of part of the charm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, if it had been all, like, 3D, HD, Uber effects, I don't think it would really be the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: That make sense?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I say, you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And good luck with all those future projects.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to plug here on our little show?
[SPEAKER_09]: Of upcoming projects or what have you?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the game... You have a website or anything?
[SPEAKER_09]: Official website for...
[SPEAKER_05]: Not at the moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: There should be a website and it'll work.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll let you guys know about it when Nick tells us about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game is Technokitten Adventures and it's available right now on the Xbox Live Indie Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one whole dollar, which is really not a bad price at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the cost of a taco.
[SPEAKER_09]: As I said earlier in the show, technically on Sundays it's the cost of three tacos.
[SPEAKER_02]: A taco is for a moment, but techno kittens are forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: From tweet to call on the show, Techno Kitten Adventure, Nick from Techno Kitten Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: He didn't tell me his last name, but we'll give him a little bit of anonymity.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not real ID here on the show after all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks to Nick for being such a good sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Zom in our chatroom says, if you have $2, you can have Techno Kittens and a taco.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, in this economy, in this economy, it might be tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: And
[SPEAKER_02]: That's value!
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's move on to more stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, release dates.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's time for to get to the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you don't want to get Techno Kitten Adventure or you've already bought it and you want to look at other games, there's other stuff coming to a store near you, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and this will probably be the last week that stuff will be coming to a store near you, at least this year, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: It is dying down to zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, literally, I think the week after next, there's one game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the week after that, possibly another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, next week, though, the kind of coincide with it's a little bit early with the launch of the new Tron movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tron Evolution it's going to be kind of a prequel to Tron Legacy and that'll be coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360 and then they're going to be doing kind of an arena based sort of combat game it's Tron Legacy Battle Grid and that's coming out on the Wii oh and I guess it's also on PC as well
[SPEAKER_07]: So definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That looks pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and then the Tron Battle Grids, I believe, is also on DS and possibly PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: SBKX Superbike World Championship on PlayStation 3 and I believe Xbox 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's going to be kind of a street bike racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yogi Bear, the video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope that movie tanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: But sadly there's kids that are going to want to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, kind of a bit of a side note here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually got an invite and I can't go to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a Nielsen screening of a summer movie that's coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a computer animated comedy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't happen to be sitting in the middle of summer as a computer animated comedy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smurfs the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, so they don't tell you what the movie is.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't tell me what the movie is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go see it just to poop on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because Nellie's like, if you leave me with the baby all night long to go see Smurfs the movie, I'm going to kill you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sniper Elite Sniper Elite Sniper Elite
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, not to get too tangenty, but I've had not one, but several friends tell me that the Smurf Village game on the phone, iPhone, which is by Capcom, is actually really good for the whole, like, we rule Farmville-y, you know, Facebook-y type of game on your phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not touching that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw it, I was like, you know, I could download it for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: and check it out and see if it's any good.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not even going to check it out to see if it's any good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only Smurfs game I've played and will only play is the one on the ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the one where you can get her naked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Smurfette naked.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a bug.
[SPEAKER_09]: You go backwards or something instead of going forwards at the very end and there's a bug where Smurfette gets naked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a ColecoVision in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Smurfs when I was like 4 or 5 years old.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was a huge fan of the Smurfs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to tell you this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Becky just told me Julian and I saw the preview for Yogi Bear and he said it looked stupid and he's 3 and a half.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Julian should be the official movie critic of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the official child of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: During Tron, they're going to have the new Transformers 3 trailers.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This other game coming out, uh, Touchmaster... Wait, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is really important, though, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, it was on the Atari 2600 and the ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ColecoVision version of Smurf, Rescue, and Gargamel's Castle contains an Easter egg or programming error.
[SPEAKER_09]: Upon reaching Smurfette's screen, the player can return to the previous screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just before the screen changes...
[SPEAKER_09]: It will appear as though the top of Smurfette's dress comes off, making her appear topless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two of the background music tracks are simple, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares about the music?
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, Smurfette gets topless if you go backwards.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you leave her ass, she'll show her titties to get you to come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was worth reporting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it was worth reporting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know when she made She Was Evil?
[SPEAKER_07]: Touchmaster Connect it's all those wonderful bar games that they have what makes it unique compared to some of the other ones you can share your scores via Twitter and Facebook using this DS title so that's kind of neat I guess Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: 50s Dual Transfer coming out on the Wii and how can we not forget World of Warcraft Cataclysm the new expansion coming out on PC what did Nick say DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: Haters gonna hate
[SPEAKER_09]: No barfing over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bejeweled 3 on PC is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: New You Fitness, First Yoga and Pilates on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I must have had something in my throat there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, a week from today, Super Mario All-Stars Limited Edition for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a Super Nintendo game!
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, are you going to pay Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_07]: They did nothing to the game other than make it work with the controls.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're going to pay them $30?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that's what you really want.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it comes in a shiny box.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what kind of a message you're sending Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll buy anything that you sell!
[SPEAKER_09]: and then it's going to be remade in 3D and be $35 on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's better ROM hacks out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, what was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: New Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole, they completely re-edited the levels for the DS version to Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 3 and bonus levels and added all these challenge maps and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, that's a value right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they put that on a cartridge, I'd buy that shit in no time, but I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't even try to make it
[SPEAKER_09]: Zuma Blitz Zuma Blitz
[SPEAKER_09]: um it's actually pretty good uh it's pretty addicting and you know it's free they have their whole like you can buy things to unlock more special blah blah blahs but as far as the whole like competing with your friends for high scores and so on you know it's it's it's cool it's just like the bejeweled one
[SPEAKER_07]: Or here's something even better.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, I know that the stuff is already available on the virtual console and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, they've got a whole damn disc.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can tell you right now this image of this disc is probably going to be like a few megs and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the rest is just all blank space or filler or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, why didn't they put like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario World, Super Mario World 2 on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make it worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_07]: And hell, you could even charge 50 bucks for it at that point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's full of all the Mario games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But no, it's just Mario All-Stars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe there's an unlockable.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there's not an unlockable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there'll be an unlockable, all right, and guess what it'll be?
[SPEAKER_07]: Demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Virtual console demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you like these games?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can get them in their original form on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else for this week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: on the PlayStation 3, also Assassin's Creed Brotherhood, price reduction on End of Eternity, a game called Free Free Bowling, which I'm thinking is the Move bowling game localized for Japan, and a USB Neo Geo pad from SNK Play More comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is basically a Neo Geo pad with six buttons for fighting games, probably for use with some of the Neo Geo games that are on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going over to the Nintendo Wii this week in Japan, Donkey Kong Returns makes its way out.
[SPEAKER_09]: For once, we got a game about a week before they did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fitness Party also comes out from Namco Bandai, and a karaoke game called Karaoke Joy Sound Wii Super DX Hitori de Mina de Utai Hodai comes out from Hudson this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is a hell of a name there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The name doesn't quite make sense to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hitori de Mina?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like... Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks a little bit like Karaoke Revolution meets once in a while the actual music video, but otherwise it's party girls dancing on a stage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I don't even... I can't even... Is there para para?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no para para.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not worth it.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Pac-Man Party?
[SPEAKER_09]: That is also coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Boom Blox gets a price reduction in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, that's the 16th.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let me keep going with this week on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Castlevania Dawn of Sorrow gets a price reduction, so does Ganbare Goemon.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as new games, though, one of the ones you might want to check out is Ni no Kuni.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shikoku no Madoushi comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is an RPG from level 5, and damn it, I think this is out here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: is something else, and I can't tell what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: but it's an RPG from level 5 in Japan I'm sure somebody in the chat room will correct me soon enough there's actually an official website for it should I look at it real quick?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is a pretty big DS title.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe somebody in chat knows the rest.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as the Sony PSP goes, not a lot of big stuff this week, although there's some price reductions on things like Valkyria Chronicles 2 and Kurogani no Line Barrels Hudson the Best.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you know what this game is?
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe this is the DS game that's made with Studio Ghibli.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because the artwork looks very... very...
[SPEAKER_09]: Like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's what this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't think it is out here in the US, but I think I've read about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why it sounds familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: This looks like Studio Ghibli, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: With a little guy with a lantern on his nose and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's got to be what this is.
[SPEAKER_07]: No other studio puts lanterns on their nose.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no other studio would do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat room's jumping in there saying yes to Studio Ghibli.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the one with the huge 300-page magic book, says Dungeon Buster.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I figured it out eventually.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_02]: In the UK, we have a number of games, although not many.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 7th is Alien Breed 2 Assault and Bejeweled 3 and World of Warcraft Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 8th is Bomberman Live Battlefest.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on the 10th, we have Cave Story and Golden Sun, Dark Dawn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: and that's about it alright not a bad week all things considered I mean considering we're getting really close to Christmas I mean whether DarkSakura likes it or not Warcraft's gonna be a huge game and hey there's Tron and there's I don't give a crap about Warcraft Warcraft I mean to be honest I just do it to give you a hard time there's Plants vs. Zombies is in it now that's all I'm saying I just like giving you a hard time about it I know you do mwah mwah mwah
[SPEAKER_07]: a couple more new stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week yes so this is kind of cool you know and they were talking about possibly making a game based on this but now it's been confirmed that Christopher Nolan is actually working on an Inception video game and I think that's really cool love the world of Inception love the movie I still haven't seen it oh
[SPEAKER_09]: But it comes out on Blu-ray this week, so I plan to rent it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do not watch anything else.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm sitting here going, all I know is that there's a room spinny thing that might be cool in a video game, but otherwise I don't know why this would make a good video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you tell me why this is going to be an awesome video game without spoiling the movie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Think of it, it's like, it'd be like why the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Except the MMO sucked, like The Matrix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why The Matrix was kind of a cool movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really the environment of it and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a really neat concept.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Matrix game that was on GameCube and PS2 was not as terrible as I think some made it out to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Inception has that vibe of the first Matrix movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: They set up a world.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the kid from Third Rock from the Sun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or he was also the kid in Dark Shadows years and years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you ever see the movie Brick?
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to see Brick.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I haven't seen Brick.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he was in some other movie I saw called Mysterious Skin.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I kind of felt dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, this is the guy from Third Rock?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a really good actor nowadays.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a pretty good actor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Mysterious Skin was by the guy, and he does all these messed up teen angst movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: He did like the Nowhere, I think was one, and was totally fucked up, and there's another one in that whole series.
[SPEAKER_09]: All those teen angst movies, and he did that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so he's an awesome character.
[SPEAKER_07]: He plays a really awesome character in the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, DiCaprio's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, seriously, the movie Brick, though, it's a film noir set in a high school.
[SPEAKER_07]: In modern-day high school.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the dialogue, though, is film noir.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just so badass.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Inception, amazing movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the video game, you know, games based off movies aren't that great all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if Christopher Nolan's actually working on it, maybe it'll...
[SPEAKER_07]: Do all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, he says now he was considering putting together a video game based on the movie, but it looks like his plans are going a little bit further than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says he's told Entertainment Weekly that the project is a go and that he's working with a full team on the game as a longer-term proposition.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's excited to explore the medium of gaming by creating a new story set in the world of the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Entertainment Weekly suggests an MMO, but hopefully it's something better than that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I could see an MMO, but the problem I see with an MMO, though, is that you remember the Matrix Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Matrix Online just had some flaws.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Matrix could have made an awesome MMO.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just that what they released wasn't it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like the Wachowski brothers could have made an awesome trilogy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're like, let's give you all these powers all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, he's too powerful.
[SPEAKER_09]: To this day, I've never seen the third movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not missing much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has an ending reminiscent of Highlander 2, which was also a crappy movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I hear.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, but didn't Highlander 2, wasn't that the one that introduced Sean Connery?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or was he in the first one too, and I just forgot?
[SPEAKER_02]: The first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, he was Ramirez.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how many years it's been since I've seen Highlander?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was like in college, where everybody got high and watched Highlander.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I didn't, because I'm... It's called Highlander, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta watch it high.
[SPEAKER_09]: I went to Chico State, folks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: There is the possibility there that there will be interactive elements into shows viewed on the console and that there'll be also content silos, meaning that like HBO and Showtime could have their own little areas to subscribe to.
[SPEAKER_09]: So could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like this because remember when I talked about the whole 1 versus 100 getting canceled, I was like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Why doesn't Xbox make more of a network?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kind of talking about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like this whole idea of interactivity or more interactive shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Xbox had a great thing with 1 vs. 100 and it's a damn shame that they lost the rights to the new Game Show Network version or whatever the hell it is that's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, have you seen the new Game Show Network version with Carrie Ann Inaba as the host?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's not as fun as it was on Xbox Live, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually really into something like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just hope the interactive stuff isn't cheesy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You see a lot of Blu-ray discs that have the interactive movie component, which is just asking dumb poll questions and things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to see them do more interactive game shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've had the rumor of a Poker Night game that's apparently in top secret testing right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe there's a show to be made of that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if you could vote on the ending?
[SPEAKER_09]: Vote on a character getting killed off or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: American Idol being voted on through your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: X Factor on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would think if anything what the interactive part might be is like marking clips or something like that and sharing them with friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say, hey, have you seen this?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, look, it's a nipple slip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, so you think this is more like a TiVo that you could share?
[SPEAKER_09]: So if there's ever another Janet Jackson boobie that slips out, people could be like, hey, I saw this awesome clip and wanted to share it with my friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's like, I guess, Justin TV, where you can save clips and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God, I hope we're not going to be lifecasting through our Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's certain people I don't want...
[SPEAKER_09]: to see their lives.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the Kinect is putting a camera in all of our homes, but this is not an idea I like.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although, oh my God, could you imagine like now when they do one versus a hundred, like with two and a half million Kinects out there and growing, they could have the one be on TV with the whole Kinect thing, which is a nice little camera in your house.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's alive.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the Xbox 720 will just be called Skynet.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where we go from here, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to chime in on this live with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, isn't Sky a service that's in the UK?
[SPEAKER_07]: And technically, isn't it a network?
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you seen this boy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ezam in our chatroom says, that's the new show on Current TV, Bar Karma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Viewers make the story and they produce it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, here's a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is totally random.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they've got to have this, like some sort of Photoshopped, you know, have you seen this boy with Pedobear?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure it exists somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, the name that I can never pronounce.
[SPEAKER_09]: Majinamicon in our chatroom says, DC figured out a way to capitalize on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: They announced a telephone poll for readers to decide whether he lived or died.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jason Todd.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, 10,000 votes later, he was dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone hated Jason Todd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's live again.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: They did that in the 70s with Andy Kaufman on Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know if that's really... Remember?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I know none of you were alive when this happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like it was 10 years before I was born.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't in the Man on the Moon movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they did a whole viewer poll thing to banish Andy Kaufman from Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he was banished.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I remember...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna really date myself and make myself super lame here but I don't give a fuck alright do you remember I'm Married With Children they had a night where you could vote on the ending if Al Bundy was going to actually tell Peg he loved her or not like it was a whole I think it was for Valentine's Day and you could actually call in and vote on the ending where if Al Bundy is gonna say I love you Peg or just go to bed without saying it cause the whole episode was about Peg was whining oh Al
[SPEAKER_09]: You never say I love you to me or whatever was the whole plot.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, that was such a great show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they had an interactive episode.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_09]: From what I remember, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: He said, I love you at the end of the night.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was all the women voting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to give you beer more often.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said that to get a reaction out of DarkSakura and didn't really get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gave him a look.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did get side-eye a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't transfer well to radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know side-eye like
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob gets a snort.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember what I was saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too busy looking at gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also remember an episode of You Can't Do That on television where you could vote, but that wasn't real.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really dating myself tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That does not compute episode where they used gray slime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100 Matt in our chat room says, I remember this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank God it's not just me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I grew up unmarried with children.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my show.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of blasts from the past, we like to do a segment here on the show where DarkSakura digs through the archives of gaming and finds a game that she says, Hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get off my lawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Al.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found the gayest game ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Dan.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should play this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying to get him to download it for me and he won't do it out of pure principle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So somebody needs to get it for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cho Aniki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said, gayest game ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of sad that I asked, but here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, when I told Rob I was picking it, he replied with LOL Gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Jovani Key, it means Super Big Brother.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a game series done by Masaya and published by NSC Corp.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out in 1992 for the PC Engine with lots of spin-offs and sequels and other versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: it's a mostly most versions are side-scrolling shoot-em-up plays kind of like Gradius we did get Cho Aniki on virtual console and somebody needs to give it to me
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually still been looking for a huge part of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to have a copy of Cho Aniki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, to start with the first game, the plot has the heroes, who are these big buff muscle-bound men in speedos, going through different areas, space, ruins, cities, fighting alien invaders.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bo Emperor Bill, which is Bo Tebiru, which is supposed to be short of bodybuild.
[SPEAKER_02]: is basically a man who achieved 10 consecutive victories in the Great Galaxy Bodybuilding Contest is facing an ever-decreasing supply of protein.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's invading other star systems to establish protein factories.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so... Wow!
[SPEAKER_02]: The Heaven Realms sent Ida Ten and Ben Ten to take over Bo Emperor Bill.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it's a sweaty, hot muscle battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the main characters actually in this one was Ita Den was just a pretty guy and Benten who was a girl with blue hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you have the Musclebound Men, Samson and Adon who are the Musclebound Men in Speedos.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they hover around and they are the brothers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the whole genre of games that these are in are what's called, they're very kitschy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're called bakage, which is like idiot game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: and Fairly Neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really pornographic, just gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gay!
[SPEAKER_02]: And the rights to the series are now actually owned by Xtreme Co.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ltd.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and in this one you fight the you actually have to raise the Neo Builder army um well the the bad guy is a name is uh Bote Kon Shiasu which is body conscious it's a pun to fight Ida-Ten and Ben-Ten and um they uh fall in love in a lope so uh Samson and Adon have to fight and uh it's
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it came out on Virtual Console Japan in 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cho Aniki, Bakuretsu Ranto-hen, which is a different one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Idaten, Benten, Samson, and Adon.
[SPEAKER_02]: They attack by gyrating and flatulating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sabu, who is a pagoda-shaped ship with Elvis Presley on the top Mami19, who is a cute girl mixed with a battleship transporting three naked, frolicking men Adam, who is actually Adam from The Creation who is half-naked and riding on the moon Bote, who is the guy from the first game and Uminin, who is a latex creature that looks like a condom
[SPEAKER_02]: Cho Ainiki, Kyuukyoku, Meteki Ginga Saikyo Otoko
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, yeah, it's still weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, it's actually available for download on PlayStation Network, uh, in North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, get it, and then send it to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we also have the WonderSwan, uh, version, Cho Aineki Otoko no Tamahuda.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually... I've explained what Hanafuda is before, haven't I?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo started off as a Hanafuda company.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's playing cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a type of playing card game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I just wanted to... I switched the music to the ending from the PC Engine version because I wanted to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's actually a portmanteau of Tamashii, which is soul, and Hanafuda, which is a card game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Tama Balls
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no, I was going to say, you know what's funny is that obviously I know of this game because I've been doing this show for a while and how can you not know about this game?
[SPEAKER_09]: But I've never played it, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never played this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like I just kind of look at it with a raised eyebrow going, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I'm sure is what most people do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's probably the point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, the last one on my list is Cho Aineke, Senaru Protein Densetsu, which is Legend of the Holy Protein.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's done by the group that did Sengoku Blade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Holy Protein Batman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to read exactly what's on the article.
[SPEAKER_02]: The plot of the game centers on the holy protein, a deity-like glob of what may be semen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Samson and Adon hover around the glob, absorbing enemy fire as they did in the previous game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has a Mona Lisa painting that fires lasers from its eyes, and a giant cross-dressing man in a maid outfit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there was Choaniki Zero, which came out by Extreme Co.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ltd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole thing with Cho Aineke is that it's so completely freaking nuts that you can't help but love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's actually... Masaya made a game called... Well, a series called Langrisser, which I've played a few of those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Samson and all of them are in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to go to the Muscle Shrine where you fight Samson.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you can use the Aineke summon.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the Mega Drive, Super Nintendo, and PlayStation versions, which I've played the Super Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom game God Hand makes fun of Samson and Add-On as powerless yet flamboyant drag queens, who are the first bosses in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, they, they have, uh, Samson and Adlon have a weapon called Men's Beam, which is white energy from holes in their head.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, it's gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I, I'm saying this, it's gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I don't really think it's gay as in homosexual, it's more like gay as in, um, Christmas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that it's full of penis references and naked men in speedos and drag queens I don't remember playing it maybe I did and I just blocked it from my mind Yeah, I'm not so sure I think I might use the word what
[SPEAKER_02]: I won it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: If DarkSakura's all finished over there, Cho Aniki on various systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Big Brother.
[SPEAKER_02]: Various systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, Rob, after I've played, I've played like a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're actually really fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's so bizarre.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just mean, you can't help but laugh and be happy while you're playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's naked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then it is gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because gay means happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wasn't meaning like... I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, it was, it's gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, it's, it's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Penis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm 12.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to need to crop that and add that to the soundboard at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, just messing.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, we're going to take a break, but don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your Twitter topics, and God, you saw what came last week and what that became, so who knows what's on the Twitter this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So get those in at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to also get to the mailbag, and we're going to talk about some other news stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to talk about some goings-on in Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to talk about the future of arcade games in another country.
[SPEAKER_09]: and we're going to talk about a game that is being pirated that's doing something kind of lulzy especially if you're DarkSakura you're going to find this pretty lulzy so we'll be back after this quick break with more of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio, the video game show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are taping live our 392nd episode on this lovely Sunday evening, December the 5th, right, of 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: I lost track of time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only 20 shopping days left.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, no, not even that many.
19.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, this is the part of the show where we like to welcome you guys back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Duke Nukem Forever Earlier
[SPEAKER_09]: True, but that's also more money.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like $18 to see if I... Because I don't know if I'm going to like it or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: You think?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then I'm also like, well, shit, Cataclysm's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you could borrow my copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then also there's always the whole like, I could just play it on Alan's computer, but we always get distracted because like, oh, but we really need to run a raid and wow, oh boy, we really need to go out and drink or whatever we're doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, have either of you guys been to the stores and looked at deals before?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I didn't specifically go shopping.
[SPEAKER_02]: When Marissa was here, we went over to the Art and Fair Mall.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we just walked and looked at stuff, and I popped into Forever 21 and looked at jackets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I like some of the clothes there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't wear all of it, but I like some of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it a freaking madhouse, though, like the rest of the mall seemed to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was kind of crazy, but not so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I went into... You see... Wait, I did buy something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's not in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought this...
[SPEAKER_02]: Look how I bounce!
[SPEAKER_09]: But you were looking at Pyramid Head on your shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peahitty.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shirt is special to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: All this month we'll be having a special which is our year-end review of comics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh boy, so now you know what you gotta catch up on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to see how much we are PO'd with Matt Fraction.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, now do you remember the show I do?
[SPEAKER_09]: I plugged your show, you remember my show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, the one with Dolly Parton and her boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Best Little Horde House in whatever fucking planet that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Azeroth, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Azeroth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, you're cute, you and Extifer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're adorable.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a fun show this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a special guest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Frat Matt is what I call him online, but Grandpa Warcraft is what we were calling him because he's been playing, and you know Matt, he's been playing Warcraft since Vanilla, so we were calling him Grandpa Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a good show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have absolutely no idea what that means.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's old and he plays Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it means.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, we have a huge show planned.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're just doing the same old show.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it is Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_09]: The third expansion of WoW does come out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're going to talk a lot about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_01]: Plants vs. Zombies!
[SPEAKER_01]: Cataclysm!
Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Splooge, splooge, splooge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: The sad thing is it goes live at midnight tomorrow and I gotta go to bed because of work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't stay up and play WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Tuesday, I have to go bake cookies because there's this whole cookie party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, there is a cookie party going on at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cookie party!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why the show got canceled.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the best part of the Sarah Silverman show was Cookie Party with what was the host name?
[SPEAKER_09]: Miss something on Cookie Party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the listeners at home are like, I thought this was a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what's going on at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's do some rapid fire news and remind them that it is a game podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, Twitter, last chance.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You may remember that Ghostbusters, a game that came out almost a year and a half ago, there was a few achievements that were unable to be achieved, I guess, because the game was broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: and well, apparently they have actually just put through Xbox Live certification the update that will fix those and I guess these now four achievements that were unable to be unlocked before are being fixed.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool that they're actually still working on patches for games despite the fact that they came out a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ghostbusters, Sanctimus Slime, Xbox Live Arcade, PlayStation Network, and PC
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of a top-down action game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're saying that it's being developed by the Assault Heroes creator, Wanako.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a four-player online and local co-op top-down action game that's going to not really have any of the voice actors because those are expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're not really sure if the characters from the movie, obviously, are going to be there or they're going to be replaced by a new team or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: um but yeah it's uh pretty awesome looking actually from some of the screenshots that they had so I'll be coming sometime soon next year uh Gameloft is announcing some new games they actually had some pretty decent ones when they're not ripping off other games um
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like how I worked that in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nova 2, it's their first person shooter game that's kind of a little bit like Halo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's inspired, I guess, if you will.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's actually a pretty solid first person.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you said they weren't ripping off other games anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shadow Guardian, New IP for Gameloft,
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's kind of similar to like an Uncharted or Tomb Raider game it's more of like an action adventure game so it looks very Uncharted-esque but you know nice to see some sophisticated games coming to iOS despite the fact Gameloft is really hit or miss with some of this stuff but yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: The original IP stuff's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're Gangstar or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a bad clone of the old PSP or PlayStation 2 Grand Theft Auto games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, let's see, Def Jam.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the UK, Def Jam is doing their Rapstar game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're having a competition that offers the winner a record contract.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, they're going to be teaming up, I guess, with Atlantic Records UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they're giving one lucky UK resident a chance to have their very own record.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to be employing the game's freestyle mode and contestants will upload their hottest 40 bars, give or take, and they're going to be judged by the Def Jam Rapstar community because they do have a really big community aspect to the game, actually, despite the fact a lot of people don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a chance to get this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to get it for just the microphone because I got it for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually passed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't a bad game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't listen to really the  I mean, maybe there's a couple songs in there I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not the type of game  I can't see myself honestly playing this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially  I live by myself and a lot of my gaming is alone, so I just can't see myself sitting there
[SPEAKER_09]: Wrapping by myself in my apartment.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there's just something kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm crying all night tonight because I just watched a sad movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll play Def Dam Rapstar to make me feel better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sip it on gin and juice.
[SPEAKER_07]: it says the top regional finalists will then have to compete in front of a live audience at the UK HMV locations they're saying 8 mile style and that's going to be in February and of course that means that the winner will be able to have the actual record contract see Loki you should be participating in this that's why you need the game yes
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet anything if you were to submit a video, you would be voted as the winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't believe that Sacramento is in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: My basic geography knowledge says that's not correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to fix this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does Kidman rap?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who else is in the UK?
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Ake Ripper?
[SPEAKER_07]: We need some Swedish rappers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get Ake Ripper.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does Sweden count?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to find that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I have some news, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just not as cool as Swedish rap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Band Reloaded is now available on the iOS systems, meaning the iPhone, the iPod Touch, the iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's $5 on the phones and phone with no phone and $10 on the iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a new expert mode and apparently full vocal support.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you could actually sit there and sing along with your phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also the iPad version now has split screen multiplayer and several different ways to have the action on screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can reorient gameplay if you're a lefty.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently there's a whole drum kit now that you can kind of have so you can kind of beat your iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are quite a few games available when you initially download it, including Kryptonite, Three Doors Down, So What You Want by Beastie Boys, White Wedding by Billy Idol.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I love that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call Me When You're Sober by Evanescence, The Perfect Drug by Nine Inch Nails, Hella Good by No Doubt.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, a lot of these games are sort of in the rock band game anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also tracks that you can download in the music store.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess there's some free tracks too in the music store.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, they're like indie bands and stuff, but the Acrobats are in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Daylight and Dollar Short, if you like the Acrobats.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people around the internets were fans of Splosion Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that game that was on the indie marketplace?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_09]: A sequel has been announced.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Splosion Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they're doing like the whole Ms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pac-Man thing, but seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a really early announcement, but there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: The CCO Josh Baer of Twisted Pixel has said, quote, We could have churned out new levels for Splosion Man, but we wouldn't have had the time to add in new gameplay puzzles or cool new character stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we didn't want to just do Splosion Man 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had to be something a little more interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is why we're making Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Splosion Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually a teaser trailer that's out there and everything, and as you can expect, it pays homage to Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: World of Warcraft news, but not the kind that gets me excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: World of Warcraft apparently is now streaming and playable on an HTC Desire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, this whole little tech demo that was out there before has now been fully realized, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: An HTC Desire smartphone is running World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't know if it's like a streaming thing or what, but there's actually a demo that's out there on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: To start us off with some Kirby.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Kirby?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kirby's Epic Yarn will be out in 2011 for our European friends on February 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to say 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to wait, but it's going to be all cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have to change it into British English, I guess, so that it can be a duvet instead of a comforter and a lift instead of an elevator and a boot instead of the trunk, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: and uh new uh characters for Super Street Fighter 4 we have dun dun dun didn't we call it last uh last week Oni Akuma who is like Shin Akuma who is the super evil one and then we have Evil Ryu so that's gonna be super hot because I loved Evil Ryu of course I would love to have Evil Sakura next Dark Sakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, for Rock Band, more download content.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get Queen!
[SPEAKER_02]: Finally, finally, finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rock Band 3 upgraded tracks from Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's what's also going to be in the Queen Extravaganza Pack 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hammer to Fall, Keep Yourself Alive, Now I'm Here, Play the Game, Tenement Funster, We Are the Champions, We Will Rock You, and the Queen Rock Band 3 Enhanced Pack, I Want It All, I Want to Break Free, Killer Queen, One Vision, Somebody to Love, and Under Pressure.
[SPEAKER_09]: which also is David Bowie I'm so buying that enhanced pack so am I the first pack is a lot of really kind of like off-cut tracks which I mean Queen is Queen they're cool they threw two big ones in there to kind of make it feel a little more valuable but I definitely want like all my favorite Queen songs are in that other pack so and for some reason this is weird I never bought the Queen track pack in Rock Band originally like I just somehow missed it or I wasn't playing Rock Band at the time like there's already like 15 Queen songs available in there
[SPEAKER_09]: and I really need to get SingStar Queen at some point because I'm sure I can find it really cheap now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like SingStar ABBA is on like every Target clearance rack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really need to get SingStar Queen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com there's some comments.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt is talking about Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explosion Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Explosion Man better have her making a sandwich in the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tigerclaw says the third one should be Junior Explosion Man or Baby Explosion Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about Explosion Baby Hey let's go to the tweeter
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100 Matt is sending us a story courtesy of Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_09]: South Korea is getting ready to set an internet curfew for young teens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had not heard about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, I did not listen to USL last night.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a very... Yeah, on Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a very naughty boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But apparently, South Korea...
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I notice I'm being linked to a story from Fox News, so take it from me with the greatest song.
[SPEAKER_09]: South Korea is apparently considering a nationally enforced gaming curfew in an effort to curb internet addiction.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know a lot of times we've had those crazy internet addicts story and they all seem to be out of South Korea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apparently it will make it illegal for internet service providers, if this bill is passed, to give online gaming access to users under the age of 16 between the hours of midnight and 6 a.m.
[SPEAKER_09]: For South Korean students, this will mean no gaming at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's normal to be in school until midnight due to extracurricular activities and studying.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That much study is actually pretty normal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, makes me feel like a lazy asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though I was doing every extracurricular activity in high school, I was still home by 7 or 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you guys think about this ban?
[SPEAKER_09]: They would never get away with something like that here in the U.S., that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the government's responsibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the parents' responsibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're not doing their job, then it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope, I agree 100%.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not the government's responsibility, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya on Twitter wants to remind us of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yes, this is something I definitely need to plug.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we'll probably be plugging a little more as we hit the deadline here.
[SPEAKER_09]: but the USL OLR Madness this used to be called March Madness but I guess they moved it for March 2011 is now open for nominations this is something a little more that our buddies at Under Station Live do and they really involve themselves with but we like to support it here at OLR and I know I have already submitted my list now if you don't know what this is it's basically a competition a la March Madness the NCAA competition to choose the greatest game ever
[SPEAKER_09]: IDK
[SPEAKER_09]: but you need to submit your top 25 list to uslmadness at gmail.com now the deadline is January 3rd 2011 so you have a little while but don't procrastinate
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with Jamie's thoughts on Cho and Ikki
[SPEAKER_09]: I got the PS1 and to say that it's weird and or gay is an understatement.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like saying water is wet.
[SPEAKER_09]: First it was a novelty for me, but once the novelty wore off, I forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: As long as you mean gay meaning happy, I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, it's full of homoerotic imagery.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is, it is, but I just, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know me, I never use the word gay to mean anything bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, penis.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, there's a lot of games like that, though, where once the novelty wars off, it's kind of over.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's sadly too many games like that out there, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, Tigerclaw sends us a variety of tweets.
[SPEAKER_09]: I seem to remember there's a two-tweet limit, but I'm feeling generous, and I had beer before the show tonight, so I'm going to let him have all three tonight, because I'm kind and generous.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, the Toronto Police recover half a million dollars in stolen Sony goods.
[SPEAKER_09]: they are on it up there in Canada a 39 year old man in Toronto was arrested for stealing half a million dollars we're assuming of course that's Canadian I don't know because they call it dollars too
[SPEAKER_09]: PlayStation 3s, PSPs, and games apparently this was due to tractor trailers that were stolen on November 15th and 16th in Brampton these trailers had about half a million dollars in PS3s, PSPs, and video games that's where all the Sony stuff went in Canada well, the 39 year old was arrested and will be in court on January 10th of 2011
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw also sends us a link.
[SPEAKER_09]: Standalone motion sensing game console believes honesty is the best policy.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is linked to a story on Joystick.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is this all about?
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently it's a knockoff of the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a system now called the Wireless 60.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's a description on the back of the box.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_09]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: The description on the back of the box says, If you are looking to purchase or own an Xbox, PlayStation, Nintendo Wii, or equivalent, this product does not compare or compete with these technologies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's awfully upfront and endearing of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's brutally honest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for being honest.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I love that it is in small print on the back.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're looking for a Nintendo Wii, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: This might not be what you wanted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you want the golf kit and the ping pong kit, this is the system for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: How much is one of these?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're probably cheap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, some of these games probably are much worse than a bunch of the crap on the Wii, honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might be selling yourself short a little bit there, Wireless60.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the name, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just shy of being Wii60.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: and lastly from Tiger Claw in our last tweet tonight at twitter.com slash OLR people really did buy Donkey Kong with bananas do you remember that there was this whole promo with UK gamers and the UK could actually buy the game with bananas yes apparently there were some folks that actually braved the cold weather and 20 people walked away with the game having paid for them in bananas
[SPEAKER_09]: How many bananas?
[SPEAKER_09]: It just said a bunch of bananas.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we don't know exactly how many, but it was the first 20 people in line to give a bunch of bananas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like a fun promo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then all the staff's like, what the fuck are we going to do with these bananas?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically a, eat them!
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, bananas are great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically a Black Friday-esque type of promotion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, Old Navy gave away Dance Central to the first few people in line, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, you know, that's not completely unheard of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's going to do it for Twitter Topics Night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the meantime, back to more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they had kind of an indie launch thing for the Xbox Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now there's kind of the Microsoft Game Studios promotion that they're doing for Xbox Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, they have three games coming out for the Games for the Holidays presented by Microsoft Game Studios.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, um, these three games would be including World of Keflings, uh, which does have Avatar support in it, Wrath of Skulls, and Ilo Milo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though Ilo Milo you can get at, you know, now if you know how.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: So, each, uh, looks like they're gonna be, um, you know, 800 Microsoft points each, uh, or $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, Ilamilo, of course, is on Xbox Live right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a way to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you can wait to the official release, which is January 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and then, of course... Now, why would I want to wait?
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, who wants to wait?
[SPEAKER_07]: World of Keflings, that is kind of a puzzle slash racer mashup game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's going to be, I'm sorry, the puzzle racer is Rascals.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's going to be coming out on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_07]: World of Keflings will be on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I said, those are each going to be...
[SPEAKER_07]: 800 Microsoft Points or $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, if you buy more than one, there's some bonuses that you get with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily money back, but some neat stuff anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get cross unlockables for each game.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, in Ilo Milo, you can get an unlockable Keflins or Rascal costume for Ilo or Milo.
[SPEAKER_07]: by purchasing the other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Additionally, you can also unlock Elo and Doug as playable characters in Ratskulls.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can also unlock Ratskull characters within Elo Milo and World of Keflings by purchasing the full range of games as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even crazier, it says you can get...
[SPEAKER_07]: and Rascals Early by buying World of Keflings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rascals can be bought from within that game a week before it's released on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I have to draw a map to follow all that, but fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically all these games are giving each other the reach around, essentially.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting promotion.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the three-way reach around.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of like that idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, even though none of these games are things I'm particularly excited about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess you never know, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, like, I didn't think I'd be excited about Super Meat Boy, and it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a neat promotion and very different from what the summer one where it's just like, buy X number of games, get points.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of like the idea they've got going on here a little better.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the way the games are interacting with each other.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any interest in any of these games, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rascals kind of sounds neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ilo Milo looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never played Kingdom of Keflin, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: I know I never played Kingdom of Keflings either, but apparently it's pretty popular.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I thought it was only popular because of the Avatar thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: but I don't know alright well moving on to a game I am really looking forward to and I was very disappointed it didn't make this Christmas but whatever it'll come out soon enough when it's ready LittleBigPlanet 2 is on its way pretty soon and there's a beta going on right now now there's an update that happened on the PlayStation blog where the marketing manager at Sony Computer Entertainment America talked through a tutorial how you can record voices in the game and assign them to characters
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Marissa needs to create Uta.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Marissa.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish I was able to see her when I was in LA.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so looking forward to this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_09]: Creating levels in LittleBigPlanet 1 was hard enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't imagine how hard it's going to be in version 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope you guys are too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, will you be doing some voice acting for a level in LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: AlphaCananagram says this is old news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever, it's new to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not in the beta.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't been following the news as closely as I should.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, and Tigerclaw reminds us as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought this was on last week's show, but maybe not.
[SPEAKER_09]: LittleBigPlanet 2 has no 3D support.
[SPEAKER_09]: There will not be 3D in LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to that I say, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is not necessary.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega is, well, looking to expand back into the arcade market, but not in Japan, not in the US, but in China.
[SPEAKER_02]: It, as being the second largest economy in the world, China seems like it's going to be a prime market for video games, especially arcade-based games, and so they are actually taking games like OutRun and Virtua Fighter and doing new versions of them in China.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes sense, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really not sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think Rob?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean I don't live in that country so it's hard for me to say what kind of culture it is but...
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate that arcades are dying here, but at the same token, when was the last time I went to one?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the reason why I don't go to them is that there's not a lot of serious arcades here anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think if they're doing it more seriously in Japan and China, which makes sense because the internet cafe culture is much bigger there too than it is here.
[SPEAKER_09]: There aren't really internet cafes here anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there's one or two, especially in the Chinatowns and Koreatowns.
[SPEAKER_09]: The biggest one I can think of is in Koreatown in LA.
[SPEAKER_09]: But cyber cafes to us are like Starbucks where you bring your laptop and use the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what I was like.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's so many neat cafes, especially in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go to the cat cafes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think it's to encourage a more social aspect yet still, you know, it offers a service with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of those social games were the best though.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it is kind of a bummer that Xbox Live sort of took that and made it not needing to go to your arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like the best example I can think of is when Soul Calibur 2 was in the arcades and it had that mode where you had your own fighter and the arcade machine would start to kind of memorize how you play.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then you could fight other people to take over the kingdom.
[SPEAKER_09]: And remember that whole little mode?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Conquest mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: or um remember when I used Kilik something uh near and dear to our hearts remember when DDR Max 2 was in the arcades and had the community unlocks where the more you played the faster you'd be able to unlock stuff that was always kind of neat I think so and we would keep being and figuring out uh which one was next and how the pattern was working and how many points and I remember we would be there for some of the unlocks it was like oh my god we got an unlock we'd take pictures and stuff it's Santa Marita yeah
[SPEAKER_02]: Max 300, what's this crap?
[SPEAKER_09]: The hell is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope maybe some of the ideas used in China and Japan, they can figure out how to make them work in the U.S., but I'm not going to hold my breath because I think the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: is just a bunch of gambling for kids and these ticket-spinning machines.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, Loki, do you have better news for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ticket Spitting Machines The We Speak Microphone
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I came out with Animal Crossing, City Folk, and they're like, oh yeah, you can chat with other people, and hey, that's awesome technology to be able to chat with other players when you're playing games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, something that's standard with, say, the Xbox and PlayStation 3, which is why we need to get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's sadly what's happening.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii Speak peripheral is now limited at retail locations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Additional shipments can be made if consumer demand increases, according to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, they are no longer producing those for retail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not to say that games won't still support it, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially since they don't really have any sort of headset options or anything like that for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, the Wii's kind of had to catch up in some ways, even though Reggie doesn't want you to think that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, in some ways, they had to really catch up to some of the technology at the 360 and the PS3 was doing, but it didn't work in this case.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think part of it was that they'll throw out these peripherals, and Nintendo's done this a few times.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'll throw out these peripherals and then not really support them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, there's one or two games that support it, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, the balance board, in some ways, is a bit of an anomaly.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it didn't have this damn good A-plus game behind it, I think the balance board would be added to the list of stuff like Wii Speak.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Wii Speak was for what?
[SPEAKER_09]: A game on the Wii that honestly, and I hate to say this, wasn't very good because we'd seen it before.
[SPEAKER_09]: If there hadn't been two other Animal Crossing games already, then the Wii version would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that wasn't the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then what else used Wii Speak?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, and it's not like the Wii is known for its online gaming capabilities, where Wii Speak would come into play, so it was kind of useless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some folks in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say this name again and butcher it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maginomicon says, yeah, that was a total waste of my money.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to be fair, there wasn't a better offer on the PS2, a better showing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's one way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then AlphaCanadagram in our chatroom says, seriously, why isn't the WeSpeak hacked already for the PC?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe nobody cared.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you could just plug a microphone into the PC and there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Maginomicon also says, what about the broadband adapter for the GameCube?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Talk about a peripheral that really went wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: That could have been an awesome must-have peripheral.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the Phantasy Star game on GameCube was actually really awesome, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Phantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's a bummer that Sega made it because Nintendo just didn't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo hates Sega, confirmed.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: One other story I have for you guys before we get to the mailbag at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Majinamacon says I pronounced his name right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I feel like I should play the level up music.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You all right over there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was singing a little music for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apple made an update to the Terms of Service on Game Center this week saying that they will now use your real name when you send a friend request or reply.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you're going to add someone on Game Center, you better be prepared for them to see your real name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the rest of Game Center will not show the name, and if you already have people friended on Game Center, they're not going to be able to see your name.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will see your user handle, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And by the way, the Terms of Service also say that users must not pretend to be anyone or any entity they are not.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this is not hitting that same kind of pushback that Real ID did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing, though, and I think a point that the game blogs are missing is that there were two big problems with Real ID that I don't see as a problem in Game Center.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, Blizzard was threatening to put real names on their forums.
[SPEAKER_09]: and fine don't post in the forums except for the fact that Blizzard will direct you to their forums to report bugs and things so it was a little bit of a catch-22 whereas we want you to use our forums but we're going to out your real name as a part of that and not to get into the rant I got into several weeks ago on this show when that was the news but let's just put this quickly if you think it's not a big deal to have your first and last name out there fine but keep in mind
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like it being out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I sort of think I know what they were trying to do with that, but as somebody, again, who has stalked before because somebody used a friend of mine to get to me, I can see where this is a potential for problem, and it made me very mad about Real ID.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now Blizzard got rid of it, they finally pulled their head out of their butt and they decided not to do this on the forum and they turned off the friend of friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: They still have the real names in the game and if you add somebody to your friends list they see your real name and so forth but at this point I'm kind of like okay well I don't add people to my friends list I don't really know so it's really not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: um and that's kind of where Game Center's at and so I don't think it's the same thing that Blizzard's doing because now Game Center is doing what Real ID is now and nothing more and I think a big part of the reason why they're doing it is that there were the spammers out there people were posting on their Twitter you know add me on Game Center friends and then they got all these spammers I don't really know how you spam people on Game Center but whatever it was out there it was a problem so I think this is how Apple's trying to fix the problem
[SPEAKER_09]: Something else to throw out there is that when I used Ping, wow to that tank, but I was on Ping for like a day.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I signed up for Ping, I was able to use an alias.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you search for Rob Roberts on Ping, you'll find me, my radio name.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if that's the name that's being used on Game Center, then I really don't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: but I don't know like I'm too I don't really know anybody else to send a friend request to because at the end of the day Game Center there is zero point to it what does Game Center bring to the iPhone gaming experience not a damn thing achievements and scoreboards
[SPEAKER_09]: whoopty shit especially for a lot of games that you could write off very easily these are not serious games whereas World of Warcraft that's a huge time thing for a lot of people and a very passionate experience whereas I don't think people get that connected to their iPhone games
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's like LOL, Pocket Frogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my Peggle, you hush!
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I don't really play a lot of Game Center games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mainly, it's just Open Feint stuff, because there's a lot more games that I play that have Open Feint in them.
[SPEAKER_07]: More of them are getting Game Center, but I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I have one game on Game Center, and all the rest of mine are Open Feint.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Game Center is... I don't think it's the same thing as Real ID.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because at the end of the day, WoW has a lot of passion behind it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Game Center has a lot of... I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one care behind it.
[SPEAKER_09]: if I had to delete Game Center at the end of the day I wouldn't cry but if I had to delete World of Warcraft I'd be very upset that Blizzard made such a dumb decision because you know I am you know call me an addict or whatever you want I am very invested in that game because it is a way for me to kind of play games online with my friends so there you go
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Every week you guys send us emails and we read them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the mailbag's been kind of light the last few weeks, but as I understand, the listeners have really pulled through this week, haven't they?
[SPEAKER_02]: They did, and I've actually cut out the really long ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to post them online or anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: I might post them on the forum.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said there's one I would post on the forum.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have to do that when I remember to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so, first email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, by the lady that sent us boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gamer girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, what, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Boobs?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boobs?
[SPEAKER_02]: She sent a picture of her chest and she's wearing an Eggo t-shirt and quite lovely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lego my Eggo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Says, I just wanted to write the show and say you guys do an awesome job.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you keep me, no, you keep me laughing and I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to know if anyone is excited about the new Cataclysm experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or do you think it's just hype?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: I missed part of that, what was that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me wrong, I've been a fan of World of Warcraft Warcraft is a hole for a good while now After all, it's my crack, aka way out of the real world for a while Anyway, just wanted to say, again, good job with the show, Sincerely, Gamer Girl
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: It was now five years, six years old.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's as long as a lot of game consoles last.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I realize now in this generation we're in, it's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_09]: But even now, we're what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Five years since the Xbox 360 launched?
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, we could use a cataclysm in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, granted, they had Dynamis, the uber elite, hard...
[SPEAKER_09]: Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the point I'm really trying to make, is that the Xbox 360 has been out for, what, five, six years now?
[SPEAKER_09]: And what are they doing now?
[SPEAKER_09]: They didn't release a new console because of economy and so forth, but what are they doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're releasing Kinect.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're trying to reinvent the old experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you suggesting that the Red Rings of Death were the cataclysm of the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now you have the Cataclysm coming to World of Warcraft as a way to kind of reinvent the game and make old stuff new again.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so for that reason, yeah, I think it is kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think if you are passionate... I mean, you already know right now if you're buying Cataclysm or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Goblin Rockets are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are.
[SPEAKER_09]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to make a long story short, and it's not really working very well.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I will say this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cataclysm World of Warcraft was a great way for them to get World of Warcraft 2 without making it a whole new game and splitting the player base like what happened with EverQuest and Final Fantasy in some regards World of Warcraft Cataclysm is WoW 2
[SPEAKER_09]: it might not be as jarring of a change but they went back and redid a lot of old shit and made it prettier and just short of the character models which I'm sure will be in the next expansion it's neat that Blizzard does innovate a little bit with each expansion it's pretty cool so I think it's a big deal
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you hear that EverQuest 2 may be doing the same thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you mean the same thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a cataclysm type thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the point behind it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just trying to get people to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, this is Rap's butt, and he's talking about games!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, my point is, they made a mistake splitting the player base.
[SPEAKER_09]: But everybody got to learn from that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, this makes my heart feel warm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, Jamie, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Having a couple of back episodes to listen to at work helped me get through what has been the worst week I've had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listening to friends I've never met talk about and have fun doing something that they and I enjoy was a much needed bright spot and distraction from everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for all that you guys do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brad.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's our Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much, Brad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a really nice message on our Facebook this week, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a week of warm fuzzies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Must be the holidays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, it's MoltenBrown.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to ask you for advice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already have a Nintendo DS and I've been debating whether or not to get a PSP for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of me wants it for the way the system looks as well as better graphics the system offers compared to the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know if it's worth the price to pay if there aren't that many games that I will like on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really like RPGs, fighting games, and games that offer a different visual or playing style than the norm, like Hotel Dusk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patapon?
[SPEAKER_09]: Patapon's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: LocoRoco?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, those are all cute games.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like RPGs and fighting games, you need that Square Enix game.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fighting one that's Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Dissida.
[SPEAKER_09]: That should be number one on your list.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you like a standard fighting game, the Tekken games on PSP are pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a Soul Calibur game out there, I believe, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also, as far as RPGs, Puppet Lacrosse was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy Remakes Final Fantasy Remakes Final Fantasy Remakes Final Fantasy Remakes
[SPEAKER_02]: but as for hand comfort given that I have hand problems after my surgery the PSP really is fairly comfortable just because of the curved ends on it but still reaching around for those buttons and I have these little short thumbs it's really about the same in my opinion don't you think Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: it's about the same feel?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, I missed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Comfort of the console itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think that the PSP or the DS is more comfortable?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or are they about the same?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the feel of the PSP because it feels like I'm holding a controller that has a video on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, you know, I have kind of, you know, I'm six foot two, so I have kind of big hands.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: The PSP is not really a problem for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: The DS, it doesn't feel the same to me because you're using one hand to kind of write.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I actually, to be honest, I like the way the PSP feels a little better, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I don't like DS games that overuse the stylus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once in a while is okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if I'm playing a DS game that now is stylus-free and uses the controller, then it's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm cool with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the square feeling is a little weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I actually like the PSP better overall, I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just a few more because we really did get a lot of email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another word from Belgium here.
[SPEAKER_02]: My girlfriend brought Kinect for my birthday last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: What an amazing piece of technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the first time ever in six years, my girlfriend enjoys gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, she played other games, but found them too complicated because of all the buttons you need to use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now she even asks to game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Truly, this must be heaven.
[SPEAKER_02]: She tested Wii and Move 2, but was not very interested in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: She thinks both are too limited to control different genres of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, even my father played Bowling and Connect and he didn't suck at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, as I stated, Connect is amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything Microsoft promised works perfectly.
[SPEAKER_02]: The major drawback is the space it needs, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: My room is too small to decently play Connect, so I have to move my 360 and connect to the living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not my biggest problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I was thinking of is this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I fear Microsoft might reveal a Connect 2 or Connect HD next to E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will not need as much space as Connect needs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft will announce this early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we need to shell out another 150 euros next Christmas?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or will they do no such thing and hold on to the spacious Kinect?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think the space needed can be fixed with a firmware update.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to thank you for OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys really make my day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yours truly, Fabrice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, you know, I think the third party company is going to come out with a solution to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think it's actually a lot simpler than it sounds.
[SPEAKER_07]: But literally snapping on a lens to the front of that would probably fix that right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I your other question about will they announce something new at E3?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not this soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see them at all doing a Kinect 2.0.
[SPEAKER_09]: if Kinect proves popular which so far it is I would expect that when we get to the Xbox 720 or whatever we call it Kinect will be built in to whatever it is they have planned next but that whole whatever's next is still a good two years out at least at least it might come a little it's going to come a lot sooner from Nintendo than it is the other two
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony has said time and time again, 10-year cycle, 10-year cycle, 10-year cycle.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only one that needs to catch up right now is Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in some ways, they don't because they're still selling like crazy because they're kind of the budget system at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I see them going more of the route like they do with the DS and the Game Boys and all that stuff where it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something that it's an upgrade but it still plays all the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I absolutely 100% think whatever we see next from Nintendo is going to be Wii Evolved.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not throwing out the whole Wii concept altogether.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Wii's been a huge seller.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be Wii HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be Weevolved.
[SPEAKER_09]: Weevolved.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, that'll be the name of the console right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trademark Dark Sakura Origins Radio 2010 blah blah blah restricted.com boobs
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh, next, uh, and I'm only gonna do two more, we really did get a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, greetings, Orange Knowledge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first thing, I believe you're all mega excited to see Tron Legacy in about two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've been seeing this ad on Facebook, and well, let me pull up the ad, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a big Flash U-Tron legacy thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, that looks like it's going to load the old arcade game or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flash.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light Cycles!
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet that's like a Light Cycle arcade game on Facebook or something, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Upload your face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get on the grid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, so you can take a picture of your face and put it in this trailer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's like those dancing elves that I see around work every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate the freaking dancing elves.
[SPEAKER_09]: The jib jab, that's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to post this in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically a face mapping app.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you click on it, you may have to take a picture of your face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Note I said face because it didn't recognize anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: And know that it didn't mean I took a picture of my balls.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if you draw a smiley face on your penis?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I used my Mabinogi screenshot of my character.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get to watch yourself get killed by Jeff Bridges.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just thought you'd think it was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, second, if I were to start World of Warcraft on the original expansion, would I just be locked out of the places or should I get Cataclysm and start there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cataclysm won't work without the regular game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm getting a lot of WoW questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: HordeHousePodcast at gmail.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't you have to have all the other expansions?
[SPEAKER_09]: You do.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, and a lot of people are missing this.
[SPEAKER_09]: When they released the Cataclysm, when they released the Kraken, or Deathwing in this case, they evolved Old World permanently.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you have World of Warcraft and nothing but, if you have vanilla WoW, you will still get the new WoW experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Old World is gone permanently.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it makes it a really good experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are other enhancements that make the Cataclysm worth purchasing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But is Mr. T still there?
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe he is.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's not outside the cities anymore, but he'll come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Such as, and just a short list, the ability to level to 85, new dungeons and raids that come with that, the fact that you can roll a worgen or a goblin, and worgen is going to be a huge race.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there's tons of furries that want to play worgens.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm half tempted if somebody gets me the game to put Star Trek Online aside to give it a try.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's one other thing I want to throw out there, and that is now is an excellent time to suck yourself back into the world of Warcraft because Blizzard's been having this huge sale, and I don't know if it's over yet or not, but Vanilla WoW, five bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Burning Crusade, five bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wrath, ten bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: 20 bucks, get you caught up to current.
[SPEAKER_07]: They even had one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already had the other two, the first two.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure if it was going on during the sale though or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was, you buy it at GameStop for $15, you get a $15 gift card.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get it for free basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me see if that sale is still going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, if that sale is still going on, I will buy you Wrath of the Lich King as a Hanukkah present.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give it a try again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I love Star Trek Online, I can alternate months.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would, except I don't want to have to go out and buy Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I, on the other hand, will not be joining the World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't have an interest, I'm not even going to try with you, you have a baby anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't join even the actual world right now, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just going to say, as long as you don't want to roll a Worgen or a Goblin, there's not a lot for you until you get up to level 80.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I hear is blah, blah, wow, blah, blah, vanilla, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Puppies, rainbows, kittens, unicorns.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do I have your attention now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Naked men.
[SPEAKER_09]: Choaniki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Choaniki.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm going to go finish.
[SPEAKER_09]: MajinamiCon and other big words I can think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, third, can you patch a UMD or download PSP import games to English?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know that you can do that for the DS, so I was wondering.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure with an emulator.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if there's people that do that, but maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wouldn't be on UMD anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: You would have to have this whole ROM thing and then you're getting into shady hacks.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm sure it's possible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't ever doubt what the hacker community can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you'd have to go to the darker parts of the internet to find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, one last thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, in Comic Insanity, do you guys talk about anime as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: Typically not unless they have a comic attached to them, and not necessarily manga.
[SPEAKER_02]: We really focus on Marvel, DC, IDW, Udon, basically US-based companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although we've gone into a little bit of the manga before.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's one of those inevitables.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know food is going to come up on OLR, and you know that manga's got to come up on Comic Insanity once in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: and He Who Shall Not Be Named on Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_09]: And just like, and extroverts masturbation habits will come up on Horde House.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, thank you, and DarkSakura, your grammar coaching is appreciated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you really appreciate it, you would have spelled grammar right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me get some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com I love this comment.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt says, So Jamie went from World of War crap to I might consider playing it over the course of an episode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might consider playing it if someone else buys it for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the awesome thing about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey look, last week we went from
[SPEAKER_09]: Guy tweeting us saying, isn't this game cool?
[SPEAKER_09]: To having the creator on our show hours ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR Dollar Bill in the chat says, shit, I'm still jonesing for DC Universe to try it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It needs work, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, this is, if someone buys it for me, I would play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that means I'd have to give up Star Trek Online for a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't want to be kicked out of my fleet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I still have to think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: SalaciousPop in our chatroom says, A UMD rip, which I've used, is like 500 to 900 megabytes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an awful lot to patch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, most torrented PSP games are just disk images, hence UMD rip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Text patches actually modify game files.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: I...
[SPEAKER_09]: I would have thought though, because you can do it so easily with, you know, like Super Nintendo ROMs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, what, the largest Super Nintendo images are what, 16, 32 megs?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I can see where it's probably a much bigger pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: But again, don't doubt the hacker community.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where there's a will, there's a way, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any more emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, they're still reading this email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: and thanks for reading my email and if you didn't, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, DarkSakura, fuck my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: And why would you let Rob lick Dan's balls just to mess with you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, Dan made balls last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were eating them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you forget about your husband's balls?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's just now they're ground beef.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your loyal listener, Haseo Sumiragawa.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I get a woot from the Minnesota listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Garrett Hedlund, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam Flynn, was born in Rosso, Minnesota, about 100 miles from where I live, and pissing distance from Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Canadia!
[SPEAKER_02]: Tron Legacy officially made a win.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's get a woot from the Minnesota listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure they're out there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have one last email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this one, you know, it's... Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just trying to keep away from the political in charge stuff, but this is a good email.
[SPEAKER_02]: With all the homophobia, don't ask, don't tell, Prop 8, among others, why does it matter if anyone is gay or not?
[SPEAKER_02]: The way people worry about being gay or being near someone gay, I can't help but make the comparison to the X-Men movie Fear People Had Towards Mutants.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where mutants came from, kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the arguments against gay marriage, gays in the military, gay teachers, to me, are unfounded and stupid, and the more they try to defend their position, by the way, there I spell T-H-E-I-R, not T-H-E-R-E, position, the more stupid and ignorant they get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for your spelling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope one day it just won't matter, there's an apostrophe in won't, and everyone is treated the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wrote this email after talking this very subject with my wife several times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just can't figure out why it matters in everyday life if one is gay or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: What people do in the privacy of their own homes is their own business and why should it dictate if you can do a job to defend our country or get married?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry for the email, not game related, but I just wanted your opinion on this again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's a game-related part, so I'll read that next.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree with everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: You missed it earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had my FKHH shirt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, what you're saying, I think, is the... I don't want to say the right viewpoint, but in a way, it's kind of like, in a perfect world, or hopefully in the world our children and our grandchildren live in, you're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It won't be a big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one care.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think right now, I think sometimes, because there's two extremes to this.
[SPEAKER_09]: There isn't necessarily just the homophobic side, but then there is the side that likes to drag people out of the closet, so to speak, which I'm not necessarily sure I agree with either.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: because there's people that don't want it to be that big of a factor that would prefer not to say that they're quote in the closet but that they just don't make it they don't for whatever reason want to make it a huge part of their life I think that one's life shouldn't necessarily be dictated by their sexuality yeah absolutely it's an aspect of the life but it's not your entire life I don't go around thinking about oh I'm gonna fuck Dan every day sorry
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: When did you choose to pee sitting down?
[SPEAKER_02]: When did you choose to pee standing up?
[SPEAKER_02]: When did you choose to be gay?
[SPEAKER_02]: When did you choose to be straight?
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Matt, when did you choose to be straight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: When did I choose?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think I did choose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Point.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Matt's also on the side of reasonableness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Matt is where the rest of America needs to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: And generally, our listenership, I think, is on that same page.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is promising more than anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, obviously, it's no secret on this show, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Rob!
[SPEAKER_09]: Like you couldn't tell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hold on, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, for the longest time, we were doing a live show and then a separate podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there were a lot of people that were listening to the podcast that weren't listening to the live show where the other talk was happening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas on the podcast, until we combined the shows, then it finally came out probably a year and a half after we've been podcasting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'd mentioned some guy I'd been dating or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there was quite a few emails that came in that next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't remember getting anything bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got one that was a little iffy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't necessarily negative, but it was more of an I'll pray for you thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was kind of one of those, you know, thanks, but no need.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that if there's a higher power...
[SPEAKER_09]: I try to live my life to the best of moral being that I can and what higher power that is nothing but love is going to send me straight to hell to burn for an eternity for trying to be the best person I can be.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a ridiculous and fear-mongering way of thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's the whole way I look at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's, I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lifestyle is like going out to the clubs and dying your hair blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, if you want to be seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, lifestyle is how you live your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: What you've chosen to do with your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just an aspect.
[SPEAKER_02]: It may contribute to your lifestyle, but it's not something that you choose to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to make sense of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't mean to laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm laughing at chat because you know Alan said something funny, so I'll read it in a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really shouldn't have to do with anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It shouldn't be anybody else's freaking business.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, let's see, Salacious Pop in our chatroom says, quote, I will inform Jesus ASAP of your wrongdoing so that he may send his healy vagina beams at you so that you can go to heaven because I'm concerned about you so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, and I don't mean to mock religion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there's a lot of good stuff that can come out of religion, but unfortunately there's also a lot of bad stuff that can come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: I never want to disrespect somebody's religion until that religion disrespects me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lord Save Us From Your Followers
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole movie is basically him actually going out and striking up conversations with people to find out why they don't like Christians.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why they have a problem with evangelicals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually just going in and asking.
[SPEAKER_02]: He went to San Francisco, to Castro to talk to people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quite a few fabulous drag queens on there too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole point is that you need to stop being right and start respecting other people.
[SPEAKER_02]: That closed-minded, oh, this is the only way it can be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's because the Bible said this, or maybe my pastor said this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the only way it is, and all the rest of you are wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to automatically close the door on anything you have to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: and the thing that gets me and just the idiot perspective and the people that have the biggest problem I think sometimes with homosexuality and even so much what they're saying the problem is with Don't Ask or why they need Don't Ask Don't Tell is that straight men or certain straight men are threatened because they don't want guys checking them out they don't want other guys checking them out and there's a part of me that goes A
[SPEAKER_09]: Get over yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's probably a lot of people that don't care less.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because someone's gay, I don't find every guy in the world hot just because I happen to be gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, there's quite a few ugly ones out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when people kind of have that perspective of like, well, I hope he's not gay because he's going to try to put it in my butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the word?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they so insecure?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, insecure.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the perfect word.
[SPEAKER_02]: There can be a level of attraction.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may not fully, I guess, swing that way to use the quote, but it has been proven, there's studies out there, that everyone carries a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if not for, and I've said, I don't know that I've made this completely, I've talked to you about it before, but I mean, if not for Dan, I could easily have had a girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had flings, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have, I'm completely attracted to everybody, I guess, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like I'm going to go up to someone and go, boobies!
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I think you did that once when you were drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say one thing, and I've told you this off the air before, but it did kind of gross me out when I saw you kiss a girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I was like, that's so wrong!
[SPEAKER_09]: Wrong!
[SPEAKER_09]: You were drunk.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have kissed women.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was dumb fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was stupid 12-year-old junior high stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying it grossed me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying that's so weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was funny, but yeah, back to the point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's interesting, but there was one other thing I wanted to say about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're that guy that's really afraid of another guy hitting on you or whatever, here's a simple line to use.
[SPEAKER_09]: If somebody ever reveals to you their secret man crush on you, brings you on the local talk show to out their crush or whatever on you, thanks, but no thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll tell you what, straight people have been using that line for a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gay people use that line with each other too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks, but no thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm taken.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was that easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I wasn't expecting it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you came out of there and you were like, oh, hey, I'm looking hot today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you were there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was tickled all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, she thought I was cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't it nice to get a compliment?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I was like, that's so cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there wouldn't be a single person in this universe I would cheat on while I'm with Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would never.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about Margaret Cho circa 10 years ago?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I am completely and utterly dedicated to my husband.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are completely and utterly dedicated to Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Matt here is completely and utterly dedicated to his phone right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's correct.
[SPEAKER_02]: You clearly love your wife very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of us in this room, we have found our person.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are very happy people.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have that level of security that even if we weren't with our significant others, that we'd just say, you know what, thanks, but no.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to say this in the chat because this is so good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Brad from PodCulture Interim says, if someone is checking you out, be flattered.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, if they stalk you, different story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it doesn't matter what the genders are in that case too because stalking is when it crosses the line.
[SPEAKER_09]: When thanks, no thanks doesn't get the message across like it should to most reasonable people, that's a whole nother problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that is free of whatever sexuality happens to be the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, stalking is never cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if someone tells you thanks but no thanks, try for a friendship or go fishing again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've had times where the first time I've been like, no, I'm not really interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: They came back a week later and said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I still would really like to try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will you give me a chance?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I'll give you a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: The third time, no, that's creepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you're cute!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll grow out of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be here to pick you up when you're off work.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, I am... This is right when Dan and I were first, you know, considering each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was like, dude, I'm not interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, thank you, but no, I'm not interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll have you know that our security guard is an ex-Army Ranger.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'll be calling him to be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the guy didn't show up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm saying, you know, you've got to be confident in yourself and take it as a compliment.
[SPEAKER_02]: If someone is checking you out, go, yeah, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: In your head.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, if you're not sure, go, no, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're not loony and crazy and, you know, bizarre and shocking, then they'll go, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sad face puppy eyes at you and then go pout.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if, again, just to try and bring closure to this, if you're one of those guys or girls or whatever that's like, I want someone of the same gender checking me out, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Your attitude is probably not attractive and no one is probably checking you out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just food for thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about the game part of the email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Game related stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Earth Defense Force is one of my favorite games and can't wait for Earth Defense Force 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope it is online co-op.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great ship.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is online co-op.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three player.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, and the honesty you have toward life and gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's a compliment.
[SPEAKER_02]: The honesty we have towards life and gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: This has been a week of warm fuzzies for as far as compliments go and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I realize it's not been a warm fuzzy week for everybody out there in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: What with just, God, the economy in general.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it seems like we always have these stories about closures and other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes me feel tingly.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it does feel nice to get paid a compliment.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've been paid several this week and totally unsolicited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like my next compliment in the form of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any other emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Too many.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sorry to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, you just picked the wrong week, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll get to you at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, this is the part of the show where we do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, it sounds weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just talked about, like, oh, what a warm, fuzzy week, and now I'm like, alright, time to rant.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: You alright over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, FU to, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki,
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, FU the stupid overclocked program because it only knows how to underclock and that's not what I want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, my FU of the week goes to traffic and people that don't know how to drive in the rain.
[SPEAKER_09]: My god, some of you California people are so spoiled.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, the rain here is nothing and just, it rains and people don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, so FU to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, uh, FU to the fact that I just, I have a very, very busy week and weeks ahead and not that that's necessarily bad, but,
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to the fact I can't just sit on my ass and be lazy all day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some days that's what I want to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's move on to a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not just yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, fuck this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't say that to the chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not the chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's having to be the print preview at 8.45 in the morning, which I guess is better than 6 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you have to get up early tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_09]: Fucking A. Lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, how about some more stories?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm looking forward to going.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Michael Jackson game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I'm not necessarily one to get it on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe the Wii, maybe the Kinect and stuff when that comes out because it's supposed to be just like Just Dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for the DS, of course, they've done some very specific things if you try to, say, pirate the ROM.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of neat, and I know Jamie will get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the things that they do, first off, is they have Vuvuzela playing on top of all the songs during the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, they render the game's touchscreen non-functional.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you don't get to play the game and you don't get to listen to the music untainted by the Vuvuzela.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to do that just for the Vuvuzela.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to admit, as much as I hate it when she breaks it out on the show, I think that is a really funny anti-piracy measure.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think more companies, you know, if they want to fight piracy, they should be doing it this way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I will have you know this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually played a real Vuvuzela this week one of my friends was having a birthday party and one of the other friends that came to the party brought a Vuvuzela with her and so I played it and it took me a minute to figure out how to play it like the first couple times I was doing it it just kind of sounded like a really loud wet fart but once I was able to get it it was kind of fun
[SPEAKER_09]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you taking pictures of me for?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's this for?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to take my soul?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's stealing your soul!
[SPEAKER_07]: Your soul is hers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dead air.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what she's doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I downloaded an iPhone app that's like... Is this a fat booth program?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it isn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: It does gal-style hair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God!
[SPEAKER_09]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to put that on the website?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think then I should get to do the unicorn pic of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll do the unicorn picture here in a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw in our chat says, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: That isn't one of Vuvuzela's sounds like a wet fart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know I was playing it wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I told you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll find a better hairstyle.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I got to take the picture of the unicorn.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Loki's going to have to take the calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, this is a game and I don't even know what to think of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a game called Cock Out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's a...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm surprised you're not still giggling.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's just basically all these guys that look like they're whacking it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess they're supposed to be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the part that gets me is that, okay, I just reported on this and it's all over the game blogs and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the actual game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why are all these guys looking like they're jerking it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that, that's it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there any type of strategy or anything to it or any, why am I asking these questions?
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why am I even bothering, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you taking another picture of me?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, hurry up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, can you give the phone information while she takes this damn picture?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, to Skype us, 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_07]: and do that via Skype or via the 1-800 number.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then on Skype, what was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our Skype line is now open.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you need one of those pictures of Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any last minute stories for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not next.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: You missed having a mistake with somebody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get the DarkSakura's unicorn picture real quick here.
[SPEAKER_09]: So in the meantime, do you have any last-minute stories while we wait for some calls?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I was just going to mention how awesome Swords & Poker 2 is on the iOS platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely need to check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you haven't already, it's a pretty awesome role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm not getting paid by them, which is disappointing because I can really use extra money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, who can't use extra money?
[SPEAKER_07]: And hopefully that's bought me enough time to get into the forum to where the extra stories are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I have not been looking for extra stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have been playing with my phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course...
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently there is a NASCAR Superstar driving game that will let you race dumpsters.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Jimmy Johnson's Anything with an Engine is a brand new game and apparently lives up to its name and you can race a dumpster with a rocket apparently on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I'm not sure if anyone saw this this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure a lot of people have.
[SPEAKER_07]: The custom Tron bikes that they had out there, the light cycles, pretty awesome, except for the fact that they don't glow.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're completely unrideable.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not unrideable.
[SPEAKER_02]: They look way uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you have to push them to get them going and you don't fall over.
[SPEAKER_07]: How they have that four-wheel vehicle that they have now, they should have made that instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: How the crap do you change the tire?
[SPEAKER_07]: you can't, it's a custom tire see?
[SPEAKER_02]: waste of money
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to mention DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've got some new download content coming out for that, which is pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially since it's got more Prodigy in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one of the songs I was hoping to make it into the game to begin with that didn't, but now it has.
[SPEAKER_07]: Invaders Must Die mixed with Debaser from the Pixies.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beastie Boys Body Movin' mixed with Lenny Kravitz, Rock and Roll is Dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, this stuff is already out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It came out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next week, actually two weeks from now, the old school pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to have Fat Boys with Human Beatbox mixed with Mantronics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mantronics.
[SPEAKER_07]: King of Beats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, Kurt Mantronics is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tag Team, whoomp, there it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once again in another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mixed with 45 King, the 900 number.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Beastie Boys, Triple Trouble mixed with Tone Lock, Funky Cold Medina.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then December 21st, Linkin Park Mix Pack with the Catalyst Does It Offend You?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, remix and then When They Come For Me remix and Points of Authority remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Points of Authority is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I have a call sitting on hold, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Caller, you're on the air.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Ranma, and this time I wasn't even trying to get on before everybody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, you know, I was so distracted because I was taking the picture of Jamie and making a unicorn out of her because I'm looking at these, what the hell are these pictures on the website?
[SPEAKER_09]: You have problems.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know you love them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I look like a Parapara girl in these pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to make this my Facebook picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should totally do it, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: So anyway, check OrangeLaunchRadio.com in just a few seconds because I should have Jamie's unicorn picture up there in a minute where it looks like the cat is jerking off her horn.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn it, Scott.
[SPEAKER_06]: You surely don't have a way of derailing, don't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, I just want to point out, I want to remind you, our guest tonight made a game called Techno Kitten Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I downloaded.
[SPEAKER_09]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played it yet because I found a Moe Japanese game on the live marketplace, downloaded that, and had my roommate playing it for the last 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I'm looking at JB's picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight's been a great night for pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, excuse me, so what did you call in to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really want to talk about a couple of things, but it turns into a lot of things, but I'll make it short and sweet as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number one, this whole German AIDS thing, for obvious reasons, I'm kind of sort of offended by it, but I'll let that be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, why are you offended by this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just whacking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's just say I have people in my family who have died of said disease.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you find this to be disrespectful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is interesting because, well, is it just disrespectful because it seems to be so trashy and in your face type of thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: That pretty much is the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think about this whole, I've got to pick your brain on this, and I'm sorry because I know this is a sensitive issue to you, but I want to ask this question because this is something that's been on my mind this week, and it really has nothing to do with gaming, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been an interesting Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you seen that whole campaign of the celebrities who have quit Twitter to try and raise a million dollars for AIDS awareness where they're all lying in the coffins dead and so forth?
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think of that whole thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was quite ridiculous, and I don't know if you saw, but on my personal Facebook page, I made a statement about that, and a few people agreed with me about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll link it to you later.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have made a personal statement about how I truly felt.
[SPEAKER_06]: And can you summarize it or am I getting a little too... Long story short, I understand this epidemic.
[SPEAKER_06]: But instead of dealing with the whole world event, let's take care of America first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's take care of the AIDS issue and the US first before we go running around taking care of everybody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why give all that money to those world charities when you can send that same amount of money to American charities for the same cause?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I would hope that we can find a cure, and that'll be good for everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my hope.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I didn't mean to derail, but what else is on your mind tonight besides potentially offensive games?
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole thing about people not being able to get over themselves because guys make these compliments and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was amusing and so did they.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no problem with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, like I'm sure, you know, a lot of straight people have that friend of the opposite gender, like a guy, a straight guy has that girl that he flirts with, but it's nothing more than that, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure there's, you probably have girl, not just gay guys, but girlfriends, not, I don't know, friend girls that you do that with too, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else on your mind, Ranma, before I let you go and get more calls?
[SPEAKER_06]: I played that ROM hack of Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That thing is three levels below Asshole Mario.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three levels below, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a pretty precise rating.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Ranma, I gotta let you go to get more calls, but thanks so much for your insight tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I was just telling the significant other, we really need to go to New York City.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when we go, we're crashing with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or as Hextafer would say, Ranny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you better be careful because I really want to get back to New York City.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a very long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my one friend that lived there moved to Texas.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm coming to the couches of OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio all one word if you want to give us a call we probably got time for about one more call we are running a little long tonight so probably because of the interview earlier meanwhile while we wait for the phone to ring Loki do you have any other last minute stories I don't know if you spent them all or what I've only done one of them so no I haven't spent them all alright then what else let's see what else can we talk about here how about how about I just look up here
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is this even open?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's odd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: While I wait for your riveting last minute stories, let me go to at least one more call here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it's Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, welcome to Orange Launch Radio, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much, just trying to kill a Sunday night before heading to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, a lot of games came out in the past couple weeks that I've been dying to talk about.
[SPEAKER_00]: Obviously Gran Turismo 5, even though I don't have a PS3 yet, that's on my top list right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so we're basically just trying to catch up on some other 360 games that I haven't been able to play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's just say I managed to get a 360 again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, talk to us.
[SPEAKER_00]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Playing catch-up again.
[SPEAKER_09]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, when I didn't have my 360, it was nothing but Left 4 Dead and Battlefield on my computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: But now I'm just playing small stuff like Sonic 4, Ace Combat 6, Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although hopefully my girlfriend will hook me up with more recent games for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've already gave her a wish list of what to get me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that what you asked Santa for?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, Santa and the four of my girlfriends is willing to spend money on me just as I'm willing to spend money on her.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, tell us about what's your favorite game been that you've discovered in the past couple weeks since you got your 360 back?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, Sonic 4 has been really challenging so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's been a lot of hate on Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's been a lot, a lot of hate on Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you disagree?
[SPEAKER_09]: You think the game's awesome?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it kind of feels like a classic Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know it still has elements from the recent ones, like the whole homing attack thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I could do without it, but it just, you're right, some may say it's not fluid enough because it doesn't, it's not, it's not like the old-fashioned Sonic where the screen would just like literally breeze by every time he just like, every time he literally moves.
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah, you're gonna have some hate from those classic fans, and I'm one of them because I grew up on that.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't played that game yet since I don't own a Wii or a DS, but from what I've seen, it's probably the same gameplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's mostly platform now, from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, 2D platform.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sonic Colors is where it's at right now in the Sonic universe.
[SPEAKER_00]: I should have bought one when it was $100 a GameStop over Black Friday.
[SPEAKER_09]: You never know when they might do the next price cut.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if they'll get that low, but then again, the PS2 didn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, but I mean, it was for used systems.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just like I picked up a used 360 for $100.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anything else on your mind tonight, Legend of Zaku?
[SPEAKER_00]: DDRX2 is going to... Well, they're taking orders for it's supposed to ship out in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, every... It's just... So far, it's shaping up to be pretty solid at this point.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, fears about, like, drifting arrows and what the community was saying about, like, being off sync.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're starting to get quelled every...
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's just say that Konami has already taken folks from Bomani Style and already proven to them that the final build of the game will be rock solid and something that the hardcores will definitely start playing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Assuming the arcades shell out $10,000 for a new machine, which is the only way you're going to get the new game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or unless you already have X and you get the upgrades.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, uh, by the way, you need to check out Home, because they have DDR machines in Home, but you don't really get to play DDR on them.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I giggled when I saw the X2 machines in the Konami Home space.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and I'm hopefully, you know, assuming I get my Christmas bonus this year, I will definitely shell out money on a PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, buddy, we're gonna let you go so we can wrap up the show, but thanks for your call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry to those that didn't get through, but we kind of are running long a little bit tonight, and we still want to get to the afterbirth and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So email us your thoughts, mailbag at orangelandradio.com, or send us tweets, twitter.com slash O-L-R.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, we've got to wrap it up, put the nail in the coffin of the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have any other last-minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: From the same guy that did the Left 4 Dead demake, kind of making the pseudo NES version of Left 4 Dead, but it's a PC game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pixel Force also did that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they have an 8-bit DJ Hero game you can check out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got a bunch of cool chiptune mashups, including the... This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Ghostbusters theme and Huey Lewis and the news I Want a New Drug mixed together.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can hear that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently they said that it got some of the background or whatever was sampled from the same song or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: But lots of cool stuff and you can check it out for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see where you can download that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, ericruthgames.com
[SPEAKER_07]: XBOX Live Rewards Program
[SPEAKER_07]: But you get some kickback Microsoft points for different things that you do.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, renewing a one-month gold membership will give you 10 Microsoft points back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three months, 30.
[SPEAKER_07]: And 12 months, 200.
[SPEAKER_07]: Purchase or renew an Xbox Live Gold Family Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: That gives you 400.
[SPEAKER_07]: Purchase or renew the first Xbox Live Online Gold Membership, 100.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make your first purchase on Xbox Live another 100.
[SPEAKER_07]: Selected content is going to vary.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you activate and use Netflix on Xbox Live, you get 100.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have surveys for 20 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do surveys and get 20 Microsoft points?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd take a lot of surveys before you can actually buy something.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you could get Techno Kitten Adventure for four surveys.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is true.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're about on out of here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, if you liked what you heard tonight, or even if you didn't, you really should still help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell a couple of friends about our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to our chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to our iTunes and leave a nice five star review or just spread the word.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell a friend or two about our program because we don't have all the advertising dollars and so forth behind our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: So just tell a friend or two.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: You look lovely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love is so lovely.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is thanks but no thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_09]: my final thought is I'm tired alright that's gonna do it have a great week everybody we really appreciate you especially those folks that tuned in live and stayed up through the whole thing but even you podcasties thanks for staying with us through the whole thing we really appreciate it have a wonderful week guys we'll see you next week with more of Orange Lounge Radio you've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_08]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next week!