[SPEAKER_03]: and I March 15, 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: GamePro goes game publisher, Call of Duty passes a landmark for online play, and which company is
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we tape live every Sunday night on allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: All Games Radio, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show, about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time on the West Coast, 9 o'clock Eastern for the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts, joining you here every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining us also every week, say hello to Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you, Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Doing good.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also joining us tonight, running fresh in from inside the house, live radio, say hello to the one and only Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had beer last night and I feel good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did ya?
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much beer was had.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you always drink responsibly, correct?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, that's why I have someone else be responsible for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and of course, not only do we tape live on All Games Radio, but you can also watch our video feed on JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just before the show went live tonight, we were taking a peek at Mad World on the Nintendo Wii, which I guess has quickly become one of Loki's favorite games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what is it about Mad World that you're loving?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the Stephen King novel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Except they were running.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the long walk, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: MadWorld
[SPEAKER_06]: is really what the graphics look like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's more black and white than occasionally red.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very red.
[SPEAKER_05]: As it is, you know, the game would be awesome just with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, oh no, Sega does not just stop there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They decide that we need sports commentators as well, and who did they get?
[SPEAKER_05]: Greg Proops and John DiMaggio.
[SPEAKER_05]: John DiMaggio, you might remember as the voice of Bender, and Greg Proops from whose line?
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have gotten Madden.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakra, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've actually been having a different sort of gaming experience in my house, which is called cleaning out the vault.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found so much E3 swag and no one wants any of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guys, trust me, it's shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we've been piling up our systems and realized that we have four Saturns, two ColecoVisions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, I want a Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk to my husband.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have two Saturns.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why I would.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would I play on the Saturn, seriously?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're debating taking one of our systems and doing a giveaway with it and having us autograph it or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who wants a ColecoVision?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck getting that shit to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it works just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you even hook those up to newer TVs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have the RCA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or not RCA, the RF.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they have an RF.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we also have two driving wheels.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'd have a spare driving wheel.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of ours is Canadian.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have my Super Nintendo, which was the very first system I bought with my own money.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the person who owned it before me smoked because it's all yellow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, we've got piles of stuff just hanging around.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, maybe a giveaway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe, but we did also... We have a stack of old strategy guides.
[SPEAKER_02]: A number of them from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, some of that stuff goes for money on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have How to Win at Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: You win at Castlevania!
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye, Dracula!
[SPEAKER_01]: Woo, I get a car!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to also introduce the chat room right now at this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeEntreter.com, always when we're taping live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: The listener experience and getting to interact with the show is really what makes this show unique.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kind of reading some comments here from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Claw says, Greg Proops is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Wolf points out, John DiMaggio is also the voice of Marcus Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he should have done it, I'm sorry, Quiltipo says, John DiMaggio should have done it in his Waka voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: PagelDS
[SPEAKER_05]: Why have I... You know, it's sad that I found Peggle now, because it is quite addicting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, wait, I don't know why you're knocking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't this a good thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not knocking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, oh, Peg, there's something else to be addicted to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's actually kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you checked out the one on Xbox yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, because I was going to ask you, how is it different on the DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you played any other version of Peggle?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't answer my question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to ask, how is it different on the DS, but I guess you can't answer that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not really that different, I don't think, from anything else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, you control it with the stylus to aim, and then when you hold the stylus in one spot, it'll zoom in, and then you can fine aim with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you just tap a button, and it'll...
[SPEAKER_05]: Shoot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt asks the wife test question, asking, would Nelly play Peggle?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't shown it to her yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got cookies!
[SPEAKER_06]: For those that are randomly yelling out, my roommate just popped in the studio here and has a really big smirk on his face.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to figure out... Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, John wants to speak on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we give you a nickname on this show?
[SPEAKER_06]: John?
[SPEAKER_06]: My roommate?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, your secret nickname is Roommator John.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to get you a mic here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your superhero name would be the roomie.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to make this short.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't usually play tons and tons of video games, but iPhone game app called Arvale.
[SPEAKER_00]: Completely amazing, old school, Final Fantasy style game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Haven't been able to stop playing it for like three days, and it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually paid for the paid version, which is unspeakable and unheard of.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's my little plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: How did you find this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little more about how it plays.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this is unheard of that you actually want to participate in the show and about video games and not making fun of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I definitely want to know a little bit more about how you found this and how it plays and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you control it on an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a little action button for most things, and there's a little control pad, so it's left, right, up, down, diagonals.
[SPEAKER_00]: Found it going through strategy games that were free on the iPhone, and liked it so much I bought the paid version.
[SPEAKER_00]: It plays like an old school Final Fantasy, like maybe Final Fantasy V or so, I think, and...
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, am I filling in for Jamie?
[SPEAKER_00]: Am I supposed to like grow tits tonight or be extra sassy?
[SPEAKER_00]: She's just going to the loo, I think.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's going to the soda, which is kind of like the loo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe we should keep the soda in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what else was I going to ask though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this game available anywhere else that you know of?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because some folks in our chat room are saying, I don't have an iPhone, so are they just screwed?
[SPEAKER_00]: Then I would say that their life is incomplete and they need to go buy an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_00]: These are obvious things.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know why I'm having to tell your listeners this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apple thanks you for the free plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you, John, for your contributions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, you forgot to wave to Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're very mad.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had to look at your butt the whole time you were talking, and now they want some recognition.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, Loki, I'm so sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, that's okay, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than PagleDS, I also played Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely a different take on Grand Theft... Well, not that different.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's very similar to 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, having come off of 4 and Lost and Damned, it is kind of hard to go back to the 2D stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, or...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And then other than DS stuff, I've also played, of course, more Lost and Damned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still lots of multiplayer in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Playing around with the glitch of the game, there's a spot where pedestrians spawn in the middle of the air and fall from the sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I played a little bit of PS3 today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went ahead and finally got around to playing the little big Planet Contra levels.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, um, I also went and played Noby Noby Boy for a few sec- I would say, yeah, a few seconds until Nelly's, like, that, like, bass sound when you're stretching is really fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: So turn it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I stopped playing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, which-
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: She cracked the whip.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, of course, Mad World.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game is awesome in all sorts of ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, I haven't really made it past the first level because I haven't gotten a chance to actually sit down and play it for a long enough time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first level is really cool, though, so I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: SuperMetroid 0
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you just have to imagine, for those, you know, I know not everybody lives where we live and knows this place, but it's a giant castle with a big golf course and a big water park that they're known for.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's just like they let little kids just run the frickin' place because of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, they don't know how to treat machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: Parents don't know how to police their children in a place like that, so the machines... And they change their diapers on the machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you think she's lying, that's a completely true story.
[SPEAKER_06]: A diaper was once changed on a keyboard mania machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But regardless, the machines run down, broken, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we heard they got a Beatmania 2DX machine so we had to go check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: We went, and I hadn't been in like a year, 18 months or so, and color me shocked, but the place looked really nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, they remodeled or something, they did some repainting in there, I didn't find a machine that was broken, everything looked to be in a good state, I mean, granted, I saw Supernova 2, the monitor was a little junky, but honestly, considering all the parts worked, the Max 2 pads worked great, 2DX was in awesome condition, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: because the place was in a good state.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I played Beatmania 2DX Distorted, which I'd played before because I had it at E3 a few years ago, but I haven't really touched Beatmania 2DX in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a long, long time, probably since this show took a more general gaming approach as opposed to just music video games that we used to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I've missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I found myself playing all old songs, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, the machine was nice and loud because you could turn the effectors on and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So tell them about, was it Guitar Hero Arcade?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they had Guitar Hero Arcade, which I played.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only played it once, so I can't really give a full review on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can just tell you I got pissed off because Roseville Golf Line also switched to cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't use tokens anymore, but cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when I was swiping the card through and everything, I somehow hit the button an extra time to start the game, and I accidentally got on easy mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can't switch it once you're on easy mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: But to me, honestly, it just looked like the freaking home game, except a smaller song list, and it was just basically Guitar Hero 3 with a slightly smaller song list, and prettier because there's lights on the machine, and it spins around, and the TV they use is very, very crisp.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a very sharp image, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you want to pay a dollar a game for something you can get at home?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I understand there is an audience for this thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's kind of cool to go out and play with your friends and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I can see where this machine might do decent.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you have Guitar Hero at home, I don't see the point in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, what else did I do in my gaming week this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I played the demo of The Last Remnant on the PC, and I was a little disappointed at how choppy it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just bought this PC back in August, so I know it's not like old parts or anything, but I was a little disappointed at how choppy it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the game itself seemed kind of fun, so I might try to check it out on Xbox 360, although the PC one was supposed to have all the extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Peggle on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: I downloaded and played for a while, and good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was already addicted to the one online.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sparkles and rainbows and Plinko.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to play some more of the multiplayer, though, before I can give my full impressions on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had fun playing Pagel and I think a lot of people are going to check this out.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I like about Pagel versus PopCap's other efforts on Xbox Live such as Bejeweled 2 and Zuma is that this doesn't just feel like a port of their PC game, the full one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It feels like they've really tinkered some stuff to work with Xbox Live, hence the multiplayer, and they've really kind of made it special for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that's what's kind of cool about Pagel.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes it really stand out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3
[SPEAKER_06]: was on sale, so I figured, what the heck?
[SPEAKER_06]: I picked it up, I bought it, because I got a new dance mat for Xbox, whatever, and got to play Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you want to know what the most hilarious thing about Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3 is?
[SPEAKER_06]: On the back of the box, they advertise these songs that are in the game, one of them being Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was like, okay, I want to check that song out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, of all the songs that are mentioned on the back of the box, apparently only one of them is actually in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I looked on web forums, DDR Freak, which is still kicking after all these years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_06]: DDR Freak apparently confirms these songs are not in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're advertised on the back of the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's false advertising.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say we sue Konami.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll turn it around on him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, I understand mistakes happen and all, but this is a pretty fucking big mistake.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised they're not trying to send out stickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: How does something like that happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who fucked up that bad?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: They probably just figured no one has noticed.
[SPEAKER_06]: My God.
[SPEAKER_06]: But look, the game itself, putting the box aside and all that trite crap, the game itself is okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not my favorite home version of a DDR game.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I think I even preferred the song list in Universe 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's definitely no Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: The interface is pretty slick, very crisp, very vibrant graphics, funny background animations.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2DX Fan Service 2DX Fan Service 2DX Fan Service 2DX Fan Service 2DX Fan Service
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I thought it was strange.
[SPEAKER_06]: The download content, the interface, you can't preview the songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd never heard of any of them, so I don't know what I want to download.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they even have download content?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Universe 1 songs, though, did not come into Universe 3, but apparently there's a Universe pack available, so I'm not sure if it's trying to make me re-buy the songs I already bought with Universe 1, and if that's the case, that's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how the dialogue has gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like the whole yo dog type stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, the, oh, everybody, you know, it's just bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dialogue by Randy Jackson.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Leo Shen asks, was the quest mode like you got served, Sky?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like this big circular thing and you go to these different places and in the first circle you gain coins to challenge people in the second circle and if you beat them you get the song.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't incredibly difficult, but
[SPEAKER_06]: I unlocked the entire second circle in one night, but now it won't let me go to the third circle because I haven't played enough in the first circle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to play the easy stuff, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And eventually you'll get to the seventh ring of hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to necessarily give this game a negative review because I don't think it's necessarily bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I do encourage people to play DDR because I think it's a way to stay fit and exercise.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, again, I think everything's pretty sharp.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't necessarily like some of the creative direction they took in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think the new quest mode is anything that exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think the new interface is that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think having the giant CD cover box art thing in the wheels is a bit much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't go for
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you, if you make me the production director of this series, I could bring it around like nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not necessarily bad, it's just another DDR game.
[SPEAKER_06]: At this point, these things are a dime a dozen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really want to see the DDR teams at Konami really try to reinvent this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: For love of God, whoever made that big mistake about putting songs on there that weren't actually in the game, that was a
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that just kind of speaks as to how lazy they're getting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm like, it's not necessarily a big deal, okay, so somebody made a mistake, whatever, but it just speaks volume as to how lazy it feels like they're getting with DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: And which is sad because I know there's a lot of people that work very hard on this series.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I've had friends who worked for the series that worked very hard on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's some of these creative things coming up from the top level.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised they didn't make a big deal about that, I mean, everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because usually, I mean, hell, they made a big deal out of
[SPEAKER_05]: The IGN watermark being on the Okami cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was something really stupid and small and had no impact really on the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there was Super Stardust Portable that was missing modes and stuff that were advertised on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, this is kind of a big deal that there's songs missing from the game that are advertised on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that right there, say if you bought it for that song...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: because they just don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like shifting your focus to actually increase your market share with groups of people that don't normally play your games and ignoring your core players and thinking they're just going to stick around is not the way to be thinking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is my last thing I want to say because I know there are people at Konami that listen to this program, and I'm not just talking about people that are like my personal friends and what have you, but I know there's people higher up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, less than three is one of the songs in freaking DDR Universe 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: The same song that was a theme song to Rice Princess' show she had on the old station, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: If that doesn't prove somebody at Konami is looking out for us, I don't know what does, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing I want to say to y'all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: DDR has introduced me to a lot of great people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would not know Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would not know DarkSakura if it were not for DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, that being said, do not throw away a good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not be afraid to reinvent yourselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I challenge you, step away from making, resist the temptation of doing a Universe 4 or X2 or Disney 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want you to nuke your code and start from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Build a new DDR game from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_06]: No recycled code.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make a brand new DDR game and really try to push the limits of what you're doing with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you would really stand to win back a lot of people that are starting to think you're getting a little lazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did it before and what did it do for the community for a while?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it really rejuvenated everything when we got the Max series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when it was new?
[SPEAKER_06]: and honestly, DDR Ultramix, especially 2, not so much Ultramix 1, but Ultramix 2 when they really were getting in their groove, no pun intended, sold me on an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really did.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was all new code because they had to make it for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, also the other thing too, I think, is the way that they're treating their series.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, look at Pump It Up and the new versions of that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of excitement behind it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They bring it out and it's like, BAM!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got all these things in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And people get excited about it, but
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR, it's like, ah, new DDR, hooray, this time it's got more Disney characters, hurrah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that no one cares anymore, and they need to really change it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm serious, I have a way to fix this, but no one wants to listen, and I don't feel like explaining it because, well, it's just, it's all in my head, and unfortunately I can't put it on paper very, you know, but I can explain it the...
[SPEAKER_05]: basically the whole quest mode thing taking a totally different approach to that basically you have stuff that goes along because the problem with quest mode is they don't know how to make it where
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually matters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you can't obviously do it as like a dance-off competition thing because that doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you can't do that in DDR because it's a technical game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not based on, you know, doing moves and that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you make it something different, like say, for example, how well you're doing a song affects the performance of, say, something else that's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Totally separate things, you know, just basically instead of, you know, your actions on a gamepad or something like that,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Try it for the exercise alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Floatwalk says, Two words.
[SPEAKER_06]: National tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's definitely what Pump It Up does.
[SPEAKER_06]: The tournaments they do in Korea are huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Floatwalk says, For crying out loud, the tournament scene made DDR's popularity in the States.
[SPEAKER_06]: True facts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acidic Vampire says, What DDR needs is violence like Mad World.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR does not need violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least not that level of violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it doesn't need that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I do agree that you could take the quest mode and literally make it like an RPG type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will tell you a reason why RPG stuff will never work with Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: It all goes back to a little known game called Dance Dance Dance.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I've played it and yes, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to spend too much time reminiscing the old days, although that's kind of what I did this week by going to Golfland.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Since that does it for our gaming week, let's get to some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: So look, we've sat here and kind of been critical of DDR for the last few minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: At our heart, we do love Konami and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: On our website, www.orangeentrader.com, there actually have been polling –
[SPEAKER_06]: all of our listeners all week long about your top three favorite Konami games since their 40th birthday is coming up and we're giving them a present now with this week long feature of the best games as selected by you guys the listeners from Konami's archives 1500 Konami games over the years if you can believe it
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of voting, March Madness is almost over.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's down to the final four.
[SPEAKER_06]: And right now you have Rock Band versus Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you have Chrono Trigger versus Zelda Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I believe voting time is going to be up very, very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're listening live here on this Sunday evening, you're going to want to go try to get in your last minute votes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the final two will probably be decided tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: March 22nd, next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to be here, so I'm not sure if there's going to be a show or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to our website, www.orangeandrade.com for more details.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they might try to find a way to tape elsewhere, but I will not be here next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be on a trip, but I will be back in two weeks, so we'll keep you posted.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's really it for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just stay tuned to our website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I want to say something about the website real fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, they've been writing articles about indie game spotlights, games you ought to be playing but you probably aren't, and highlighting music from video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's been actually really cool to kind of go to the site and see this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what I love about it is that, in a way, it's because we're not doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, you know, kind of what the show is all about, letting the listeners have control and the community and what the community wants to hear about.
[SPEAKER_06]: So props to you guys who've all been working hard on the website.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I have an idea for a feature too that I'm hoping to contribute very soon and I'll be back on posting regular updates very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, now I think that's it for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're only like 30 minutes into the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, start us off with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, so anyways, there has been some concern by MTV's Totillo that
[SPEAKER_05]: There might not be enough exclusives during 2009 for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, unfortunately what Steven doesn't realize is that there are, but he just doesn't understand that there are a lot of things coming out that people think that aren't exclusive, are exclusive, and that they think that are exclusive that aren't exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's kind of confusing.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, he says the loss of Xbox exclusive franchises like Mass Effect...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Project Gotham Racing Project Gotham Racing
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, there's also Halo 3 ODST, or whatever they're calling it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I mean, that's just for right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, they haven't really been talking much about their 2009 lineup, which they're probably saving for E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just going to be like, bam, bam, bam, bam, here's all this shit that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think they are going to, at E3, just blow us away?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can kind of see where this guy has some concerns for Xbox 360 because they don't have a big Halo 3 this year or anything of that caliber.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, you had Halo Wars, but it's not the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no big, big must-have title.
[SPEAKER_06]: It feels like we got a lot of that last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're not going to let us down with just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock 2 is going to be a huge Christmas title, but it's not specific to any system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, I think it actually is going to be coming out in August, just like it did the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's tons of stuff coming out that we don't know about yet that are going to be big titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure that each side, both the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360, are both going to have exclusive titles that are going to be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't really think it matters about the exclusive titles because there's just more titles coming out on the Xbox 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Period.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Developers Conference
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so, I mean, there's going to be announcements probably there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not only that, but they're not only focusing on just console stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you've got XNA, which is really hitting its strides now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows what they're going to go with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think a Game Developers Conference, though, you're going to get huge game announcements.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think you'll get, like, infrastructure type things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, remember, Game Developers Conference was where, like, Home was announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that was announced at Game Developers Conference, but I could see that being the type of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things that affect the developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things that affect the backbones of these systems are the types of announcements I would expect to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Upgrades and things of that note.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this would be a great time for Nintendo to finally put out that SD card thing they've been talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got a 2GB card right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right here, just waiting to go in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: To store all my crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I'm hoping that thing will come out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, there will be...
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, wait, I gotta read.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be some comments from chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the one I gotta read right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acidic Vampire is betting at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft will reveal that Final Fantasy XIII Versus will be on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I doubt that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru says Microsoft at E3 will announce that the best non-Sony games that are appearing on PlayStation 3 will also be on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amaze Satsuma corrects me and says Microsoft did Gears 2 was announced at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it is not unheard of for games to be announced at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because they're talking about the enhancements to Unreal 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might hear something about Unreal 4 maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That may be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe some stuff from about Doom 4 because I think they're going to be talking about that and probably Rage a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was I going to say though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the whole rumor thing about Final Fantasy Versus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Square's kind of already done that with Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you notice, the last few games that they've put out have been only on Xbox 360 and have been exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Ocean, Last Hope, The Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before that... Oh gosh, I'm forgetting now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, a lot of their RPGs are going to be strictly...
[SPEAKER_05]: on the Xbox 360, but now they're going to start getting some PS3 ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Infinite Undiscovered?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Infinite Undiscovered, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff I did not buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be a lot of companies that are going to be developing for them because it's easier to develop on that platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless Sony figures out a way to educate these guys a lot faster and figure out how to develop for a lot easier, that's going to be the problems they're going to face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, being this far into the console cycle, it's probably not going to change.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll just have to wait for the next round and we'll see how it goes there.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But they still have yet to really just break through and be massive over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this will help because the Japanese love their shmups.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shoot them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shmup.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one is called Mamoru-kun Has Been Cursed.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be the English translation of this title.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to come with a soundtrack CD and a Super Play DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a limited edition that's coming on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out for 8,500 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you want the regular edition, it's 5,980 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now let me tell you a little bit about this game here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been developed by G-Rev, and apparently it has character designs in it by Mizuki Takayama.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did some other famous shoot-'em-up games.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually a translation of an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like you play a little dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not actually a ship, but it looks like you're actually a little person that's walking around, kind of doing the fighting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about an elementary school student who finds themselves in a nightmarish underworld.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it definitely looks...
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: The interesting thing, though, about these shoot-'em-ups, they don't translate well for widescreen systems because, you know, shoot-'em-ups are usually very vertical-oriented and you can't really turn your TV on its side, so you only end up using a very small portion of the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can if you have a really kick-ass mounting setup.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true, but people don't usually have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my husband's new monitor, the widescreen HDMI, has access to Pivoton.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually a lot more that you're finding these days are built to shift position.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think some of the games, even the Xbox Live Arcade games like Ikaruga, I think did support that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a few Saturn games that actually will let you do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one of the Thunder Blade games will do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, just to give you an idea of some of the other things that G-Rev has developed, because it's coming out here, they did do some work with Ikaruga and Gradius V, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did some programming and background graphic design for Ikaruga, and same thing for Gradius V. So, you know, they have touched those games, and they've also done some work with Doki Doki Idol Star Seeker, which is an old school Dreamcast game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game, a shmup coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: No word if it's coming out over here, although I gotta be honest, probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about we shift gears a little bit?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah ha ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Cause it's Gears of War 2 patches!
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that fun, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's going to be a premium map pack called Snowblind.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming out on March 31st, and it'll have three new maps and a remake of Fuel Depot from the first Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's supposed to bring in experience-based ranking and rebalance the gameplay a bit more, try to give everyone a better sense of progression.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you'll still be using the true skill system, but it's sort of background now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really just something to make people feel more rewarded for how well they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can earn your experience in matches that will get you through 100 levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get milestones for each level, I think, each certain level that you get.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you get an achievement for it, as well as, of course, the packs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's a possibility of getting another 250 gamer score points.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's an auto-balancing feature that will put a bot in place if you fall out during mid-match, although you also get an XP penalty, and it will correct scoring issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's no real price on the map pack yet, but as comparison, the combustible map pack is 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_02]: The maps that are coming with this, one's called Grindyard.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a wintery junkyard processing plant thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be a spiritual successor to Gridlock.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Underhill and Courtyard also, in addition to the Fuel Depot remake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Actdeft approves in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuel Depot was the best map of the first Gears of War, says Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's probably why they're bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's probably why it's coming back for another round.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, people are going to be excited that they can increase their gamer score by another 250 points.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here goes your EP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I just want to say my EP hit a landmark today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I crossed 10,000 gamer score today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, apparently, there's a good use for some of your Xbox 360 systems that may be broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: One use, of course, would be to convert it into a bong, and that's what someone has done, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have converted their Xbox 360 system into a bong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, it doesn't work anymore, and I'm sure it's been gutted, but yes, now it is a bong, and you can smoke out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But of course you would only smoke tobacco out of it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, because anything else would be illegal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, everybody smokes tobacco out of bongs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I do know people who actually will do tobacco in a bong, but you can only do ginseng and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that like a hookah type thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's pretty much like just a modified hookah, but it's the same difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm looking at the picture of it and...
[SPEAKER_02]: I would do better with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, would you really want to turn your Xbox 360 of all things into a bong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be calling it the Xbox 420.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, to be honest, you wouldn't have to necessarily have an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could buy a replacement case and it's like, just buy a bong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, it's just, it's not even worth, you know, just getting a hookah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, why bother?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, why bother other than, oh, look, I did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now one person's converted their system into a bong.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one else needs to do it because it's a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I the only person here who's reminded of Dennis Leary?
[SPEAKER_06]: How so?
[SPEAKER_02]: Saying that smoking pot doesn't lead to other drugs, it leads to carpentry?
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_06]: AcidicVampire in chat says, if you use your 360 as a bong, you will see Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is very possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would...
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, look, look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't turn your 360 into a bong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get it to work again so that you can get new games on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although this game is not on the 360, but it's a developer that makes a lot of games for 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: PopCap is giving away a free game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, a free game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a belief going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like a St.
[SPEAKER_06]: Patrick's Day promotion.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to go through March 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game you can get is Big Money.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get the game for free on PopCap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So go check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of like the game Pop It, if you've ever played it with the balloons.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're basically trying to make...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like four of the same color that touch and it has a money theme going to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like the balloon game if you ever played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no, don't you click them away in this one?
[SPEAKER_06]: When you see matches of four, you click on it and then they go away and everything compresses together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how the balloon one is.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: You click on them and then it compresses together and you don't want it to go past the top of the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've played this before, like a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's free, so now I can go play it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I have to get it before the 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't Rhapsody already come out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: Rhapsody, A Musical Adventure on DS, The Last Remnant on PC, The Wheelman on PC, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The US doesn't have much coming out, unfortunately, this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting things off, of course, we have on the DS, and I think this held over from last week, but World Championship Games, the track and field event, it got delayed to Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Valkyrie Profile, Covenant of the Plume, also coming out on Monday on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Tuesdays when we have most of the stuff coming out, including another DS game, Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on the DS, Henry Hatsworth and a Puzzling Adventure, which is pretty cool, kind of combines puzzle and platforming there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on the DS, Mind, Body, and Soul, Big World Puzzle Book.
[SPEAKER_05]: On another Nintendo platform, the Wii, we have Ready to Rumble Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Pro Evolution Soccer 2009 on the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also have Rune Factory Frontier.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some more DS titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have on the DS and PSP, Scrabble.
[SPEAKER_05]: On PlayStation 2, SingStar Queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on the DS, Suikoden Tikris.
[SPEAKER_05]: um Trackmania DS also on the DS and on the Wii Crayola Adventures Colorful World wow that sounds awesome not awesomely bad awesomely bad yes um
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, this week on Xbox Live Arcade, we're supposed to be getting Hasbro Family Game Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on DS, SBK08, Superbike World Championship.
[SPEAKER_05]: On PC, a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Path, Runes of Magic, Grand Ages Rome, Aether Saga Online, Tom Clancy's Hawks, and Woman's Murder Club, A Darker Shade of Grey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and Men of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty kind of lame release week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and on PSP, how could I forget this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually going to play this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resistance Retribution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't wait to check out the linking stuff on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I can't wait to finish Resistance 2 since I haven't really played much of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, quick question for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Completely random, but since you know about games that are in demand and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up with the Retro Game Challenge?
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried to go to Best Buy to get it the other day and they said they had none in stock and they weren't expecting any more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this a hard to find game now?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Atlas, so Atlas puts out their games in very limited quantities.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of these places think it's going to be too niche of a title, and so they don't bring it in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then people start asking for it, and then you can't find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, because I actually was hearing Bobby say good things about it last week, and he's not the only one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of my other friends are talking about how they enjoyed Retro Game Challenge, so I was actually going to pick it up on the DS, and then I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: How about the Nintendo Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you get some stuff for Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Darts Wii Deluxe, Monopoly Here and Now, the World Edition, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 09 All Play, and Winter Sports 2009 The Next Challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of those titles coming out on the 19th of March.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I knew you were a big fan of Cookie Mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would rather just cook it and have someone else do my gardening for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out, Kuroshitsuji Phantom and Ghost comes out from Squeenix on the 19th of March.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the Pets series also making its way to Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cats, Dogs, Horses, and Monkeys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are all separate games making their release in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zookeeper gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game's been out forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Ball Evolution Dragon Ball Evolution
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, Amazon's been having a new deal now with their game downloads where you can basically buy a game to download for $9.99 or less according to their ad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a bunch of game developers are not happy about it because they think that their games...
[SPEAKER_02]: should be sold for more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So PopCap and iWin actually pulled a lot of their games off of Amazon saying that it was completely unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, they'd want to put like Jewel Quest for $19.99 and think that $9.99 is way, way too low.
[SPEAKER_02]: That $20 is an acceptable price, $10 is not.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you can't get those anymore, and from what I understand, the rest of the selection is kind of ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a pretty cool...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout Paradise
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm keeping that shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I'm not recycling crap because they're just going to put that back in a package and sell it to me again.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, screw it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to say that you can't take the glasses out of Disneyland either because they have the Honey, I Shrunk the Audience or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get the 3D glasses for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they actually have a cast member waiting there for you to dump them off.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the Muppet Show one's freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm keeping the glasses.
[SPEAKER_05]: That I can understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess kind of changing topics here a little bit, talking about this story out of the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's this campaign called the Change for Life campaign over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's interesting about this is it's trying to, I guess you could say it's a campaign, an ad campaign, trying to get folks to not play video games, basically insinuating that video games cause obesity, diabetes, cancer, and so on and so on, just all these bad things.
[SPEAKER_06]: and basically trying to get people to go out and about.
[SPEAKER_06]: For instance, let me read the text on one of their ads here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Risk an early death.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nine out of ten kids risk growing up to have unhealthy amounts of fat in their bodies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if you think they look healthy today, adult could bring an early death from heart disease, type 2 diabetes, or cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: So make sure your kids are active for an hour a day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reduce how much fat they eat.
[SPEAKER_06]: For more advice, visit this website.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what's interesting about this particular ad that I'm reading from in particular is it features a little kid sitting on the couch holding a PlayStation controller in their hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, oh, I'm just sitting here lazy looking, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: A healthy looking kid, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Half dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but he definitely looks bored playing PlayStation games, which, you know, there are quite a lot of boring PlayStation 3 games that are out right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, that's not the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on here, Sony's pissed about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Sony is to the point where they are actually thinking about possibly filing a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently the agency who made the ad, The Gate, they did not get permission from Sony to use the controller in the ad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so it is possible that they're talking about possibly Sony Computer Entertainment Europe is considering legal action against the folks that made the ad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, kids need to get up off the couch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kids should not sit and play video games all day.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's there to say that video games aren't actually a healthy thing to incorporate into a lifestyle?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe an hour a day or a couple hours a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you limit it in your kid's life, I don't think it's necessarily such a bad thing at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They're also, though, not factoring in the fact that there are many people who may be clinically overweight who are actually in better health than, like, say that you've got the person who's in their BMI range, correct?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they don't eat properly, they don't exercise, they can't lift much but you've got the person that maybe is say a little over their BMI which by the way BMI is bullshit, you know are overweight but yet they go out and you know bike, go swimming, do things, are active people and have much better cardiovascular system than the you know stupid little anorexic cheerleader type and
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you could also have someone incredibly muscle-bound who's the same BMI as someone 300 pounds overweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, really, you've got to look at the factors of biology, genetics, and more than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just sitting in front of the couch playing video games all day is not going to make you die.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to read chat.orangelongeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xlink says, it's good hand-eye, but so is masturbation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says, go outside and play Dragon's Lair in the backyard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbandit says, you can be fat and happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can be fat and happy, but you just got to make sure you're not fat and unhealthy.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be a triathlete.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be a professional bicyclist and get cancer.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can be a triathlete who gets hit by a car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, what does it matter?
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you die an ironic death.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing is that I think a better ad might be instead of the big text up there that says risk an early death, do just nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about one that says stop using games to babysit your children?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be an effective ad in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be one because the kid looks bored and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how about stop using games to babysit your children?
[SPEAKER_02]: A responsible parent is going to look beyond... And this is something that I've had to think of a lot myself lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're going to be a responsible parent, you need to be 100% for your kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Including taking them outside to get them some activity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Including telling them, you know, I think you've played enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to go do this now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got to set, you know, you have to do the things that are good for them, not just the things that are convenient for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's an awfully nice way to phrase it as a parent, is that, you know, I think you've played enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I know my mom would have said, turn it off and go outside!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: My mom would be just like, you're not on that thing again, are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I'd go out and play, come back and she'd be playing my Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: that's how she got her turn go outside, it's my turn
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see if Sony does end up suing over this or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure what's gonna end up happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know who else will sue?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But speaking of Sony, we have some stuff about Noby Noby Boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Takahashi Keita said that there's going to be an offline multiplayer mode on the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that he wants people to enjoy the game, so they're working on an update.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all going to be, though, offline, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Specifically offline.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're saying that it should be roughly around the 18th of April.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, not boo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, multiplayer is better than none at all, but, you know, I wish, you know, it's not like the Sony's not connected to the internet, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, a lot of people are familiar with GamePro, the magazine that's still around, surprisingly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, GamePro is actually going to publish indie games now under their new label, GamePro Labs.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you may see some of these games coming to XNA, PC, Zune, iPhone, etc.,
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they're going to sort of act as a middleman between indie devs and platform holders.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's also interesting is GamePro has announced that they're planning to produce a free custom edition of its magazine for distribution exclusively at 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when you get your Slurpee, you can get a free copy of your modified GamePro magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this going to be an addition to the current subscription magazine?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: How is a company like that growing in this economy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to add as a further dib at the crap that is 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can go pick up your free magazine when you're picking up a game that's broken street again.
[SPEAKER_05]: You make it sound like it's an issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: 7-Eleven doesn't adhere street dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nor do I. I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the problem?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you were in full support of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm in full support of Slurpees.
[SPEAKER_05]: God damn, if I became rich, I'm getting a Slurpee machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I miss Vanilla Coke Slurpees.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those were the bomb.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell do I have to do to get those to come back?
[SPEAKER_06]: GamePro doing their own game publishing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think we're going to see anything big come out of this?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think it's just going to be of the caliber of the types of things that come free with a magazine?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because they have to give away demos that are already available on live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Demos!
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't download those.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I canceled my... See, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to subscribe to Xbox Magazine back when they used to have demos way before they ever came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saints Row demo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: But now it's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: demos for old shit that have been on live for a long time now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, no thanks, I don't need to subscribe to your magazine anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I already get a free membership to stupid, well, not even technically free, but I get a membership to Game Informer because I have that stupid card at GameStop because, you know, it gives me an extra 10% or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's paid for itself, but hey, I get a magazine out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, the magazine's not bad, so I'm not buying Xbox Magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Salad Game Salad Game Salad
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't like RPG Maker, it's still pretty good actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, it's not going to be any good at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, RPG Maker is pretty awesome, but I've seen some of these games that are hell like click and play.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just so many limitations to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I think it's just... Well, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just for shooters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, some of the games they say have been made on this that are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game called Darkwood that's like a Zelda-ish type of RPG that was made by three students in a week's time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then DRFT, a 2D racing game that's kind of like the original Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it sounds like everything that Click and Play could have done, because that's the type of stuff you could do in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very limited and yeah, you can make these wonderful little racing games and stuff, but they're just not great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hope to God that you can't publish these on the Apple Store because that's all they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's put out a game making program so any idiot can create all this crap and then we can pad our numbers on the App Store and use that in our next commercial.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Any idiot can make a podcast and get it listed on the iTunes Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but iTunes doesn't go, hey, we've got X million podcasts, look at us, we're so awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't really care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apple doesn't care about podcasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apple doesn't care about a lot of things except getting you to buy their crappy products.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're almost to the end of Part A of the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming up in just a little bit, we've got a couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: That we do.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, something about Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's supposed to be a versus download content and it's supposed to be out for 160 Microsoft points or 250 yen on a PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, which we're probably going to be getting it for twice as much or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're basically saying in Japan it's going to be out, um, March 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, of course, we were talking a little bit earlier about exclusives and that kind of stuff and mentioned Bioshock 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, of course, this month in Game Informer, which also goes back to another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, we're transitioning from two different stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock 2 was the cover story and, of course, they revealed the big sister
[SPEAKER_05]: and is a new Big Daddy-esque creature that you're going to be fighting against in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, there are no real details, at least, leaked out yet about what exactly you're going to be doing, but the second game, apparently, you will be playing as the first Big Daddy, the original Big Daddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock 1 was really sweet, and I can't see that it's going to be any less than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game has an awful lot to live up to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think it's going to meet the hype?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it will.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're going to have to do some interesting stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that it was going to be more above ground and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that you're playing as a big daddy from the beginning is kind of... I'm not too sure if I like that idea, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, hey, let's take a trip back to the past here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not talking about the Classic Game of the Week just yet, but here's the interesting thing is that the Genesis, of course, is a system that's been featured many times in the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there is this new kind of like...
[SPEAKER_06]: 3rd Party Sega Genesis
[SPEAKER_06]: Going for about $53 and with the system comes about 15 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic & Knuckles, Altered Beast, Alex Kidd, Golden Axe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So all these old school games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess this is what you start to see as these consoles age.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess the patents expire or something like that and now third party remake these old ass consoles which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the best part about this though, because they did release something before, they've done handhelds and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The best part about this though is that it does have its own cartridge slot that will play Mega Drive and Genesis games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So not only do you have the 15 that are built in, but you can put in new ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, now what we're going to do, we're going to take a trip back to the past.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know if DarkSakura has picked a Genesis game this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: She might have picked something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's take a trip down memory lane and see what the classic game of the week is that all you kids should check out this week by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the secret, the secret, the game of the week is Secret of Mana, which was known in Japan as Seiken Densetsu 2, and I picked music for it that is actually some of the overworld music, which is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I thought we were going to do a little...
[SPEAKER_02]: The game came out, it was actually developed by Square, which is now Squeenix, and came out on the Super Nintendo, and we eventually got it on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually, as I said, it's Seiken Densetsu 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first one was called Seiken Densetsu Final Fantasy Gaiden for the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we got into Final Fantasy Adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of an interesting little game there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But going back to Secret of Mana, it didn't use the turn-based system.
[SPEAKER_02]: It used a real-time battle, more like how it was in Zelda.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you also had an AI that you could actually control to be either attacking, defense, or somewhere in the middle.
[SPEAKER_02]: and a second player could come in and play one of your other characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was pretty much a two-player RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: I personally have not tried to do it with the multi-tap to see if you could do three people.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if anyone has, let me know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just never occurred to me until I was an adult.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the game itself in the American version is...
[SPEAKER_02]: basically you're kicked out of town and you have to go and you hook up with a princess and a sprite and you run around trying to get a different well first of all you get your experience in battle and you level up and you can level up your spells as you you know as you attract them and by the way the multi-tap does work thought I would mention that and the virtual console version will let you use three people
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, you have to rescue different elementals, and they give you different attacks, different skills, different things that you can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the magic is your party's mana power, which will increase as the game goes on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, really, it's just you go through different places.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also get flammy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember flammy?
[SPEAKER_02]: The second thing I put on there, Rob, was Flammy's music.
[SPEAKER_06]: The best way I can describe Flammy is...
[SPEAKER_02]: It is like Falkor from The NeverEnding Story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, it's the same concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: You ride on this big white dragon thingy's back, and then you can land in different places.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, it's Mode 7-tastic!
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so you can go over the background and you can move and the map will move with you and you can land and it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, it's just a cool little game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's funny though the way that you call them is by doing the little drum with the balls on the string.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot what they're called.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but anyway, it's super cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, then at the end you get the mana sword, and you kick ass, and game over.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, the game was designed by, um, uh, Ishii Koichi, um, and, um, was actually, um, released after Final Fantasy III, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: They wanted to actually use the system from Final Fantasy IV, but it wouldn't work in the series, so they did it all for Secret of Mana.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was originally going to be an SNES CD add-on, but when they dropped that, they just did it all to fit on the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually had one of the faster localizations.
[SPEAKER_02]: It only took 30 days to translate the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was also stated that they were going to bring it out for the Wonderswan Color.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they cancelled it when Square decided to tell Bondi WTF, we don't like you anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's really, it's been one of the, I think, most popular games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been considered by Nintendo Power, it was number 42 in their top 200 games of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's actually because of this that I went nuts trying to find Seiken Densetsu 3 and played the most of it on...
[SPEAKER_02]: on a fully translated mom hack I wish I could find again.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's really, it's a very worthwhile game.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't played it, play the hell out of it and then play Seiken Densetsu 3 because it just evolves on the awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know why I hadn't reviewed this earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well there it is, your classic game of the week, Secret of Mana and what a classic game it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if they'll ever be highlighting Secret of Evermore
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well we are going to take a break here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got plenty more Orange Lounge Radio coming up though in Orange Lounge Radio Part B. So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be right back.
[SPEAKER_06]: And welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, March the 15th of 2009, where we do tape live, of course, every Sunday night on allgames.com, All Games Radio, bringing you lots and lots of great gaming shows throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're on right after another great gaming show called The Bobby Blackwolf Show, and we run for about three hours until we're tired and we want to go home, is basically how long we do the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Snake360Light.com
[SPEAKER_06]: on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's the same game as pretty much was up there before, except now it's half the price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, of course, since it is half the price, there's a little less features than what you have in the full game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now I guess you get some two different multiplayer modes now, three single-player courses, three difficulty levels, multiple control schemes, just like in the other game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You still get some of the soundtrack from the same recording, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Support independent game development.
[SPEAKER_06]: Snake360 Lite.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, now we're going to get back into some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some pretty cool stuff...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, this is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo has addressed complaints that they had not that many games coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're low output of first party titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, it says this year, Nintendo seems to be getting some more games coming out, including the equally awaited Punch-Out!!
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, they've just...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're like, well, we don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now that they're putting out more games, they're trying to make sure people are going to be happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing, though, you ask me...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: That does not count.
[SPEAKER_05]: Putting old things in new packaging.
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't count at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: ExciteBots and PunchOut.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does count because those are brand new.
[SPEAKER_05]: But these new play control games, I'm sorry, I'm getting a little sick of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've just started coming out, but just tell people to stop buying them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the thing is, that's all that's coming out now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, people are so hungry for Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh god, I want a new Pikmin game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now you're going to buy the re-release of Pikmin 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameGuru in our chatroom says Punch Out is very much a remake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is, but it is adding new characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not so much, you know, it may be a remake, but it's not a port.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a Super Nintendo game, too, and it's at least kind of redone from the ground up, and there are some new things in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not a port.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like, oh, I took the GameCube game, didn't really change anything to it, and then just poured it over.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now, you know, Pikmin 1 and Mario Power Tennis, they didn't really add anything to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Donkey Kong Jungle Beat from what I hear they're adding some additional levels I don't know if it was in the Japanese version or if these are brand new levels but they're adding something to it and then Pikmin 2 are supposed to have two different types of Pikmin that weren't originally in the game so they are adding something to it but still it's a port of a game that's been out for a long time now GS68 in chat asks where's my new play control Custer's Revenge
[SPEAKER_06]: That wasn't on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't, but maybe it's a game he's thinking needs to make a comeback.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, look.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to look for some new Wii games that actually look kind of interesting and you want to talk about a remake, I don't know if this is really a remake, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is like a reinvention completely of the old game Pong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to actually play a little clip here from the little trailer that we have here in studio because this actually looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a... Let me see if I can play a little clip here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a music based game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Bit Trip Beat and it's by a company called Axis.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's actually coming out to WiiWare on Monday and it's like all these little pong balls consistently are coming at your little paddle and you have to bounce them back and when you do it makes little beat music like the like 8-bit weapon type of chiptunes music that's what I was looking for um I guess this game's coming out it's gonna be 600 points here's the thing the controls you just tilt the control back and forth you tilt the little Wiimote back and forth
[SPEAKER_06]: This should be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I like the idea of only having to pay $6 for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this should be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe if this does well, it will be.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this boss stage looks just like a freaking regular breakout or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trippy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very trippy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hence the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be out on WeWare on Monday, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the time most of you hear this podcast, it'll already be out.
[SPEAKER_06]: ActDeft in chat says, BitTripBeat is basically Pong and Rez's bastard child.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have bad, bad news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, not really bad news.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not likely news, but Capcom US is hoping that we get a Tatsunoko vs. Capcom, which I think would be freaking fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, I mean, it's got Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else do you need, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, they're saying, um, it was basically a quote by Christian Svensson, um, who is the developer, the business developer and strategic planning VP at Capcom said, do not rule out, um, do not rule a Western release out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I can say right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are still actively working on having that happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't say it's happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't give you a time, but as badly as the fans want it, we want to bring it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem that they're running into is what do we all say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Licensing, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tatsunoko rights are actually split among several companies in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas, of course, in Japan, Tatsunoko Pro has all of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have to worry about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here, it's like, you know, whoever had, you know, Gatchaman 2 has Eagle Riders here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there was Battle of the Planets.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was G-Force.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: in later anime, home releases, different things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or even people who just thought about bringing it out over here and paid the licensing rights.
[SPEAKER_02]: That does happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a pain to get everything together, so they're actually going to have to do a lot of work for us to get the game over here, and it's all down to freaking licensing.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: These are originally our characters, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess, sadly, in a sue-happy world, that's not what can be done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the way that it is is that once Tatsunoko's given up the rights, they have to abide by contract.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and Tatsunoko Pro, I don't think, really has any holdings in the U.S., so it'd be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So then they couldn't be sued in a U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: court.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Tatsunoko wouldn't legally be able to give the approval, which they clearly did in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just would not legally be able to do approval in the United States.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't get, uh, what's his name from, oh, you know, Frank West from, uh, you know, Dead Rising in there and stuff as a character?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, sadly, I'm not gonna hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need Gatchaman Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they need to make it for me, specifically, and say, because Jamie demanded it, we give you... And it would actually say that in the opening credits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We give you Gatchaman the Battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then I would be very gratified as a fangirl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resident Evil Remake Resident Evil Classics
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if that's going to be a new play control game or something like that, but that's going to be coming out for a $30 price point.
[SPEAKER_02]: The studio is haunted.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're having the attack of the random beeping noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, just give that to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll turn that off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live radio, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my sensor bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Batteries are going out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry about that, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you were going to say Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, forget it
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Tree Run Super Sandwich
[SPEAKER_05]: The game looks crazy and Nellie keeps asking me when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we don't know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: The 22nd or 20th of April?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too far out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it's time for a birthday present.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always got to be about you now, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it always must be about me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to have the show's ego after all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, how about something related to Namco, maybe?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Namco has actually registered Excalibur as a trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not really saying much about it, but it actually has an ESRB listing some achievements revealed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said, the registered trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: um and so it's there Namco Bandai is releasing Excalibur so of course the theory is that you know it's about King Arthur but maybe it's another in the Soul Calibur family or maybe a fighting game using the same engine or a remake of that old game Excalibur 2555 AD um
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a feeling that whatever it is, it's going to be lame and disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be about Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's Namco for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's either going to be really awesome or really lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's usually nothing in between.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm voting really lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Caliber is the storyline based on fighters that have dropped out of the Soul Calibur series and now have to find real daytime jobs, including working fast food restaurants.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Caliber.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a fun guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or it's a fighting game featuring all the exes in the relationship.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think now's a good time to just go to the next story, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll stop now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do know what this game is though, Wii Rock Drum King.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a brand new drumming game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, not using any actual peripherals other than the Wii Remote and Nunchuck, or possibly two remotes if you have those.
[SPEAKER_05]: What it does have though is a pretty cool song list, and the track list was revealed this week, including some stuff that you would not normally see in a music game like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Feel Good Inc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gorillaz
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the weird ones that was in there, they had Organ Donor, the instrumental version by DJ Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You normally wouldn't see that in a rock game like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other songs that are in there as well, they have All Star by Smash Mouth, No One Knows by the Queens of the Stone Age, The Takeover, The Breaksover by Fall Out Boy, and
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't Stand Losing You by The Police, Spoon Man by Soundgarden, and Click Click Boom by Saliva.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was still tempted to get Rock Revolution this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's tons of them sitting on the shelf.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm almost thinking it's going to drop to $9.99 before too long.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's when I'll have to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It won't drop officially to $9.99, but just let it sit there and fester a while, and it's eventually going to drop down.
[SPEAKER_05]: So bad, they actually canceled the Wii version of Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was actually supposedly slated for April, still coming out at $50 retail.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yeah, no one's going to buy that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, they just canceled it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if there's sales figures on how much that game actually sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sure there are.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I have an idea where to look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, while you do that, let me talk about some other games that aren't necessarily just there to be sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Nintendo Game Seminar program, and if you're a student of this, you get to make your own DS game, basically, as a part of the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Nintendo has actually taken these games that were created, and now they're available at DS download stations throughout Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can also get them through the Wii Nintendo channel.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's four games available.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them is a mic-controlled game in which you blow to kind of create air that sends stars up in the sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one is where you are a voice artist that reads lines, and then when they're played back, they're given by like a weird character on screen, a random one or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one is an action game where you move around and you pose, but I'm not sure exactly how that's done because they didn't say these were for the DSi, although...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and not just that, but now they have kind of a way to get it out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's almost kind of like a little bit XNA-ish.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know if that's something, maybe this is a sign that Nintendo might use the DSi download service for this or some of their other distribution channels, but that is kind of an interesting thought, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although it could just be a bunch of crapware, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: 0.5 million copies were sold for the Xbox 360 version.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the highest of the three.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a half million, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: 0.5 million or 0.05?
[SPEAKER_06]: 0.05 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, so 50,000 copies.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that is the best one out of all three versions the PS3 version sold .02 million copies or 20,000 and then finally the DS version only sold 10,000 copies well that's sad because the DS version seemed like the only one that made sense out of the bunch
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It made me giggle inside in a painful way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we get any emails of substance?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, this is, it says, So this is a multiple email.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, where are my shows and two, boy, do I have a slew of reviews for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, alright, first, Tony Hawk's Project 8, another Tony Hawk title for the PSP, but this time around, it is a bit more challenging, no auto-kick, the story is cheesy as always, but anyways, it's awesome, and if you are a skater, wanna be by this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I really can't read this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm looking at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it was written on a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm going to translate into English, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Will that be fine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Wipeout Pure.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of us kids who own a DS and owned a GBA know of F-Zero and GX.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have not released anything for a long time, and I own a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that it would be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead, it was, and I'll tell you, it was more of a challenge than F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: GTA Liberty City... Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what you're thinking, what a 15 year old is doing with a GTA game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought it on Amazon using my debit card and got it a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I popped it in and I instantly love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The custom soundtrack stuff takes some work, but once you do it, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killing police from my safe house with a sniper rifle and racking up a 6 star rating is so fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely recommend it to a first time PSP buyer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lords of Dogtown, I Love Skateboarding and Surfing Stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: This movie combined a little bit of both with a story about Jay Adams, Tony Alva, and Stacey Peralta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, last thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you guys ever heard of Neo Geo Advanced Entertainment System or the Neo Geo CD, King of Fighters is Better Than Street Fighter, Peace Out, DS Lover?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, first of all, I own a Neo Geo and I have a Neo Geo CD as well and I have
[SPEAKER_02]: A Neo Geo Pocket Color and a Neo Geo Pocket So I'm really not sure which one you're asking about But King of Fighters
[SPEAKER_02]: It really depends on what you're into.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the King of Fighters series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, talk about your cheap bitches and hard to pull off attacks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Street Fighter is a little bit more gratifying to play, but King of Fighters is just a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes there's a bit more of a fun factor involved with the King of Fighters games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I do have to say that if you've got it on the Neo Geo, you've got it arcade perfect and you have also paid for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's all I can say about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, you know, yeah, King of Fighters is sort of like an evolution of Fatal Fury and Art of Fighting and those games, and it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it's not something I really can usually tolerate long-term, though, the SNK games, but they do have that whole, like, you know, foreground and background thing, which is kind of what made them famous.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was just Fatal Fury.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't, oh, was it just Fatal Fury?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought King of Fighters had it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Art of Fighting have it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I think just Fatal Fury.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Art of Fighting had the weird zoom in and out thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was its little niche.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Summer Showdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: R-Fighting did it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first one did at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no, it was Fatal Fury that had the background foreground.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's different and worth a play, but I don't think it's necessarily better.
[SPEAKER_06]: If that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I love Capcom vs. SNK.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one of my favorite fighters right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Matt, what's your preference?
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter or King of Fighting?
[SPEAKER_02]: King of Fighters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have a preference, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Robin Street Fighter vs. King of Fighters?
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: You hate them all?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not hate, but I just don't really care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will tell you this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any of the King of Fighters games on Saturn have a bitch of a load time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: In between rounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Load time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, I was just wondering if it was possible for you guys to create a widget for Samsung phones for your podcast as I would love to be able to listen to you on the go and download your shows wherever I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, Simmel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've not even heard of the Samsung phones widget thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not something I'm familiar with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send us more information on how to make one.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's just doing a simple website or something, I'm sure we can figure it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it involves programming like an iPhone application, well, I don't know so much about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: if it's something you can connect to iTunes I don't know if your phone I don't know because there's a lot of Samsung phones if your phone my old phone was a Samsung and if it has a memory card like my old one you can put your own songs or your own music on it basically you should be able to just sync it up with iTunes and download our podcast on iTunes and do it that way
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the best thing I can think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: With all its fails, we can look and see what that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if it's easy enough, why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: We also got one... That last one and this one that I'm about to read is actually put in through the website.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, the catchphrase thing you got here is fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got it wrong because it's really confusing and erased my whole goddamn message.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really think that's the fault of the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I was just wondering why the show takes so long to go up now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It used to go up the day after recording.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not take this as a complaint.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am just curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because my setup here changed, and I have two computers now that I have to go back and forth between, and then also this week I was on a work trip, so I try to do it as I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other people are offering to help make the process go faster, so we'll hopefully get on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, you know what, I'm going to save this one for a last minute story, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I am going to go ahead and credit the story to, well, they didn't sign it, so I'm just going to say, Nigel, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will be one of our last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have contributed to the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, level up.
[SPEAKER_02]: The winner is you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a no prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send us emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send them to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's some really neat download content that's going to be coming out very soon for Fear 2 Project Origin.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called the Toy Soldiers download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what it is is it's a few multiplayer maps that they're adding in.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's kind of neat about it is...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all done from the perspective that you're small little toy soldiers fighting in these giant areas.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for example, some of the maps that they have, they have a hospital room that you'll actually fight around in.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a playground.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then finally, one that Jamie I think will like, they have one that you fight inside of a pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of a unique twist to the whole multiplayer stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm glad that they're actually having a little bit of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say that the pinball machine looks the best out of all of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now only if the giant metal ball is rolling around in there too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no word on when exactly these will be available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I guess it'll be in April and it will be free.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free stuff is always welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the best kind of download content is free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, a new trademark has been filed this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sing Hero is the trademark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, you know that was filed by Activision, Blizzard, the folks behind Guitar Hero and DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently now Sing Hero has been patented.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this going to be their version of Sing Star or Karaoke Revolution?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to milk the Hero franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I will say though, keep in mind this company also trademarked Drum Villain and I don't think that ever happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just because they trademarked it doesn't mean the game is actually going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but they also could mean just because they trademarked Drum Villain, maybe they just rolled that into Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_05]: But singing's in Guitar Hero World Tour, so I'm not sure why they're going to have this whole separate game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe this is going to have more pop music.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know about you guys, but when I hear stories like this, I can just hear the sounds of the Guitar Hero franchise being milked even more, and that's like after seeing the arcade game this week and everything, and it's just like, I'm starting to get pretty sick of all this stuff, and it just makes me angsty, because, you know, it used to be such a good game, but now it's just getting, like, beaten to dead horse.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I get angsty, and that's why the FUs of the Week happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a couple of FUs, but one of them is a very big, very major one, and it's directed towards my body for reasons that I choose not to disclose publicly at this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But certain people know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the second one, it goes towards a lack of tact.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy to Burger King for burning my fries.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have never... Honestly, I'd expect this kind of thing from McDonald's because they fuck up their fries more times than not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Burger King, come on, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your fries are usually pretty tasteless and they're fixed by ketchup, but these fries were burnt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they were browned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and the other thing too, if you ask me if I want ketchup with my fries, don't just not give me ketchup.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't ask me the question and just say, oh, here's no ketchup for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd like some ketchup, wouldn't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm not giving you any.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not giving you any.
[SPEAKER_05]: So F you to minimum wage Burger King workers.
[SPEAKER_06]: um well geez as GS68 in chat says poor poor Loki's fries um I don't really have anything that major this week I guess two FUs one FU goes to jet lag because that sucks and my sleep has been all screwed up like for the past four days because of it um I was in Washington DC this week by the way just for a few days
[SPEAKER_06]: If you were following me on Twitter, you probably saw some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, my only other F you would go to the fact that we have no Dunkin' Donuts here in California, at least NorCal.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's sad because I freaking love their coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I actually brought back a Dunkin' Donut for my roommate on the plane from Texas because I always gush about...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dunkin' Donuts, even though the donuts are only okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: To me, I'm not as huge on the donuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the coffee.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not bad at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are my not-so-serious FUs of the week, but that's what I've got.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess the jetlag one's actually pretty serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: That really was annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did want to say, though, about a Sing Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to read some comments here in chat about that because I thought one of these in particular was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru, I believe, said that they might just be trying to protect their trademark.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just protecting trademarks.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru GameGuru
[SPEAKER_06]: Hitstun says, F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sky, you have arcades with Street Fighter 4 and we don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I guess here in California, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just haven't driven to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not around us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, not here in SAC.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we do have the Guitar Hero Arcade now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have Mario Kart 2, which I didn't check out, but they have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to get drunk and go play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really care for Mario Kart Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was, but maybe the sequel has fixed some things.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, doubt it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get into another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need more F-Zero GX.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do need more F-Zero GX.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is another interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how all these LEGO games have been coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's more!
[SPEAKER_02]: More, more, more!
[SPEAKER_06]: Which means people must be buying all the ones that are out there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing it for a good reason, because they are pretty damn fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one's sort of a late franchise now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing a Harry Potter Lego.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's never too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: But basing your game, I would have to guess it would probably be the original game plus the new stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I understand why they're coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like one of these games that I look at and go, WTF, why are we getting this?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it's not really a surprise at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you've been speculating, Loki, for quite some time that the Harry Potter game is going to be the next Lego thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is no surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they've got a toy for it, they're going to make a game for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, if you see all of a sudden LEGO Halo toys coming out, then you better believe that there's going to be a LEGO Halo game at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: But otherwise, it's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, otherwise it's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be surprised if we see another LEGO Batman game, because that's something that they can keep adding to and basically have unlimited content for, because they're not based off movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a problem, basing stuff off movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they don't make any more movies, you have no more games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another comment from GameGuru in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, Lego Prince of Persia will likely be next when the toys come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: They rebooted the Prince of Persia franchise recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Won't they make the sequel in that kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if they do, if the movie comes out and it's really popular and stuff and everyone's interested in it, I don't know if they're really going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would all depend on how many toys come out and how well the toys do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rice Princess in chat says, I love Lego games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Harry Potter games.
[SPEAKER_06]: The two combined would make my head explode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Giovedea says, Lego doesn't sell the HP sets anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't even get the sets off Lego.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dr. Tatsuya says, still waiting on Lego Watchmen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it come complete with a detachable penis?
[SPEAKER_06]: For Dr. Manhattan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Special soundtrack by King Missile.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he'll have his little, like, you know, molecular underpants.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I did not understand because, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: He could wear underpants, yet he didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he doesn't really exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never saw the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole point was that he's detached from humanity and humanity's standards, so it doesn't matter to him if he's dressed or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, I mean, seriously, if you think about it...
[SPEAKER_05]: What are the Viet Cong going to be really scared of?
[SPEAKER_05]: A giant glowing blue penis is coming towards them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am so down with Dr. Manhattan.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's wearing his black pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: He should have just been buck wild there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to do the show naked from now on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree with what Dr. Manhattan said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: No amount of blue penis makes that movie any good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sad Trombone
[SPEAKER_05]: I should do just as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since it's going to be Infinity Ward again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because everyone knows that Treyarch sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of people who play Call of Duty 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: This number doesn't surprise me one bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Danny Harrison, son of George Harrison
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So as if this game wasn't going to sell to the Beatle collectors already, imagine if this game has never before heard Beatle stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't believe that anything like that still exists, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, by the way, Donnie, who's the son of, of course, George Harrison, he's been a big part of actually trying to get the Beatles rock band to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's in a band of his own who has an album coming out this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: AppleCore
[SPEAKER_06]: And convinced everyone to sort of have a presentation.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game has been in the making for two years.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say it's historically accurate, a real headache, but it's the most enjoyable work that he's been a part of, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it sounds like it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_06]: 9909 is when this game's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty hard to forget that release date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hey, all we have to do is remember Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to mention in the gaming week, we actually did bust out the Dreamcast and go through some Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of our VMUs still work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have all of our Samba files too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's some other news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wallace and Gromit is still out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is actually a game coming out on March 24th with a demo on the 16th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Telltale Games is putting this out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's part of, as far as I'm aware, the episodic Wallace and Gromit's Grand Adventures.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hey, keep your eyes open for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's also going to be another Strong Bad game.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you pre-order Wallace and Gromit, you'll get a full episode of actually Sam and Max and Strong Bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice little bonus there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like full games as bonuses.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now this is kind of not new to the MMO scene, but Final Fantasy XI has finally jumped on board, much like the Blizzard Authenticator.
[SPEAKER_05]: They now have something very similar to that that will generate random passcodes every few minutes, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Final Fantasy XI security token.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, the constantly changing login passwords will apparently protect your account from hackers.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the only thing though is they haven't released a price for it yet but it will come with some in-game exclusive items when you purchase this token huh okay so you get special stuff in the actual game?
[SPEAKER_06]: yes, you get like stuff in the game I'm still not interested in going back, sorry alright
[SPEAKER_05]: One more story for you guys, then we're going to open up our Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR Username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio Oh, I was going to, real quickly, I was going to mention the Vanadio Collection Yeah, $14.99 now Oh my gosh, on Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Windows Wow, they're really trying to get new crack addicts on that game Because, you know, you pay that once They might as well just give the game away Because you get 30 days for free with that And $14.99 is how much it costs a month, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised they haven't gone the route of just doing a downloadable demo, or have they?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just missed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they did, and I might have missed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Completely different side note here, but something also to kind of take a note.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy from a Yale University, he's a Yale University student, so you know he's smart.
[SPEAKER_06]: His name is Jesse Myman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it's connected.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, could be.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a report in the Cincinnati Inquirer that Jesse's a little pissed off because he flew U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Airways and he was flying them in December from Connecticut to Ohio and they basically lost his Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: He went to pick up his luggage after he landed and he noticed that everything was there except for the Xbox 360 and all the accompanying components.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm assuming he believes that it was theft.
[SPEAKER_06]: His suit says after that that he got weeks of an unconcessionable runaround.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you know what happened next, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why you're using the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Upscale on the HD, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wants the airline to pay him $1,700 for the loss of the gaming system because apparently he probably had his own additions on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for non-economic distress of at least $25,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he's seeking the maximum, $1 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know exactly how that works.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: US Air would like to point out their policy state...
[SPEAKER_06]: The federal loss limits are capped out at $3,300 per bag, and the airline's luggage policy excludes liability for electronics.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when the bag gets to wherever, they should have scaled it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there's a clear difference in weight in the bag.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, those Xbox 360s weigh like 15 pounds, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, they stole it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's no way that it didn't break during the flight, which I don't see really being the airline's fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt says I always bring my console on the plane with me or not at all
[SPEAKER_06]: Deekman says if it was broken, yes, but it was stolen.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you ask for a million, though, suddenly a settlement of $500,000 is looking pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe this guy's just trying to highball it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: He is trying to highball it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gripper01 says God help Microsoft if it ever red rings.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, alright If you want to give us a call 1-877-GAME-OLR Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio We're going to open up the Skype line Take a couple of calls Probably not too many tonight Because we are running a little long tonight But we also want to get to last minute stories here In just a little bit And all that fun stuff So go ahead and give us a call now We do have a call, we'll go to that Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's GS68 Hey, GS68, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on Okay, I'll wait
[SPEAKER_08]: I got Gradius Rebirth this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: It came out this Monday, much to my surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Gradius 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us, or wait, Gradius Rebirth or Gradius 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rebirth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little bit about Gradius Rebirth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to put you on with Loki here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to take care of something in the studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright then.
[SPEAKER_02]: So tell us about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think of it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, basically it's a new Drydance title, and it looks more like a 16-bit or 32-bit Drydance game, kind of like Drydance 3, or a bit like Drydance Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's basically a remix, it's more or less a remix of older Drydance games rather than a completely new title.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'm watching a replay of my soft right now, and my replay's on stage 2, which looks like a level from the MSX and MSS games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's only five stages, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: For 1,000 weak points, that might turn off a few players, but as a driving fan, I just had to get this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of my favorite things is on stage one, there are two enemies, and if you destroy either one first, you can change the entire stage depending on which enemy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's sort of like
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't destroy either, the stage continues as normal, but if you destroy the top enemy, the stage becomes frozen.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you destroy the bottom enemy, all the weapons in the stage become active and the stage gets harder.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, um, looking at the weapon arrangement for the game, you have the usual, like, regular missile and double and laser.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you have...
[SPEAKER_08]: Another one where you have a bomb attack and then a twin laser that's weaker than the... It's not as powerful as the regular laser, but it shoots faster.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there's two unlockable setups that are more or less for more challenging players, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually kind of thinking of checking this out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just haven't gotten a chance to download it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: That and that new one that's coming out on Monday here, BitTrip, or was it BitTrip Beat or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hopefully, you know, I know they've been probably a little bit inspired by the Mega Man 9 stuff, so hopefully we see more of these retro remakes that aren't exactly, you know, retro, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I always... Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope they bring some of this stuff out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They should do a Gradius collection on DS or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a Gradius collection on PSP in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but they have it here too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a Proteus collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they need it on DS as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to sell them at a collection, but the fact that my old PSP has a crappy D-pad is turning me off from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't want to get a new PSP because then I'll
[SPEAKER_08]: because then I have to restart my DJ Max save files because they're locked to the current PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there any other WiiWare games you're looking forward to checking out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a few favorites that I want to buy eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a few older games that I eventually want to buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, crisis averted?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, we have Rob trying to find his microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we're back to normal, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm sorry I missed the review, but let me just quickly ask for a summary.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it worth breaking my boycott over?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's certainly not the best... Well, it depends on what game is enough to make you break your boycott.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's more of a game for hardcore Guardians fans like V.I.N.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most people forget the fact that it's only five stages and it doesn't really add much to the series.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to wipe Defender Castle to get this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do love Defend Your Castle, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls, but thank you for the review.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry I wasn't here to hear it all.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, see ya.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had like an insect outbreak here in studio because a piece of my sandwich fell on the ground, so all the ants rose up from the ground and were like, rise from the grave.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rise from your grave.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so they all decided to, yeah, have a piece of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was cute how you took care of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I took care of it right away, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's take a couple more calls here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, that was pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's me, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up everyone?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're ant-free now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want you guys to know that I took one for the team two weeks ago, and I want some type of compensation for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh dear, what's this about?
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have compensation.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't get compensated, so this has got to be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually sat there and watched Street Fighter The Legend of Chun-Li
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they made the movie a little bit too realistic, and I don't care if I give spoilers or not, because that's how bad this movie was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one, Bison should not be walking around in a mustache and a goatee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two, Vega's mask should not look like a cross between Vader and Shy Guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three,
[SPEAKER_04]: In the fight sequence in the club, Chun-Li could have at least had on some type of blue dress or something to signify her traditional outfit, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: And how the hell does she have injuries on her when you didn't look like she had any in the movie when she was fighting?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not for nothing, I'll say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: After seeing this movie, the original Street Fighter is ten times better...
[SPEAKER_04]: and I am so looking forward to Dragon Ball Evolution after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it doesn't look, well, Dragon Ball Evolution doesn't look as bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much, I'm just saying, I think after seeing this, that's gonna be a lot better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think it's a shoo-in to win all the Razzie Awards next year?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't think it's that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if U.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boyle had anything to do with it, by default, it would.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think U.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boyle makes better movies than this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can make better movies than this and I have an amateur digital camcorder I got from Joe Dea that I'm borrowing well congratulations there are my sister who is a who's graduating from Hofstra has a degree in filming she can do something better than this I've seen her do better work than this you know
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, every actor, every director usually has a stinker somewhere in their career, so what can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know, and it does help the fact that my roommate's a big Chun-Li fan, and I warned him, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, we all told you it would suck, and I have yet to hear anybody say it's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to hear a good review on this movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're asking for a little too much there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody just linked Rotten Tomatoes there in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to look at this and see if it still has a 0% from all the critics out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to see your stupid ad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm skipping the ad right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm trying to skip it too, but it's so freaking slow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
4%.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody gave it a positive review.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is from Variety, of course it's Variety Neither the best nor the worst of movies derived from video games, Street Fighter The Legend of Chun-Li at least gives action fans plenty to oogle besides the titular heroine Huh Well, there you go A whopping 4% on Rotten Tomatoes Well, Ranma, nobody forced you to watch it, I don't know what to tell you
[SPEAKER_04]: I was bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can I tell you?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I couldn't get any alcohol.
[SPEAKER_06]: No compensation for Morris Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our compensation is go watch Silent Hill again and see a good game movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the original Mortal Kombat if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first Mortal Kombat was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would even say it was really close to theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: The second one is Life I Wish I Had Back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope the third one comes out someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Ranma, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, later everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll try to do at least one more call here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, I know you had one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You alright over there?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's going to hopefully give us a last minute story here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I'm glad the microphone didn't catch that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, this is Ray.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually my first time calling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been listening to this show for four years now, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Four years now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've missed once.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Ray.
[SPEAKER_06]: R-A-Y?
[SPEAKER_09]: R-A-Y?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's my real name, heaven forbid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what is up, Ray?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, nothing really.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's 11 o'clock on spring break.
[SPEAKER_09]: All my friends are away, so I have nothing to do but stay up until 11 o'clock and listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think I've missed a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate you listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear something on tonight's show that you wanted to comment on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Any of the stories?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Indie games, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't remember any specifics, because I was just thinking of something to call about, so I'm not just here babbling like an idiot on the internet, but Cave Story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has anyone played it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pretty sure Loki might have
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, no, tell us a little more about this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I've heard of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, Cave Story.
[SPEAKER_09]: You haven't heard of Cave Story?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-mm.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a PC title.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I guess Loki knows it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is coming to the Wii, that's why I brought it up, because it's getting a graphical redesign, but on the PC, it's free, it's translated from Japanese, and it's kind of a, I want to say classic-style shooter, sort of like Mega Man, but
[SPEAKER_09]: No wait, I'm lying, no, it's a little easier.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I beat it, and I'm not that good at Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought I'd notice that Google Cave Story or English Translation should come up in one of the first few topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, our chat room sure seems to know this game, and I'm actually trying to look up a little bit online to see if I know anything about this, and sadly, no, I don't know how I missed this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I just, I'm not cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've talked about Cave Story before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a couple times.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talk about a lot of games on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care for it, but it's neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they're making a version on PSP as well, it looks like?
[SPEAKER_06]: Homebrew.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's a homebrew project.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh, interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: How did you find this game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was looking through a list of homebrew PSP games and I found it there and I learned more about it and had a PC version which is really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're the same game almost but it looks bigger, better.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why... Is it just me or does this game look very old school 8-bit NES style graphics?
[SPEAKER_09]: Precisely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another thing I wanted to mention was Team Fortress 2 had an 8-bit demake
[SPEAKER_09]: Gang Garrison 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have not seen this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's a side-scrolling isometric shooter, but it's team-based online.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's anywhere from 10 players at a time to 100 players at a time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can play as all nine major classes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of simplified, but there's still techniques to it, like the Pyro has the puffer instead of the backburner.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's none of the special extra weapons.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can deflect rockets back, and 50-on-50 matches are crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been installed on the computer lab at my school.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they let you do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a kind of lax administrator and we put it on thumb drives anyway, so it's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's only 5 megs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed you mentioned this game as a demake and we've talked about, I know last week's show we were talking about like a Final Fantasy X demake and some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think makes these demakes so popular where people go back in time and remake games such as like Team Fortress 2 or whatever the game is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think people want to keep remaking or Guitar Hero has had tons of these like in the Commodore 64 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do people want to remake these games on old systems?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think is the allure of it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's kind of like
[SPEAKER_09]: Almost the opposite of the, what was that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's the opposite of, say, just a second here, how Mega Man X, one of the later X games, took the classic Mega Man action to a pseudo-3D view.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's sort of strange seeing a new medium exactly like with the Guitar Hero Commodore remake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get into a whole lot of these.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I necessarily... Usually I'm just kind of like, oh, hmm, that's neat, but I don't really have to play the whole thing in its entirety.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of interesting that there's this whole kind of community around there, around the demakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always thought it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a Silent Hill 2 demake.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was like Soundless Mountain 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: For what system?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Google TIG source.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how they pulled that off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dig Dug Demake?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't Dig Dug kind of an old-ass game to begin with?
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pretty sure they had a Bioshock Demake, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I've seen the Bioshock demake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, there's a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And again, lots of positive feedback to Cave Story in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru says, but yeah, Cave Story is a Metroidvania worth buying and it's free on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any PC gamer should own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have to just seek that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you found that amongst all the chat about Wang?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I haven't been paying attention to chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, I have, but I haven't.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the big deal with Wang?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a discussion about Watchmen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I saw Watchmen.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was an amazing movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you read the comics?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've read the comic.
[SPEAKER_09]: They almost used the book as a shooting script.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of disappointed it left out the death of the first night owl, but they had to make room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, question for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think the movie ending was better or the comic ending?
[SPEAKER_06]: And don't spoil it, because I haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't spoil it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just say which one you prefer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I honestly think that the movie ending better fits the audience today.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Without going into how hokey the comic one was.
[SPEAKER_09]: All my friends gave it bad reviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: They went in there expecting Spider-Man or Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's its own thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, this is R-rated, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movie ending doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you read the comics?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Difference of opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't make any sense because... I will go see it and be the Tyvo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Without trying to explain too much of the ending of the movie...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Except that it happened within the one country, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so confused right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll let them argue later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another discussion.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should do a movie cast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe as a one-off.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should call it Ultimate Spoiler Cast.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ray, I've got to wrap up and let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thanks so much, and I hope you had a good time on your first call.
[SPEAKER_06]: And call again sometime, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll call back next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: We may not be here next week, but in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like first-time callers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good note to end on tonight, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: So sorry, guys, who didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to close up the Skype line for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always send us emails, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, or, of course, we will continue to read chat comments throughout the night.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still have some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, I'm sorry we didn't get to you, but, hey, if I hadn't taken that call, it wouldn't have been a first-time caller.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't have been burping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so there is a marketing stunt that went kind of nuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was actually by Monument PR for Friday the 13th for the launch of Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically the big stunt was a treasure hunt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, where about 50 members of the public would go and retrieve arms, legs, heads, and torsos from a number of different areas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically part of the big campaign.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they hid all the body parts within a square mile of London.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like in bins and on window ledges.
[SPEAKER_02]: And 100 people signed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually said that the people paying attention to it, passers-by, complained to the police.
[SPEAKER_02]: And officers were there at the finishing line to greet the people who were trying to assemble the bodies.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I read about this earlier in the week and the whole thing sounded stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It did look kind of gross.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's just certain things that you gotta wonder who the hell thought this was a good idea, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was just me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, well thank you to our emailer and to Jamie for that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, did you have anything tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just some small stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watchmen The End of Nigh 2 has been announced, and apparently it is more of the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it's supposed to be a little bit racier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently it's been rated by the ESRB and describes some sexual content in there, including... Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, basically the sexual content, I guess, is the more racier part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't know the blue peen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's not necessarily in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: As a Watchmen, I guess you'll fight in a strip club that includes go-go dancers in cages, peep show booths, and a pornographic film in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, in case you haven't played the first Watchmen, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so if it's more of the same, it's more of the suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or at least try the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, apparently Peter Moore of EA is saying that Wii Motion Plus is going to put an end to lazy Wiimote gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, apparently the 1.1 motion capture that is part of Wii Motion Plus requires you to actually make the full swing when playing a golf game or a tennis game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't just, like, move your wrists a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is great, because that will encourage more people to throw stuff through their TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Now of course we talked about earlier a free PopCap game you can get on St.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paddy's Day, but of course there's going to be some more stuff coming out as well, including LittleBigPlanet is going to be giving away a free St.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paddy's Day costume.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll include a beard, a shiny green suit, a green top hat, and other stuff to make your character look like a leprechaun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, in April, there's going to be another free costume that's a Monkey King costume.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, it was the winning entry of the PlayStation Asia contest, the design costume contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's some more paid costumes coming out later, including a Killzone minipack, Buzz minipack, Patapon costume, and a Heavenly Sword minipack as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I want some more damn expansions.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: More stuff like Metal Gear Solid, because that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then finally, Resident Evil 5 is already going to get some download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: The versus download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been dated in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be available for 250 yen and 160 Microsoft points on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is...
[SPEAKER_05]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, I'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blarg.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is Cherry 7-Up is delicious, and I've had two cans tonight during the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: That can't be healthy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is Peggle is fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for listening to our show and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, if you like what you hear, we do this for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do it for fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do it for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just tell two people you know about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help us spread the word because word of mouth is how we are able to spread the word about our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will be back maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to the website for updates on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for sure in two weeks we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: So until then, thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_03]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next week!