[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki Tonight, January 30th, 2011, Sony unveils Project NGP, Portal 2 promises user-generated content, and could cloud save soon beyond the... Hi friends out there on the internet, and welcome back to another week...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is episode number 399 for January the 30th of 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games with the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I am doing better than I was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've heard you've been kind of sick lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to hear about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I have some warm drink.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have my fuzzy blue binky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a snuggie, but it kind of looks like one from far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very soft fleece, and I think that I got this as a freebie from somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's been super soft and goes with me on trips.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's like my comfort blanket.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: If it was just like this blanket, then maybe I could be convinced.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I kind of like being shrouded in my warm blanket and being able to pull it over my head if I want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it like a Linus from the Peanuts thing where it's like your security blanket has to go with you everywhere?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it makes me feel comforted when I feel weak and sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I can use my really low... I just realized I touched that blanket when you were sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really hope I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been washed, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's also say hello to the one and only Tech Master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sick as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_09]: I caught my son's cold.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: The plague.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright, it's just... I feel like I'm marked because I haven't been sick yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dot dot dot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really hope I don't get anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sorry to hear about you being sick as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope you get over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I have to point out, just before the show started, while Bobby's show was finishing up here live at All Games Radio, you were giggling like a schoolgirl over there playing, what was it, Grand Theft Auto 4 on the PC?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, episodes of Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was really funny because you were listening to some gay dance music or something in the game while you were just blowing up
[SPEAKER_03]: It was listening to the Russian electronic station in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I was playing, well, I was working on map edits, and then I decided, because I still have the crazy car handling in place still, that I'd play around with that, so that's what I was doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it looked like you were having fun because you were giggling as your car was spinning around and around and around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because you're not supposed to be able to get in those cars because they go crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But since I have the trainer, I can spawn cars and make it so I don't fall off of motorcycles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, and also joining us tonight, of course, you guys, because we are the show where every gamer has a voice, as they have over the past, what, nine years we've been doing this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you are listening to us live, because we do tape live at All Games Radio, www.AllGames.com every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_09]: and yes we are doing a show next week which is very brave because we are going to compete against Super Bowl Sunday in some ways I don't know I think most of it's wind down I think they're in like the last quarter by the time this show starts but next week's kind of a big deal for us because it's episode number 400 I don't think we're going to do anything too special we might have some surprises in store little things but you know we don't want to do because then we could do we could do a 400th special then we could do a 9th anniversary special then we could do a 10th anniversary you know
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't want to overdo it with the special.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like teniversaries.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every week is special.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dang it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we appreciate you guys listening to us over the past few years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com, Tiger Claw says, It's funny that Snuggies have taken off considering the Slanket was the first one to come up with the idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Jim Sally says, Snuggies, now with 10% more Slanket.
[SPEAKER_09]: So is Snuggie like the Zynga of the blanket making world?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take with that what you will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's get into the show and talk about some video games and how is your gaming week and the types of video games you have been playing since you guys have been sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you guys have been playing some games, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what have you been up to?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've really just played World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Addict?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dealer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I hate Icecrown.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hated it so much that I was like, I just need to power level through it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Need to get through with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have to thank Alan, by the way, for running me through that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was a dungeon, but it was like some tournament area.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it was in Zul'Drak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, the Ring of Blood or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I could get the Slobberknocker.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it got me a crap ton of experience on top of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that saved me a couple hours of work and stupid quests to control water elementals, which sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I just did the joust thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there's a little parody.
[SPEAKER_09]: And she's not talking like an actual joust thing, although that's in the game too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ride a griffin.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's like a make-believe 3D version of the old school 80s game, Joust.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get a pet from it that's one of the little griffins with a dude on it with a lance.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get to keep the lance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I'm going to sell it for probably nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a zero to one damage item, which makes me laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm actually having a really good time in the really pretty Cataclysm area.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just really pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flowers and fairy dragons.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love fairy dragons.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll tell you why I love fairy dragons from D&D.
[SPEAKER_04]: My friend played a fairy dragon named Shimata Hentai.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm high on Sudafed.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be a fun show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sudafed, Robitussin, and Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you find that wow?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still blown away every week this goes on.
[SPEAKER_09]: That you were a wow hater in 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wasn't a hater.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you were.
[SPEAKER_09]: You turned it all around in 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't a hater.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, you were a disliker.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just bored by it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Disliker's going to dislike.
[SPEAKER_04]: well you know me I'm gonna give something a chance before I decide that I hate it and enough like I said enough people said it's different that I had to give it a chance
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of MMOs, I've got to go to a comment from TigerClaw in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says his gaming week pretty much consisted of playing DC Universe Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still haven't reached level 30.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I'm around level 16 or 15.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I've got to kind of ask, are there any other MMOs?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I know you're a comic book, even though you're not so much DC.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you're more of a Marvel girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do any of these other MMOs interest you?
[SPEAKER_09]: And you've talked also about maybe, maybe I need to go back to Star Trek Online and check out what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm missed on Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I do miss my fleet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're cool guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to go back to Star Trek Online for a month to see the new episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it really got to be super redundant.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's been enough different stuff going on in World of Warcraft that I think it's going to keep my attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've liked all the little neat throw-in stuff, and I really haven't had enough of that in Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna give it another go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I love Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love everything about it, except that I've run out of shit to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except the endgame got old, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, pretty much, and I hate PvP.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of curious what you're going to think of the endgame of WoW, because I know you haven't done a lot of the grouping, and to be honest, there's not a whole lot else to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've done a lot of stuff when it comes to reputations and crafting, and there's kind of that to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of daily quests you can do, but I worry you're going to find yourself a little bored when you get to the endgame.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But I want to eventually get into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got so wrapped up in questing and it was so much fun to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've got a worgen now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to make my shopping list over here for WoW School.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, buy Sorting Hat for Jaimee.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a worgen now, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because while I was feeling so sick and miserable, Dan decided to cheer me up by getting me Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then promptly yelled at me for playing too much Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I named her Veruca Salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: With two A's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Veruca Salt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Veruca!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I couldn't get Volk's worgen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, enough MMO chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know he doesn't play any of them right now, so I'll ask him what has he been playing this week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing, um, not a whole lot actually, just, you know, mainly like Grand Theft Auto stuff, cause that's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just been dealing with, I had my JTAG system repaired, and it died in five minutes when I got it back, so I was like, um, that sucks, so I sent it away to get fixed again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did play some stuff on the iPod yesterday, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may remember this from when we were talking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a news segment we brought up.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game Hamlet, or was it the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Last Game Without MMORPG Features, Shaders, and Product Placement HD
[SPEAKER_03]: and basically it's like a point and click adventure game except really dumbed down in a way it's dumbed down the fact that you don't have an inventory you don't have any real exploration or anything it's just okay it's one level and then the next room you're in and the next room you're in and you have to solve a puzzle in each one and there's about 20 some rooms so I was able to finish the game in like 3-4 hours but um
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just very weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, now I'm interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who from our generation didn't love Ren and Stimpy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you play this like... Rubber Nipples!
[SPEAKER_09]: What rolls downstairs, hops over in pairs, runs over your neighbor's dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: You play this time traveler or whatever who comes back to, I guess, Hamlet and accidentally crushes Hamlet and he's injured, so you have to basically do all the things Hamlet would have had to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they've already teased a sequel, which is going to be Romeo and Juliet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hamlet 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be Romeo and Juliet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hamlet 2, Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bummer, because the Hamlet 2 movie is one of those movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually watched the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know they have a movie called Hamlet 2, and it's about a guy who's putting on a stage play?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a comedy, and it's actually not very funny, but it's one of those things that's so stupid, you kind of laugh in some parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock me, rock me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, rock me, sexy Jesus.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's so absurd, you have to laugh, because this movie clearly was just set out to offend people, and that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, the game's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only problem I have is that it's short.
[SPEAKER_03]: And once you've beaten it, there's really no reason to play it again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it a free game, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, as long as you kind of get what you pay for, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some of the puzzles are pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to think about it, and they give you a little hint.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that hint sometimes doesn't really help you.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can usually figure it out pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I played the whole game through without using any sort of, you know, cheats or anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is Telltale in trouble?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they are the kings of the whole point-and-clicky games right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little different than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of like, you know, someone that hasn't really played an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very, okay, you solve this puzzle on this stage, you move to the next stage, and you solve this next puzzle, and they have little boss fights and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the boss fights are just very, very odd.
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole game is very odd.
[SPEAKER_09]: uh Spazinator's in our chat room saying that he bought some Ren and Stimpy episodes via PSN I had no idea see I wouldn't know what the hell was on the PSN video store if we didn't have Spazinator in our chat room every week or on Twitter or wherever he's at because I never pay attention to what's on I had no idea he had Ren and Stimpy episodes can you even get those on Netflix I don't even know like I'm sure they're all on DVD but they're probably all over YouTube as well I don't know all right anything else uh for your gaming week you want to share with us Loki
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, that would be it
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: and they have a couple neat things like they have a 9 minute preview of Tron Legacy which is you know what you would expect to see they turn the Muppets theater into the Tron theater which is kind of funny but they do like lighting effects where when the recognizer comes out the whole theater glows red kind of cute little things like that
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: It's guaranteed right now on the calendars through March 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: That means we should be there when we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: But people are thinking like, oh, maybe it's not going to last through April when the Blu-ray is coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But my other thought is, what are they going to replace it with?
[SPEAKER_09]: Electronica replaced what they called Glowfest, which was the same type of thing, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just didn't have a Tron theme to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when you see the Tron stuff, it's pretty rad what they did.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's not a whole lot else to see besides that classic arcade and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's crazy because this arcade is full of people.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is a freaking line to play the Tron game, which they have perfectly placed in the back with a little subtle cutout in the wall.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once in a while, you'll see things glowing behind.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it is perfect, this replica they've set up.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they even created this is the thing that just freaked me out they created a game called Space Paranoids that they have in an arcade machine and it's clearly running on a PC because it doesn't use tokens but it's like in a cabinet and it's like a 3D game where you go around and shoot recognizers but you only have so many bullets it's pretty hot I think that's their browser they had a browser game that was like that
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's probably just a browser game like as an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's what that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I played Dig Dug, which is one of my favorite classic games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tease me if you will, but I walked out of there with the number one score on the machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, I don't know if it resets every night or what, but hey, I was happy for a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: If you are anywhere near SoCal, you gotta see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're an arcade enthusiast, you gotta see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least once.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a pretty cool thing to behold.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't say it's alone worth the $90 price it costs for a one-day park hopper or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pushing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're gonna be going to Disneyland anyway, you gotta make sure you're gonna see this somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really hope...
[SPEAKER_09]: that they went to all this work that they just keep it open like really they weren't using that building for anything else just keep the damn thing open until you have something really really good to replace it because it looks like they spent a lot of money converting that building into Flynn's Arcade don't I mean even if they're going to end Electronica keep the freaking arcade don't get rid of it please Disney so
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, folks in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shezro says, wow, Flynn's replica.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bochikawa says, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it was crowded, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, gosh, I only had time to really play like the one game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tiger Claw says, Sky, are they blasting the Daft Punk soundtrack all over the park?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do some of it, especially during the pre-show leading up to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when the dance party's going on, it's mostly Top 40 remix stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they have people decked out in Tron outfits that are up there dancing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I felt kind of cool because...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: this is our makeup trip because we didn't get to go that weekend she had two of the discs one blue and one orange and like everybody was coming up to her asking her like where she got the discs and it was just from the freaking souvenir stores and you can get the blue ones at Target actually they have them at Toys R Us yeah so they're not hard to find but it's just kind of funny so Ziba wants to know if I took any pics yes I did I actually took some video too so I'll try to kind of put that all into a compilation video and upload that to YouTube or something if you want to see I'll try to get that up later
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyhow, so that was really it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was, uh, TigerClaw in our chat says, top 40 music, yuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I might be misrepresenting a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a lot of remixes of top 40 music, but TigerClaw, I know you like the electric and trance stuff, and I think you would be happy with the stuff that they played.
[SPEAKER_09]: They played some cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um, I know my friend constantly had her phone out with SoundHound or whatever that program is that lets you identify songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, what's this electronic song?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's this song?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it's kind of a mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, let's move on and actually get into the show itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: For some housekeeping, please follow us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also you can follow us on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next week is the 400th episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be starting at 6 o'clock Pacific, promptly 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby actually has the night off due to this.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some football game that people care about here that a lot of people apparently are going to be watching.
[SPEAKER_09]: and we have the balls to go up against it but if you must listen on the podcast feed then I suppose you can join us there too but it'll be more fun I promise if you join us live next week for the 400th episode of OLR all right let's get into tonight's gaming news there was some big stuff big conferences things to talk about right Loki
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the big thing of course is talking about the NGP.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the NGP is what I guess Sony is calling, what everybody's pretty much dubbed the PSP2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it is one sexy looking piece of equipment there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, of course, they, um, had a lot of the stuff that was rumored to be in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a, you know, carrying a 5-inch OLED screen, uh, with pretty high resolution on it, four times the PSPs, a front touch screen, a rear touch pad, uh, 3G, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, GPS, dual analog sticks, um, and it looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I've gotta get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't really give a price point.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is supposed to be out at least in one region before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess it looks like both the front and rear little touchpads are multi-touch.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does have a front and rear camera as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Built-in microphone, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also got six-axis motion sensing, including a three-axis gyroscope, three-axis accelerometer, and three-axis electronic compass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, you said something that I think I just totally missed during the press conference.
[SPEAKER_09]: You said built-in microphone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a built-in camera on this too?
[SPEAKER_09]: Two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Front and back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, this thing's going to have video conferencing then, no question.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's something they didn't even really advertise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no other reason to put a front camera on the damn thing than to have some type of competing FaceTime technology or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then Bluetooth and all sorts of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm pretty excited about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, a bunch of things I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were mentioning, of course, it's going to be backwards compatible with PSP games, like digital games, so you can play PSP games on there, PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if I have the games on UMD?
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I just kind of screwed?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's compatible with PSP Go games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: but you'll be able to play that stuff on there and I would imagine that it's going to be fully compatible with the Playstation 1 stuff now because now you have the dual analog sticks and they're saying that they're full analog sticks so I'm not sure if you can click down on them for the L3 and R3 stuff but as far as like the L2 buttons that right there is your back little touchpad you know you can just the right half is the right button the left half is the left button
[SPEAKER_03]: and then the shoulder buttons could be for everything else since I assume the multi-touch stuff is probably going to be also pressure sensitive so that would be kind of sort of analog but that's pretty awesome and it looks very similar to what you know the normal PSP 3000 looks like right now they're gonna also have I guess there's some
[SPEAKER_03]: Some special slots for memory and games and stuff like that, because obviously they're not using disks this time around.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a proprietary format for both, so it'll take just a little bit longer to crack, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: and of course they were talking about some of the games that are going to be out for it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the games in the works, Uncharted, Killzone, Resistance, LittleBigPlanet and a game called Little Deviants which looks like the first kind of original game for the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously most of their, I'd say all of their big franchise games are going to be coming out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did show Uncharted which is
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty, Broken, Gravity Days, Hot Shots Golf, Hustle Kings, Reality Fighters, Resistance, Smart Ass, and Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they didn't name a price or a date, but if you thought they were going to do that this early, then you were kind of wishful thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because E3 is really the time to do that, and let's face it, when Nintendo first unveiled the 3DS, they didn't say any of that either.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just came out with the price and date, what, two months ago?
[SPEAKER_09]: And now it's coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or no, last month, and it's coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we talking about price and date for the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it just came out a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I meant two months out of the actual release was when the dates came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So to think that Sony was going to release the release date of this and the price and everything now, 11 months before release or whatever, was a little bit... No, I bet they don't even know what it's going to cost yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're probably trying to gauge the whole consumer reaction or also the price technology.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it goes down so rapidly.
[SPEAKER_09]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Price is kind of important, obviously.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's too early to say if I really want to get one or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it really depends on what's all there when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm definitely getting one just because I have store credit for the Sony store.
[SPEAKER_03]: $280 of that's already spoken for.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as it's not something stupid or ridiculous like $400 or...
[SPEAKER_03]: Even $400 might not be that bad with $280 taken out of the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually thinking $400 might not be completely out of the realm of possibility.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's going to be $400 because it would be hard to justify a handheld system being more expensive than a console system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at its competition.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't mean the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: The iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the iPad with 3G is what?
[SPEAKER_09]: $650 for the lowest model?
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and I sure as hell am not buying an iPad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, but you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: that may be if they want to play that gamble then go ahead but I think it's going to end up flopping on them just like you know the PSP Go although this will be a little bit easier of an argument because it's you know a new system and stuff but you know they're talking that there's probably going to be multiple SKUs on it one for 3G one for Wi-Fi personally I'd just pick up the Wi-Fi one because I don't want to fucking another data plan exactly tethered to my fucking phone that's what I'm going to do
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkKisuke in our chatroom is dying for an educated guess from us gaming analysts wants to know an educated guess for the price I'll give you my best guess I'm going to say $300 without 3G and $400 with it
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's... Considering the level of technology they're trying to put in this thing and all these other little features and stuff, I think that's not outside the realm of possibility.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, one big, big wild card to keep in mind is Apple's next iPad, which they're going to have a big announcement and they're going to release it within the next couple months.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have to be an Apple psychic to know that.
[SPEAKER_09]: so if they manage to really cut the cost of those things that could make Sony have to kind of do a counter move but seeing as I don't want to go too far off base here but I believe those new iPads will probably have the same retina display that the iPhone 4s are using right now and it's going to make those things absolutely gorgeous they'll probably still be charging at least $600 if you want an iPad with 3GS
[SPEAKER_09]: so we'll see so Sony can still at least be cheaper than an iPad if they do that and I kind of think that's going to be where their niche could be is that the Sony NGP could kind of be like cheaper than an iPad but does a lot of the same stuff at least as far as games are concerned
[SPEAKER_09]: so, we'll see Ranma on our chatroom says, can someone tell me what NGP stands for?
[SPEAKER_09]: Next Generation Portable it is a working name, like Natal was, do not expect that to be the final name, I would be very surprised if they really, I actually don't really care for that as a name because, and somebody in the chat had said it earlier, by the time the NGP releases, it's going to be the CGP, the current generation portable, so it would be a little silly for them to actually call it that
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the Neptune.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or the Dolphin was the Nintendo GameCube at one point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or the Revolution was the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: So these code names, nothing new.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm very curious to see what they're going to name it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of don't think they would do PSP2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't roll off the tongue as nicely as PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that sounds really nitpicky, but it's like all the extra syllables or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know I'm being weird, but I just don't see PSP2 being it either.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk a little more about what's going on with the new Sony system and its feature.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of like this because I like to see what the systems are doing besides just remakes of the same old games now on a portable.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like to know where are they going to be taking the games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I was very interested with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something called Live Area.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might have seen some of the little promos, some of the art's
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very curious.
[SPEAKER_09]: and people, you know what, that Pokemon thing with the walking trainer and all that was really popular so it's not outside the realm of possibility that people kind of like these ideas of being rewarded for going places.
[SPEAKER_09]: 3DS is doing something similar too with the whole coins thing, built-in pedometer.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, hmm, will be interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, news for our UK listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 3DS eShop is actually not going to go live like they said it would with launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually said that it's going to go live in May.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Nintendo UK said that it was going to be there with the launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Iwata basically said, nope, nope, nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first system update is scheduled for late May, the same time around the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not just them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I'm glad Iwata came out and actually said something himself.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, they need to make sure that all of their reps are on the same page.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it kind of makes it sound like they don't even know when the damn thing is launching.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of like, it'll be done when it's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be out in Europe on March 25th, but we won't have the eShop until the first system update.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is going to be in May.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it seem now that maybe they're rushing the 3DS a little bit?
[SPEAKER_09]: A bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they should have just waited to release it until summertime.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe there's something about May, like why you have to release it in that type of time frame or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, March.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why they couldn't have delayed this a little bit if it's not really ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they're going to sell most of these at Christmastime anyway, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be reasonable to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I also say that because of the launch games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It kind of doesn't have the must-have title that's going to be out at launch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably the coolest stuff that's coming out at launch is the Street Fighter game, the Dead or Alive game maybe, and maybe Nintendogs and Cats if that's what you're into.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's kind of a stretch for a must-have launch title.
[SPEAKER_09]: That Kid Icarus game didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't heard of the Zelda remake or any of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: None of that kind of made the launch, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you guys in our chat room think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.orangeonsradio.com Well, I was going to say, actually, it does seem like that they're like, well, either we wait and put everything out together or we at least get the system out, get some early sales going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then once everyone sees what else is on the eShop, then we get another boost in sales come May.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's sort of what I'm seeing of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw a lot of that happening at PAX East last year when I went.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spazinator says, I'm a bit paranoid about taking portable stuff out and about, if only because I live in a rough neighborhood and I don't want to be jumped and robbed.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually not a bad point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not everybody's going to want to find the players near them.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: That could be a little scary.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I apologize if I'm pronouncing this name incorrectly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nipros says, it does seem Netflix has Ren and Stimpy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Since we were wondering that earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for checking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, the other thing, too, is that something like that actually might work in Japan, because you remember with all the stuff that was happening with Monster Hunter, you know, that was such a big thing, and people would just randomly challenge it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nintendogs thing, you know, that's something that I think would happen more often in Japan, but not so much here, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, years ago, the barcode scanner.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just got people that are more into it who will go to the cons and just walk through the street.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I forgot about that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was some type of battle game that was battle barcodes or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they sold out of this one brand of ramen or something because it created some uber monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there was the CD one.
[SPEAKER_09]: what was the game that you put in your CD and you get a different monster based on the CD and you got like this great monster by using Madonna totally don't know but well now it would be too easy to just burn your own CD yeah because obviously it was measuring track length and number of tracks or something interesting hmm all right let's go to the next story then we'll chew on this 3DS news a little bit see what happens closer to launch mm-hmm
[SPEAKER_03]: And now back to more Sony news.
[SPEAKER_03]: We talked about last week how the people figured out ways to load custom firmwares and stuff like that on their PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's the first thing that happens when they do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, release new PS3 firmware update, or this could even go for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: and patch all that stuff out or at least try to break it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what they did.
[SPEAKER_03]: They released 3.56 firmware.
[SPEAKER_03]: It adds no functionality whatsoever other than a security patch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it basically changed some of the keys on different things and...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Other methods to, I guess, cheat the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they've permanently banned those people from playing Black Ops in multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay, cheaters get smackdowned.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just think about that, future cheaters.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one thing if you want to cheat amongst people you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care if you cheat in single player where you're not going online or any of that, or if you cheat with friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: But going just to be power tripping in random online matches is a dick thing to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dicks deserve to have dick things happen to them in return.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you remember how they were saying, oh, well, there's no way for us to possibly stop these guys from cheating on our games.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, poor us, Activision.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Weren't they trying to use that as an excuse or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, now the excuse is out of the way, and hopefully they're going to fix everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do believe there was a patch for the PS3 version as well to fix some stuff, but now it's not an excuse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me move on to what's coming in a future PS3 update, if the rumors are to be believed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I would believe this, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, there are some folks in the development community that are getting notices from Sony saying that in firmware 3.60, cloud storage for saved games will be available.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called online saving.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not calling it cloud saving.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe make everybody think of Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're calling it online saving.
[SPEAKER_09]: This means that you could actually save files on a remote server.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that way, if I'm playing a game at home, I could save to the online save and then access this at my friend's house.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, this feature will only be available, of course, to PlayStation Plus subscribers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this doesn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I seem to remember when they first announced the PlayStation Plus that this was one of the features they were touting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not too surprising this is finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I kind of like that idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you go to your friends' houses and sometimes forget your save files or hauling the memory cards around is too big of a bitch or whatever, you know, or you forget, then it's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of wish Microsoft had one too that didn't involve save cards.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I think it's neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, is this a feature you'd use?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think anyone in here uses PlayStation Plus right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this something that might make you want to get it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: No?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'll never take my game saves anywhere other than, you know, on my PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if I really was, you know, aching to do that, I can just throw it on a jump drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, anything that would interest you?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fun concept, but I'd have to see it more in practice before I make a judgment on it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: This would have been perfect in the college dorm where everybody had a video game system and you're going from room to room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would have been great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that would have been cool back in the DDR edit days.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know.
[SPEAKER_09]: and the mom was all over the media saying he's autistic and he's just really good at games and Microsoft's like no we caught him cheating he's banned from the network just like anybody else would be and turns out it came to light yes he was doing that whole save file exploit thing where he can unlock achievements from opening up a save file and so yeah I don't care if you're autistic if you cheat you're a cheater and you should be dealt with appropriately that has nothing to do with the end result
[SPEAKER_09]: Totally agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't matter the color of your skin, the sexuality, any type of handicap you might have, physical, mental, cheating is cheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: Period.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a little silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like how when someone with a disability or some persecuted group will just come right out and say, oh, well, you're doing it because of this, this, and this.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you wanted to be treated like everybody else, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: How far do I want to go with this?
[SPEAKER_09]: How controversial do I want to be on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a difference between actually singling somebody out and then treating somebody like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you guys remember there was that burger joint in town that was very popular?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was all over the Food Network shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they ended up getting sued by the American Disability Association or whatever because apparently the place was called the Squeeze Inn.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it kind of made its whole little reputation off of being packed and crowded all of the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: and some folks sued them based on disability needs and the damn place almost closed that's ridiculous and I kind of I agree and here's the thing well technically it did close it did close and had to reopen in a new location
[SPEAKER_09]: but they and this is important to say all you had to do was to honk your horn outside the restaurant and they would have served you whatever I mean they they you did not have to actually go into the restaurant so I don't think anyone was like totally being discriminated against or what have you you know it just it just kind of struck me as you know ruining it for everyone I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a mess.
[SPEAKER_09]: But at the same time, that place never got more publicity than when that whole thing happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spazinator in our chat room says, I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta read this comment from Derek H. Maybe lighten the mood a little bit too.
[SPEAKER_09]: At our chatroom at chat.orange.radio.com, Derek H. says, Confirmed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob says it's okay to cheat with friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think a lot of bored housewives share the same philosophy.
[SPEAKER_09]: So are you saying that the mailman is a friend?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure quite what you're saying there.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if you're fucking him, he is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you know what I meant.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay if you're a bored housewife cheating in... What would bored housewives play?
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_09]: Bunko.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're all cheating in Bunko, you have...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a house rule.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a house rule.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a rule.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're cheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you agree to house rules because it's kind of how you play with friends, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: More stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so this is kind of more about the whole firmware updates and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ties in all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony, of course, was granted a temporary restraining order against Geohot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obtained by hacking the PS3 and more to the point, he can no longer engage in acts of circumvention of the TPMS in the PS3 system to access, obtain, remove, or traffic in copyrighted works, which I don't think he was doing anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then of course there's still issues about the whole jurisdiction issues since of course he resides in a different state than Sony and a different state from where the claim was filed and they're saying that because he purposefully directed his activities at the Forum State of California they're letting it go through
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of, that's not a good precedent to be setting by the courts, saying, oh, well, because you conducted yourself on a website that was located in California, we can try you in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody who uses Facebook or Twitter or whatever can be tried in California, no matter where you are in the world, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: I find this comment from our chatroom interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to ask Loki about it here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's from Napreos.
[SPEAKER_09]: I finally figured out how to pronounce the name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Napreos says, FGO hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: He deserves it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cocky bastard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, I haven't really seen this guy in action.
[SPEAKER_09]: I realize he's been in the media and so forth, but is that a legitimate claim?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is he really cocky?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did he kind of have it coming to him?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if he's cocky, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: It all comes down to... I mean, this is just part of the discovery phase of the whole trial.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like Sony is getting his equipment.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they'll have access to it along with the lawyers to kind of make sure no funny business is going on, but it's not like this stuff gets shipped to Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even still...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: um and they've actually gone and they've been um doing ceases and desists on different um websites hosting files and whatnot but now people have kind of diverted that stuff to um a file hosting place off sea you know in other countries so they can't be touched I guess
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me play devil's advocate here for a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not that I necessarily feel this way, but wouldn't that sort of be the equivalent of you shut down a file sharing site such as Pirate Bay or whatever because they're enabling people to facilitate illegal downloads.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not posting the illegal downloads themselves, but because they facilitate it, they're the ones that get in trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say that makes sense if you're basically... If he was releasing the backup creator for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, this could be used for legitimate backups, but some people might not use it for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not what he's doing at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is basically saying... I guess it would be the equivalent of... I don't know...
[SPEAKER_03]: A car salesman handing you the keys to a car And you go hit someone with that car They're enabling you to get in that car And murder someone with that car So they should be held liable for it That's basically what the equivalent of it is Dealerships actually do have liability Against that type of thing It's retarded I understand that they may get away with that In the laws of the United States Because it's absolutely retarded But people can sue and win for hot coffee It's
[SPEAKER_03]: And granted, he posted stuff, and I'm sure they don't want people giving them backdoor access to the entire PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what he's done, yes, may eventually lead to piracy or easier piracy on PlayStation 3 because...
[SPEAKER_03]: These tools allow people to run unsigned code and people can create unsigned programs for piracy purposes, but also they can create code for other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not necessarily that he's directly responsible for it, but yes, he plays a part of that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But once again, this court case isn't about necessarily...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say, and this is a great comment from Bob Coffey in our chatroom here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hackers aren't cheaters.
[SPEAKER_09]: The trial isn't about hacking.
[SPEAKER_09]: The trial is about your rights as a consumer, not about CFW or any shit at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The real precedent this may set is, do you own the computing product you buy or is it a licensed product?
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting note to end it on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess we'll see what develops with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: To prove that he did all this stuff, or he's actually doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is that Sony's claiming all these things that obviously aren't true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they're saying, oh yes, he's pirating stuff, or he's enabling people to pirate stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: When they initially made that statement, that was not the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it may be the case, because now there's the ability to do that, but it wasn't anything he did.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know, it...
[SPEAKER_03]: it's difficult to it all depends on how intelligent the court the judges and stuff like that whether she's going to buy into this retarded nonsense alright well we will see what develops I'm sure we have not said the last on this so let's go ahead and move on to some release dates and travel the world and see what is coming out in a video game store near you this week
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a whole lot this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there will be some better stuff in the upcoming month.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week, they've got a track pack for Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're missing out on some country music, there's a second country track pack coming out this week on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other smaller games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Junior Brain Trainer 2 is making its way out on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sims 3 Outdoor Living.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of an expansion pack for The Sims 3 that's coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: On PC, they have a game called The Ball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently someone took my advice and made a game about ball.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, a week from today, sort of, Mario Sports Mix will be out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a really, really dead week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there a reason for that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that just because of the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not yet into the middle of February.
[SPEAKER_03]: February is a pretty light month.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's more games than there would be in January, but it's not March.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well let's move on and look at Japan and what they've got coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I gotta tell you, it's kind of the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't have a whole lot coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's a couple things to note.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dodonpachi Daifukutsu Black Label comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a cave shooter coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is coming out on February the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, because they get a lot of those shooters over there where it's just pretty much...
[SPEAKER_09]: That little center of the screen getting taken up with a shooter, but quite an audience for the shmups over here, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2011 gets its localized edition on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is also coming out on the PlayStation 3, and that's the only PS3 release this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going to the Nintendo Wii real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Things are dying down on the Nintendo front, of course, because of the 3DS's impending release on February 26th over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although the Nintendo DS does have a couple things to note.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dragon Ball Ultimate Butoh Tuden comes out this week from Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Gyakuten Kenji 2 comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is in a regular and a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming out from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe that is a Phoenix Wright spin-off game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It definitely has some of the same characters from that series.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this looks to be a little more like walking around adventure-y type of game, but I'm sure still the whole courtroom scenes and objections that you know and love.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on quickly to the PSP, there's a release on there that some folks might be interested in.
[SPEAKER_09]: White Knight Chronicles Episode Portable, Dogma Wars, comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an official Sony product from Sony Computer Entertainment in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll be interesting to see what they improved on in the PS3 version, if anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also on the PSP, Macross Triangle Frontier.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that does it for your Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, that's a Macross Frontier game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Macross Triangle Frontier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see, because Macross Frontier is the... Yeah, that's for the new one that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new series that was out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which Dan and I watched all the way through.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks kind of like a 3D shooter game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not like a typical shmup, more like a polygony shmup game We're big fans of the Macross games, I bet it's a lot like the VFR games Actually, we've got Macross M3 for Dreamcast, which is a really good game So yeah, I love the Macross games Was that Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: that's it for Japan in the UK on February 2nd we have Bionic Commando Rearmed 2 for Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 we have long cookies on the 4th we have Earthrise Lord of Arcana Mario vs. Donkey Kong Miniland Mayhem Nailed Sega Mega Drive Classics Volume 4 and Two Worlds 2 that's it alright
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on with some more stories in the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what's more ridiculous, the whole lawsuit that this company is facing or the name of this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Facebook game Blingville is getting the cease and desist from Zynga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently Zynga believes that they own the rights to the use of Ville in any product.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it's out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gosh, what are you, the new monster cables?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to start suing everybody for using Ville, or Doodle, or Monster.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently, they have sent a cease and desist to Blingville LLC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a unique company name, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_03]: The creators of the Facebook game, of course, that
[SPEAKER_03]: has the same name.
[SPEAKER_03]: According to Zynga, the use of vil in the game and the company's moniker infringes on its own collection of social gaming trademarks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blingvil, of course, not associated with Zynga in any way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Bress Lowell's comment in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cruella DeVille?
[SPEAKER_09]: Will they be suing Disney?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's possible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on, Zynga.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of find it to be a taste of their own medicine a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't Farmville like a ripoff of Farmtown?
[SPEAKER_09]: Which of those two came first?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Farmtown.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, so, I mean, come on, Zynga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, Zynga's, like, evil, okay, and that's all it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_03]: People hate Zynga, like, they don't have any original content, it's just ripped off from stuff, and they just, now they're suing people out of the way, because they're, they may, you know, come in and start taking away some of the money that Farmville or Cityville or, I don't know, whatever...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because you have names of stuff that end with VIL does not mean all of a sudden you own the trademark to VIL.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to sue Danville next.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the people that made Farm Town should sue them because they started farm games, honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: If that lawsuit didn't already happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm looking at Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I know it's not a definitive resource, but it's a pretty good place to start researching.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I do notice it says Farmville started as a clone of the popular Farm Town, which also featured on Facebook in June 2009.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there are some citations for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the other big Zynga game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't YoVille another big one?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do they even have that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that's what it was called.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see an article on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are the other big Zynga games out there?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to know if they were knockoffs too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan plays that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to see if they have a list of games somewhere here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mafia Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't that a knockoff of a game too?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know this is very exciting radio yeah the makers of a similar online game Mob Wars sued Zynga over the launch of Mafia Wars accusing them of copyright infringement Frontierville that's the other big one too that's the one I always see on my stupid wall I don't think that was necessarily a rip off of anything though interesting
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think all of those Bill games are a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I would sit here and criticize it, but then, again, I can't stop playing that stupid Knights of the Clicky, or what is it really called?
[SPEAKER_09]: Knights of the Crystal is the real name of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That Square Enix one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the dumbest game ever, but I just keep clicking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Click, click, click.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep doing quests.
[SPEAKER_09]: The artwork's really good, at least I can say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get away with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Portal 2 is coming out on the PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360
[SPEAKER_09]: There's going to be a lot of cool stuff on the PC version as well, including mod tools.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is a Valve game that doesn't have some mod tools available for it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Some mod tools will be available on the PC version of Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, that content is not going to be available on the 360 or the PS3, meaning the mod tools.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, what they're saying, and this is a quote from Chet Felizik, who is from Valve, saying, the content that comes out is agnostic, and so we will be seeing that on all platforms.
[SPEAKER_09]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_09]: by the way, they are also saying that each of the game's two campaign modes will have individual surprise rewards when you beat them, so single player has one reward co-op has another there are two sets of credits and two sets of endings interesting, so if you really want to get the full game, you're going to have to play single and you're going to have to play co-op that should be very interesting
[SPEAKER_09]: there you go Portal 2 coming out whenever Valve's ready I know there's a release date out there somewhere but I refuse to believe anything final until the game is actually out on shelves if you need something to play in the meantime how about the classic game of the week
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a chance for DarkSakura to dive into the gaming vault and pick a game that she thinks, hey, you kids ought to be playing this.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a true classic game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of all this newfangled Farmville crap, and I mean crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get off my lawn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go play this game instead and get off my lawn.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pull up your pants.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is the classic game of the week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that the chat room will be able to tell the moment the music plays.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then let me pull up the little music here and...
[SPEAKER_04]: And whoever guesses first in the chatroom, I'm looking, gets a no prize.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm looking at you, chatroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're on a minute delay, so you might want to see it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it is Final Fantasy VI, or as we got it over here, Final Fantasy III.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is one of my all-time favorite games because of this music.
[SPEAKER_04]: This music is epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me want to climb a mountain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, had a great, great, great story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Had really amazing classic scenes, like the opera house, which of course everyone knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the great, you know, this whole music plays when they're in their little, um, machine walker things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Bolchikawa gets the no prize, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, it was just amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game came out in 1994 in Japan, and then it came out in 1999 on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was amazing, like I've said a bunch of times.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually sort of based about the second Industrial Revolution, meaning that it's got the sort of technical aspects into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Character designs were done by Yoshitaka Amano, and he did pretty much everything with that game as far as the character designs and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, well, actually also he and Yoshinori Kitase and then, of course, the composer for the music was Nobuo Uematsu.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it was really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had, you know, random encounters and you had chocobos in your airship and it was just everything that one expects to be in a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had an active time battle system.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had four players per party.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you could also change your main person walking around, I think, by hitting one of the shoulder buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had your thief.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had the runic ability, which was absorbing magic attacks until the next turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Selly's.
[SPEAKER_04]: All kinds of different stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you had your special hidden characters like Gal, who was the monster mimic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you had...
[SPEAKER_04]: A Moogle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who, um... God, why can't I remember Moogle's name?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mog, yes, thank you, it was Mog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, because, Mog House.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, um... And he had dances, which was always really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: The dude, it was all about Realm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who had the drawing attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was really sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, it had all kinds of neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very steampunk-y in ways, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Combining technology and magic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it had the most insane bad guy ever, Kefka, who just had this funny, funny laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and don't forget the man.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can find the music, Rob, you should play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I can find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: because he was freaking amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it actually had alterations made in some of the character sprites.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, there was this one character who you could see her naked butt, and they covered her butt up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, some of the item names were changed here and there, especially for the PlayStation release.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo, you found it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also the good music in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Turn it up a little bit, Robin.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan said he would slit his mama's throat for... I know, but I forgot the line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't Shadow... Like, wasn't the whole thing that Shadow's a chick?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought... Isn't Shadow supposed to be, like, Realm's mom or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Realm's father.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: hinted at but never confirmed Dan's talking off mic that'll be confirmed in Final Fantasy 6 too when Square gets around to making that
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, and keep in mind, you know, they used the characters from this for doing the Nintendo 64 demo, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: When they were going to put Final Fantasy 7 on the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which the demo is kind of weird looking, but it was neat at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this was seriously, I think it has to be one of the highlights of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely one of the highlights of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's also discussion about it being remade for the 3DS version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: There it is, folks, your classic game of the week, Final Fantasy VI.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or as you might call it, it's so good, it's Final Fantasy VI.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it's up to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's going to do it for Part A tonight of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're not done with the show yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Part B is coming up.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have more news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to talk about an interesting funding program for independent video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll get into that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some clarity on the next wave of 3DS games, including Kid Icarus and some other things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some developments in that whole Sarian.net thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember how you could play like King's Quest on your iPad?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have some updates on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to get into all that in Part B as well as your Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: So get them in at OLR on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your emails and much more when we come back of more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live on this Sunday, January the 30th of 2011 for the 399th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We hit a little bit of a milestone next week and then I get to start saying for a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: No plans of ending anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll still be here until, I don't know, one of us is hospitalized for a long time or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I shouldn't say something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I hope nothing like that ever happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, we also have side projects.
[SPEAKER_09]: This thing's been going on so long that now everybody wants to do their side project.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not everyone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Loki, your baby is your side project.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of... 18 years worth of side projects.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Josh, the... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would love to hear Nellie do a podcast about video games because she kind of hates them all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, she's like, I have to always stay here and watch the baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, well, you can go do the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll stay here and watch the baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's like, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think on April Fool's Day you should send Nellie over.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll make her read stories and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: She'll be like, I don't even know what this says.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just words.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys, what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys care about this stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's welcome to bring Josh over.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll watch the baby and she can read my stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: He can't come over.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other things to talk about that's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spinoff shows, side shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Sakura does a comic book one every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_04]: We basically just talk about what's coming out this week, every Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: The show goes up on Tuesday, ideally.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talk about what we're reading, what we're looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all have a pick that all three of us are going to read, and then we also review different things that we've read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, we all just read...
[SPEAKER_04]: IDW's Infestation which I'll give our reviews on it I hated it and talked about other comics that we read and next week if you want to hear our review on a comic called Witchfinder then we will be reviewing that one next week
[SPEAKER_04]: We also have an app for Android, so you can listen to episodes and tweet us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have our iPhone app coming soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Want to know our app for Android?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hey?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm working on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to know more about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just found out about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, and you can find us on Infamous.net, N-F-A-M-O-U-S.net.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Horde House, the best little Horde House in Azeroth.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want more Warcraft talk, and how could you possibly want more after this show?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, there's a whole show I have with my pal Extifer that we talk about Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't have a show this week, so I can't tell you what was going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Extifer had an emergency he had to deal with, so we didn't have a show this week, but we are going to be back next week talking about what's going on in the world of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a new patch on the horizon that's likely to drop this week, so I'm sure there's going to be a lot of talk about some of the changes they make.
[SPEAKER_04]: They already put up a patch, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they patch that game all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, because I upgraded to Cataclysm, and that's when mine patched.
[SPEAKER_09]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's the patch you're thinking of.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there is a new... It's the post-Cataclysm patch that fixes some of the problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Fix the Arcane?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I don't know if I'd go that far.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll be talking about some of that next week on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Breslow would slap me in the face if I did not mention what's going on with USL Madness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Under Station Live's little tournament that they do where they try to find the best video game of all time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Time, time, time, time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vote now, all the links are in our forums at OrangeLodgeRadio.com Which we know is going to win, and I know it's not on any of the lists But it's going to be a write-in winner, you watch Barbie Horse Adventures It's going to be a dark horse I'm not sure that there's a write-in thing you can do after the beginning But if there's a way to hack it, Loki will Loki will hack the results of USL Madness, just watch
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll all be Barbie Horse Adventure.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, the Die in a Fire reference has made it into a video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it had said Die in a Boat Fire, then we'd know that they were listening to OLR, because I don't think you hear that expression anywhere else.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you have never heard Die in a Boat Fire before, DarkSakura's eating, so I'll have to explain it to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, DarkSakura's gonna chew, chew, chew.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, Die in a Boat Fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would you tell someone to Die in a Boat Fire?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it should actually be an oil tanker fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: because then the water will be on fire too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the worst kind of fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, how do I put it out?
[SPEAKER_03]: The water's on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just more fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got to get to some rapid news.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of quick stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a lot tonight between Loki and myself doing some quick news tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, two great games from my childhood coming back on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oregon Trail and Carmen Sandiego are coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're making their return.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, getting a little bit of a facelift as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it's Carameldansen in Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I mean, kids need to grow up on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be required PC game playing as part of your curriculum in grade school.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I hope to hell, I hope to hell this song is in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell me where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, that's going to be coming out very soon February 2nd, the Oregon Trail will be coming And then February 9th, very next week, Carmen Sandiego So that's pretty awesome So Rob, are you going to be playing these on Facebook?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll at least check them out at least once You know you have to try at least the Carmen Sandiego one So I can post to my wall
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob has found Carmen Sandiego.
[SPEAKER_09]: She was under the mattress the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click here to find her.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had these giant posters in our computer lab with different country flags and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to know geography and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know geography.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm good at Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can shoot animals.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I was always super good at wearing... Actually, I was really good at wearing timeless Carmen Sandiego because I am a big history nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have been since I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're just a big nerd.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you have been since you were a little kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and?
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's why we love you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was gonna say the Oregon Trail you know in this one if it's not already out in this one you will be able to pick your friends like literally from your friends list that will go on the Oregon Trail with you so I can post to your wall like hi Jamie you just Jamie insert real last name here you just died of dysentery on Rob's Oregon Trail click here to find the cure I'm so gonna play that it's called Modern Medicine
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, drink this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know what's in it, but the snake oil lady said it would help.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't we get further expansions to the Oregon Trail?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zombies have attacked your party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oregon Trail 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck it, we're going back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wagon's East, Chris Farley, John Candy, Canadian Bacon, Invading Canada
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the Japanese folks are getting their hands on Scribblenauts, and they're also getting their hands on a few additional characters and objects added in thanks to a translation from Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Japanese version will feature some wonderful Konami staples, including Old Snake from Metal Gear Solid 4,
[SPEAKER_03]: And where is Twinby?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where may I ask is Twinby?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Translation fail.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are just the screenshots that were posted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe there are more things in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe people haven't tried Twinby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you never know.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool, though, that since a different company kind of works with it in another country, it gets some extra Easter eggs.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also rumored that if you type in failure, a version of Rock Revolution appears.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miserable failure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's a copy of Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to a financial quarterly report from Nintendo, a new Kirby sequel is coming from the developer HAL, and they have a teaser actually for it, and apparently it looks like a 3D Kirby game, just not all yarny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is going to be a more traditional Kirby game, but still pretty cool looking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now with less yarn and more sucking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's a good thing when you're talking about Kirby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pokemon Black and White are actually getting some PC connectivity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently using, of course, they also have the PokeWalker peripheral, which was from Heart and Gold, but that won't be used in Black and White at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're going to have the Pokemon Global Link.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a website launching this spring, I guess shortly after the game is released.
[SPEAKER_03]: which allow players to sync their save files to an online profile giving them an access to a wide range of tools including
[SPEAKER_03]: to network with fellow trainers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, check their battle statistics, assigning them worldwide rankings and granting them eligibility to participate in live regional, national, and global tournaments.
[SPEAKER_03]: The site will host mini-games which let players collect Pokemon items which they can transfer back to their cartridges as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll also let them sync a monster from their games to the website and explore their
[SPEAKER_03]: Explore their dreams online Nerds
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, let's see, last but not least, Rock Band, of course, having more stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week is actually going to be The Clash and their London Calling album.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can buy the whole album for $20, or you can buy each individual track for $2 each, or whatever in your preferred console's space bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Includes tracks London Calling, Brand New Cadillac, Jimmy Jazz, Hateful, Rudy Can't Fail, Spanish Bombs, The Right Profile, Lost in the Supermarket, Clampdown, The Guns of Brixton, Wrong and Boyo, Death and Glory, Coca-Cola, Card Cheat
[SPEAKER_03]: Lovers Rock, Four Horsemen, I'm Not Down, and Revolution Rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, for it looks like London Calling, Rudy Can't Fail, Spanish Bombs, Clampdown, and The Card Sheet.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do have the pro guitar and bass expansions available for an additional dollar if you're feeling like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So look forward to that this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on to some other stories, and we're going to start off with some news on Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, they have done such a good job keeping this game relevant, because they let a little bit of news out every week about some new characters that are in the game, so pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sienko and Sentinel have been confirmed as characters that will be in Marvel vs. Capcom 3, which is kind of funny, because I thought they had come out and said, no more Darkstalkers players, but yet it was a lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yep, there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sienko is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember I used Sienko all the time in Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: She had a different name, I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, in Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was Lele and her sister was Mei Mei.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about Sentinel?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you excited about these characters coming to MVC3, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sentinel is badass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just remember playing the Sentinel in the old X-Men Children of the Atom.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually talked about that this morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came up in discussion on recording Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saga Genesis Steam
[SPEAKER_09]: You can talk to people using the Steam interface and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alien Soldier, Landstalker, Light Crusader, Shining Force, Shining Force 2, Shining in the Darkness, Sonic 2, Sonic 3, Sonic & Knuckles, Streets of Rage, Streets of Rage 2, ToeJam & Earl, ToeJam & Earl in Panic on Funkatron, and Wonder Boy 3, Monster Lair.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are all there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You did say Gunstar Heroes, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gunstar Heroes was also recently released so I think that might be what is already there but there is now a new collection that I think has some of that stuff and new stuff as well I think those are all the sections with the old games let me see what is the new stuff here ah there we go Alien Soldier, Gunstar Heroes, Landstalker Light Crusader, Shining Force Shining Force 2, Streets of Rage Streets of Rage 2, Wonder Boy 3
[SPEAKER_09]: QuakeCon
[SPEAKER_09]: If there's any fans of Quake in the house, QuakeCon 2011 is taking place August 4th through 7th this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be in Dallas, Texas at the Hilton Anatol.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you could also bring in your PC and play some Quake there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lan, have fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll be interesting to see what they're going to announce at this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if there's maybe going to be some stuff on Rage, that whole new... Oh, I'm sure there will be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, so take a look for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, there's a brand new iPad and iPhone app for Pac-Man Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the arcade game that's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's actually like a little teaser or whatever you want to say that's available on the iPhone and the iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, I guess, like an actual first level of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can actually play that and then check it out in the arcades near you.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: So who have they brought in?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they've brought in Dan Licht.
[SPEAKER_09]: He does Dexter, the music from Dexter on Showtime.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know if you know that show.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually a little clip that's rolling around the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can play a little bit for you right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I can try.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, it has an interesting sound to it, but to me it sounds a little more orchestra, whereas Akira Yamaoka felt a little more like dude in the basement banging random things together that made for an awesome soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This sounds like he's actually trying to emulate Yamoga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because it's got some of the same, like the mandolin in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really think he's trying to emulate Yamoga style.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody loved him.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll be interesting to see what this full thing looks like when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, you can't tell from just a minute and a half clip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's going to do it for Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move into some Twitter topics tonight and see what you guys are tweeting us at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tweet, tweet, tweet Oh, a few tweets tonight Let's see, Spazinator wants to give us an update on what's going on in the video marketplace Not too much new in terms of freebies to announce aside from a preview episode of An Idiot Abroad on both PSN and XBL What the hell is An Idiot Abroad?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never heard of that Surely that's not an anime Is that a reality show?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never heard of this before.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm Wikipedia-ing it right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: An Idiot Abroad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, an entertainment travel documentary on Sky One and Science Channel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Starring Carl Plinkington.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Ricky Jervis is in it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's pretty cool, I guess, if you're a fan of him.
[SPEAKER_09]: An idiot abroad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt is tweeting us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Resident hockey fan here with some game-related news.
[SPEAKER_09]: A minor league hockey team celebrates SNES NHL 94 style.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he gives us a link there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess, what is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was playing on my old console Super Nintendo one day and I scored a spectacular goal.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is from one of the goaltenders of the Blazers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone just stopped and threw their sticks over their heads and I thought it was the funniest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it looks like when they actually scored a goal recently... They started waving their sticks over their heads just like they did in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That guy doesn't even have a stick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at him.
[SPEAKER_09]: What happened to that guy?
[SPEAKER_09]: He lost his stick.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's just waving his hands in the air.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why that's really funny, but it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And SSJ100Matt continues with another tweet saying, Also, two friends got me this awesome painting by 8-bit video game painter Adam Shub.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess is the name of the person that did that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I can't see the link that he put.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I see this one though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, is that like the Earthbound?
[SPEAKER_09]: I get linked to a DeviantArt page called Square Painter.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's like a Ninja Gaiden picture and an Earthbound picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Tetsuya tweets us and says, on the topic of Daft Punk, any of you guys ever seen Interstellar 555 or Interstellar 45?
[SPEAKER_09]: Freaking epic anime set to their Discovery album.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen the one clip, like One More Time was a whole little anime thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They all are.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I haven't seen the whole thing together.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've only seen that one song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all by the same, I don't remember, the anime artist.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the guy that did Galaxy Express and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I've watched the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually had the DVD at one point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might still have the DVD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I've watched it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Got a tweet as well from Leo Shen.
[SPEAKER_09]: The NBC, Marvel vs. Capcom, of course, 3 final boss has been leaked.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we get to a YouTube here that says Galactus boss fight in Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: That apparently is the final boss.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's this whole fighting going on on a TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is probably very no-no that this is out here on the internet, but now it's out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're fighting Galactus.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the final boss.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was awfully stunted for Galactus.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he's in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, here he comes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what you're fighting is Pinky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember now, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it was in Galactus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everyone keeps picking on Galactus.
[SPEAKER_04]: All he wants is a sandwich made out of, you know, a planet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw sent us some links, but sadly they are stories that are coming up later, so I gotta save those for a little later.
[SPEAKER_09]: That does it for Twitter tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to send us some tweets in the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get to those later on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's move on with some more stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, so this is kind of cool, I guess if you're either lazy or you are disabled.
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, I'd say it's because I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But MLB 11, they are including a one-button association for disabled virtual athletes mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically what it will allow you to do is play the game using one button.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's going to have AI handling all the fielding and the player only needs to press one button in order to swing the bat or pitch and allows gamers who might not be able to throw a baseball in real life or wield a dual shock controller ease of play.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, the mode was inspired by Hans Smith, a baseball superfan with cerebral palsy, whose limited mobility made it impossible for him to play a real baseball game as well as a video game as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Sony San Diego added him to last year's MLB game as an avatar, and then this year they went one step further with the disability-friendly gameplay mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that they kind of did that, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you get to play online in the one-button mode?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can see people that don't need to be using that mode using that, but hopefully that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if you think about it, no, if you do that, just, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: so there's a big big difference between that one handed mode alright well if you think maybe there should be more games like this that are easily accessible to those folks or maybe there's just a really cool idea you have for an indie game maybe this site is something you want to take a look at it's kind of a spin off of a site called Kickstarter which honestly I had never heard of until this project kind of came across my path 8bitfunding is the name of the site 8bitfunding.com
[SPEAKER_09]: It's what they call crowdsourcing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, you can donate to different projects and you might get something or a perk in return.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there might be these games that need help.
[SPEAKER_09]: They need money to fund the games or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you buy into it, maybe with a certain amount, maybe they'll promise you 10% of the gross receipts.
[SPEAKER_09]: or maybe you'll get a cameo in the game or maybe the developer will come over to your house or something like that or develop something for you in exchange um so kind of an interesting little thing is when i was first reading this i was like okay so this is basically like a paypal donation button donate to my game now what what is the big deal about this but it's kind of some of the perks that they're offering in fact i'm kind of looking at the site right now unfortunately a lot of these games have not really raised a whole lot of money uh
[SPEAKER_03]: They did the same type of thing with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was on the, not this 8-bit funding site, but the other one that was group sourcing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was for the Cthulhu, was it Cthulhu Saves the World or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were doing the PC version and having all these different things that you could donate and get a character in the game and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm looking at some of these projects and all of them are looking for like $20,000, which, you know, I'm imagining must be the cost of a dev kit or to get the game online.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I notice the game that has the most money right now is The Boo Keeper.
[SPEAKER_09]: $105 is how much they've raised towards their $20,000 goal.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the site is still new.
[SPEAKER_09]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to look at some of the little like perks they offer here.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're trying to get this in 86 days.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, they have like a little video as well from the developer.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they actually will give a game for a $5 project or two games for $20 a thank you package for $50
[SPEAKER_09]: Give Your Voice to a Character for $1000
[SPEAKER_09]: uh trials and tribulations they go through 8bitfunding.com what I also noticed was here was a magazine was posted on here that they're trying to fund an actual magazine for a thousand dollars it's an indie gaming magazine kind of neat maybe we need to get some of these people on our show to hock their products who knows could be interesting I like hearing about new ideas all right so 8bitfunding.com let's move on to some more stories DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: How about something on Kid Icarus?
[SPEAKER_09]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not going to be out until after E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Zelda, for that matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually saying that, of course, we've mentioned earlier that neither of those are going to be launch titles for the 3DS, that they are going to be out early June, which is right after E3, so it's speculated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you said the news, I couldn't help but feel like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's kind of the news I think we were all expecting, honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if the game wasn't coming out at launch.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was convinced Kid Icarus was going to make it out at launch, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: They made such a big deal out of that at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of, last year anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of shocking that it is delayed.
[SPEAKER_09]: But again.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just teasing, Rob, teasing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you've got to make sure the game is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't release a mediocre game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gaming foreplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm all for them taking more time to do it if they need the time to make the game great so it's just a bummer they didn't have anything done ready to go with the exception of I guess Nintendogs and what is it the submarine game or whatever that's true Pilotwings might be interesting I don't know though I didn't feel Pilotwings 64 the same way I did the original SNES version which is still one of my favorites I love Pilotwings on the SNES so there you go
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: The mailbag's coming up soon, by the way, you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and soon your calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to use the week and so much more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: More disappointing congressmen coming from California.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God, it's just... What do we have?
[SPEAKER_03]: Idiots working in Congress over here?
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't vote for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's...
[SPEAKER_03]: This time it's not Lee though, so it is a different Congressman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joe Baca, he introduced against legislation back in 2009 that required games to display labels of warnings between link of violent video games and aggressive behavior.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now apparently he's come back and now he's trying to pitch a similar thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's saying that he wants a warning to be put on these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So warning, excessive exposure to violent video games and other violent media has been linked to aggressive behavior.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it says, I guess the 2009 act failed to gain momentum, but he's now relabeled it the Video Game Health Labeling Act of 2011.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's basically the same act with the same goal, putting warning labels on games rated teen and above.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently now, I guess the only difference this time around is that he's gained support of Virginia Congressman Frank Wolf.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just as we warn smokers of health consequences of tobacco, we should warn parents and children about the growing scientific evidence demonstrating a relationship between violent video games and violent behavior.
[SPEAKER_03]: As a parent and grandparent, I think it's important to have people know everything they can about the extremely violent nature of some of these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is great, because that's what's on the ESRB label.
[SPEAKER_03]: It shows you what kind of content's in those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you don't need to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand what the point is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently they are...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how I feel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you know, I mean, if you're going to put warning labels on video games, you're going to put warnings on movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to put warnings on sugary candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: May cause your kid to have a short attention span.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you, I mean, I'm sorry, but first off, violent video games don't affect everybody the same way.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there hasn't been, there's been studies that go both ways with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing definitive about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we already have a label on the box that shows what kind of content's in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It shows if it's violent.
[SPEAKER_03]: It shows if there's nudity.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you read the back of the box, you can get a pretty good idea, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need another label saying that there's nudity.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're going to buy a game called Zombie Massacre 2011, the back of the box is probably going to indicate to you that it's probably pretty violent and that you will be massacring zombies in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not suddenly going to get...
[SPEAKER_09]: A game with puppets and rainbows and whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Puppet Rainbow Massacre.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did that in an episode of Angel.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I'm sorry, but isn't there like a budget to be balanced?
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't there jobs that need to be created?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this stuff does cost money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And why are these congressmen wasting time on this stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially California congressmen.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a word for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two words, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Budget allocation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Funding.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're trying to get donations for their 2012 campaign by pleasing some moral superiority board?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the stuff like that that actually pulls in other funds for the different areas of...
[SPEAKER_04]: The different committees and different stuff that they're trying to allocate money to.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why we have the big problems, because they need to go through and do a whole big audit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they need to have the audit done by someone not in government, but by an outside party.
[SPEAKER_09]: So in other words, if this type of movement didn't exist, the committee might get folded?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then fold the fucking committee!
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a waste of our goddamn time!
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody's goddamn time!
[SPEAKER_09]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more time, Congressman Joe Baca, I'm expressing my First Amendment right in telling you...
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joe Moron.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Pendulet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was funny because... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: If that's the best thing that committee can come up with, then it deserves to be folded.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can hear it in my head now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You mad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I am mad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let me move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sarian.net Remember that website?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the website where you could play action Sierra games, adventure games like King's Quest and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: You could play it on your iPad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we were all sitting here going, just a matter of time before this thing gets shut down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, we are waiting for this thing to get shut down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guess what happened, guys?
[SPEAKER_09]: It got shut down this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And a letter from Activision's legal counsel got posted on the website for everybody to read.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I liked how some of this email went.
[SPEAKER_09]: While we appreciate your dedication to the Sierra Classic Library and understand that you are a fan of these games, Activision has not authorized the development or distribution of these games via your website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Accordingly, we must demand that you immediately cease any further distribution or exploitation, I like that word, of the Sierra games on your website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, as much as you want to paint Activision as the big bad evil people, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They kind of do have a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it is their games and this whole thing, posting them public, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're not going to do anything with it, then what the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is another interesting development that happened this week that's worth mentioning, and that is that it wasn't totally shut down after the cease and desist.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like Activision ended up giving Sarian approval to continue running in a limited capacity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sarian.net is now able to publish the first game of any series in its multiplayer HTML5 form.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I guess this whole new little way of doing it is available.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, the iPad versions are no longer there because they might want to develop it sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Activision has allowed at least that, which I think is somewhat generous.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are also links to buy the games on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's free advertising for retro titles.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, it's one of those things where it's like as much as you want to hate Activision...
[SPEAKER_09]: you can't say they're not doing anything with this you are able to buy the games legitimately out there somewhere so I don't know it's a little bit hard for me to get mad at Activision for cease and desisting somebody trying to give that away for free it does pain me that Activision continues to do nothing new in this genre but I guess at least we always have the silver lining which by the way episode 3 was delayed but it will be coming out when it's ready
[SPEAKER_04]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com is where you can send us your emails every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I got to say, guys, the email bag is still in a pretty sad state.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got one email this week and it's not signed.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'll just say it's from Adam H. Wanting us to talk about the PSP2 or the NGP.
[SPEAKER_09]: and linking us to the blog where we could talk about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I think we did go over pretty much the big stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did go over the big stuff in part A. I will give the courtesy of looking at this website here and see if there's anything we didn't cover because you never know.
[SPEAKER_09]: There might be little stuff that falls through the crack or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Screenshots.
[SPEAKER_09]: Got those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uncharted Portable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: 5-inch organic light-emitting display.
[SPEAKER_09]: We already mentioned that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or did you use the word organic?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did OLED.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sixaxis is in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: GPS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think we covered all this, dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some nice little pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the whole back touchpad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks kind of funny with all the little PlayStation symbols over and over.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yes, our mailbag is in kind of a sad state tonight, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at OrangeLaundry.com if you want to help us out for future weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll fold your laundry, wash the cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, meanwhile, let's get into some FUs, some angst.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have three FUs, and I love you.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FUs... Aw, I love you too!
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU goes to being sick, because I hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My second FU goes to the CW for playing Supernatural by week, because damn it, I've been waiting for this damn episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, stop teasing me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then F you to all of the people in the torrent community who decided to capitalize on the fact that certain people don't actually watch active TV and download the episodes as a torrent and decide to put out a virus torrent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which thankfully, the moment you see the Windows error, you know, codec thing, you have to stop it before it goes to whatever site to update the codec.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it doesn't, you know, accidentally virus you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my love goes to Dan, because he's been taking good care of me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a little sick there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, I think I caught whatever you guys have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob's got our plague.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: mainly just to Xbox 360s being so delicate and fragile that they'll break within five minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: What, did you drop one?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't drop one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't have to drop one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I turned it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I switched the monitor resolution and it went and died.
[SPEAKER_03]: So no, the original consoles, man, I swear, if you have a Xenon console, it's gonna die.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a matter of if, it's a matter of when.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a lot of FUs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Things are relatively well right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'll just say FU to money or lack thereof.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never having enough of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: FU to Disneyland being crowded yesterday.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's never fun to go on a crowded day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody else needs to go somewhere else when I'm there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess FU to the fact that I didn't get to spend enough time there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really was just like a fast, fast trip.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, things are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: If those are my FUs, then things are pretty well in my world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: A couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please make sure before you call us, echo 123 if you are on Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: You must, must, must test yourself first.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think even Skype puts in there now, click this button to make a test call.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to do that before you go on the radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, listen to the nice lady that says, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, welcome to the Skype call testing service.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to hear her before you hear us, so please do that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're using the phone, that's easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can just pick it up and call.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, but we're not taking the calls just yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got a couple more stories for you first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: One other thing that was announced during the PlayStation conference, and it wasn't necessarily the PlayStation phone...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the PlayStation Suite.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what the PlayStation Suite is, is actually a couple things.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, it's going to be a PlayStation store that's going to be available for Android phones.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll allow you to purchase different PlayStation games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and of course some of the games that they're mentioning that are going to be available are actually early PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cold Borders 2, Syphon Filter and Rallycross, Wild Arms and Medieval.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: or the Android iOS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we can't really say it's just for phones now since they do have tablets now with the Android iOS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I remember something about this is all going to tie into the NGP as well too, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so it's a way to get PlayStation content out there on more than just the PlayStation phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: But honestly though, I mean, just looking at, unless you have that PlayStation phone, I can imagine this is going to suck just because, I mean, just look at the controls.
[SPEAKER_03]: It takes up like so much screen space.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, touch controls are ridiculous too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need tangible buttons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget it otherwise, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one thing we've learned from iPhone gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very few iPhone games really, really work.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have to be designed for that touch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Things like Cut the Rope work because it's very easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Things like, I guess, Angry Birds, although I've never played it, work because it's based around the touch controls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Things like a port of Mega Man fail because you need tangible controls in order to be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say that Escaluda worked very well with touch controls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but that's because it has auto-fire and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did it without auto-fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually plays really well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Mushihime-sama was really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need tangible buttons.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that was all Sony's thing with the move.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't you like buttons?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, one more story for you guys before the Skype line tonight, and it has to do with World of Warcraft, but it's kind of an interesting one because you know where WoW goes, other MMOs tend to follow.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: WoW has gone after gold sellers in a whole new way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Paypal Paypal Paypal Paypal
[SPEAKER_09]: very interesting because you know these places are in other countries and so forth and they accept PayPal as a method of payment which you know a lot of folks don't want to give companies well folks shouldn't be using these fucking things in the first place but on the other hand you know when they do use them they don't want to use their real credit card info so they'll often use PayPal well now they've kind of cut off that bridge so I think that's kind of cool that they did that that was a smart way to go about doing it so yeah that's how they're going after it cut out the middleman
[SPEAKER_09]: and they could kind of strong arm PayPal too because I'm pretty sure they take PayPal as a method of payment for the game itself so they could tell PayPal either do this or we're going to stop taking your thing as a form of payment you know they could kind of strong arm them like that I'm not saying that's what they did but I could imagine that being part of the conversation
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but I mean, I think it's convenient to have it there if you want to get a little thing here or there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And certainly, you pay $10 and get 1,200 points, which I bought tons of stuff with my points.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that they need to be a little bit more judicious with what they will and won't accept via PayPal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I heart the guild.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, because they've helped you out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Find a guild.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't need to buy gold.
[SPEAKER_09]: Find a guild of nice people.
[SPEAKER_09]: And don't steal from your guild.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't steal from your guild.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're in the game to just profit profit and steal everything from your guild, then you're in the game for the wrong reasons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play the auction house game if money making is what you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Buy out a certain item and then sell it for triple.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's open up the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: The phones are open.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take your calls on any topic we've talked about tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you have a comment on the NGP itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you want to talk 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you want to talk about that whole PS3 hacking mess or something we haven't brought up yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever you want to talk about, the phones are open.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_09]: While we wait for those calls to come in, Loki, do you have any quick last minute stories for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, that Galactus video, that was someone that was playing on a pirated Xbox 360 version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Naughty, naughty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you can see the 360 in the background there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, some other fun stuff we could talk about here.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is kind of neat, we haven't mentioned this yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Platinum's new game that's coming out, Max Anarchy, well at least that's how it's known in other places, is coming over as Anarchy Reigns.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of an MMO brawler game, and it also features the main character from Mad World, but in full color this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's actually kind of in all the trailers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly though, I kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of like him better black and white.
[SPEAKER_03]: He doesn't look that cool when he's non-black and white.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's go to the phones and take some calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, since it's pretty much the topic of the night, I just want to chime in on the NGP or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever they end up calling it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, even though some people within the Dialgames community would like to pick me as a Sony fanboy, I'm a little hesitant to even consider getting the NGP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although the system does sound nice on paper, but the truth is, even with my PSP, I very rarely touch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, nowadays, I only use it for downloading podcasts and whatnot, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me back up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why did you abandon your PSP?
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it a lack of the games that you have to play, or what caused you, you think, to abandon... Or, I don't know, are you a DS player now, or what caused you to abandon the PSP?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was a DS player for a while, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had both systems, but truth be told, you know, there's more games on...
[SPEAKER_06]: The PS3 and the 360 that I would much rather play.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, on the 360, I constantly play Game Room.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on PS3, I play a lot of Super Stardust, HD, so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And between the two main consoles, there's more games on there that I'm interested in as opposed to handhelds.
[SPEAKER_06]: And considering that I'm on the budget, I have to watch...
[SPEAKER_06]: How much I spend on games and don't really have enough money to go all the way around.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would rather play my games on consoles as opposed to handhelds because really, isn't the point of handhelds to go out and buy a Play-Doh when you're not at home?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm usually home pretty much 24-7.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at first, yeah, I did play my PSP a lot initially, playing out like the Darkstalkers games and the ports of PS2 games, but I just generally found myself playing the system less and less.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of the price that freaks you out, too, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, because you mentioned that you have a very limited budget, kind of like I mentioned earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's just certain people, especially in this economy, this day and age, that don't have a lot of the extra money, and they kind of know this is going to be expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: So is it kind of like the price that scares you, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, basically, in a nutshell, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I live under $800 a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that basically...
[SPEAKER_06]: That basically, that $800 a month not even has to go towards rent, food, my time order bill, so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's not a lot of room for entertainment there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I can manage to keep my expenses low because the cost of living in Buffalo, New York is pretty low, but still, even with that, that leaves me with...
[SPEAKER_06]: roughly $200 a month that if I'm lucky I'm able to save and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact,
[SPEAKER_06]: It took me like a year just to save up for this netbook that I just recently got.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me ask you this, though, because obviously the system is expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think you would use or try to save up anyway for one of the competitors to a PSP2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there something that maybe interests you more about the 3DS or maybe even the iPad, you could say, as a competitor of the NGP, whatever it's called?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there either of those that maybe interest you more that you would save up for or no, I'm not interested in this wave of technology at all?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of hard to say just now because obviously all those systems aren't quite out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I do consider going out and buying any handheld whatsoever, whether it be 3DS or PSP2 or what have you, I would have to wait like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Just to pull a figure out, but let's say a year, year and a half.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait to see what comes up for whatever system and see if those games would interest me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then maybe, yeah, I'll consider getting them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if nothing of interest comes up for me, like at least bare minimum, I don't know, 15 games at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just say forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So in other words, it's the games that are on the system that are going to make it or break it for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and they would have to be like exclusive games, not found on the home systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: No ports of any kind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, truly exclusive stuff or...
[SPEAKER_09]: I hear you buddy it's you know our golden rule of gaming a system is only as good as the games that are on it so I think it's a smart approach for you know a budget gamer to wait and see you know let the people that have more disposable income kind of beta test everything for you I suppose so Spazinator I gotta let you go to get more calls but thank you as always and who knows maybe you'll win a contest at a local store maybe win one of these guys for free I'll be hoping for you alright have a good one buddy
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, 1-877-GAME-OLR is our number or our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt agrees in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: The price will be key.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bonds006 says, I am PC till death.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an interesting way of looking at it, especially from the whole budget perspective is that, well, I have this PC anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's tons and tons of games available on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why even bother with a handheld or even a console?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got everything I need right in my PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the way a lot of people look at it, surprisingly enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: 877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have any other last-minute stories, Loki, to hold us over?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we get more ringing rings?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just see here what I've got here.
[SPEAKER_09]: What can you pull out of your butt, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I pull out of my butt?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to know what Loki can pull out of his butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: I meant like story-wise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not actual.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: There wasn't a whole lot, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny, this week I was surprised that there wasn't a whole lot of news other than the PSP stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, other than that big press conference, that's really it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just kind of like, wow, isn't that NGP awesome?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder how much it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then 3DS was like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone remember about me?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I think by the time the 3DS comes out, that will change quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're saved.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can find something else for after this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hey!
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't heard from you in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind tonight, buddy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: but it's gotten a lot of controversy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Gal Gun for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gal Gun, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Set the stage.
[SPEAKER_09]: What type of game is Gal Gun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Gal Gun is a very perverted shooter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like a dating sim shooter, I should say.
[SPEAKER_03]: All dating sims should be shooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm interested so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's gotten a lot of controversy because Microsoft
[SPEAKER_07]: I posted a video in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of panty shots and a lot of questionable material in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So a friend of mine has a Japanese 360, so he bought it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we played it, and I felt immediately dirty afterwards.
[SPEAKER_03]: You spray your love on them, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game looks disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: This looks like Elebits, but with girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Little school girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure they're all 18 or over, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you also get to shoot teachers and all that, so... This looks like Elebits.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this like Elebits?
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that game on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what the funny thing when you mention that is?
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole game has the feeling of a Wii game that was rejected, but it was put out on the 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: They wouldn't give up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so usually games like this end up being crappy, and you said you felt dirty afterwards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was she tied up by a plant?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tentacles!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a boss battle in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the whole thing is centered around
[SPEAKER_07]: When you start the game, you have to choose a girl that you're interested in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now the whole thing is you're trying to go through your high school and all that to try to get with this girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you have to go through all these women who are going after you, hitting you with postcards, fans, you know, typical anime stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my goodness, postcards.
[SPEAKER_03]: He might get a paper cut.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what you're supposed to do is you're supposed to use a gun that shoots pheromones at the teenage girls
[SPEAKER_07]: that makes them drop down in ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's like your love gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's a love gun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, there's a special mode where you can zero in on a girl and shoot her at specific parts of her body.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there's like a Fallout 3 mode?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, there'll be parts where she'll try to stop you if you're zeroing in on certain things and
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you allowed to shoot these girls in the butt or do they not like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you can shoot them in the butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, it's funny because the game is so dynamic that different girls have different hot spots, I should say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you get an ecstasy bonus, as it's called.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's both.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's essentially both because it's just so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was looking at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people who made this game made a lot of kids' games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made, you know, the X-Men Zero series.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually made Mega Man 9 and 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, the whole thing is, you know, it's very...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, it's kind of tough to play because it's a dating sim and it's all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no English and it's never going to come in America.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're kind of guessing through the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of mini-games and bonus stages that are ridiculous, but
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, was that sheep?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, I think you need to bring a copy of this to the show one night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on, it's episode 400 next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you say?
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to import one of these real quick and get it over here to the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Expedite the shipping.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's bad, you know, I had to take a long bath after this just to
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure those girls have to take a long bath too to wash what they got off I'm watching them shoot the teachers I want this game I totally want this game I totally think you should get a game
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for the call, Matt, and bringing this game into our lives.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: I missed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I accidentally hung up on him early.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, Matt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't mean to.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use name on Skype, Orange National Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Akuma JP says, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: It does totally look like a rejected Wii game.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got time for a couple more calls, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you had another story for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh just real quick stuff uh no Kid Icarus or Zelda until after E3 yeah DarkSakura did report on that you were probably playing Grand Theft Auto no I wasn't playing Grand Theft Auto you were playing Gal Gun I was not playing Gal Gun um
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, we have like, Atlas is bringing out Divinity 2, the Dragon Knight Saga, which is kind of an update to Divinity 2 with all the extra bonuses.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out in May or April.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, there was some chatter earlier that accused me of never listening to Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to point out it's been proven it goes both ways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I never listen to any of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called multitasking.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how we do this live show where we interact with the chat room, talk to each other, and take calls like the call we have on the line right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hola, bienvenidos a Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, this is excellent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, how are you, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Doing good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what to say now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm flabbergasted compared to that last caller.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now it's just a one-up that I don't know if I can do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're becoming like the Ranma of the new year.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're getting on the show every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, if no one else is calling in... No, I try not to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't try to call unless one, you need to call, or two, I have something to call in about.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what does it happen to be tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: One or two?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, two actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, what do you have to talk about today?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to talk about the, uh, next gen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people talking about that today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the fact that, I think the price point's even scaring me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like what they...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was going to say, a lot of the things I liked when I saw, when I was watching the coverage as it came out, and I liked a little bit that I saw, and the fact that I could actually have a handheld that plays quality games of that of, like, the PS3, would be absolutely amazing, but the price point, the fact that I know it's going to come out, it's going to be like, oh, it's $799 or $800, so that's what's going to scare me more than anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one would be like...
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I'm going to have to put that on the back burner for like three years before getting in and trying to catch up with everybody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will never sell if it's over $500.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, this is the perfect time for us to kind of take a step back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's hop in the time machine and go back to five years ago, 2006.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: Back in 2006, it was the Sony E3 press conference.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kaz Harai Ridge Racer The essence of the PlayStation DNA is real change and the consumers are ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: Genji 2 is an action game which is based on Japanese history.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer Being based on history, the stages of the game will also be based on famous battles which actually took place in ancient Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's this giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you attack its weak point for massive damage.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_10]: PlayStation 3 will retail for 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_10]: Giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_10]: 599, 599, 599 US dollars.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ridge Racer Ridge Racer
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ridge Racer for the Xbox was the same as Ridge Racer 7, was the same as Ridge Racer on the PSP, was the same as Ridge Racer on... Well, actually, the PSP version was like 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the 3DS version is basically the same as Ridge Racer 7 and Ridge Racer 6.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not even putting any new effort into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, eh, let's put the game over.
[SPEAKER_09]: New cars?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's port the game over.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exometer Charm thinks that'll cost 599 US crabs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are historically accurate crabs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I'm sorry, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're getting away from what you wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did he hang... X-Link?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, it's better right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to keep it too long because it sounds like our connection is getting pretty bad here, so... Uh, well, so... No, I just wanted to say that, though, because, you know, a lot of people, you know, like, I'm in between jobs right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have $599 to spend.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do have a job and I don't have $599 US dollars to spend.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a little freaked out.
[SPEAKER_09]: This thing better blow me if it's going to be that much money.
[SPEAKER_01]: I better just do more than that.
[SPEAKER_01]: My God.
[SPEAKER_09]: This thing better come with a love gun or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, if they port Gal Gun to the NGP, yeah, I want it to talk dirty to me for $590.
[SPEAKER_09]: If there's a Gal Gun on the NGP, then I might be able to be talked into it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: this is going to be a fun year nonetheless for E3 and it's going to be a lot of fun because this is going to be probably the year of let's see who won the up to and what category and what area so yeah this is going to be a lot of fun is he shooting his love pheromones into that plant's mouth alright X-Link I'm sorry they're still fascinated with Gal Gun so I gotta let you go but have a good night and thanks for calling no problem
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, poor Inks fall on her from Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Gal Gun!
[SPEAKER_09]: Gal Gun!
[SPEAKER_09]: Now everybody in chat's just being dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're all being dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt says, Fleshlight attachment coming in June 2012.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, since you all are being dirty, let me bring this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you all heard of that show, My Strange Obsession, that's on TLC, the network that brings you hoarders and intervention?
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's got midgets or multiple kids, it's on our network.
[SPEAKER_09]: TLC now has the show My Strange Obsession where they like to show things like there was the chick that ate couch material.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: She had to eat the foam inside couches.
[SPEAKER_09]: A chick that slept with her blow dryer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saw that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this week, or maybe it was this last week, I don't know, they are going to have a guy who is infatuated with his real doll.
[SPEAKER_09]: his love doll that believes he is married to it or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what the deal was.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was something like he treats the doll like it's a real person and sleeps with it at night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't that a movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is real life, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is not like Weekend at Bernie's.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the real deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a, remember it was with, I don't remember the guy's name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nah, I think I know which one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was that Simone about the virtual chick that comes to life?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: De Niro was in that, but that movie went straight to video.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, there was a movie about this guy who had a love doll or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was him and the whole town kind of pretended it was real.
[SPEAKER_03]: For no reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like a dumbass movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those fucking artsy films.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one of those things I was like, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to go see that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something the wife made you watch?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I forgot to mention!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gaming Week, totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week we had this kind of a kickoff for the 2011 year type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do like a
[SPEAKER_03]: People from different branches out and stuff, and they're doing these team-building events and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: From Salacious Pop, Lance and the Real Girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, because I'm too lazy to look that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they had a bunch of Connect Adventure games that we were competing in teams for high scores, and we win stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'd like to say...
[SPEAKER_03]: That two out of the three days, we kicked the crap out of everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: The third day, or actually I should say the first day, we would have won had we played together, both myself and my co-worker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, we were on separate teams with other people, which is why we lost.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we won like $80 worth of movie passes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice, what movie are you taking me to?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we don't go to see movies very often, so when we do go, we're going to get popcorn, hot dogs, $60 in bulk candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a matter of time before your kid's going to want to go see every Disney movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe a couple years, but still.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, a couple years.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just thought it was funny that we kicked the crap out of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, you're the video game team.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're supposed to kick the crap out of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys who got through.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you didn't get through, you can always email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we're going to go ahead and start to wrap up the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little early, but I guess it wasn't outside of the NGP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a whole lot to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can just have an extra long afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, and by the way, the chat room is yelling it's actually Lars and the real girl, not Lance.
[SPEAKER_09]: And SalaciousPop says, it's actually really good, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard it was actually good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just looked dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought tonight is, it's like I'm walking on sunshine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I never would have thought that Pandora would introduce me to a bunch of awesome music that I never would have heard of thanks to Pandora.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it also introduced me to a lot of crappy music and music that I've heard of numerous times.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a little difficult to hit the thumbs up and thumbs down while driving my car.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you guys so much for downloading our show and checking us out.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you've enjoyed Orange Lounge Radio, all we ask you guys, tell a couple people about our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Word of mouth is how we spread the word.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how we've been doing it for the past nine years.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're not able to advertise in video game magazines or have E3 booths or have any of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't have a full-fledged team bringing news to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: This isn't our day jobs.
[SPEAKER_09]: We work very hard with balancing our family lives and all that stuff in this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a pity story.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if you're like, I hate every single show on all games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a real picky bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's got to be something in the indie universe that's for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So support independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We will see you back here next week for episode number...
[SPEAKER_09]: 400 OMG.
[SPEAKER_09]: Until then, good night.
[SPEAKER_05]: or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!