[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight, January 23, 2011, the 3DS US launch gets some details, Final Fantasy games get sequels and new names, and after over a decade, we finally have a release date for Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are live with our 398th episode on this January the 23rd of 2011.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts, joining you every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: With me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have hobbit shoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why am I not hearing you at all?
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I muted?
[SPEAKER_07]: The fabulousness of live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm wearing my hobbit shoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is the hobbit shoes?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Vibram Five Finger multi-sport shoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're the shoes that look like feet.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not really shoes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take a picture.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like Spiderman webbing that go on your feet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're foot gloves.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're the strangest things I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're comfortable and when they break in they're supposed to be really good for your feet and give you a natural stride.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you play DDR in those?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen people do it before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play some Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shake your booty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to play Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to play Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Dance Central's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Para, para.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance Masters gets old after like the first five songs you play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see if Tech Master Loki cares.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care about Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we don't hear you either.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called ill preparation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what this is all about tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus that mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something's up with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been getting quieter and quieter every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because I'm talking quieter and quieter.
[SPEAKER_07]: They get really loud!
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why we have to be careful how we tune it for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do that on purpose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, how's your week been, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything exciting going on with the baby?
[SPEAKER_07]: Growing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting older?
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting older.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's eating some... He's starting solid foods, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw the avocado post.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's eating avocado, rice cereal, and... What else?
[SPEAKER_07]: When's it okay to start feeding a baby bacon?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: What a bummer.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's getting... Well, it's avocado, rice cereal, and... Cheerios!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's actually it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Avocado and rice cereal.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then he's going to be eating... I think carrots this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just fabulous.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our 400th episode is going to be the same day as the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if we really have anything exciting planned, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just, I don't know, it's just, after this long... I have something exciting planned.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you've got a little something.
[SPEAKER_02]: But both of you need to actually stay instead of depart super quick after the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've offered I don't know how many times, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not the one I'm worried about, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I made level 75 on World of Warcraft and got two of my friends to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm the dealer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Pyramid Scheme, I say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pyramid Head Scheme.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played some Portal and some more Mushihime-sama and lots of Solitaire because I was at school.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I updated and installed my own Linux Mint 10 by myself on two computers and fixed the networking problems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I know I've heard you talk favorably of Linux Mint before as something you like to use as another OS besides just Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is the advantage, I guess, of doing Linux on one system and Windows on the other?
[SPEAKER_02]: Specifically in the case of my netbook, it uses less memory and less space.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I need to, I can actually boot it off of a USB that I've installed Linux on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, say that this computer that I'm on now, say that something goes haywire in it, all I have to do is boot it off Linux and I can run through the file system, and if I need to delete something, I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works on everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's it for DarkSakura's Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll move on over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: How was your Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played a couple things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried, I don't know, just the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried that one free game that was made by that 14-year-old or something like that, some bubble something or other.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was okay for a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, wow, this looks like a really cheaply made game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I got bored with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you think it's doing so well?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is that iPhone, iTouch game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, because people like fucking human interest stories, and because people are simpletons, and they like free shit, and as long as it has a good storytelling, well, I better support it, because a 14-year-old made it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, 14-year-olds make a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: These are the same people who like Angry Birds, so, you know, what am I... It's not a stretch for them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Then I literally dusted off my PS3 to finally put the 500... Those things are dust magnets.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't dust them off.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'll turn gray.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so I dusted it off, and I finally installed my 500 gig hard drive that I had for it, and then I did the noble thing, and I installed a custom firmware on it, and now all my systems are modded as they should be.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're so proud.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was seriously the black sheep of the bunch, and now it's all perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I've read stories about systems bricking and stuff like that, but seriously, if you just wait a little bit to make sure everything's okay, let the dust settle, you're all good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So easy to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's seriously scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I did that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then played a little bit of Planet 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a few levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, just one online level.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like LittleBigPlanet 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And LittleBigPlanet 2, obviously very similar to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have some new features that they added in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really care for the grappling hook too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know if it's just the design of the DualShock 3 analog sticks or something like that, but for some reason, I was having issues with it trying to swing my character back and forth and having the grappling hook change length, which would normally be controlled by the up and down on the analog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I'm not pushing up and down on the analog, it was just very... The dead zones for it were really...
[SPEAKER_06]: Really large, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was difficult to accurately get it to swing and adjust the size of the grappling hook and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it actually killed my character one time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's alright, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I played someone's user-created levels, the first-person shooter Resident Evil thing, and that was actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely different and a good indicator of what you can do with LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there was also a top-down RPG game that someone made, which I tried out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: so um lots of unique stuff and I like how they're kind of hinting at some of the things that you can do in like the first few levels like they have the ability where you can link two different levels together or more than two levels together so like for example say you want to create you know like a Mario Brothers game you can do that you can create all the different levels and just link them all together and I'm sure it's only a matter of time before somebody does create Mario Brothers in LittleBigPlanet it's probably already happened actually oh I'm sure it already has
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been trying to play it for the longest time, but trying to be able to play a game on my big TV is not really working out for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully, though, and this will also kind of help out with...
[SPEAKER_06]: If I have to ever stream DJ Hero 3 or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a new capture card for my laptop that I can just plug in USB.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it allows me to play games and just hook straight up to my laptop and I can play it off the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: No lag.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that'll give me an additional screen to play a little Big Planet on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to our chatroom at chat.orange.radio.com There's some people that are asking about your hacking habits.
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf says, Now you never have to pay for another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is a very tongue-in-cheek comment from BlackWolf because he's actually very anti-video game piracy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, Loki, you do still buy games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You bought, what, like seven copies of Grand Theft Auto 4 on various systems or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like you don't pay for games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So then I guess this leads to the question from AkumaJP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what is the benefit of custom firmware for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, you can play all the different homebrew stuff that they have on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can add different features to your system.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just really early, so a lot of the stuff we don't know yet what you're going to be able to do with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yes, there's definitely the backing up portion of it that you can back up games and pirate stuff if you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will I do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not, because I had the ability to jailbreak my PS3 for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had the tools to do it, but I just didn't... There was no reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I literally sat there going, well, I could do this and pirate a bunch of games, but there's no real games I want to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like, that's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I really don't want to... If there's nothing I really want to play on there, then I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: but as long as I've known you and as long as I've been doing this show with you you've always kind of been the type to me that just likes to do it because you can like you know because somebody's like you're not supposed to hack your PS3 to be able to run this and you're you're very much the type that's like well yes I can you know I'm gonna do it anyway pretty much yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that it for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I wanted to ask you something about Little Big Planet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Little Big Planet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mentioned there's some new features and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was one of the first things that jumped out to you you noticed was different about the game from Little Big Planet 1?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean the springboards, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was like the first thing that they show that's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like it did import my character and all my stuff they had collected in the first game, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't... There's not a lot right now that's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a few different things, but I mean, I know that the game is going to be really... Because it's kind of... I'm still going through the first few levels of the game, or the tutorial levels, you know, so they haven't really introduced a ton of stuff yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just very much like the first game right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: but that's alright because the first game was awesome I do like how they had some voice acting in the game like the cutscenes, the cutscenes are actually very unique and then also like how and I'm not sure if the Da Vinci character or whatever is voiced by John Cleese but it sounds like it and then later on because they only have voice acting through the cutscenes through the rest of the game he's just kind of mumbling and it sounds like John Cleese mumbling which is kind of funny
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought they had gotten his talent to voice something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it was that, but maybe a different... No, it was Fable 3 I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he was the butler.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's for the phones and it's basically a DOS emulator for the iPhone and what you can do is that there's various like DOS games that were actually kind of included in the little store that come with it like Duke Nukem the original side scroller is in it and Wolfenstein 3D the shareware episode is available there and so on and let's see I can actually fire up I'm going to fire up Wolfenstein 3D here real quick on the phone so you can kind of see this and
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing that kind of sucks about it, which actually is a really big drawback, is that, again, the iPhone makes for a shitty controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: A very shitty controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially when there's like eight different buttons on here to be able to play this, which is next to impossible.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can kind of like... I don't know if you can hear the old school AdLib sound effects there in the mic, but... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: The only one I wanted to get that got pulled immediately was Minecrafted, which was the Minecraft client for... Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even know they had that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was very brief.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be coming back later, but it was a leaked version of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny that you mentioned Duke Nukem and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Duke Nukem was on the store, I think, already, and then Wolfenstein's actually available through, well, through Cydia if you have a jailbroken device.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I know hella people jailbreak their iPhone and they even came out in the courts and said that you can or whatever, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm all paranoid about that stuff because this thing is like my life, my texting, my phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't have it go wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not worth it to relive Wolfenstein 3D all over again, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of my perspective on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so that was really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Otherwise, just more of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, WoW, Pac-Man, the new Championship Edition Deluxe, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's it for my week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some quick housekeeping before we get into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can, of course, follow us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're also available on Facebook at Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course we do tape live at All Games Radio, AllGames.com every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwell Show.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ever do want to come in and join a live episode, please do join us sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you can sync your iPhone with a PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were saying use it as a router for a controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you don't even have to really necessarily do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some actual homebrew programs through like Cydia and stuff like that allows you to sync a Wii Remote to your iPod or iPad to play Nintendo or Super Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just not worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too much work for not enough payoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on to tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will start off with, of course, the one and only Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, so it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were trying to find a buyer for Bizarre Entertainment or Bizarre Creations or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And unfortunately, Activision was unable to do so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, dude, they put out some pretty awesome racing games and hell, they had a pretty awesome arcade shooter game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe no one wanted to buy the developer of the original Project Gotham games and Geometry Wars, which was huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft, hello!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm shocked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shocked.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyways, this is kind of a trend if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, no buyers for Harmonix either, other than themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, maybe just people aren't snapping up...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you expect?
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is Activision's fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is plainly their fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you expect when you release a okay first-person shooter the week before Black Ops?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: You expect it to do well?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: They expect it to die.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could have done a lot better if it was released in a different part of the year or next year or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it really was, oh, well, we have the license to the Bond series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, crap, they're not making another movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we need to make some money off of this license we paid for, so let's make a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And ironically, now they are making another Bond movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't they announce that a couple weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're just making another game?
Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not bizarre.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just such a bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I had heard somewhere, I don't remember, it was earlier in the week, so forgive me if my memory is a little rusty, but there's some type of new tax in, I don't know if it's Britain, the greater part of Britain, or if it's just this area that the Bizarre Creation studio is in that has something to do with video games that actually may have had an impact that maybe was too expensive to keep these guys up and running where they're at now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of those, you know, it's cheaper to get folks in another country to do the development or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, they're basically recommending that they close them now is the recommendation, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess they recently did the same thing with Budcat in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm hoping that, you know, it's one of those for every door that closes and other opens type of scenarios where at least these guys might get, you know, on their feet somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or maybe they'll do that thing where they start up their own darn studio, which we've seen a lot of developers in the past do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try some different ideas.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe that means there's never going to be another Geometry Wars game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really like that series.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ain't really going to improve upon that, I mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you could look at it that way but I and I guess technically what Activision would own that so they could always have one of their other developing houses do it but I don't know just it wouldn't be the same yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com for some comments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isam in our chatroom says, this is probably a time where they would rather purchase intellectual properties to re-release rather than take on new employees.
[SPEAKER_07]: AlphaCanadagram says, WTF?
[SPEAKER_07]: Geometry Wars 2 was the shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree, Geometry Wars 2 is awesome and it's kind of a bummer but maybe since the Xbox Live Arcade especially and I guess to some extent the PlayStation Network is pretty easy to develop for I mean, I don't know, I'm not a video game developer but I am assuming that what, the folks that put out Super Meat Boy not exactly a large development studio, correct?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wasn't it like three or four different people kind of buds getting together doing this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted it's not on PlayStation Network but it could have been because I think they have some dealio with Microsoft
[SPEAKER_07]: so my hope maybe these guys that end up losing their stuff at Bazaar can kind of go and develop maybe for these smaller platforms like handhelds and Xbox Live Arcade the Geometry Wars-esque sort of games or whatever other ideas they might have because you know Blur was a pretty good idea too that was a
[SPEAKER_07]: I really think if there had been a Blur 2 it would have been awesome Blur 1, it was a good game but it did need some work but I love that idea of the arcade racer meets Mario Kart and the commercials for that were always so awesome where it was the little Mario Kart cute characters that are practically getting run over by the adult cars or better yet, make it an arcade game
[SPEAKER_07]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_07]: Derek H in our chatroom seems to agree with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope the people from Bizarre reform a new studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope so too, or at least a good portion of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear Respawn's hiring.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never know what might happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, moving on to some other news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this has something to do with kind of like basement development, if you will, on a very large scale.
[SPEAKER_07]: StarCraft II, of course, you know, has some very flexible development materials, we'll say, in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people have been able to make all sorts of games within StarCraft II.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, there's an endorsed by Blizzard shooter that's actually in the game, like a shoot-em-up type game that's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: StarCraft Universe StarCraft Universe
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there were some teasers that were up on the internet and they got pulled pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blizzard put the smackdown on those and took them down.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a lot of people were saying, Boo, Blizzard, you guys are a bunch of bastards for taking this stuff down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_07]: And the modder who created this, Ryan Winzel, even kind of went on his own forum saying, I don't really know what's going on right now, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is all kind of developing at a fast pace.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Activism Blizzard is actually not trying to shut down this mod altogether, but I think the problem that they're having is that it's the World of Starcraft name that they don't like.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't want this guy making his mod called World of Starcraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it looks like this MMO is actually going to continue on, but under a new name.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Ryan Wenzel, the modder, has actually been invited by Blizzard to go meet the Starcraft 2 development team.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, this whole thing expanded so fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was also invited by the folks that made the MMO League of Legends.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you've seen that, but that's like Defense of the Ancients.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that is a game I did get to see like 15 seconds of a little bit this weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my friends is into that, and it's like a Defense of the Ancients kind of like game, the old mod.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people that make that invited this guy to go interview with him.
[SPEAKER_07]: So his net celebrity went up exponentially real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cool that he was invited by Blizzard, though, because Blizzard was like, dude, dude, dude.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not the mod we're not cool with.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the name.
[SPEAKER_07]: So hopefully they're going to be able to work this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blizzard wanted to make it clear.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was never our intention to stop development on the mod, but with the name so closely resembling that of World of Warcraft, we wanted to discuss the title of the mod with the developer.
[SPEAKER_07]: And as part of our routine procedure, we contacted YouTube to request the video be removed while that discussion took place.
[SPEAKER_07]: Such a little politically correct way of saying that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's like we're not trying to be jerks, but no.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all branding and identity.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think what's going on here, the unsaid part too, is it's a lot of that big company syndrome where I'm sure the developers actually kind of had their eyebrows raised going, that's kind of cool what this kid did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whereas the legal team and the protections of all this were like, hell no, shut it down.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't protect it, you lose it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think whereas the development team was like, yeah, come on over and play with us for a day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see what you're up to.
[SPEAKER_07]: The legal team was like, hell no, you need to shut it down under this name.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of interesting how that all works together.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds very corporate to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what else is stupid?
[SPEAKER_07]: What is stupid?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, basically, they were talking to Kotaku and said that they didn't see any reason to put in some sort of trophy or achievement system because they don't want to tell people how to play the games to get some kind of, quote, mythical reward.
[SPEAKER_02]: The U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: exec Bill Trennan quoted saying, basically, the way the games are designed is they're designed for you to explore the game yourself and have a sense of discovery.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's like, we don't want to give you directions on what to do in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want you to find everything on your own.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they said that they're not really against the idea of trophies.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just don't want it to be the whole purpose for playing the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They believe that except for Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_02]: In which case they don't care about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I said.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are not against them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that they don't want that to be the full basis of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't think they want to license the rights to... You know how a lot of these people copyright different things or have patents for trophy systems and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They probably just don't want to license that crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea and neither do I care.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just they...
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of think it's interesting that they went on a limb to say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since everybody else is doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once Xbox started having it, PlayStation had it, and they have them in MMOs and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even on our phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to not embrace something that's popular right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Online gameplay, whatever, we don't need that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trophies, we don't need that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Organized community, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get this story and all, but it strikes me a little bit as a reason that's invented after the fact.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, the Wii simply was not programmed to have this type of functionality in it, and I sort of get that because the Wii doesn't have anything like Xbox Live, like PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no centralized Wii service, except for, granted, Wii Connect 24, the thing that lets you send the mails and all that stuff, and the friend code to play online.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't know, like, it just...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know enough about how computers talk to each other and how the internet actually works, but it doesn't strike me as quite the centralized system that the other two are.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be patched in later if they really wanted to.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did it with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or they're launching a new console.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they could kind of roll it out with that if they wanted to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just feel like there might be a little more value in virtual console, especially if they're going to try to get us to buy the same games again on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: to have some type of trophy room for actually having played these games and getting scores on them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, even if it's just a freaking high score table, fuck, I'd take Game Center over nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Game Center, not that great, but it's better than... I also personally don't care about achievements myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just play the games to enjoy them and have fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do, I get that, but it's sort of like, it's kind of nice to have that little pat on the back.
[SPEAKER_07]: To have that in your portfolio.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only reason I've tried to get any achievements in World of Warcraft is for the experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, I've got experience points for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get experience points for doing like quests and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got them for getting the exploration ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, because you get experiences.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other than that, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I laughed at that one because I thought it was funny, but other than that, it was like, okay, someone did something that they were going to be doing anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, since you bring that up, Blizzard also doesn't really have a centralized server for achievements.
[SPEAKER_07]: This came up on a previous episode of Horde House.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't link your StarCraft and your Warcraft achievements together right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe when Diablo comes out, there'll be some type of Blizzard centralized thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, that'll only ever be for Blizzard games It's never going to connect to the Steam And all the Steam achievements I get that it's starting to get a little fragmented It is a little silly that you have your set on the Wii And your set on the 360 and the PlayStation 3 And it really should just be about beating the game start to finish But I don't know, I sort of like having that little sticker in my book That says, you did something really weird in this game Rob, I know how we can fix that problem How?
[SPEAKER_06]: We send out patches.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm pretty sure that's where the whole idea of achievements on the 360 came from in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really a bummer, actually, that when they did Game Room, you didn't have any type of resurgence of this, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess there were the little trophies in Game Room, but it wasn't quite the same, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because patches are expensive, and if a publisher doesn't have to make unnecessary expenses like that, they won't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Spaginator in our chatroom says I wonder if they'll ever be a Diablo MMO It's kind of World of Warcraft actually When I first played World of Warcraft I was feeling a lot more Diablo than I was Warcraft Because Warcraft is an RTS And World of Warcraft really isn't So it's interesting Derek H says he had a patch for Barnstorming And DefectiveCandy says my grandfather had one of those patches So some people remember those patches
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, see, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how awesome it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: People are still talking about them today.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, if they did that now, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: People would be talking about them for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now, missed opportunity.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all about cash now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, what else is in the news, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: 3DS 3DS 3DS
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really certain on which games are going to make the launch, although two that have been nailed down in the launch period by Nintendo, coming from Nintendo, unfortunately are Pilotwings and Nintendogs Plus Cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked Pilotwings back on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looked neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Pilotwings game looked neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendogs and Cats...
[SPEAKER_06]: I know the game's gonna suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be awesome to try, but I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I know I will get bored with it so quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_07]: I know exactly what you mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like the original Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You read about it on paper and all the features they're putting in.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're like, oh man, this sounds like it's going to be really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I just know it, just like the first Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I buy the game and it's going to be dumb after 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to feed it every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to play with it every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendogs is kind of, at least the original one, is kind of an overblown Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The original Nintendogs has a lot in common with a Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't explain it, but it's what it feels like to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the interesting things that they were talking about, which is kind of weird, is the system actually has a pedometer built into it and you get coins by walking around.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you earn coins that you can spend in games for different things.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then they have an activity log or whatever attracts your gameplay as well as your steps.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're also talking about how you can make Miis in the interface and they have that cool feature where you can take a picture of yourself and they give you a bunch of different options for Miis and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can import your Miis from the Wii
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can't go the other way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just because it's... Well, because they say it's more complex than the Wii system.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one on the 3DS is Wii 2.0.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and it makes sense because if you think about it though, like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you guys think about that price point?
[SPEAKER_07]: $250 for a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that's fair?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think it's too much?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there's some people on the internet that say, you know what, that's too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it makes sense because they're not going to really have any competition right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guarantee that thing will be selling for a lot more than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not going to be able to find these things.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you get your orders in while you can and if you're savvy enough, buy two and sell one on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the price point is actually better than what I was expecting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was going to be 3DS, $300 was what I was originally thinking they were going to do with it, but no, this is actually lower than I thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's right at what I expected, based on what they put out the end retail price.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it kind of leaves them a little room to lower it later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like if they want to do a cut for Christmas, they probably will.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they could cut it to 200 by Christmas with some type of package.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they will.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they need to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be like the Wii where it was in short supply for a very long time and they're not going to cut that thing for at least a year.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It brings money.
[SPEAKER_06]: The price cut will come when probably a new system revision will come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guarantee you that thing will not be dropping in price by the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every kid will want one, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every freaking kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 3D without glasses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: People are like, oh, it's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: People are just going to be blown away by just seeing the actual screens.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to be blown away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even want to quote certain analysts, but there's people out there that have said they could have charged more than that and they could have still sold all the units that they had.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking at some of the comments in our chat room GameGuru says 250 is a bit too expensive for a handheld game system Tigerclaw says when you put the 3DS with the PSP Go from the price standing point the 3DS has the most features How much was the PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Was the PSP Go 250 as well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but see, okay, there's a difference with the PSP Go and the 3DS, okay
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and you couldn't buy games for it in stores so it had people scratching their heads like why do you want me to get this there's no enhancements to it other than onboard storage which memory is so cheap nowadays it doesn't matter there's no UMD drive so I can't play any of the games I normally have right now there's no way for me to convert them into a digital format I have to re-buy my games if I want to buy the system um
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some Bluetooth support, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the thing is, and this is the best part, their retail partners or whatever, like GameStops and stuff like that, or just mom and pop shops, they weren't bringing them in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, GameStop might have because they have better partnerships with these guys, but individual mom and pop shops were not bringing them in because what money are they going to make off it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The system they're making no money on.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me get to a couple more 3DS stories here and we'll kind of continue this discussion because there are some other interesting developments in the 3DS world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of it has to do with online play.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, did you hear that the friend codes are getting reduced to one friend code?
[SPEAKER_07]: So sadly, friend codes aren't going away, but it's one friend code for everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you won't have a separate friend code.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I still don't like the idea of a friend code, but I understand that they want that in there so that the rapists can't rape our children through the internet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hide your kids.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hide your wife.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still don't get why you can't just have a name instead of a 16-digit randomized code.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's a step in the right direction, but when Nintendo is already three steps behind when it comes to online play, that news kind of just makes me go, whatever, Nintendo, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: it's a good thing you figured the 3D thing out because I don't know otherwise but that is I guess whatever at least you only have the one friend code despite the fact that it'll not really be something customizable it is supposed to show you what your friends are playing though
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds like a little better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and there's apparently an app in it that will show you what the status is of your friends at any time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can see what they're playing or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: So a little more like you're familiar with Xbox Live, even though it's in an app.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the other thing, though, that is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to be fair, I should say this when it comes to friend codes.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you are connected to another friend local on the local wireless, you can push a button to accept or send a friend request, and you won't ever have to exchange a number.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 3DS will just automatically grab...
[SPEAKER_07]: and there you have it, your friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's, okay, now that's a little better.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you will, and you're at a convention, you can push a button and get gang raped by friend requests.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but it has to be a mutual button pressing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's a mutual button pressing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Meaning you both have to accept the request.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a big old friend request gang bang.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, the next Penny Arcade Expo or E3, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the 3DS will be out by this year's E3, so it's going to be kind of interesting to see how.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I know E3 is not so much a fan event as it is a trade-slash-journalism event, but still, there's going to be, you know how many fanboys still manage to go to E3 because there are blogs and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, there'll be plenty of that exchanging and stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if they're going to have like a booth like they did back when the DS was new where you could kind of do the download of the demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: That used to be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how I played Meteos for the first time, which is still one of my favorite DS games to this day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Electroplankton
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it was Shane or somebody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some people left their DS on and plugged in after E3 was over so they wouldn't lose the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some people had it for up to a week after the show was over just to still play it more.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a great puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, another quick story about the 3DS, and this has to do with the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did confirm, I mean, we kind of already knew this, but just a confirmation, Game Boy and Game Boy Color games will be coming to the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Land is the first confirmed, which, by the way, blows compared to other Mario games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't even play like other Mario games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have a fireball, you have this random ball that bounces off walls.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like this Egyptian theme.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it was supposed to be Mario game at first.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was supposed to be something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Mr. Do.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, well, okay, yeah, the weapon is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the gameplay is still like a Mario game, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, Super Mario Land is confirmed.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word about advanced games, because keep in mind there's no longer an advanced slot on these things.
[SPEAKER_07]: So no word yet if that's coming in the future or what.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe something not about the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: This actually has to do with... Well, it has something to do with Nintendo, but not specifically Nintendo's side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yoshinori Ono, who is the producer of Street Fighter 4, said he wants to make Nintendo vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, he's, uh, quoted as saying that he wants to, uh, pitch it to, um, Masahiro Sakurai, who is the, uh, um, creator of Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I think that that would actually be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're already doing Marvel vs. Capcom 3, and then we have, uh, Tekken and Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you like to have Jigglypuff farting on Blanca or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be really odd.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they would ever do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would kind of be a dopey game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of dopey games out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't necessarily mean that in a bad way.
[SPEAKER_02]: If something's going to work with Nintendo, it's going to have to be like... I think Namco would do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the Tekken games had weird characters like Gon and Yoda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't you just
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that'll be the most that you see come of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think in a full Marvel vs. Capcom or even Tatsunoko vs. Capcom kind of way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless they do all the cutesy characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe all the cutesy Capcom characters could do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cutesy Capcom battle!
[SPEAKER_02]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_06]: Tatsunoko vs. Capcom would be awesome with like a Mario character or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I could see them doing maybe like Link or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like they ported Marvel vs. Capcom 3 or something to the Wii or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could add Link in there and just like Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that maybe, maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_15]: Super Chibi 3D Capcom Fighter.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be the game that comes of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know Capcom did Pakato Fighter.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep, so it's been done.
[SPEAKER_07]: anything's possible I suppose so Ed Seaton Beaver in our chatroom says I mean Capcom characters would fuck up the stupid Nintendo characters I don't know though couldn't Kirby just go and you know just kind of have his way with the Capcom characters he does suck
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let the fanboy wank begin after that story, but I don't think anything will come of it except maybe in the next Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: game, which will probably be on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and everyone will get a big ol' heart on about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, you can play it on the Wii, friend code, across galaxies and locally, and oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Mii's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Watch that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be a Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: fighter thingy on the stinking DS and your Mii will be a character.
[SPEAKER_06]: That wasn't in the Wii version?
[SPEAKER_07]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been years since I've played it at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the little adventure part of that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The adventure stuff was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a really cool part of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on with some release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Travel the world and see what's coming out to a console near you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a lot of stuff coming out this week, but there is a couple good things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead Space 2 coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC, as well as the collector's editions with the wonderful replica gun in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paws and Claws Marine Rescue on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two Worlds 2 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, as well as the Royal Edition of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: and Lord of Arcana on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That, I believe, is it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to take a look here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, that is it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we do things a little out of order and go to UK dates?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, my thing wasn't loading, but it just popped up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I blame your thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid thing!
[SPEAKER_07]: Dream Club Zero and Gal Gun are both coming out very soon on the 360 over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I hear
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Though... Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't... I have to recover that account.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out on the PlayStation 3, Dragon Age Origins gets its Japanese release.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know that's a long time after we had it, but they've probably localized quite a bit for Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it took a little while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on the PlayStation 3 this week, Mindjack comes out, Shooting Studio, and Wizardry Twin Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, is that like the old school C64 Wizardry games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a new version of it?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're RPG games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, I think these might be new versions of that old school game from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very, very text heavy in Japanese though, so you better be fluent in Japanese if you're going to import that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see that Zork is on good old games now?
[SPEAKER_07]: I had heard about that, but you know, I can't justify paying what they want for Zork.
[SPEAKER_07]: you know what I mean plus I had the whole resurgence you could play Zork on GameTap like back when GameTap was cool when Turner owned it you could play the Zork games and you know I kind of got my fill of retro back then and now I'm over it on the Nintendo Wii huge week on the Wii huge gigantic monumental week on the Wii the last story comes out this week that is a huge game I would be so excited if this game would come out in the US they have said nothing about it yet
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: What are they going to talk about on the Wii at E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least this would be something to hold people over because, again, if you don't know what this game is and why I'm so excited about it, it's a Mistwalker RPG on the Wii and the graphics actually look pretty phenomenal compared to the 360 and PS3 considering the Wii's
[SPEAKER_07]: MissedWalker
[SPEAKER_07]: but nothing about when it's coming out over here if ever besides that coilo comment that Loki already referenced just to like kind of put this in perspective when you look at like Japanese releases for February there are four games actually three because one of them is a collector's pack
[SPEAKER_07]: Three games coming out in February.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is, right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo of France.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says they have no plans to localize the last story.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just fucking France.
[SPEAKER_06]: No plans at the moment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't listen to the guy from France.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says the adaptation of this game could be very long.
[SPEAKER_06]: 12,000 dialogues.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it says it has 12,000 dialogues.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen up, Nintendo of France.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to surrender to the idea of having last story.
[SPEAKER_06]: And their translation teams are overstretched in the short term.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doing what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hackers will do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hackers will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hackers going to hack.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hackers are going to translate this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hackers are going to hack.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it will happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will get released.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that will piss people off.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't trust some guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: If Reggie Fils-Aim had come out and said it's not happening, then I'd believe it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some random executive with Nintendo of France says it and we're all supposed to accept that as the final word, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I say no.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they followed it up with, I fought in your general direction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, not a lot going on in the DS either, but this is a little more understandable, of course, because we have three DS on the horizon in February.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there are a couple puzzle games and then a game called Sora no Otoshimono Forte Dreamy Season in regular and deluxe editions.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an adventure game that's coming out with three chibi little cartoony babes on the cover.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like it might be some type of card game, but I do want to point out that this chick is not wearing pants in the screenshot.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's wearing gym uniform.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, it looks like she's not wearing pants to me She's not wearing pants, she's wearing shorts Fine They're bloomers They're very short shorts They're bloomers
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they have to be agile.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lastly, on the PS3, I'm sorry, PSP, Toaru Majutsu no Kinsho Mokuroku comes out from ASCII this week, which that game, it's a futuristic world with magic powers.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like Dissida, but just with general characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this game might catch people's attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: Valkyria Chronicles 3 Unrecorded Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_07]: That comes out on PSP this week, so I'm sure that'll have its fans.
[SPEAKER_07]: and importers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now we can go to the UK, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 25th, we have Dead Space for the iPhone, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 28th, though, we have Dead Space 2 for PS3, PC, Xbox 360 and Mario Sports Mix and Yogi Bear the video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen the alternate ending, quote unquote, on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where Boo Boo shoots Yogi Bear?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the alternate ending to the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would mean you'd have to go see the movie, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I would hate to see that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just look it up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand that, but I don't want to even try to pretend to see that movie or part of the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's all the sad music and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Yogi Bear sees the little wanted ad for himself or whatever up on the wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Boo Boo looking all sad and pointing the gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: All this sad music.
[SPEAKER_07]: God.
[SPEAKER_07]: This, by the way, I started it like a minute and a half into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, seriously, who did that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because that's... I know, it looks... Some people say it might be a viral thing for the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: That they're saying it's independent, but it was actually like a viral thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there's the bear skin rug at the very end.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura's rolling her eyes so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: See now, if that movie had that kind of humor, like it was an adult movie with violence and titties How do you have titties in a Yogi Bear movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you had violence and titties in there, that might be a cool movie
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember titties being in the old cartoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember the cartoon being raped across.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was now, but I don't remember it being terrible like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, the chat room is asking for a link.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to get one for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: But let's get back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we finish UK dates?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get back into some news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just don't understand why we can't have violence and titties in Yogi Bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was an Xbox 360 dashboard update this week, which pissed me off because that delayed me from playing my Grand Theft Auto game for a good half an hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because our internet's really slow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the first thing I was worrying about is, is console amusing going to get banned?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's flashed and not hot swapped like the rest of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I got lazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, that wasn't the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually a small update to restore, I guess, the planned launch or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically the option where you can have the disk in the drive and when you start the system up it will actually play the game instead of going to the dashboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was something I guess that broke in the last dashboard update.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they will have a second update later this week because I guess they just didn't have time to finish the update to darken, I guess, your gamertag pictures or whatever it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead of it being on green or something, now it's on dark gray.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and the other thing... Let it change.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other thing is it also broke the ability to play backups of Call of Duty Black Ops, Mario Warfare 2, and of course, Halo Reach.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also known as the real reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the real reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: What it did was it added the... What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The API 2.5 checks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's what they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a new...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess an authenticity check that they've been adding to some new games to make sure they're not backed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if, for example, you're playing one of these games and it happens to be backed up, your console gets flagged for banning on the next... We ban you!
[SPEAKER_06]: ...on the next go-around.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_06]: it doesn't always well they have the new light touch firmwares for the DVD drives already this is back when the first dashboard updates came out or actually the new checks and stuff came out and they've already patched it out on these drives assuming you have your drive up to date modded and stuff and there's some drives that actually don't support this at all so it doesn't matter you can patch it all you want but they can still play backups all they want and there's no way for them to check
[SPEAKER_06]: So that really sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and there's ways also to patch your games so that you're not checked by this too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least you'll get a good chunk of the people that are playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me, on the other hand, I'm safe for now because I'm not playing Black Ops or Modern Warfare 2 or Halo Reach.
[SPEAKER_06]: And unfortunately, I don't think they're going to be checking episodes of Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I am playing a legit copy of episodes from Liberty City, but my drive is flashed.
[SPEAKER_06]: in one of my consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Naughty, naughty.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for testing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because my JTAG's broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to test it on that right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm looking at our chatroom for some comments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, everybody's lit up about the adult Yogi Bear movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Salacious Pop is practically writing the movie right now in some of the chatroom comments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, boo-boo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't Bogart all the coke, boo-boo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you, Yogi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, no bears allowed in the strip club, violent mauling.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you do to my car?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you know that saying about bears only shitting in woods?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puts on aviator shades.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft in her chatroom says, Boo Boo has a right to bear arms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ladies and gentlemen, it took 398 weeks, but this show has officially driven DarkSakura to the brink of sanity.
[SPEAKER_07]: To madness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had sanity, ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: One other quick story for you guys, and then we're going to get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take it back to the old school way.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll kick it back 14 years right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember when they originally announced Duke Nukem Forever?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh boy, yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duke Nukem Forever was that game that was announced before some of you were probably born.
[SPEAKER_07]: This game was supposed to come out, and now it finally has a release date.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, it was published in the latest Game Informer magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: May 3rd, 2011, or 2011, whatever you want to say, is the new release date for Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is what Gearbox Software is aiming for.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, of course, obviously, they're really hyping up this release now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the game that was never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, guys, once this game kind of changed hands, it's happened pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think it's not surprising that really all it took was getting it away from 3D Realms and giving it to someone else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully, I mean, I don't mean to disrespect 3D Realms, but damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the trailer?
[SPEAKER_07]: You never did anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I didn't see the full trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, well, let me take a look here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, when's your birthday?
[SPEAKER_07]: When's your birthday?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to say I was born in 1931 because that's where my mouse clicked first.
[SPEAKER_07]: February 1st, 1931.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fresh and white.
[SPEAKER_00]: Try mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't show me these goddamn ads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just go to Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gonna be done in a second anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rated M. Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: They used to tell stories of a man who saved the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: A man whose very presence sent aliens running back to their motherships.
[SPEAKER_03]: A man who disappeared without a trace.
[SPEAKER_03]: When the invaders came back, they came back angry.
[SPEAKER_03]: They tore our planet apart, bit by bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they made one mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: They shouldn't have gone after our women.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do they always take the hot ones?
[SPEAKER_13]: You want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: The captions are the best part.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did he just punch that alien in the face?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now... We're fucking bringing it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you think I was gone forever?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they get the original voice actor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a big giant alien with three boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's peeing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's going on for way too long in this trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be done soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, a lot of gum.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the vehicle drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It should be good, because this guy just did Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coochie, coochie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hail to the king, baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the game, Duke?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it any good?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but after 12 years, it should be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: The minute I heard it was going to the guys in Borderlands, I was like, okay, it's in capable hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious to see how the game plays like a first level walkthrough type of video or something which I'm sure probably exists out there from the Penny Arcade Expo where they brought it but yeah it looks like it's keeping that same sense of humor and definitely not holding back on the tits and ass that's nice to see I remember reading that everything that's in the that's blurred out or bleeped out is actually going to be in the game so nice
[SPEAKER_07]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, our chat room is oversharing as they're watching this trailer here with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ed Seaton Beaver in our chat room says, I am touching myself to the trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Defective Candy says, I have quite literally been waiting for this game my whole life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bonds006 says, punching it in the face never gets old.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or is it punching E.T.?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not Scott Pilgrim.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Prodigy, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Prodigy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not Scott Pilgrim.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was in that trailer, but it's the Prodigy.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also a cage match pick that won a couple times.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enough about this stuff that you had to wait 14 years for.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about something that was out 14 years ago?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's 12 years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: He said 12 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going by Duke.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about we say 13?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excite me with a classic game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The classic game of the week is Power Stone 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Specifically Power Stone 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Power Stone was great, but Power Stone 2 made all kinds of fun improvements over the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So first of all, it's got all of the characters from the first Power Stone, and it's basically a four-player fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just so much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have all kinds of different gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got the one-on-one, which is like the original.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a two-character storyline game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have arcade mode, which is a four-character storyline game, and two characters advance per round.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you have original, which is multiplayer, so you can pick stages and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a fun party game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then adventure that has an unpredictable storyline, and you can collect cards, items, and money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, it's got five different stages and the boss stages.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all kinds of different fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got the desert stage that has the Pharaoh Walker.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all kinds of neat things.
[SPEAKER_02]: It even had secret characters like Pride Falcon and Mel.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in the PSP version you also get Kraken and Valgus back from the first game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Jack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jack was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think for Dan he was always using Fokker, or as they had him in the US one, Falcon.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, because Fokker's like Roy Fokker from Macross.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what he always said.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or he's a real mother Fokker.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would always use Ayame.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was me.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get different items like flamethrowers and giant hammers and bear traps and a magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, you get food and invisibility and wings and all kinds of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can, you know, drop bombs and icebergs at people.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you've got, like, the bad guys with, like I said, Pharaoh Walker and Dr. Erode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Dr. Erode is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he has a Power Stone of his own.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and actually the secret character Mel ran the item shop and with the VMU it had this thing called the mini book that you can look at your players item inventory you can trade items with other players and you can register things in your inventory as handy items that appear in original mode so they give you this advantage
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you put the disc in a CD player then it plays the same message well, it plays the same message that was used on the Dreamcast one except there's piano music with it and that's Power Stone 2 awesome Dreamcast
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: with eight players.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week, Power Stone 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good choice, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very good choice.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we're going to go to a break, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's that time of the show where we take a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's plenty more Orange Lounge Radio to come.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't even talked about some of the things that were announced at the Square Enix event this week, which we're going to get into.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little more news about Duke Nukem Forever, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: A story about the Rock Band Network and some things going on with Apple.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we have to talk about...
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going on with the PlayStation hack case?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there's more developments.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get into all that, plus a story involving boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's not even a Yogi Bear related thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got all that after the break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be right back with your Twitter topics, emails, or lack thereof, and more in just a little bit here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are live on this Sunday, January 23rd of 2011 for the 398th episode of our little program.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we've got plenty more news coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some rapid fire news in just a moment, but we quickly want to give some plugs for some other shows that we work on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every week, DarkSakura has a show that she does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: With her buddies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can find it on Infamous.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's N-F-A-M-O-U-S.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have a Twitter for Comic Insanity as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Check those out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both available on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Comic Insanity, that's the letter N, no I in front, and Horde House.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can find those both on iTunes or whatever podcasting directory it is that you use.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then the Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got just a couple minutes to lock those in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twitter.com slash OLR for the Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: First, some quick news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's a rumor that an official software development kit for Windows is coming before the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're saying it could actually be coming within the next few months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, if you think about it, would time just perfectly with Game Developer Conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: And wouldn't that be something that they would probably want at Game Developer Conference?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good theory.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, apparently, this is coming from a website WinRumors, sources are familiar with the plans, and that official software development kit and Kinect drivers are being prepped for a beta release in the coming months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Potentially arriving with the upcoming XNA update dubbed Community Technical Preview.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the report, I guess they're saying that there's statements being made by Microsoft's head, Steve Ballmer, earlier this month saying that the Kinect support would be coming to PC in a formal way in the right time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes sense that it would be at something like Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: My bet would be that's when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll probably see an update to XNA and stuff like that around that time as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good anyways because you get support for the XNA stuff, for PC stuff, and for the indie games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd really like to see what the indie games do with Kinect.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Scary at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it could be very scary as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pixel 4's Halo is now free to download.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the Halo demake by Eric Ruth, who you may remember ran into a little bit of trouble with his last...
[SPEAKER_06]: DMake of DJ Hero but this time though it's kind of a side scroller shooter game so go check it out and you can find that on I guess bigdownload.com slash games slash pixel dash force dash halo slash pc slash pixel dash force dot halo dot dash free dash game or just go do a damn google search for it because it's probably a lot easier than writing that all down
[SPEAKER_06]: and last but not least, speaking of DJ Hero DJ Hero 2 has added some new trance anthems this week and you can get these for $8 or 640 Microsoft points and they are also available separately on the Wii for 300 points a pop and with that you get Foreign Angel by Paul Van Dyke mixed with 9pm Till I Come by ATB
[SPEAKER_06]: Which even though that song I don't really consider like a trance anthem I do remember that it was on a bunch And apparently that song is remixed as well, my bad It was on a bunch of trance albums back when I was buying CDs a long time ago Not Over by Paul Oakenfold featuring Ryan Tedder And Punk by Ferry Corson versus Imagine by Armin Van Buren Sounds cool
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: There will be a number of RPG elements in this, meaning there'll be different job classes, there'll be PvP, you can party up with other players, and of course, hack hack slash slash and all the button mashing you are used to from the originals.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will be a free-to-play game, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microtransactions, of course, that's how these things work these days.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word on when this game will announce in North America, if at all possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, this is going to be another country's first.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big news on Portal 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal 2 has announced that when it comes to the PS3, it's going to have cross-platform chat between the PS3 and the PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: That includes multiplayer as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, get this, you buy the game on the PS3...
[SPEAKER_07]: you're going to get the Steam version for free if you link your PSN and your Steam accounts you will get the Steam Play version of Portal 2 free because you have the PS3 game so boy did they just sell many more copies of the PlayStation 3 version of this game at least versus the Xbox 360 which is really what Sony wanted at their conference I'm sure when they came out and announced this whole new friendship they now have with Valve
[SPEAKER_07]: so they are also saying with this a quote from Gabe Newell from Valve quote we hope to expand upon the foundation being laid in Portal 2 with more Steam features and functionality in DLC and future content releases could be very interesting for the future these two companies working together by the way cloud based storage will also be working on the PS3 which I think they had announced before but it's kind of interesting to see how that's all going to work with the PC integration as well
[SPEAKER_07]: One other quick story here, and I mean quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know there's a new Justin Bieber movie coming out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Think of how I felt when I had to see that trailer before I went and saw Tangled.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta give Nintendo props, because they wanted to use a 15-second clip of the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: theme song in the new Justin Bieber movie, and Nintendo said no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo said no.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because cereal's more important.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, funny enough, I remember back in the day there was Nintendo underwear you could order from the magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you think of how bad of an idea that was?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is much worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like underoos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we may have made a failing cereal brand and we may have whored out our brands to all sorts of different merchandise out there, but no, we are drawing the line here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck off, Justin Bieber.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for fans of Bejeweled Blitz, it looks like Bejeweled Blitz Live is going to have a 16-player online play with Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of people can play.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be crazy, GoNuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dance Dance Revolution is having download content!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Greatest Hits pack that's got Paranoia, Brilliant to You, AM3P, Trip Machine, Put Your Faith in Me And there's a premium pack that's free that says Let's Get Away, Dreaming Can Make a Wish Come True, and Private Eye
[SPEAKER_02]: and just a whole bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of stuff on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Konomics Greatest Hits, which has a B4U Higher Burn in the Floor Hysteria Trip Machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that these are worthy packets.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hoorah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, there is video out that has two more characters for a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Super Street Fighter 4, there is Evil Ryu and Oni Akuma.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool, which I kind of saw coming anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's video out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It hasn't been officially confirmed, but dude, there's video, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got red glowing eyes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Evil Ryu.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have some better screenshots out there too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's official.
[SPEAKER_06]: As official as it gets.
[SPEAKER_02]: And his moves are the same ones that he had in Alpha 2 and Alpha 3, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, this is what it's about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Arcade Unlocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that shit when it was around with DDR Max 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It got people, got asses in the seats, as they would say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got people to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fans of DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure people that play Street Fighter don't give a shit about DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we ready to get to the tweets?
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like actually they're just calling him Oni.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take that as a no.
[SPEAKER_02]: which kind of makes sense because anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we have tweets.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember when Oni Mode and DDR was a big deal and everybody was like, what does Oni mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oni means ogre.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, ogre.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now let's get to the tweets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every week we invite you guys to show us your tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll invoke some discussion here on our lovely program.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys sent quite a few tweets tonight, so we'll start it off with Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jumping ahead a little bit here, but I'll go ahead since most people know about this already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIII 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shouldn't they be putting their attention towards fixing the fuck up that is Final Fantasy XIV?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, but that's going to take some time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIV relaunch in the US?
[SPEAKER_07]: At least Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: If not later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's true Alright, let's see Spazinator, PSM There are rumors that an MGS HD collection is in the works A Metal Gear Solid HD collection I wouldn't be surprised We've got two already coming out in March We've got the Tomb Raider and the Prince of Persia Ah, good point
[SPEAKER_06]: And they just had the Sly Collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's popular nowadays.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on to another tweet from Spazinator, kind of keeping us up to date on the video releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: The pilots to Being Human, Perfect Couples, and Fairly Legal are free on Xbox Live, while Perfect Couples and Fairly Legal are free on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like to sample new TV shows or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a problem with Being Human.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is that show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I've watched the first two seasons of it on BBC America.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a show about... No, it's not a comedy.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, a copy show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's about a vampire, a ghost, and a werewolf that live in the same flat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds like the beginning of a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've said the same thing, but it's actually a really good show, at least the British one is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard the American one is not so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how far do I want to get into this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you heard about that Skins show?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's big in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made it here on MTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have zero interest in that show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, if there's a number less than zero, I have that amount of interest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Negative Infinity?
[SPEAKER_07]: Negative Infinity is my interest level for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I can't get away from it on my entertainment gossip websites, which pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: ActDeft sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's about the PSP 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little rumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: 3G connectivity and a very fancy screen on the PSP2 if this tweet from Actdeft is to be believed where he links us to a story on Kotaku apparently it's a report from Nikkei that the portable in Japan will be on the NTT Dokomo network via 3G
[SPEAKER_07]: Could that mean like this is going to be like T-Mobile's answer to the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm pulling that out of my ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: But one of the providers that doesn't have the iPhone, maybe they'll have the PSP2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not saying anything about phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just 3G connection.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like an iPad.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be interesting because that means you could play multiplayer anywhere you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would you think about 3G on the PSP2?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would that be cool for you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the killer right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, unless it's included in the price of that system, it's going to be fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you're going to have to pay another $100 a month or $60 a month to play your stupid system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wi-Fi, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, if I can do it via Wi-Fi, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just tether to my phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, Sterlok sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crimson Echoes finally leaked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Suck it, Square, and then links us to the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was like, what's Crimson Echoes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes, it's the fan-made Chrono Trigger sequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the fan-made Chrono Trigger sequel finally leaked out to the internet, which we all knew it would.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the one that Square Enix shut down not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: We all knew it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once it hits the internet, it's out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sure enough, that's what happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crimson Echoes made its way out apparently also a game called Flames of Eternity got leaked which was I guess a branch off of the same title so there you go by the way I'm looking at the fighting in this game it looks like Final Fantasy 6 kind of interesting maybe it's like a really elaborate ROM hack or something I don't know alright let's move on to defective candy I like this send us a tweet connect hacked for surgical robot
[SPEAKER_07]: a group of graduate students at the University of Washington have modified the firmware and software of the Kinect to guide the actions of surgical robots wow
[SPEAKER_07]: And it gets into more of the details of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking for some quotes here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just seeing this story for the first time.
[SPEAKER_07]: The hacked unit adds the sense of touch and feeds information to the surgeon.
[SPEAKER_07]: The setup could save $50,000 on the standard rig used to perform non-invasive surgery.
[SPEAKER_07]: We could define basically a force field around, say, a liver.
[SPEAKER_07]: If the surgeon got too close, he would run into that force field and it would protect the object he didn't want to cut.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then, what about the day the machines take over?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you really want a machine operating on you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Cyberdyne!
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, Skynet.
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple tweets from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_07]: Telltale Games strongly hints at doing The Walking Dead game I guess really the title says it all but we're linked to a story there The Walking Dead is a show on AMC and it was a comic book series that now is this big TV show I know a few people that are into this I haven't watched this but apparently Telltale Games is hinting that perhaps they're doing something on this and that was well Telltale's got a big event going on they're going to be talking about five new multi-platform efforts and I'm assuming Jurassic Park of course is one of those
[SPEAKER_07]: They're also saying one of the titles announced is based on a just-launched property from the TV and comic book world whose popularity is changing life as some know it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So some people are inferring that from that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds like we'll find out in a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: MNZiba sends us a couple tweets as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Kinect hacker that made himself into a bunch of Minecraft monuments has now put those monuments in motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weren't you saying something about this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was during the break or right at the end of Part A. I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was just saying that we were talking about this a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, this is a Minecraft monument where now it moves.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have never played Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that make me a bad gamer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or just lazy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope, I haven't done it either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, apparently the Minecraft monument moves at 30 frames a second while he juggles three balls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, I mean, I guess if you had to kind of create this, like, bit by bit, it's probably a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's better, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the one that they have where it's a cat chasing a laser.
[SPEAKER_07]: MNZiba also sends us a tweet about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: A letter from the Final Fantasy XIV producer explaining upcoming huge changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a very long read.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this was just produced a little bit this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually did some polls...
[SPEAKER_07]: This is really long, so I might have to read this while someone else is doing a story.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it looks like they really took this poll and kind of like took some of the feedback to heart.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what are they talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tutorials for new players, quests revolving around the danger facing the world, public company quests, improvements to the log, improvements of dialogue windows, character jump feature.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guildlevs so yeah they want to do a whole bunch of new shit in the game we'll just leave it at that there's a long letter available lodestone.finalfantasyxiv the roman way of saying 14.com that's where you can find that last couple tweets here another one from TigerClaw saying consumer group reporting Activision to UK fair trade office over Black Ops glitches and this is a link to a story on Gamasutra
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a British consumer group, The Gamer's Voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to complain to the UK Office of Fair Trading about the performance issues in the PS3 and PC versions of Call of Duty Black Ops.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess the publisher did not respond to an open letter from the group one month ago, which talked about the freezing and online multiplayer login, that the game is not functioning as intended or advertised.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess you could say it's kind of like the Better Business Bureau in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, somebody's going to take him to task over that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: These things usually don't end up in much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually like either a settlement or a letter or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it'll be interesting to see what happens overseas.
[SPEAKER_07]: One last tweet from Alex P. Carson on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, maybe this isn't the show for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they need to subscribe to a sex podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_07]: But we always appreciate any efforts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'll even read your Twitter name on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright!
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: and stuff like that I remember talking about that last week yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: Because according to the judge, it says if having a PayPal account were enough, then there would be personal jurisdiction in this court over everybody, and that can't be right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it says the case is pending further discussion over jurisdiction, a decision Sony is likely to frown upon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now, seeing as how the hack is completely available online, and as I mentioned earlier...
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be an interesting case.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the story's going to come up every damn week until they settle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they'll settle either.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you have companies using the whole PS3 hacking thing as an excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: According to Infinity Ward, I'm assuming this is what's left of Infinity Ward...
[SPEAKER_06]: Modern Warfare 2 has been kind of made unplayable thanks to people hacking the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says Infinity Ward cannot patch a fix.
[SPEAKER_06]: People are saying it's making total shambles.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's unplayable.
[SPEAKER_06]: According to Infinity Wars, these games rely on security of the encryption on the platforms they're played on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless the security exploit itself is resolved on the platform, updates to the game through patches will not resolve the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: At this time, we do not have any ability to restore or adjust individual stats.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are looking at every option to help us help any user affected and
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and they've been doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is totally unrelated to anything that has to do with those PS3 keys.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on top of that, they're doing the same thing on the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're hacking save files and stuff and that stuff's kind of been patched.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it really comes down to they just don't want to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you think about it, why would they?
[SPEAKER_06]: Modern Warfare 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it goes to shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy Black Ops.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know Interesting There's no way to just track down who's fucking up the game and just ban them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they could but they could just create another account I guess They'd have to actually track down systems Interesting Sorry about that, you cut off there in the beginning So wouldn't that go back to the laziness factor?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so Yep
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: People aren't actually reading into this.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're kind of saying, oh, well, thanks, Geohot, for doing all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now Modern Warfare 2 is unplayable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, if you're going to believe everybody and what they say and without doing actual research into what's going on, then sure, go ahead and blame those hackers.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it is a different...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a special kind of hacker out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the little kid that figures out, oh hey, I can grief somebody this way or I can cheat in this game and screw it up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like the whole Grand Theft Auto hacking or modding community.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's people that actually want to make stuff that's kind of cool and then there's people that want to make cars that freeze people or guns that freeze people's games because they're douchebags and that's what they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, no matter what you do, those douchebags will find a way to be a douche.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play with your friends and nobody else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's sadly where some of this is going, honestly, online.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to play a legitimate game, you've got to play with your friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take your ball and go home.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, some news coming out of Square Enix this week, involving a tweet a little bit ago, kind of references.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIII 2 was announced.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is coming out for the 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was during a little press event that Square Enix had this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, they are saying that Final Fantasy XIII 2 is set to launch in Japan in 2011, but that's probably just Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not saying anything about the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: just yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, they said next winter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said next winter is the release.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that mean next February or next December?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you can kind of take that a couple ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully it's a quick cycle.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'm assuming this is just going to be done in the same engine as the first game was.
[SPEAKER_07]: But just, you know, new story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some new models and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully more Dresh Sphere, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_07]: The name of Final Fantasy Agito 13 has been changed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's now Final Fantasy Type 0, which would explain some of the stories in the past couple weeks about these trademarks showing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Type 0 is the game that is coming out instead.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is going to be on the PSP, of course, and they just said that this title just seems to be more appropriate because this is a more action-oriented design of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be coming out to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: 30 voice characters in the game, multiplayer supposedly in it as well nothing announced just yet for what's going on in North America but it is coming out to Japan this summer on two UMDs not one but two that must be a big game we'll see well how about going back to something that we touched on earlier
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a blast from the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there going to be download content?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh, huh, huh, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they haven't announced anything about it, but they are saying that they are trying to, and this is a quote, on making possible the un-possible, shipping Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they are saying that there could be some download content that they are keeping the future in mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there will be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Build your own strip club DLC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: I want voice macros to come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't be surprised if they have DLC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, look at the awesome DLC they had for the original Duke Nukem 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have the fourth episode, the Atomic Edition, which is just awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the supermarket level.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the level that was kind of Disneyland, but not, you know, with the Pirates of the Caribbean ride and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just miss Duke Nukem Deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope this game is as awesome as the old Duke Nukem was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does.
[SPEAKER_07]: The trailer's sense of humor is any indication, but how often do games look cool and they suck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just as irreverent as the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some developers out there developing for the iOS platform that are pissed off at Apple because they just don't take piracy or theft seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Theft in this case happens to be a game called The Blocks Cometh.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an iPhone game that's out there right now that's completely ripped off of a Flash game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It didn't just copy the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They took the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: They took the assets, the music, everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: They ported it over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, it's not by the creators.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's by somebody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the creators of the actual game actually have a version for the iPhone that's in the works right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're pissed off.
[SPEAKER_06]: They contacted Apple and their customer service or whomever said their legal departments contacted the people responsible for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they've kind of given them the runaround.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's nothing really that they seem to be doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess it's kind of a serious case if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just, oh, this game is sort of like Angry Birds or this game is sort of like something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: We took this game, stole everything from it, and threw it on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like if I created Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: and popped it onto the iOS, Apple's app store and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, could you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if this game gets by, why hasn't someone done that yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they need to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: or Great Giana Sisters.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take your pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: The What's Hot Section
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a feeling a lot of that runs on an algorithm though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that they necessarily specifically targeted that game to promote.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably getting a lot of downloads.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably been getting a lot of downloads because of the coverage, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it a pay game though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is a pay game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pay games aren't worth it.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Alpha Cananagram, I don't know if you saw this, he's following up in chat saying they have taken it down since then.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it is no longer there.
[SPEAKER_07]: but look at what it took for that to happen I think that's still fairly notable you know what I mean nobody saw that right away but of course if I'm working at Apple and I'm testing these apps am I going to recognize this game probably not you know they don't do the peer review thing like XNA does where lots of people are prone to recognize stuff that's ripped off but if it's just like a couple people at Apple I mean I would never recognize that this game was ripped off I'd never play the original so in that way I can kind of
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so let's move on to another story that has to do with the Rock Band Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo, Rock Band!
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Band Network 2.0 is coming out in February!
[SPEAKER_07]: February 15th is the date to be exact that's when the new track creation system will come out all songs currently being made for Rock Band Network they must be done by February 14th when 1.0 will be phased out and then everything after that for Rock Band Network 2 will require Rock Band 3 I'm assuming this means because of you know the keyboards and all that other stuff so there you go
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Rock Band 3, sadly, not doing too well on the sales charts, did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't do too well after Christmas, did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe forcing people to upgrade will do some good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they should just slash the price of the game to 20 bucks and watch it fly off shelves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I have a friend that bought the pro guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's pretty heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty cool, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so with that, I guess we're going to get into the mailbag at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place where you send us emails every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to get into the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, we actually, well, the mailbag kind of sucks because we've got nothing in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Read the spam!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we don't have any spam either, so I dedicate this to everyone who did not send an email.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll take the box!
[SPEAKER_09]: The box!
[SPEAKER_09]: You took the box?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see what's in the box!
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing!
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely nothing!
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid!
[SPEAKER_09]: You're so stupid!
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's the movie that Dan and I got engaged over.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want a drink from the fire hose.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wheel of fish.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think I've ever seen that movie from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the best one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Badgers!
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't need no stinking badgers!
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird Al needs to do another movie, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: He totally does.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, what an appropriate time to get into this segment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I know we have some of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to certain situations that are beyond my control that involve finances and my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to the people at A&W for not knowing how to fill up a half gallon of root beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually not to mention it is impossible to transport this without it spilling everywhere as it was and it made it very difficult to drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will never be buying a half gallon root beer again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is just too much root beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: A half
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to be vague.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually a lot of stuff going on, but nothing I can talk about on my public show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, FU to stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then skyblind in just a little bit after a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you need to cheer me up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have a story that might cheer me up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about the brand new, um, Yogi Bear movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm not cheered up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's about Tiger Woods and a weird glitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: This really isn't cheering me up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about a weird glitch that's being reported, I don't even know if we should take this seriously, by The Sun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the tabloid magazine in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, apparently, there was a glitch that this one woman has, um, encountered Britt and Joe, um, Ile, or whatever, um, apparently, her avatar that she had set up on there one day, when she popped on the game, it was topless!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, now you have my attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nipples and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the, um, the avatar is topless, and, uh, of course, EA was quick to say that, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: There is no possible way that that could have been done without some sort of hack.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, as we've seen with games like Heavy Rain, I could believe that it could be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, she doesn't actually have boob textures or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: The nipple bumps are there for the clothing and stuff, but I think that just for some reason it's not drawing the clothing on.
[SPEAKER_06]: but she's topless and playing golf boobies you know what you get those women topless and playing golf I bet you a lot more people Tiger Woods would sell like twice as many copies as it does now Tiger Woods the M rated golf game there you go well it just took a story about boobies to cheer me up a little bit Tiger Boobs I like that
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's now coming back on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Judgment Silver Sword and the remix Cardinal Sins.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are both going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they're bonuses in a new 360 retail shmup.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eshkatos?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I'm saying that right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course all these games are coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: there's two trailers for this game that are out there on the internet you can import it on March 24th I like this because I guess there's like one trailer here that shows like a split because you know how like vertical shmups on the 360 don't use much real estate on the screen at all like there's all this wasted horizontal space well in this game sorry it's a little loud sorry guys
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks very pretty, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like some of the effects they're doing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then there's one part of the trailer here where they're showing multiplayer in like three screens on the screen at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they're dodging lots and lots of bullets.
[SPEAKER_07]: And dying.
[SPEAKER_07]: WonderSwan Color shoot-em-ups making a return on the 360, but only in Japan, which makes sense because WonderSwan Color was only out in Japan, never came out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was such a good system, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our Skype line is now open.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll talk about whatever it is you want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the meantime, should we see if there's any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I know it takes about a minute until the folks that are listening hear us begging for calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a rumor, uh, well, we talked a little bit about this, the 3G and stuff, and the OLD screen, uh, PSP2, already, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was in Twitter topics, now that I think of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, nevermind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, I had to pull it up and I was ready to go and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, no, I know I have more stuff to talk about here, I just have to pull it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_00]: Words?
[SPEAKER_06]: Words, yes, specifically.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was going to say that those people out there that are thinking about possibly hacking your PlayStation 3 using the readily available custom firmwares that are out there, you may remember that they have ways of tracking you down.
[SPEAKER_06]: So make sure you get one of those things that erases your... What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The...
[SPEAKER_06]: Game History or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the new programs still have that built in so that you don't get caught.
[SPEAKER_06]: LA Noire.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a game that also had a trailer leaked out for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also going to be coming out from Take-Two in May.
[SPEAKER_06]: This on May 17th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big game for Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plants vs. Zombies and Peggle coming to the Android Marketplace the second quarter of this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, the phones are open.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it, call!
[SPEAKER_07]: Our usual name on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be another one of those nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get your lazy butts up, pick up your phone, and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have something to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just going to sit here on the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk about a video game, and you better not be... What's your face?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now see, I saw this story and I thought of you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Epic Mickey, they're talking about 10 different Easter eggs that are in this game from different Disney history and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, in the game, actually in Mickey Junk Mountain, they actually have a basketball court in the...
[SPEAKER_06]: in that part of the game as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of allude to the basketball court that's in Matterhorn.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do have a call on the line.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_07]: We sure can.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, this is DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I took your advice a couple weeks ago, and then I actually picked up a, well, I guess you could call it an indie game, but one that's been getting a whole bunch of hype from everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, for those that didn't hear, you called in a couple weeks ago and I believe it was something about, I am just frustrated with games today.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's same shit, different year, you know, I feel like there's no games for me to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I said, well, try indie.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you went for a popular indie title, but an indie one nonetheless, Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think of Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did we lose him?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you still hear us?
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we lost.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we can now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you think of... Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you mute yourself?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you think of Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we can.
[SPEAKER_10]: For a beta, I'm very impressed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's weird that it's the total freedom to do anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's almost like I feel like I have nothing to do, but I'm just enjoying just doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I have never played Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: I read a lot about it on the interwebs, but I've not played it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So can you tell me what Minecraft is?
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you do in Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_10]: The best way I could say this is you pretty much make stuff to sort of build...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the idea is that you pretty much have to build your shelter and your tools and everything out of different parts you find here and there during the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you have to make a good shelter because at night you get invaded by zombies and skeletons and spiders.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you want to be safe at night, and then you do the same thing every day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Daytime, you build stuff and raise trees and make flowers and kill animals for food.
[SPEAKER_10]: At night, you pretty much either hide or you defend yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so there is kind of an actual game to it, because I was always under the impression that there really wasn't a lot to it outside of creation and building.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so you're trying to prevent zombies from eating your face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like stuff...
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So did this help kind of break your video game blaws or are you still looking for that game that just makes you love video games again?
[SPEAKER_10]: It sort of helped kill the blaws because I also realized that I'm pretty much a PC gamer for life now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty much shied away from PS3 and Xbox and I like playing on a PC a lot better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll give you an example.
[SPEAKER_10]: I tried out the demo the other day for Mass Effect 2 just for shits and giggles.
[SPEAKER_10]: It ran so much better on my computer than on the Xbox or PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's more a matter of you feel like the technology that the games need today, maybe the console cycle's gone on too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, let's face it, 360's been out now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going on its fifth year, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe it's time for some new consoles?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, either that or some heavy updates and whatnot, because my computer's not that old either, but it was running circles around, like, the consoles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, a lot of it has to do with your, um, uh, lost the word, the video card as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that's a big part of it, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you have a newer video card in your system?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mean, I got one just last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still a new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: My processor's old, but it's one of those things where, logically, it doesn't make sense, but it just works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orange.radio.com, Bochikawa says, Minecraft is like Legos, the RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, there is actually a really fun, like, just a Lego builder game that is on the official Lego website.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not really a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a tool.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, DDR Dollar Bill, we're going to let you go to get some more calls, but any quick final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, support PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll try.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Steam is going to save PC gaming, if it hasn't already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Steam rocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the indie stuff, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You too, thanks guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other last minute stories for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll just have to make something up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, no, I want DarkSakura to make something up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make up a video game news story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that actually didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm putting her on the spot, people.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's live radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chirp.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, a new Angry Birds game is coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a new Angry Birds versus DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Angry Birds versus Angry Co-host.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I was going to say Angry Birds versus Zombies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, because everything indie these days is something something versus Zombies, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, buddy, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got to play with the PS3 Move for my first time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, what'd you think of the PS3 Move?
[SPEAKER_00]: I, depending on the game, I really like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Though I did like the bowling and the sports one they had out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It had a lot of similarities to that of Wii, but the graphics and the way they did it was a lot better.
[SPEAKER_00]: The output and the way it was controlled was, I think, personally for me, was a lot smoother.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe this is a really hard question to ask, but it's something I've given a lot of thought to myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've said this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Connect and Move, they're out there now, and most of the games that have come out originally are, for the most part, with a few exceptions, copies of Wii games with nicer graphics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where do you think the Move goes next?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you see the Move integrated into Sony's core franchises?
[SPEAKER_00]: The world.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to become the world like that of .hack//.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're gonna have visors and everything and it's gonna become one big MMO.
[SPEAKER_07]: It already is in their core franchises.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of it really feels like an afterthought, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the move support's there, in a bonus level.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just basically the prehistoric thing that's in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm saying it's in their core franchises, as in SOCOM 4 and Killzone 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are core franchises.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, I don't pay attention to a lot of the first-person shooters, and I remember seeing that at the GDC even, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: But granted, their gun that they have, their little shell, is retarded looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I agree with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I agree with you on that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm hoping that people will step up to the plate on those things and make stuff better, like actual better looking guns and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, like, for example, like Time Crisis with Namco, I like the guns they use.
[SPEAKER_00]: It makes you feel like you're playing the arcade with the actual guns.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the guns are quite different from that of the arcade because of the feedback and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's no pedal button.
[SPEAKER_00]: But still, I think it'll do good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's moving in the right direction, I believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's sad, though, because it's really killing off stuff like arcades and stuff that I grew up loving as a kid.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just, you know, it's hard to compete.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, MMOs for real used to be going to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's depressing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Instead of booting up your computer or your Xbox and playing the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it really was.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was a lot of fun putting your quarters and stuff on top of, you know, in certain areas saying, hey, look, I want to be next, you know, or have to be, you know, wait in line.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I guess maybe it saved that 20-minute wait from playing that one game that you really want to play.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time, too, you know...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_00]: That feeling you got of being around a big crowd and they're cheering you on and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not really the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it would be cool if they would make an MMO that kind of, if you can't beat them, join them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make an MMO about going to arcades.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what Game Room should have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: An MMO where you're going to the arcade and playing these old school games and
[SPEAKER_07]: and the better you get at games, the better you can skill up your character to maybe help you get like cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to say cheap, but get better in other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's an idea there.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I agree on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the best thing you played on Move?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll kind of end it with that question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, unfortunately, I only played two different games.
[SPEAKER_00]: So probably the bowling because I did really well against my friends on that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the Bronx was bowling.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, really quickly, Gearbox I think is going to do really great with the Duke Nukem because they did a really great job with Borderlands and their DLC, so if they keep it close to making it somewhat of the original feel, from what I've seen from the trailers and stuff, I think they're going to do a really good job.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be really interesting to see what they do with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I know they really are with their fans and what the fans want so I wouldn't be surprised if they make some kind of mod so you can build your own strip club or or build your own like miniature you know I would see a lot of that probably coming out near down the road also because a lot of feedback has been really positive on it so and they really want what the people want so it's that's been a really good positive thing too so
[SPEAKER_07]: One day, one day we'll have our arcades again, but we'll take that next great invention to bring people back.
[SPEAKER_00]: UQ.
[SPEAKER_07]: More beer in arcades, that's what it really needs, because you look at the arcades that are popular, Dave & Buster's, the retro arcades, they all serve beer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there's one by where I used to live, believe it or not, that did the same thing too, and it was very popular.
[SPEAKER_00]: Less kids, more beer.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's EDR, so I mean, pretty much go hand in hand, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well buddy, we're going to let you go to try and fit in a couple more calls, but have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, you too, no problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's Zappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Zappy, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what's on your mind tonight, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've been playing one of the big releases of the week, well, only big releases of the week, Little Big Plan 2, and I can't say more than it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I noticed that there's a lot more variety when I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: LittleBigPlanet 1 was a good, solid platformer, but with the second one, they really tried to make it different, having different gimmicks in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sort of like how they had Yoshi in Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what's some of the cool stuff you've seen in the user-created levels?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you've had a chance to dip in there, but have you seen any really cool user-created stuff yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the cool things I saw was they made an entire tower defense game out of the little big tiny engines.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh wow, nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was kind of surprised they could do that, but they designed this in mind that you can basically take whatever game ideas you want and make it, which is really exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of taking whatever ideas you want and making it, and I apologize for deviating from your call a little bit, but in the last call we were talking about ways to save arcades.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course our chat room is going off on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: SJ100Matt says, tits could save arcades.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Xlink says, now that could be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe you need to mix strip clubs with arcades.
[SPEAKER_07]: When in doubt, show some tits.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I shit you not, look it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nuts and Milk.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that could be the name of the arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: How does that get past censors?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: How does that get past censors?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have the same slang.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So have you played the Nuts and Milk remake in LittleBigPlanet 2 yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it's coming along any day now, but unfortunately not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so anything else you've been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a little bit of Planets 2 taking up your time, or any other games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've also been playing some Dead Space, the first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking forward to the new one that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I can't believe you missed this game in 2008, because it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it went off my radar for so long, going, okay, to make a second one, there must be something to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really going back to the survival horror roots
[SPEAKER_08]: where you're actually getting freaked out, like you're thinking that something is around that next corner and there might be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of sucks when games, like, you find out about them, like, three years after they were out, and then, like, by the time you're like, this game was fucking rad, you found out that the development studio got closed and everybody got laid off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I bet you anything that still happened to Blur.
[SPEAKER_07]: When the game's down to 20 bucks, if it's not already, it'll start selling more copies, and then people are like, wow, they should really make a sequel to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shit, they can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's a shame it happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: Literally, it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, anything else you want to share with the listeners tonight before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, have fun with LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully, I'll be playing it pretty soon as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, you know, got to wait to save up the money.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: 877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't realize that call came in from Canada.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: maybe he had said that before that he was kidding my friend just got back from Toronto actually he's coming back in tonight you know Grandpa Warcraft went to Toronto went to Toronto and is coming back tonight cool yeah I want to go to Toronto I've never been here it's really fun Vancouver is awesome though I want to go to Vancouver like how can Toronto be better than Vancouver I'm sure there's a lot of people that live in Toronto that are mad at me for saying that but seriously Vancouver is awesome awesome let's go to the phones there's some more calls coming in hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Chortles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chortles!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi buddy, how are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_12]: Chortles?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, honestly, I was just considering, is it just me or is this your PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know how Activision, is it true that on PlayStation Network, the publishers have to put out the servers themselves for the multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_12]: I've been considering that in the wake of...
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I'm not sure if I'm overhearing this, but basically, have you heard of reports about PlayStation Network getting hacked recently?
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, does that sound familiar to you?
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation Network's been getting hacked recently?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't follow that stuff as well as he does.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure somebody's trying to hack it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PlayStation 3's getting hacked, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, which probably includes PlayStation Network and all this stuff with the Modern Warfare and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm sure you've heard that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to jump quickly back to your question about the whole central servers and who's really running them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think to some extent the publishers are running I mean I don't know the ins and outs of games but like for example EA we just had a story on them a couple weeks ago that they were shutting down the servers for a bunch of old sports titles so I think they do run servers I think what Microsoft and PlayStation what they're running is kind of like the matchmaking and distribution services when you download upgrades and so forth that's coming from their servers because they're getting a cut of the profits
[SPEAKER_07]: DC Universe Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess most people aren't looking to it for Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the reason I was wondering that is because on the one hand, you know, you have the whole idea about, oh, you get... Yeah, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just realized that I'm actually hearing what we just said previously for like a few seconds later as a background echo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good old school first rule of calling into radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turn down your radio because it throws everybody off.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, fair enough, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was just considering that in...
[SPEAKER_12]: The fact that Activision has the deal with Microsoft to have released the DLC first on 360, isn't that like for the next two Call of Duties at least as well?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure the specifics of the agreement, but it's certainly not uncommon that one console gets download content that the other consoles don't get.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's, I think, buying exclusives for further.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to cite another example?
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at what's going on with the PlayStation 3 and Portal 2, which we talked about in the Rapid Fire News earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Portal 2 coming to 360, by the way?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is, but Sony is really trying to do everything they can to make theirs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is the quote from what they said at E3, the definitive version of Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, which is funny considering that that means free access to the other two versions.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, to the home computer versions, which come to think of it, that's actually a business model I really like.
[SPEAKER_12]: You pay for the game once, and then...
[SPEAKER_12]: You have the game period in whichever way it's playable other than 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that model too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you heard the guy earlier that called in saying that he's all about PC gaming now because consoles just aren't doing it for him and the games run better on his PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think he'd be frothing at the mouth about an idea like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine buying Mass Effect 2 on the PlayStation and you get it on all consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, like, that would be my sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I could not get enough of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's funny that he's revived his love of PC games, because, okay, I'll just let you know what I've been doing over the winter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think one of the only games that I bought for a console in 2010 was Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mind you, that was a launch game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was immensely satisfying for a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't regret that purchase.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then...
[SPEAKER_12]: After a while, it petered out, especially when it came to trying to get good connectivity for the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_12]: And while there were some severe issues with lag and multiplayer... The baby escaped.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a baby in the background that appears to have escaped.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I'm...
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not going to pretend how she would know the word lag.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just going to leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, can you get CPS on the line?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry if this is boring everyone who's listening in, but basically I found that over the holidays, I was doing my Christmas shopping and...
[SPEAKER_12]: Unlike last year, I found that there wasn't much that I was looking for in the way of Steam.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, yes, I know about the legendary Steam holiday and summer sales.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have partaken of them in past years, but this time I found that even though I was sitting on a nice chunk of change, I mainly just wanted to upgrade my hardware.
[SPEAKER_12]: For example...
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, main thing that I changed is my video card.
[SPEAKER_12]: Originally, I was using onboard... I was using onboard video, don't ask.
[SPEAKER_12]: But as a result, basically this time around, I decided to upgrade to a...
[SPEAKER_12]: Radeon HD 5770 made by MSI, 1GB.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think a lot of the draw for me was the cooling.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like two fans, three heat pipes, a heat sink.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so far, it seems to run all my games decently.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's really about, I think with the PC, it's really about the hardware and making the right choices with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you invest with that, you're going to get a huge payback.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know I upgraded my video card last year so I could run Warcraft better, which is the only PC game I need to be playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, I've played World of Warcraft for a long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I took the weak trial for Cataclysm, but I'm not paying for that right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, I will give this advice to anyone who plays World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even if you take a break in the form of, like, canceling your subscription or not playing a while, get the Battle.net authenticator.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, if you don't already have it and you use a smartphone, just get the mobile authenticator.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because you don't want people using your account while you're not there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I've actually had that happen to me in, like, in the summer of 2010.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like...
[SPEAKER_12]: Two weeks after my subscription ran out, boom, my account was hacked.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of stuff got stolen.
[SPEAKER_12]: My all-time highest level item got jacked.
[SPEAKER_12]: And by the time I found out, got my account unhacked and got back into World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was too late for Blizzard to recover my stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and it's a story I have heard way, way, way too many times.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Chortles, I gotta wrap up and let you go because if I keep letting you talking, pretty soon they're gonna give you our time slot.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I gotta wrap up and let you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Find the baby!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll probably be more focused next time, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_12]: That baby has walked out the front door by now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go get him.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Chortles, for that call.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was just really happy to be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: He sounded happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like enthusiasm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was just enthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're saying it was a zombie baby in the background?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much for calling us.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you didn't get through tonight, please consider sending us an email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send your emails to.
[SPEAKER_07]: We would really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there any other last-minute stories we've got to get out?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ribbons and bows, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ribbons and bows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spank it on the butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slack.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll start with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: My sound card decides when it decides to work and not.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is I took Friday off, so yay for four-day work week next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, you have a final thought?
[SPEAKER_15]: Reject false icons
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, you going old school.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't expect you to whip that out until episode 400.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me whip this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's just getting warmed up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm warming up my bitch slapping hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you guys so much for tuning in and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, we don't play commercials.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't ram, you know, stuff we're trying to sell down your throat.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like the show, all we ask, tell friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll ram other things down your throat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shh, stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like candy.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura's like, I got a lollipop.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to do a plug.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a very important plug I'm trying to do here, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop derailing me with your toilet humor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you plugging it already?
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go on to iTunes or whatever favorite podcast site you use and leave us a nice review.
[SPEAKER_07]: We would really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Five-star reviews on iTunes helps go a long way to promote
[SPEAKER_07]: tell your friends about the show tell people you think would be interested in people talking about video games and giving folks a voice and hearing people call in and just talk about games they really like that's it
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell your kids, tell your wife.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And tell your husbands because we're gaming everybody out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that's going to do it for another week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will be back next week to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just can't hide it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_11]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_11]: or allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next week!