[SPEAKER_00]: Overwatch 2 consoles cross-play segment stats and player pools based off the use of a controller or keyboard and mouse.
[SPEAKER_00]: When I played Rocket League Sideswipe, I frequently wondered how many people thought I was cheating, because I could manipulate my car faster and more precisely using an analog stick instead of touching the screen alone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Though this was getting through the starter tiers, where all matter of excuses fly.
[SPEAKER_00]: My body was ready.
[SPEAKER_00]: No Johns.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's fly.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the most wunderbar Deutsche Zeit of the year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you about this week's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_00]: Starting right now on the show, wherever gamers have voice...
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, you're not cheating.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're just really good at the video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: and 59 of our program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting with the scheduling is that we were off last week and we'll be off next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is this is an island show.
[SPEAKER_05]: August is just a busy month, but we'll get into more of that in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you all about the scheduling and why some pretty awesome reasons.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm here with you every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my co-host couldn't do it without the one and only Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lynn's in the live stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is what we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have lasagna.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything else is irrelevant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh man, I don't have lasagna, but I do have coffee.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, coffee and lasagna.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a great combo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm not drinking the coffee right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's if it was ladyfingers and coffee cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which tiramisu is my favorite dessert.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next to Boston cream pie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got me thinking about desserts.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a Stouffer's lasagna because we are trying to eat all the stuff in the freezer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got me thinking about desserts now and that's not a good thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going like, remember all that weight I was going to lose before DragonCon?
[SPEAKER_03]: For the record, my coffee is drunken out of a Michael Myers mug that says Slay All Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now it's that season because the week before Labor Day is when Starbucks and obviously various other companies too really dunk in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I just got a pumpkin drink at Dutch Bros and say pumpkin season is here.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been to my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: When is it never not scary season?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not pumpkin season.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's David S. Pumpkin's season.
[SPEAKER_05]: David S. Pumpkin's season.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to the one and only, our own version of David S. Pumpkin's.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why he doesn't wear the suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I'm too fat for the suit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought the suit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have the suit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't fit.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just doesn't fit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, to be fair, it didn't fit when I bought it either.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you can't really gauge the size of those things.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you bought it online, it probably came from another country where the sizing doesn't always line up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, because I've had that problem a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought it in person last year at the... Well, the building's torn down now.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, the husk of what is now a Spirit Halloween store.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, they tend to...
[SPEAKER_01]: Be Parasitic with all the different empty buildings, but yes, I bought it at a Spirit Halloween and I intended to wear it, it just doesn't, it wasn't, it just felt really cheap and it was also not fitting really well.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's kind of normal with anything that like you buy from there, it's not always going to fit.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of like, oh yeah, one size fits all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now there's food chat in our chat because we do tape live, of course, every Sunday night at – well, almost every Sunday night at 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific right after the Bobby Blackwolf show over at the Voice Geeks Network, twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's lots of great programming you can check out on VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you all remember it's not just us and Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have other video gaming shows such as GameBooey.org, Video Game Podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love those guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have shows about anime, Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have British television connoisseurs over British Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we hope you'll check out all those great shows, especially on weeks where we're not here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have plenty of other cool little things to check out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So going to our chat, because we are live, PodCulture says, I thought of Rob the other day because Costco had pallets of Starbucks pumpkin spice lattes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of surprised that Alan didn't text me a picture of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I've been very open about, I'm a type 2 diabetic, so I have to watch things like how many carbs and the sugars.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in reality, a Costco pallet of that is a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will usually, these days, ever since the diagnosis, I will allow myself one celebratory pumpkin spice latte the week of DragonCon, usually on the way to DragonCon, but I might do it on Tuesday because our coworkers are talking about doing something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can, when you order it, you can do something, you know, customize it so I get...
[SPEAKER_05]: I get half the sweetener in it, so it's a little less than normal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there is no sugar-free pumpkin at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not just get sugar-free pumpkin spice syrup, which I find all the time at home goods in those places?
[SPEAKER_05]: and make it at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSH100 Matt says they have the New York State Fair and I've eaten a lot of insane snacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Giant mozzarella stick rolled in fruity pebbles and another rolled in flaming hot Cheetos.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just had the State Fair here in California and all I heard about was how fucking expensive it was for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's expensive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but they have like something that my son was describing like it was like a deep fried Twinkie hamburger or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, no, like you've gone too far at that point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like it's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: If they make a Twinkie Wiener sandwich, Weird Al will sue.
[SPEAKER_01]: They may have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, it's not food, it's video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get into a video game talk and there was a big event that happened this week I'm going to have Loki jump into, but actually I wanted to ask you about this, DarkSakura, not to get too far into our gaming weeks, but I know you are a connoisseur yourself of Dead by Daylight, and I've been on a little bit of Dead by Hiatus, but
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they updated to the most...
[SPEAKER_05]: recent version of unreal it's one thing to watch like nick and prince or you stream it where like it doesn't look that different to me but when i look over my husband's shoulder i'm like this looks different to me somehow i don't know what it is like i don't know if it's just the eye for the fighter details but yeah i can tell it's different but then um he was telling me well you should patch your game and sign on because they are giving away five million blood points right now which i don't know how to quantify that for people not familiar with the game but it is a
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the cap of free leveling money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, it's it's a I'll put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: My pig was at and don't say nice level 69.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, prestige 69, like level 20 something.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I applied that 5 million directly to her in the most optimized manner, I got up to prestige 70 for level 42.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got every survivor to level one that I own.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't own a few of them at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got every single one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I actually got a couple of the killers that I never want to play just to unlock their perks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I dumped a bunch into Billy and I dumped a bunch into Trapper just to get their perks in the pool, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why'd they do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: which was an artifact on the loading screen that was part of the scaffolding holding up a street sign in the background of the lobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes, because now it's an icon, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Literally an icon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have made icons of it, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have icons that I made.
[SPEAKER_05]: A player icon, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can get it as a player badge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for those who are in chat, I will just use my little emote that I made of Jim Beam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jim the Beam.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also get a shirt that says RIP Jim the Beam.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made it myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, back to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there were already things going on and they put out a fix for it and said that they were delaying more DLC to do a quality of life thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what happened at the 2v8, now I will rewind and say that I didn't exactly experience this, but it did happen when the 2v8 event came out on October 20th.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was an outage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hundreds of people couldn't play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Matchmaking was having problems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game wasn't launching.
[SPEAKER_03]: Login issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: High latency.
[SPEAKER_03]: I experienced the latency problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played for maybe two hours and then switched to, I think, Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for me, the biggest way I get latency is input lag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would rather just have the game be slow than have input lag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because then there's seconds where I can't control my character because she's still walking based on the last command that I put in.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it was pretty crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was really just a massive failure of launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this was scheduled to run from August 19th through the 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're still waiting to see if they're going to extend it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as an apology to everybody, they have issued out 5 million blood points to everybody, which, as I recall, is the current cap for blood points.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I said it before, you can get a lot of levels with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can put it on so many different characters, but I'm trying to P100 my pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've P100 Meg.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pig's turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, you have to claim this no later than September 2nd at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eastern Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, so they haven't said exactly what the issue was, but it did affect so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: It lasted about two hours, and I felt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing, though, is that if you are just thinking of coming back to Dead by Daylight, even if you don't play during this event, you can still get 50,000 blood points daily just by logging in and going into your inbox and claiming it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are also, I think, because a community thing was met, there's also some bonus badges and things that you can get for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of it will be in your inbox in-game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I logged in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't logged in in a while and collected a bunch of free stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like, okay, neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'll play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe one of these days I will give in to DarkSakura going, Rob, play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, play.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should play tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do after DragonCon at this point.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about your subby?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about your subbython?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm here doing your next little subbython.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to not say it live, but now that you brought it up... Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm having a subathon on my channel, DarkSakuraTTV, because I'm trying to raise money for my hotel room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I have enough now, but I want to make sure I have extra money in case, you know, emergencies happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's going to be the 13th, September 13th, which is a Saturday at 11 o'clock a.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pacific time till 11 p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can pay me to go longer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did that during your last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did go longer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Rob, I went longer than I was paid to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I opened my purse and dumped out all my bits and gave them to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went 14 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You, too, can watch me be unintelligible at the 14-hour mark.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the longest I could play a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I went longer also because Shay popped on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, I'm playing with Shay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know Shay is a treasure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shay is a small treasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we gotta get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other quick things for your sub-a-thon, September 13th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe my room will be clean and I can actually use my camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just, you know, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in Europe and they're eight or nine hours ahead and they're not going to do it in the middle of the night.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, it's going to be early.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've got a lot of work commitments and things I have to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I could not really follow that until later, much later in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I kind of had to look at the recaps.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like when you look at the recaps, it's not as impactful as actually watching a lot of those trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I tried to go back and watch a few, but I will admit I didn't watch everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Loki, what were some of the things that caught your eye?
[SPEAKER_05]: What should we be aware of from Gamescom?
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was even stuff that was in the pre-show as well that I don't think we have on this list here, but I can try to recall it from my memory.
[SPEAKER_01]: So starting things off in the most randomly possible way, the announcement of Bubsy 4D.
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who asked for this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's the game no one asked for.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know who asked for it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Atari.
[SPEAKER_01]: Atari asked for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they're like, hey, those kids are playing Bubsy.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to get in on that Bubsy train.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember when little Sarah was growing up, she used to play this game called Bubsy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we do another Bubsy?
[SPEAKER_01]: We need our own mascot platformer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see who we got.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bubsy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bubsy's got the stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And while we're at it, let's reboot Yars Revenge again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, let's do it again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's bring back Yonoid.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: The character that you don't have anymore, but you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, so they had that.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also a really cool trailer for Densha Attack, which is this just absolutely insane anime jet set radio looking thing where you're a train that grinds rails and flies into the air and fights things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm down.
[SPEAKER_01]: Give me that, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that looked amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was some other stuff too, but I don't remember what those were.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, so the actual Gamescom stuff though, lots of announcements.
[SPEAKER_01]: The biggest one, of course, is that, you know, Silksong still coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was then later announced in their own like direct event that it's coming out very soon, actually, in just a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Call of Duty Black Ops 7 has a gameplay trailer and it looks like some of the Far Cry Dream sequences and apparently this is something that was also in Black Ops 6.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it looks fucking stupid, but you know, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember back in my day when Call of Duty was a military shooter game, not this bullshit Fortnite shit, but apparently they're going all in on bullshit Fortnite shit, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: More power to them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then we had trailer for Lords of the Fallen 2, which looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very excited to see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sekiro No Defeat looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the games I'm most excited about that was announced was LEGO Batman Legacy of the Dark Knight, which is kind of a brand new Batman LEGO game, because they haven't done that in like...
[SPEAKER_01]: God, years, over 10 years.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what's cool about it though is it follows not only like the Arkham games, but it seems like the movies and like other stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a culmination of all of the Batman media empire, but now all together with the Lego humor and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I am 100% down to check that out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um,
[SPEAKER_01]: Warhammer 40k, Dawn of War 4 we got to see a trailer for that coming out next year also a new crossover with Monster Hunter Wilds I think they did this recently with Final Fantasy 14 now it's going the other way so now you have Final Fantasy 14 stuff coming into Monster Hunter Wilds so they showed off Chocobos and stuff like that that's coming in October
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Onimusha, The Way of the Sword Looks pretty cool, that's also set for next year We've got a trailer, which funny enough I actually saw this before I saw Opening Night Live But a trailer for Season 2 of Fallout, the TV show Looks great, I'm excited, it's supposed to be coming out in December So can't wait to see it, I will binge the hell out of that
[SPEAKER_05]: My buddy Aria Snark saw that trailer and screencapped something and put it on her Instagram and said, this isn't a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like there's some fight going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's some like building looking thing and went, this is the empty grocery store behind my house.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just thought that was so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just LA things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You gotta use what you got.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love seeing places that I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love seeing things, especially when they don't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, the famous one I can think of is that old 90s ABC TGIF show, Step by Step.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step by step a day, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Patrick Duffy show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Suzanne Somers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the opening of that is them all getting on a roller coaster, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And that roller coaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: so if you ever watch the opening to that show and you see the ocean roaming up against that's all fucking CGI that's the parking lot for the theme park that they just it's so funny everyone's cars are underwater the worst part about that though is it's rotoed so bad so like as you're watching the ocean like the coastline just like keeps shifting like I remember that from watching that show like how ridiculous that looked it's like
[SPEAKER_01]: Fine, okay, this looks stupid, but okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the great magic mountain flood of 1994, and Suzanne Somers had to row to- This is what happens, global warming, see?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone's hell happy, you know, but it's-
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: We have an announcement for John Carpenter's Toxic Commando that's expected out early next year as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Death by Scrolling is a new game by Ron Gilbert.
[SPEAKER_01]: A little bit different style of game, but it's like a roguelite where the screen is constantly scrolling and apparently the Grim Reaper is trying to kill you as well during all this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one looked interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one caught my eye.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the name too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so it looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had Zero Parades, I guess, which is by the developers of Disco Elysium.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Darkest Files.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that was the one that was, I think, like, you're like hunting Nazis or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they came out and talked about how Nazis are bad, which, I mean, do we really need to say that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess we really do nowadays.
[SPEAKER_01]: another trailer for Ninja Gaiden 4 now it's coming out October 21st Cinder City which apparently I guess it looks like Warframe I'm not familiar it's a new MMO shooter also Time Takers some third-person shooter game we had a new trailer for Silent Hill F that's showing off the the gameplay it's
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we had La Divinia Comedia, and that looks like another Souls-like type game, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kronos the New Dawn, I swear the character in this reminds me of Bioshock's The Big Daddies, but yeah, it's a survival horror game, looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's also being done by Bloober Team, and that is coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ironically enough, also in September, actually September 5th, so next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then we have a new trailer for The Outer Worlds 2 starring Ben Schwartz.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, look for that October 29th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Vampire of the Masquerade Bloodlines 2 is going to be coming out October 21st.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we have a new trailer for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cult of the Lamb, Woolhaven.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a, I think, DLC.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's coming out next year as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks cute and culty, which I think is the point.
[SPEAKER_01]: World of Warcraft Midnight, the 11th expansion for World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it really the 11th?
[SPEAKER_01]: Holy smokes.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is coming out next year and I don't know anything about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the one that's going to bring player housing, which is a thing in Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been other MMOs that have had this as well, but World of Warcraft's kind of doing its own thing with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it really sounds like they're trying to do some things differently to fix some of the bitches people have about Final Fantasy XIV's housing.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, you don't have to bid on lots.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody can have a house if you do the quest for it and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: and yeah that part sounds really neat and they have another system they're building into it is something called Prey the Prey system not like Holy Church but like the video game P-R-E-Y type of thing meaning the Predator and the Prey and that's actually exactly what it is is that while you're doing quests if you turn on this motor I think you have to talk to a quest keeper to do it you can actually be hunted by an NPC while you're doing quests that could come out at any time and try to get you
[SPEAKER_05]: It sort of makes me think of like trying to play on the old PvP realms.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really sounds like that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, it sounds like there's some interesting new features.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think WoW has been really good actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would I want that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Quest Rewards, Glory, Fame, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's not worth being jump-scared by the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is optional, so if you don't want it, don't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I will say WoW for me has been on an upswing ever since that really shitty expansion that made Sylvanas the main baddie.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a terrible expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember what it was called.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfector.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's been a lot better since Dragonflight was pretty good and this most recent one, War Within, was pretty darn good as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I can't say I will stay subbed forever to World of Warcraft, but I will buy the expansion and renew my sub.
[SPEAKER_05]: I enjoy WoW enough to play through the main story.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might have to go back to it if I've got a guild to play in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't think I have a guild anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it time to rebuild Danger Squad?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if the Game Boy kids are full Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if they're in WoW at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like Spike and John might have tried one of these recent ones, but I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm
[SPEAKER_01]: Project Spectrum Ghosts of Yotai
[SPEAKER_01]: Ghosts of Yotai Legends we're showing that off that's coming out now October 2nd and we had Resident Evil Requiem a new trailer for that as well that of course is announced for February 27th next year and then the big one Black Myth Zonghui which is a brand new Black Myth game following Black Myth Wukong looks fantastic another game of the year contender probably
[SPEAKER_01]: probably.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so lots of, I think what was interesting about that, it was a lot of kind of, I don't know, for me it was a lot of games I wasn't expecting to hear about.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, it's cool, but I feel like outside of what you just talked about, the news this week was very light.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like we made a lot of space for Gamescom and I feel like the news we got, I don't know, hasn't exactly been, you know, it filled a couple of days of buzz, but because they didn't do a lot of shadow drops, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that He-Man game shadow dropped?
[SPEAKER_01]: That was, I don't remember, but that was also one that was shown off in the pre-show as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the He-Man game, and that looked pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Reminded me a lot of, like, Golden Axe.
[SPEAKER_01]: But seriously, go pre-order, or not pre-order, go wishlist Densha Attack.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: I posted the trailer in Discord.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_05]: well the other thing about that He-Man game that kind of caught my eye is that He-Man has never really had a good video game I'm sorry like and like quick name a He-Man video game there haven't there's been don't think there has been no there's no there has there's been like seven of them one was on the Game Boy Advance Bobby
[SPEAKER_03]: brought up a Commodore 64 one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there were like three of them on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a text adventure game, I believe, at one point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the reality is, and I'm sure somebody in chat is going to say, you're wrong, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of them were particularly memorable, or we wouldn't be sitting here going, wow,
[SPEAKER_05]: A He-Man side-scroller, like, Ninja Turtles fighting game-looking thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe nobody did this before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we wouldn't be saying that if we had, you know, other He-Man games that were extremely memorable.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I'm excited for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now we need to take all these properties that are cool, like, you know, the Power Rangers, Ninja Turtles, He-Man...
[SPEAKER_01]: Smash them all together.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's smash them all together.
[SPEAKER_05]: All those games have had all those franchises have had relatively successful games recently.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's like 80s, 80s, 90s, you know, Saturday mornings, Saturday morning Smackdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure a lot of people would play the hell out of that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get some G.I.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joe in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, we'll throw in She-Ra, you know, like all sorts of and screech from Saved by the Bell just because.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, that guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That guy kind of turned out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Canceled.
[SPEAKER_05]: That guy kind of turned out a little crazy McGee, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine, then how about Slater?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Slater?
[SPEAKER_05]: Slater from Saved by the Bell.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because he's also bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he?
[SPEAKER_05]: What did he do?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about Urkel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Urkel wasn't Saturday morning, was he?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eh, he's TGIF or like Tuesday or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, Urkel had a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't he?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Urkel had a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that mean then that we have to have Ed Grimley?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: so then you'd have to whatever well if we're doing that then we might as well open it up to like 80s Nickelodeon and be like you know what we're gonna have like the unicorn from Eureka's Castle's gonna be here the fucking puppet from uh Pinwheel or no today's David the security guard from today's special uh
[SPEAKER_05]: Barf Barf from uh you can't do that on television I'm Rob I'm so happy you brought up today's special because I fucking loved that show I who didn't that show is if you're if you're up you have to be a very specific age range like you had to have little brothers who were super into it
[SPEAKER_01]: Hell yeah, I get Cherry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cherry in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, from Pee Wee's Playhouse.
[SPEAKER_01]: See?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: All of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: contender is sitting right in front of your fucking noses, and you license holders can't get your shit together.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could all be sitting on mountains of cash if you would just license your 40-year-old properties.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically Mugen at that point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and you know, though... Mugen's not real.
[SPEAKER_03]: They all have...
[SPEAKER_03]: They all have to do the other Saturday Morning Classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every whatever of this has to end in a Soul Train line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like during the credits.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the credits.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that was the other Saturday thing was watching Soul Train.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I watched Soul Train.
[SPEAKER_05]: Martello4 in chat says fucking Rob bringing back Eureka's Castle memory unlocked oh you want let's go to the deep let's go to the deep cuts y'all want turkey television come on let's let's bring that on there too uh oh oh Deft Deft just won the chat for tonight Sabato Higante I never heard of that until just now oh my god Sabato Higante was like
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it was on... Yeah, I grew up in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, you didn't... Did they not get the Spanish channel in Alabama?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I guess... Well, if they did, no one in my family ever watched it because I come from a bunch of redneck assholes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, it's just, we... You just needed bigger rabbit ears on your TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just wasn't as big of a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't as big of a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just the South.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never even knew what a quinceañera was until I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Martello4 in chat says, anything before Hey Dude is purely historical for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that's kind of that early 90s Nickelodeon is kind of where I draw the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would accept the characters from Hey Dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would accept Marsha Brady when she was on Hey Dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would accept her as a playable character.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would accept the little redhead punk guy from Salute Your Shorts could be a character.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would accept
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Moe!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Moe!
[SPEAKER_05]: Moe!
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Moe!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm playing the aggro Craig.
[SPEAKER_01]: I get to be the aggro Craig, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, why isn't this a thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you guys are just going off and now Fifth Dream is bringing Vicky the Robot into this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Y'all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you went on a rabbit hole reading about behind-the-scenes stuff for Small Wonder, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and so this was a big what they call an anomaly event where the two teams because this is a Ingers is very player versus player that's the other thing that some people like about it some people don't like about it but I've always enjoyed it it gets it motivates me to go to places even within my own town that I wouldn't usually go to so and Rin Mari in chat says ENL gang rise up we
[SPEAKER_05]: were like honestly I wasn't doing much because there wasn't much to do but I really felt like this time like there was you know a lot of activity going on uh me and one of my best friends who plays the game Johnny we were running from portal to portal to to try to do a link to what's called like a shard we were doing all this stuff um so yeah we were having a lot of fun yeah it was nerdy it was nerdy but it was I got like 20,000 steps that Saturday so but
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a lot like we drove up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So me and two of my buddies that I know from the game, we drove up on Friday and drove back on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is about a 10 hour drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's maybe eight and a half actually on the highway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, factoring gas, coffee.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's a long day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God my friends went because that would have been a really long drive by myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I probably would have flown if I was by myself, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was it was a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next weekend, however, is Labor Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as I've been doing for the last decade, I'm going to DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I will be at DragonCon and I am really, really excited about the show this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can finally tell you because the app was released while we were out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can tell you some of these pretty cool panels I'm going to be a part of.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just want to quickly run down my schedule for those that may be going to DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can see a picture version of this over on my BlueSky, which is robroberts.bsky.social, or my Instagram, which is MrMRRobRoberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see them, MrRobRoberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say if you want to meet and say hello, the best time to say hello to myself and Bobby Blackwolf, who's also going from the Voice Geeks Network, because this is his backyard, but it's still like a vacation for him.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: HiltonGallerySX
[SPEAKER_05]: This is for people to meet each other and mingle and just get to know each other from the digital media track because there's a lot of people that talk on the Discord.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's always like, when are we meeting up at con?
[SPEAKER_05]: When are we meeting up in con?
[SPEAKER_05]: So last year, Bobby and I were like, we should have a meetup at con that's like official.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we did a thing, but not a lot of people showed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I honestly, in retrospection, think it should not have been called the VOG Network Presents meeting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mixer, or whatever we called it last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: This year, we kept our name out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's in the description.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it says Voice Geeks Network in the description, but this is simply called Content Creator Networking and Mixer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to know where do I meet other people that do other... For me, the most interesting thing about it is I meet people that main YouTube or TikTok, which are venues I'm less familiar with than Twitch or podcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, that'll be for about an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come by and say hello to myself and Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is really...
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: On Friday, I will plug this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one of Bobby's events, but I'm going to really try to go too because I actually don't have any digital media panels except for the one on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Bobby's going to be doing one at 2.30 called the Podcast Track 20th Anniversary Panel because digital media started as the podcast tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the digital media podcast track.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this track has meant a lot to me over the years too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just want to go and make a cameo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though Bobby's on the panel, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to be in the room and heckle.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's my plan.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Friday at 2.30 also in Galleria 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the first big panel, I'm fortunate that as of last year I'm working with the main programming track at DragonCon and I feel myself, I consider myself very lucky and fortunate to be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so happy that they will have me because now I get to do some big panels such as this one that's going to be Friday at 4pm in the Atrium.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is...
[SPEAKER_05]: Once Upon a Time Once Upon a Time
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was called Once.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Once, dot, dot, dot, and sometimes you would see it stylized upon a time, but Once was the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have six people that were on that show, including Regina.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Hook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hook is on the panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we got a lot of really cool people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's on Friday at 4 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saturday is a pretty big day for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is wild.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe this is happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Saturday, and Ranma, yes, I am cosplaying, and I'll come back to that question in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is all because of my friend Victoria, Arya Snark, who is going to her first DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are doing a couples cosplay on Saturday night, and I'll explain that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Saturday at 11.30 a.m., I am doing a panel also in the atrium with the cast from the Fox television show Bones.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: In the West and Peachtree, Saturday at 2.30, Baldur's Gate 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once again, we have the other half of the cast of Baldur's Gate 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sadly, nobody last year is coming back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Tim Downey, who played Gale, will be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Emma Gregory, who played Minthara, will be on that panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sissy Jones, the Absolute, will be on that panel as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Jones, who played Halson, will be there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they just announced, it was only going to be those five, and this is how things change.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were able to secure last week, Amelia Tyler, the narrator, is going to be there as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_03]: She is a treasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they all are great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every fucking person in that game gives an award-winning performance.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why we are still talking about this game this far after the launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, obviously, Amelia in her role frames the whole stinking thing and is your biggest introduction to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love her outtakes, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh man, I'm just like, I'm hyped for that panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is a Q&A panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, please come ask questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll have a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have... Ask her if she'll narrate my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is gaming related.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have gaming related stuff too.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is super gaming related.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the Westin and the Augusta E-H rooms on Saturday at 4 o'clock, I'll be doing a panel called The Way of the Loremaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is just myself and Sean Copeland, who is with Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is the Blizzard Loremaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is the keeper of the lore at Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny because I attended this panel as a fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went just because that was the year Diablo 4 launched, and I just wanted to hear all about the Diablo lore and what went into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I've been on this panel on the other side in the audience, and so I'm very honored to be sitting and being the one to moderate the questions for Sean about the Blizzard lore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm very excited about that panel and that opportunity.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is Saturday at 4 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to plug a panel that's not mine, but I really want to try to drive attendance because this is also a gaming-related panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So also on Saturday at 7 o'clock at night in the Westin E3H room, Bobby is going to be hosting the first-ever Speedrun Showcase at...
[SPEAKER_05]: DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be speedrunning with... Actually, Bobby's not speedrunning.
[SPEAKER_05]: A very popular Twitch name.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this guy's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He gives off game show host energy, which I love.
[SPEAKER_05]: An Eternal Enigma is going to be the one that's actually speedrunning Silent Hill 4 The Room.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the reason why I shout that out is that I want butts in the seats at this because this is...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S
[SPEAKER_05]: which she has a from the stage version of Wicked she has an amazing Elphaba outfit that she's wearing I think Sunday but Saturday she's put together an all new costume and she is going to be dressed as Fiona from the 1999 2000 that era classic Josie and the Pussycats that was the character Parker Posey played so she said Rob it would be very easy for you to dress as Wyatt and I said Alan Cumming
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm in.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to dress as Wyatt.
[SPEAKER_05]: But her outfit, like she literally, so it's from the end of the movie where she's in that dress and it has 400 like vinyl mega records, decals on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She made that fucking dress.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's incredible.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's been detailing it on her Instagram.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so I'm going to go as Wyatt to compliment her Fiona, but that is going to be Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to wear that during my panels because that would be a little weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't want
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna say it's unprofessional because I know other moderators do cosplay, but I just feel like it takes it out of the zone a little bit for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: For me, in my right headspace, so I'm gonna do that at night.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you might catch me at that speedrun showcase for a little bit dressed as that, but that's, yeah, that's the cosplay I am bringing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm almost done, sorry, but I have two other panels to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am going to be, and I just clicked off of it on the app.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can find me in the app under speakers, Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know nobody is going to the con just to see me, but if you're curious where I'm at, that's a good way to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sunday at 10 a.m.,
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is over in the Hilton Grand West.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this is where I did a Lower Decks panel last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in the Hilton Grand West, we have the Shaolin Brotherhood, The Journey of Liu Kang and Kung Lao.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is a Mortal Kombat movie panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's the recent reboot from 2020.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the sequel, what they can say about it, I'm sure will come up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we have Ludi Lin who played...
[SPEAKER_05]: Luke Kang, and Max Wang who played Kung Lao so very excited about that they will be on that panel with me talking about the Mortal Kombat films and we will do Q&A at that one and then again another pinch me moment I can't believe I'm being asked to do this but once again in the atrium on Sunday at 1130 a.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Wars panel I've been asked back to do the Star Wars hodgepodge panel and
[SPEAKER_05]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is quite the hodgepodge of celebrities from the Star Wars universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am so honored that I will get to sit down with John Boyega, who plays Finn, of course, the Stormtrooper in the movie trilogy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on that panel, Diana Lee Inosanto, who plays Morgan Elsbeth in The Mandalorian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Simon...
[SPEAKER_05]: Cassian Etis, who plays Axe Woves, I think in like four episodes of The Mandalorian.
[SPEAKER_05]: So a little bit more of a minor part, but had an important arc in The Mandalorian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Emily Swallow, who also was in The Mandalorian as the Armorer.
[SPEAKER_03]: She is amazing for the record.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was also in Supernatural.
[SPEAKER_05]: as Lilith.
[SPEAKER_05]: but he is a prolific voice actor and it's gaming related.
[SPEAKER_05]: He played Starkiller in Star Wars The Force Unleashed and Force Unleashed 2 and the Soul Calibur cameo for Starkiller.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Sam Witwer.
[SPEAKER_05]: He also played Darth Maul in a lot of the animated projects and Emperor Palpatine in a few of them as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's a very prolific Star Wars type of person in a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a very... This is that kind of infamous DragonCon hodgepodge of people that are related to the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm very curious to hear how the Q&A is going to go at that panel when you've got John Boyega, you've got some very talented folks that were on The Mandalorian, and you have animated and video game universe kind of people all
[SPEAKER_05]: All on the same panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really excited to see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Last year's Star Wars panel was a very similar sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were all on different shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had a blast.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like to think the audience did too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think we'll have a blast again this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very excited for this year's DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of can't believe it's Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm leaving on Wednesday, so I have to pinch myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I bought some last-minute outfits.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have some new loud-ass shirts and loud pants to wear on some of these panels.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm very, very looking forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to rock the bald.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm ditching the hats this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I may take one or two cabi hats, but overall, I'm going to rock the bald this year, which is new for me, too, on television.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm very excited for all of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's talk about our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we have been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Dead by Daylight, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played Palia, I've played Mass Effect, and then whatever I'm playing on my phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing big, just my usuals.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, then we'll go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I've been fighting PC stuff this week, but mostly I've been...
[SPEAKER_01]: finishing up the Slumber Dome, which was my massive project that I was working on on our Channel 64 SMP.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a massive battle arena with a custom data pack that I coded.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's basically a PvE arena with 20 different randomized waves of mobs you get to fight, and I mean, it goes on forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get gear, you get power-ups, items, all sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's like a full...
[SPEAKER_01]: Fledged game with custom music, audio, visuals, all the flair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fireworks, there's fireworks in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should have my new episode out about it tonight, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like I said, I've been fighting, like, there were some weird random crash issues I had with my PC that I think I've sorted out, but I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it caused a lot of weird stuff to happen, like
[SPEAKER_01]: Streamlabs OBS, which I've been trying to get away from for a while now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It basically wiped all the settings in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or no, it didn't wipe all the settings.
[SPEAKER_01]: It got to a point where it was incredibly choppy in Streamlabs OBS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like I was recording playback.
[SPEAKER_01]: My view is like 100% fine, 120 FPS or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the capture, it's like 2 FPS.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, okay, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I dumped that finally, which I should have done a while ago, but I'm now in vanilla OBS, and everything's working fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: After I got past some learning curve stuff with the extra inputs and stuff that it has in there, it has like a default, like...
[SPEAKER_01]: Game Audio and a default mic capture in there that's always set and so I had to like figure out that that was in there and take it out so that I have better control because I don't like to record my mic audio in OBS when I record I record separate so in case if I flub something or I want to rearrange where my audio is plus I'm able to put more filters on top of it that kind of
[SPEAKER_01]: And then Bellatro, I was playing a little bit of Bellatro
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I played a little of that too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's about it, I think.
Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So obviously there was the Ingress stuff going on, so that counts.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also, you know I'm still playing Final Fantasy XI on the Horizon server.
[SPEAKER_05]: I even did a stream and had some people that are also playing on Horizon dip in, and that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very supportive community.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of talking about this where I was like, I think a good chunk of the people that are playing Horizon...
[SPEAKER_05]: are people that were playing Final Fantasy XI in their teens and 20s.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so now it's like a late 30s and 40s crowd.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so there's just... I'm just going to keep it real.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a certain level of maturity that comes with that, I think, that you don't have as many edgelords as maybe play other MMOs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not to say those don't exist.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen a couple questionable...
[SPEAKER_05]: type of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for the most part, I've really enjoyed the community with Horizon and dipping back into Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got my Red Mage to level 30, which means I get to unlock the advanced jobs next.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be my next big thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the wild thing is, so like Loki, you remember the Final Fantasy XI days, and DarkSakura, you too, to an extent.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did a couple of Dunes parties, but otherwise, these parties have been in places like
[SPEAKER_05]: Sarah Magoo, Champagne, Palboro, or excuse me, Rollenberry Fields was one of them, Maze of Chakrami.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's zones that you don't usually go to, but the way Horizon sort of, I think they rebalanced some of the monster distribution and made some other XP camps so everybody wasn't always in the same fucking place.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I never did an XP party in Quiffham Island, which in the old vanilla days was like your level 20 to 30 zone.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never did a party there, and I'm level 30, which is wild.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I, I'm, I'm, again, I'm just loving the experience there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was been sinking a lot of hours than I care to admit on 11, but it's a lot of core memories unlocked for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just, I've been relatively enjoying the experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did promise.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm getting stuck on Quiff of Mailand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like you get stuck back in the jungle there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was just like, you're thinking of Kazam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're right, you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still collecting my Kazam keys, which now I can solo because there's less pressure to go there until you're more in your 30s and 40s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was it Juno?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's right, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's with the giant green ogre things are out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's that it looks very dark.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Quiff of Myland.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just remember the leeches and the worms, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like playing this has been a lot of like, oh, core memory unlocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and now I've been learning thanks to watching some other streamers and looking at some YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I learned how to unlock the frames per second so that you can play the game or I should say cap it at 60 frames.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is very smooth and looks great and some of the other graphical upgrades which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I did say I would play other games as well too and I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I checked out a free game that was on Epic Game Store which was called Hidden Folks and
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So I like it as a chill type of game and as a very sort of like pick up, easy play.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can save your spot, come back to it later, almost like a crossword puzzle or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: The one questionable choice in this game is that all of the sound effects is like somebody beatboxing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like somebody did a bloop, bloop, beep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every time you click something, it makes some funky noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a big fan of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I actually try to disable sounds when I play the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the game itself, I am enjoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand the stylistic choice to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's my one feedback on that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But otherwise, especially knowing that it is a freebie, or at least I think was last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it is anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know they get paid by Epic, so that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: so I checked out that game and then I've been playing some retro games too just going through some NES classics but something's fucky with my NES emulator right now because I'll play the game for five minutes and it'll be great and then all of a sudden five minutes in I'll start getting frame skip like bad like on a game like fucking Donkey Kong that should not be getting the bad like lag and stuff and slow down and it's not like NES you know hardware slow down or anything like that it's something to do with the emulator and retro arc I gotta figure out what the fuck's going on
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody, I've been trying to, you know, sleuth online.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like it could be something like the games recording element or something could be screwed it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I got to go in and see if I can disable that because that would make a lot of sense as to it's fine for five minutes and then suddenly starts acting fucky would make sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something like some sort of buffer in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to look into that and try to fix it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody had said, just delete your configuration file and let RetroArch make a new one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might just do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: See if that fixes it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have some more news to get into, so I'm going to go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Start us off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, let's talk a little bit about Black Ops 7, my favorite game!
[SPEAKER_01]: So one of the things that was definitely noticeable in Black Ops 6 last year was some of the questionable choices that seem to be coming from AI generative art use in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the most notable example of that would have been the six-figured zombie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, to be fair,
[SPEAKER_01]: Call of Duty does do some silly stuff with the zombies where the number of fingers is the version of the game so it could technically be that but
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: We live in a world now where there's AI tools.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think our official statement is, we said last year around Black Ops 6, is that everything that goes into the game is touched by the team 100%.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have generative AI tools to help us, but none of that goes into the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, there are some things that look like they've gone straight into the game and it looks like no one's touched it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he said, well, it was probably by accident.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it was never the intention for it to be just dumped in the game like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've come out and been very clear that we use these tools to help the team, but they do not replace any of the fantastic team members.
[SPEAKER_01]: that we have and what they're doing with the final touches and building the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I have to wonder though, like, you know, when you're crunching your team like this that cut, you know, corners will be cut and that they might do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, and then of course, you know, they asked him straight up, hey, what about Santa Claus with six fingers there?
[SPEAKER_01]: And he's like, well, not my department, but I know the team that's actually looking at stuff and making sure that's not shipped.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how we fix it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You take no responsibility for the stuff that's out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you're like, oh, no, we touch everything and then you show them, well, no, actually you don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he's like, not my problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That doesn't fill me with confidence.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, expect more AI slop in the near future.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guarantee that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you all know I'm not a fan of the generative AI, especially as replacement art.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think we've seen a lot of companies that have used it for placeholder projects.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, everything is...
[SPEAKER_05]: about Magic the Gathering was recently put to the fire a little bit because they had sort of been caught using some AI and their response was to sort of deflect and blame Adobe's generative fill because what they were doing, I guess they were taking the 2D card, which obviously Magic has some stellar human art behind it, but it sounded like they were-
[SPEAKER_05]: Boris Vallejo for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Julie Bell.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were taking the 2D card art and they had to, for certain things, expand it into 3D box space.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were using Adobe Generative Fill to do it and they got caught doing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you think generative in that means?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not generated out of space by magic artists that live in the cosmos.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's AI that's doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to see more of these places where the tools are sort of unavoidable.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Bobby brings up a great point in this too in our chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf says all of these companies are forcing AI into all their products because nobody was using it when it was extra.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're just bundling it in and raising the base price.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is, yeah, that's a huge thing that's happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft obviously did that pretty recently with Office.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, now you have fucking Copilot in Notepad, which nobody asked for, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just, I definitely think, and while you can turn that off in Notepad, and I did, it's wild to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand a lot of people are gonna combat that with the computing power it uses and all of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I would say that train has already left the station.
[SPEAKER_05]: These companies are already incorporating AI into all of these different ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think we are left with where do we as consumers
[SPEAKER_05]: Draw those lines of what are we willing to pay for that comes out of AI and what are we going to reject?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think you've already seen that in the gaming space that when generative AI is used to basically do the art assets in a game, people are not fucking interested in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're about as interested in that as they were the NFT type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually read an article in Forbes not long ago that was talking about how it's only 5% of company AI initiatives actually show any success, that the majority of them are failing and losing money for companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think especially where people are thinking AI is going to replace people, I think a lot of companies are going to get what they pay for in that regard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Martello4 says, AI should be regulated heavily and they know it because of the reasons they are going to and are using it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and actually I think there's a pretty big lawsuit against MidJourney?
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those AI?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's coming from Hollywood because they basically went to MidJourney and said, paint me a picture of Shrek.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it made the copyright and trademark character Shrek.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paint me a picture of Jasmine from Aladdin and it spat out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's spitting out copyright and trademark things so Hollywood is bringing down its iron fist and all of its lawyers on AI.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that is the battle that needs to be fought and needs to be fought quickly because they are raising some good points.
[SPEAKER_05]: in that particular circumstance with all the generative stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it'd be interesting to see what comes of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I agree, AI needs to be regulated.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when we can't fucking get trademark and patent and all this other law updated, I could go on a whole other tangent about what the drag performer Lexi Love is going through right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: because she's sending cease and desist things to the venue when nobody gives a fuck who this other person is.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're a no-name performer in Hollywood that is using this to profit off of what a trans woman has done on television and the past she's drawn for herself.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really sick, to be quite honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the type of thing where it's like, trademark law is really fucked right now that she has the ability to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: She, being the adult performer, has the ability to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hope the drag performer takes her ass to court because the trademark had lapsed and gets that fucking thing yanked away from her.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I bet it reminds me a lot of how the, and then sues her ass for getting all those things canceled, reminds me of when somebody tried to, was it trademark or patent?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was patent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that'll happen in that scenario.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, I know we're getting a long way from AI, but my point being is that when we can't regulate these other laws that were written decades ago, the technology is moving faster than the laws.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the problem is all the lawmakers are consumed with dumb fucking shit right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and even that there are people today using outdated laws to make other legislation, even to push more governmental control that needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am not done.
[SPEAKER_05]: What it regulates the companies to store because the companies basically have to store your proof of identification that you're an adult.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Blue Sky is like, we're not taking part in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not going to store that type of sensitive information on our end.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's because of that they're saying, we're just going to pull Blue Sky from Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have the resources to enforce that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then good for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if the people care enough about it, they'll do something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, yeah, and as Stuart Hunter-Matt says, too many stupid wars on a lot of fronts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now it's this whole, you know, bullshit over gerrymandering.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're trying to distract us.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all trying to distract us from the important things going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could pass a constitutional amendment, and I bet most people, most rational people, when not sitting next to a television, most rational people would agree with all 50 states ought to have independent districting commissions that draw the maps.
[SPEAKER_05]: All 50 states ought to have that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that could be a thing that they could put in the Constitution.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it would end all of this other garbage, no matter what side of the fence you're on.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're Texas, Newsom, no matter where you sit, that could end relatively quickly with a constitutional amendment.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll never do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No politician would agree to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, everything is too fucking...
[SPEAKER_05]: Black and White now, and two extreme, to one end.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is no more middle ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: None.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have also said on repeat that I think that the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: is too big for proper governance.
[SPEAKER_03]: By size and by population.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, it's not on our show roll tonight, but the prices of the PlayStation 5 went up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does anyone want to guess why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of a dumpster?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're terrific?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you all know the answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're terrific.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just the world we live in, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, there are things to bring us joy and merriment in times of strife, and that would be Kirby Air Riders.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love Kirby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Kirby always makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kirby always makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they're putting Kirby on ketchup bottles now, because Kirby makes people happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's an all-new Kirby game, as you know, that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Kirby Air Riders.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, this was the game that was originally on the GameCube, but they are doing an all-new version for the Nintendo Switch 2, and it's coming out November 20th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was a whole direct that they did that is showing off the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do question Nintendo putting out two racing games as flagship titles in the same year and this early on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure that's the right strategy, but I also realize they're very different types of racing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know y'all are typing right now to correct me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I realize they are very different experiences at the end of the day, but it's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a little interesting, that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: But either way, I'll still buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll still play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just recently played the GameCube one for the first time, and I enjoyed myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll check out the sequel for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the direct, they were spotlighting things such as writing techniques and the different forms and traits of the writing machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the boost charge.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you hit the B button, your little machine hits the ground, and you can do a boost charge with that for a boost dash.
[SPEAKER_05]: Specials they were doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Y button does a unique special move for the character.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now there's more than one button to push, for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Air Riders also unleash strategy into your choice of rider.
[SPEAKER_05]: So every rider in the game has different traits that will impact the machine's performance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weight, durability, specials, what you do at close range, and all of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's a lot of faces from Kirby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meta Knight, DDD, Bandana Waddle Dee...
[SPEAKER_05]: Capy, Starman, so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of characters in the Kirby world that are showing up and that'll be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can also inhale or copy an enemy's abilities because of course it's Kirby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why wouldn't you be able to do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's Kirby.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, the game looks really fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: People will be able to get their hands on over at the other convention happening this weekend in Seattle if for whatever reason you made your choice to go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess if you are a resident of the Pacific Northwest maybe it makes more sense to go to that convention.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Let us see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Roblox.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many times have we talked about all the various different user-made games on Roblox that they're making money off of?
[SPEAKER_05]: That are rip-offs of other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not just that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at any rate, Roblox published a post recently where they were talking about some changes, including restricting unrated experiences, which is what they call those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: and to those developers or those who are actively working on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it will be rolling out in the coming months with changing things from allowing users 13 or older to access unrated games.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is coming after a series of lawsuits that are claiming Roblox isn't providing a safe environment for underage users.
[SPEAKER_03]: So for any inappropriate behavior, social hangout experiences that show private spaces like bedrooms or bathrooms will be limited to ID verified users at 17 or older.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will restrict these hangout games that take place
[SPEAKER_03]: The previous ones that take place in those sorts of adult-only places are places like bars and clubs, who are at least 17, and have been ID verified.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they will roll out a tool that automatically detects what they're calling violative scenes, or basically anything that goes against the rules, and that if a server hits enough violations, it automatically gets taken down
[SPEAKER_03]: and they have to work with the Roblox team to get it adjusted to get it back online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, these lawsuits, there's one by Louisiana's Attorney General.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a number of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm going to just read what the company's statement is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any assertion that Roblox would intentionally put our users at risk of exploitation is simply untrue.
[SPEAKER_03]: No system is perfect and bad actors adapt to evade detection including efforts to take users to other platforms where safety standards and moderation practices may differ.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they done fucked up and now they're trying to fix it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Internet2CatchAPredator.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, the predators that you're pointing out too.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: But they do let them know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now he's working with Chris Hansen to make a documentary on the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask you this, Loki, because I don't know Roblox that well besides what I see on TikTok and social media and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it just looks like – I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like this weird shithole of the internet, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've said your kids have played that before and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's your take on all of this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this a big part of the platform based on your experience watching your kids play Roblox?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like –
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, I mean, I think with the platform, you can kind of look at it like Steam almost.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or even like just a lot of the other marketplaces where you have some content that's quality, some content that's not great, but it's like, it's still...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, instead of addressing those things that people have been complaining about saying like, yeah, there's inappropriate stuff on here.
[SPEAKER_01]: They only react to it when there's a big stink made about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So like, for example, one of the things that Schlepp brought up in his videos were the only time that they would ever take one of these people that have been arrested, you know, off of their platform was when he made a big video about it that got millions of views.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now, this whole reaction to his videos, that's the only reason that they're acting now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they even keep changing stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, well, wait a second, this is adult-only content.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are you making the age to see it 17?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why is it not 18?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, why are you doing this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are you exerting more effort to protect the pedophiles or potential predators on your platform versus addressing the issues that people keep bringing up to you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, why do you have a game on your platform or even allow a game on your platform, whether it's marked 17 plus or not, that allows you to just hang out in bathrooms with other people and like chit chat about stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why is that a thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just say no, you can't make those types of games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Done.
[SPEAKER_01]: So easy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Curating your platform maybe I don't know if it's you know one of those things where like they can't curate the platform because then they lose their like title 2 protections or something like that you know like YouTube or something like that um I don't know I don't know what the rules are but like as far as it seems like and it seems to be the agreement from a lot of content creators because even a lot of their partner like streamers and content creators have like said buh-bye we're not dealing with you anymore after all this and
[SPEAKER_01]: they're not doing enough and so I think that this reaction that they're taking right now is not enough and they're losing stock value from it and everything interesting thanks for the take on it because Roblox is really like a foreign world to me I think I downloaded the client on Xbox once and maybe I tried to open it and I was like I don't know what the fuck this is it's like downloading Steam as a platform except it's a platform that you can
[SPEAKER_05]: make content in there's some stuff that's like extremely polished there's some stuff that's popular but it's not polished I do see like some of the stuff like the squid game inspired game like somehow some of that stuff worked its way into my TikTok algorithm but it does it always is weird because I feel like it involves screaming kids like it's and I'm always feel a little weird when I see that stuff on TikTok because I'm like this video is profiting off of some kid having a meltdown on Roblox I don't know that I love that
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a weird environment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't seen that stuff in a long time, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think finally I skipped enough of them where they stopped showing me Roblox videos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thankfully, I've not gotten a single Roblox video except for the Dead by Daylight one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen the Dead by Daylight one too, but that was a little more like one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like watching it would be, to me, it's like watching somebody made a port of Dead by Daylight for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like watching somebody made a port of that for the PS1.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, SGO100 Matt in chat says, my nephew who is nine plays a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully, his parents play with him, so they're able to moderate anything bad there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, as much as I sit here and I go, I don't get Roblox.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm an old man.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think to when I was 12 or 13, I was dialing into BBS systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let me tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: there were definitely things happening in those environments that should not have been like like there were definitely adults that were talking to me when I was 13 which nothing nothing ever crossed the line at the time so it's this isn't that kind of story but looking back on it I go that's fucking weird that that happened when I was 13 you know and so it's just interesting yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, since we were talking about Steam, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Steam is overhauling their Steam review system, and so what the main change is going to be on it is that now, when you look at Steam reviews, they're only going to be of your language.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the reason that they're doing that is because some of the things that maybe, like, say a player that speaks English...
[SPEAKER_01]: is experiencing in a game, especially a game that has a lot of translations and stuff, may be different than somebody that is speaking a different language.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so for those games that have enough reviews, where the threshold is, I think, at least 2,000 reviews total, and of those, at least 200 written in a particular language, those are going to be the ones that kind of split out those reviews by region so that
[SPEAKER_01]: you get a better understanding based on your region you know how the game is like say for example i was playing a jrpg that had just horrible absolutely the worst translations altogether like an english speaker might say oh well this game sucks it's poorly translated where in like say if it was just japanese or something like that it could be just perfectly fine in which case that would not necessarily reflect their experience
[SPEAKER_01]: and so that's kind of where the the breakdown is there and they've um they're trying to do that to improve their system for uh you know including like translations culture cultural references network connections in different regions of the world obviously a thing with servers everywhere so that could be a thing with ping being like really bad in specific spots so it's just to give you a better um a more accurate review for your area i guess
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I think it's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're kind of trying to do some things, especially with, you know, when people want to review bomb shit and, you know, like that you can sort of look at it or a game that's had a journey like No Man's Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very poorly reviewed when it came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We all know what we know the journey of No Man's Sky by now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's received very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, maybe you want...
[SPEAKER_05]: Your review perspective to really only consider what's happened since the last patch or how people feel about, or the other way around, quite frankly, Final Fantasy XIV, not having a lot of great news around it lately, just with this latest expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now they've ceased and desisted a very popular role-playing mod that has a lot of people pissed and are now review bombing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that I think review bombing is a legitimate tactic to take against companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's silly, but it certainly does get attention, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it does also create a lot of noise when you're really trying to figure out what's going on with a particular game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I can't wait to see how this game reviews because y'all haven't shut the fuck up about it for about seven years.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Hollow Knight Silksong, Loki referenced this earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did show up at Gamescom opening night live.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we got a specific sort of announcement release trailer that came later in the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Silksong is coming real soon, like two weeks away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silksong, September 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: So by the next time we have an Orange Lounge Radio, you will all have played Silksong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe not all of you, but some of you that have been chasing this game will have had your chance to play Silksong.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently the game is available to play at Gamescom or was at Nintendo and Xbox booths, so I haven't heard a lot of the hands-on stuff, but that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, that game is finally coming out, and I'm sure it'll be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of the stuff, I just give this game shit because the internet has sort of done this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've turned this into a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how these... On the internet, we tend to turn things into a thing that maybe don't need to be a thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: The release of Hollow Knight Silksong became a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now it's no longer going to be a thing because it's finally fucking coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: We go through different eras in life.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had the Battletoads era.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had the Silksong era.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We can now all move towards Elder Scrolls 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Metroid Prime 4?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because suddenly Nintendo's not talking about it anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you noticed that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did we get a whole direct?
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that game is coming out in 2025.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get a whole direct about Kirby Air Ride.
[SPEAKER_05]: What have they said on Metroid Prime 4?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but Kirby Air Ride is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but still, it's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf suggests GTA 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good example too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't care when it's coming out at this point.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll come out when it comes out and we'll all celebrate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some people might be celebrating this next news article.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think that this is definitely a cause for celebration.
[SPEAKER_03]: I a thousand percent am behind this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Bungie CEO, Pete Parsons, is retiring because shit sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: He spent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, we know the thing about his cars, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: about him spending like two and a half million on classic cars after the layoffs.
[SPEAKER_03]: My favorite quote about him was said about his cars that I hope all of your cars break down.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, he's leaving.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is leaving the studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is going away.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about this one, Julie?
[SPEAKER_05]: May all of your roads have the construction of Highway 50.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking more of may all the roads have the quality of whatever that one leading to Long Beach is, but still...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know which one I'm talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like 107 or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: 705, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: 705, that's the one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's bumpy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never go on that road when you have to pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there is nowhere to stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, back to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Taking over will be Justin Truman.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going to be taking over...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope he knows what he's in for because, well, Destiny 2 is kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marathon, in trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, oh my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, and then on top of that, there was the situation that went on with the Sony acquisition.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's looking crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: This just feels like accountability six months too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, there's been a lot of choices, trademark, when it comes to how things have been going with Destiny 2 and some of the recent stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, you know, Marathon did not have...
[SPEAKER_05]: A warmly received alpha in some ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so there's a lot of things they're needing to work on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so it's, you know, who makes a lot of the decisions that go into how these games end up in the state that they're in?
[SPEAKER_05]: The CEO.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's very rare that you see a CEO held accountable.
[SPEAKER_05]: And especially as you started off talking about the optics of, I'm laying people off, but I also have to polish my 15 collector vehicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's... I don't like to celebrate people losing their jobs, but this is one case where I might make an exception.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a healthy thing for this company right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They obviously need new leadership.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, except Truman may not be as great either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was...
[SPEAKER_03]: He was the one who was also count at GDC 2023 where he warned about the dangers of over-delivery in the live service game because it was set too high of a standard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope all the people at the front lines at Bungie hang in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, obviously this isn't the fault of anybody working hard on, you know, our art or programming or, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just always sucks to see those are the people that then end up in these layoff situations, which is unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to something a little more happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Pokemon World Championships.
[SPEAKER_01]: So lots of announcements and stuff happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Pokemans, let me show you them.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little happy Pikachu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pika.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's kind of go down the list of some of the different things that they talked about and discussed.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Pokemon Go, new updates of course with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they had a trailer for Pokemon Go showing off some more legendary Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we have Eternalis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I played a fuck ton of Pokemon Go yesterday with that whole Eternatus.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how it's pronounced, but that was the raid I did at least 15 of them yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so we have that wrapped up today.
[SPEAKER_01]: And of course, if you were there, you were able to get that Pokemon early.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, Pokemon TCG Pocket was getting new Mega Evolution cards later this fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mega versions of Altillaria, Gyarados, and Blaziken.
[SPEAKER_01]: will be featured, I guess, in the app's new season.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pokemon Unite is getting three more characters as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Emplorian, Delmise, and Vapirion coming to the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: The physical trading card game is also getting more Mega Evolutions.
[SPEAKER_01]: They showed off new EX cards for Mega Charizard X.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mega Gardevoir, Mega Lucario, and Mega Dragonite as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about the Megazord?
[SPEAKER_01]: No Megazords.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn, could you imagine that as a Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds really weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pokemon Champions...
[SPEAKER_01]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_01]: of the World Championship Tournament in 2026.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also announced is Pokemon XP.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sounds like a new convention fan experience type thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: They said that apparently tickets will go on sale September 17th.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's going to feature panels, unique workshops, special guests, exclusive merchandise, and so much more.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool?
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of Pokemon stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane was trying to tell me that he might come out to the Pokemon World Championships at Chase Center, which would be great to see my friend, but I feel like the time frame is going to be terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard it might be during DragonCon next year, which, nope, that's a hard no for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next year's the 40th DragonCon, so I don't care what else is going on that weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a must.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be a bummer if the timing doesn't work out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have thought it might be a similar time frame where it's like one or two weeks before and I could swing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: San Francisco is just a few hours away.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not that big a deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's not the drive that Portland was, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: One game I am really looking forward to that is coming out, I think relatively soon, is the Mortal Kombat Collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we just got announced this week, additional games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it was rumored for a while that some of the spinoff Mortal Kombat games, including Mythologies Sub-Zero and
[SPEAKER_05]: and Special Forces may be included in
[SPEAKER_05]: is out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they are also adding what's called the WaveNet arcade version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea what that was.
[SPEAKER_05]: That implies that it must have been something where you could network arcades together or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never experienced that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm curious to learn about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: and this is again it's a digital eclipse game so it's that whole documentary style such as you know what you saw in the you know Tetris collection that they had recently and Atari 50 and those types of games really I think it's gonna be a great thing for this so yeah I will definitely pick this game up that's the Mortal Kombat Legacy Collection available pretty much everywhere on September 30th all right well since we're bringing up retro games what a great time for this segment let's get into this
[SPEAKER_02]: and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and DarkSakura is stepping into the gaming vault and finding a game for us to celebrate tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what did you pick for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me, I have to dust off some cobwebs for this one even though it wasn't super long ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is called Off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we remember off, everybody?
[SPEAKER_03]: We had this before we had... Why can't I think of the name?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Deltarune.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Undertale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was thinking Claire Obscure because of all the French.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, I'll let you do your thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Off came out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a roleplay game that was done by a Belgian team called Unproductive Funtime that consisted of Mortis Ghost, also Martin Dioris, and is it
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just this alias, or is it Elias?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's Elias Conrad Coldwood.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, he's Belgian.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's about this human-ish entity called the Batter, who is on a sacred mission to, quote, purify the world of Off, basically ending eternal oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he goes to these four different zones in this world and reveals more about the world and combats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it got a big cult following.
[SPEAKER_03]: I even played a fan translation back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it did get its official fan translation in 2011.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we are still past the 10-year period, even with the English translation.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I remember everybody was freaking into this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft.com
[SPEAKER_03]: But Off has a system where your character is able to attack once a cooldown has passed, meaning that you can attack each other at the same time even enemies can.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's encouraged that you make fast decisions.
[SPEAKER_03]: you can do like an auto option so it's basically just auto battler you also have an element system so instead of like you know earth wind fire water soul or whatever you have smoke metal plastic meat and sugar
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you go through four different zones that are labeled 0 through 3, and then you have a fifth one called The Room, which is the final act of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's only accessible once you have Zodiac cards that are acquired from different zones' guardians when they die.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you go between them on a map that's called Nothingness.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the other thing is that you have a whole lot of puzzles some multi-digit passwords that you enter into a giant keypad missing book pages repeating room puzzles you go through multiple instances of the same room in the right order to escape
[SPEAKER_03]: So all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at any rate, the batter is a man in a baseball uniform who is out to purify the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: He gets guidance from a talking cat called the Judge.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My next cat's going to be called the Judge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to kill specters to purify the zone.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the guardian, you put them down and you keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: But after each zone is purified, there are scenes of a sick boy named Hugo.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's something about a connection between this boy and the zones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to spoil the game in case someone, but the last zone is very much a series of non-linear puzzles that are supposed to belong to the boy Hugo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's got some very resentful feelings.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you have a special ending where you can side with the judge, or you can side with the batter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to say what you're doing with the two, but there is a
[SPEAKER_03]: There is a difference of opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you have a joke ending that involves space apes and it's very reminiscent of the Silent Hill dog ending.
[SPEAKER_03]: So as far as this was developed, this was made with RPG Maker 2023.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was just made by Mortis and his buddies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, they were living together.
[SPEAKER_03]: It
[SPEAKER_03]: He lists things like Killer7, Silent Hill 2, Final Fantasy, Metal Gear Solid 2, and an Agatha Christie novel.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there were none and missed as inspirations.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was a very spontaneous development period.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did a demo on a small internet forum and people liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he decided to release a full game.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then there were the English translations that were out by September 8th, 2021.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there is going to be a remaster of OFF.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was announced this year and the original composer of the 2008 release, which is Coldwood, said he would not be involved in the development.
[SPEAKER_03]: The publisher is Fangamer and they offered to reuse Coldwood's music but he refused to
[SPEAKER_03]: Do it to be nervous about signing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll have a new soundtrack for the remaster composed by seven different composers, including Toby Fox.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll probably have a version of Megalopolis in it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Megalovania, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Lee Morse's rendition, If You Want the Rainbow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's slated, there is a Switch version that is slated for quarter one, 2026 and a physical copy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, the game has been well praised for story, characters, atmosphere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heidi Klempz of PC Gamer called it a memorable and haunting RPG filled with tricky puzzles, bizarre symbolism, and challenging thematic elements.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it has...
[SPEAKER_03]: A huge, you know, it had a huge fan base on Tumblr, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually where I heard about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was the sixth most reblogged game of 2013, with the other five being AAA games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, very timely pick with that remaster on the way too, I was kind of like, oh that kind of worked out conveniently, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hadn't thought of this game in a little bit, and then I was, believe it or not, I was looking up games made with RPG Maker And I saw it pop up on this, I was like, holy shit, yeah, I remember Off, and that's why I went for it Okay, no, it's a good pick, good times Any of y'all in chat play it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to... Well, let's look at the chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, there's more people talking about Undertale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Tetsuya says, hadn't heard of it, also missed the whole Undertale thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, that's... Especially with Remaster on the way soon, a great time to experience it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here, I absolutely recommend...
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead and play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a treasure.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was very weird, but very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quite surrealist in aspects.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk about some other things that are happening in the industry that you might have missed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're going to get to the Lister Roundtable pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to call us on Discord, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would also encourage you to join Discord so you can talk to us throughout the week over at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we actually have a channel for convention talk.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so Bobby and I being at DragonCon we will be sure to post updates so the cosplay came up earlier in the show I'll post a picture of it but it's only going to be on Discord so there's your I guess motivation I'm sure there'll be one on my socials too to be real but you should still join our Discord VOGnetwork.com slash Discord and check out the conventions channel this week from DragonCon and if you all are going to be there again I hope to see you at the Thursday panel or so I mean
[SPEAKER_05]: Just ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: As busy as I am, Saturday is really my worst day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have worst, best in many ways, but also worst because it's three panels back to back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So my most busy day.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other days I should be able to do an impromptu meetup like at the arcade or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: So conventions channel is a great place to find me over at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, let's get into rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Jamie, you're going to go first tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my favorite band ever in the universe, Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the Gorillaz, just Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_03]: So get it right, people, or I will find you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it was...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was announced that Gorillaz is coming to Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they will be the next Fortnite festival headlining act.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the characters will appear as in-game skins and some of their music will be available for festival as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: and yeah, the thought is and this is just the speculation on it is that 2D and Noodle will be in the shop and Murdoch and Russell will be available for Festival Pass so of course you know I'm going to have all of it forever so yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking forward to playing the songs in Festival because that seems, yeah, almost even.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want so badly for them to put Oil in it, the duet with Stevie Nicks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: This song is so good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, what do you have?
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, so Shinobi The Art of Vengeance is getting Sega Villain Stage DLC, and they announced that it's going to have three guest villains.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of those guest villains is Dr. Eggman of the Sonic the Hedgehog series.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all we know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds interesting, Dr. Eggman in a Shinobi game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Sega.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know they'll make it work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know another game I'd like to see Dr. Eggman in, and that would be Overwatch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somehow I don't think that'll happen, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Overwatch 2 is getting a new season, Season 18, starting really in just a couple days, August 26th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a pretty major change, and Jason referenced this in the intro tonight, but just to make it official, Overwatch 2 is going to change matchmaking
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: We're like playing Widowmaker on controller versus keyboard and mouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two very different experiences.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I believe if I remember right, you have a little bit of assist with aiming on controller that doesn't exist on keyboard mouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, some things to consider.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's, yeah, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played Overwatch 2 in a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of, I want to, but do you know, you know what stops me at this point?
[SPEAKER_05]: well maybe I need to look into it I can't mask my battle tag name if I could do that I would play it again because I now use RobRob as my name and I don't want I don't necessarily want Overwatch shitlords knowing my name and I guess I should have known better when I checked my battle tag but since my entire online is like RobRob like yeah I don't know maybe I'm being silly but keyboard and mouse on a console is definitely not silly I'm excited for that
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates, some games that are coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what's coming out in the US?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we've got quite a few things coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So starting things off, we have Turret Girls on PC, Zuchosis on PS4 and PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chip and Claws vs. the Brainoids on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series Gears of War Reloaded on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series Helldivers 2 on Xbox Series Neptunia Game Maker R Evolution on PC Space Adventure Cobra The Awakening on PC, Nintendo Switch
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I have a wish list as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Death & Request, Code Z on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pastel Parade on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Story of Seasons Grand Bazaar on PC, Nintendo Switch, and Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Varlette on PC, Nintendo Switch, and PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Destiny Rising on iOS and Android.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got Kirby and the Forgotten Land Nintendo Switch 2 Edition plus Starcross Worlds on Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Nightling on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Metal Gear Solid, Delta, Snake Eater on PC, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got Nori, Kago, The Grudged Domain on Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Robots at Midnight on PlayStation 5 Super Robot Wars Y on PC, Nintendo Switch, and PlayStation 5 Star Trek Resurgence on Nintendo Switch The Exit 8 on Nintendo Switch 2
[SPEAKER_01]: Lost Soul Aside on PC and PlayStation 5, and Shinobi Art of Vengeance on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll do one more because it's technically on the weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kaiju number eight, The Game on PC, iOS, and Android.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dig Rock, Documentary of Viewful Sounds
[SPEAKER_05]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a manga or anime based thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm assuming Ranma's typing in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Dig Rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never heard of it, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seifuku Kanojo 2.5 is another one that is coming out and also looks, let me just say, it's the one with- Cool uniform girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the women and young women in various stages of undressed games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely what the name is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lens is also coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the scary game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the scary game with the girl that looks like Sadako on the cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have a game called Varley is coming out in a regular and a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have Him.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Smile and Bloom is out on the Switch 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have Telnet Shooting Collection 2, which is not a reference to the old BBS door software.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a reference to, I think, some arcade era games that are obviously shooter games, as you can tell in the title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trying to see if we have... Oh yes, PC Engine Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kiadan Zero, Final Zone 2, Browning, and Legion are the four games in that collection so we have that in a regular and limited edition and DarkSakura DarkSakura attention DarkSakura we have a Toa plan arcade collection volume 1 and 2
[SPEAKER_05]: in Volume 1, Tiger Heli, Flying Shark, Fire Shark, Twin Cobra, OutZone, Fix8, Doggyoon, and Batsugun are in Volume 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: Volume 2, Zero Wing, Hellfire, Slap Fight, Alcon, depending on your region, Grindstormer, Vivi, Truxton, Tatsujin, Truxton 2, Vimana, and Twin Hawk.
[SPEAKER_05]: so DarkSakura gonna drop some money on that I think no I'm just kidding as we speak we also have OU is coming out in Japan this week as well the picturesque adventure game actually that looks pretty cute I'll check that out and then Hello Kitty Island Adventure gets a Switch 2 release on August 28th we have a lot of fucking releases this week to make up for a slow week the other week quickly looking at the PlayStation 5 I'm sure we're gonna have some overlap there we do have Meltdown
[SPEAKER_05]: Metal Gear Solid Delta Snake Eater gets its PS5 release on the 28th as it's coming out everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Robot Wars Y, also in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lens, also coming out on PS5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Varley, the Toa Plan, the two games I mentioned, also on the PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello Kitty Island Adventure, I know you're excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a game called Lost Soul Aside, which is from Sony Interactive Entertainment, on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go over to Europe, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have on the 25th, we have Particle Hearts for PC, PS5, Switch, Xboxes Pizza Bandit for PC Vlad Circus, Curse of Asmodeus for damn near everything Turret Girls for PC Pizza Bandit, Early Access for PC On the 26th, we have Neptunia Game Maker R Evolution
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of War Reloaded for PS5, Xboxes, PC Helldivers 2 for Xboxes Space Adventure Cobra The Awakening for Damn Near Everything Story of Seasons Grand Bazaar for Switch and Switch 2 on the 27th Ascend for PC
[SPEAKER_03]: The Nightling for PC, PS5, Xboxes, Varley PS5, Switch PC, Destiny Rising for Android and iOS, Metal Gear Solid Delta Snake Eater for PC, PS5, Xboxes, Kirby and the Forgotten Land plus Starcrossed World Switch 2 Edition, Super Robot Wars Y for PS5, Switch PC, also known as Super Robot Taisen, and
[SPEAKER_03]: Shinobi, Art of Vengeance PS5, PS4, Xbox PC Switch on the 29th Goosebumps, Terror and Little Creek for the same Lossles, Aside for PS5 and PC on the 29th and on Switch 2, The Exit 8 And that's it
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well we have just, actually I don't think we have any stories left.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was the end of what we had slotted for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll move over to Lister Roundtable.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you guys have any questions for us, why don't you ask them in our chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will also open it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if we had any emails, but I'll check in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody had said... We ain't found shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody had said that they emailed us on Bobby's show and I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So participate at orange.trader.com is the place to send emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just double check that email.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's a real email, just free forwarded it because everything that was in there looked like it had been spam.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so we do have a caller and we haven't talked to this person in a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's go to Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hey, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the one and only Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: How is everybody doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Invited you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, as you must know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love you mean it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Chad is apparently telling me that my brain malfunctioned and I said Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you say one thing for 15 years, habits are hard to break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Discord, vognetwork.com slash discord.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma, you look like you're in New Digs now.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, this is the same place I've been in for the last year or so.
[SPEAKER_08]: New Light?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was too lazy to get up and turn on the ceiling light, that's all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well to what do we owe the privilege tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there's something that you brought up early on in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something about Saturday morning Mega Mix beat-em-up Smash game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, our little fantasy for a, I don't know, Saturday morning showdown or whatever we're going to call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, there was a game called Saturday Night Slammasters that Capcom did that was a wrestling thing in the Street Fighter era.
[SPEAKER_05]: But like Saturday morning Smackdown or something along those lines.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we don't want it to be restricted to Saturday morning because like somebody pointed out, He-Man was a primetime cartoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't have all the Nickelodeon shit in there necessarily.
[SPEAKER_03]: Childhood chaos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Childhood chaos.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to make a nomination.
[SPEAKER_08]: This goes on the list of OLR Dream Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, step before the council and make your suggestion.
[SPEAKER_05]: The council will now hear from Ranma, citizen of New York.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want this to be an OLR Dream Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: 50 bucks if anyone knows that reference YYR is very busy though he's got a child now he can't keep making our wishes come true he has his own projects he wants to work on too
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be fair, Loki also has other projects because Loki did do Pixel Poops number two.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also this is like a million, billions of dollars worth of licensing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The licenses are going to make this hard to be an indie game, but we can still say it's an OLR dream game that we need a AAA studio to produce.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the Ubisoft, if you want us to ever forgive you, spend the money on this instead of AI slop, that would be the type of thing we would need.
[SPEAKER_08]: please do not get me started on AI they've rolled out perplexity to everybody at work and I'm just like I don't even know what the fuck that is and I don't want to know it's another I don't want to know I can't, no comment
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, look, it doesn't matter where you work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your job is looking at how can AI help us.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter where you work.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if you're at a store or a place you wouldn't think, like retail, they're still looking at how is AI going to help us.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all looking at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like when computers first came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard it compared to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a time, believe it or not, there was a day when we didn't have computers, and then computers became personal computers, and that changed a lot of industries as we know it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we had computers, but they were human.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, AI is a similar sort of thing, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can go on a tangent about that, but this is not about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to say that if we're going to go down this route, we need the Smurfs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need Alf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, what else do we need?
[SPEAKER_05]: If we got Alf, we'd be the official game of Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we also need a kid video for intermissions and bonus rounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: I support it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are good picks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if the Smurfs is Gargamel's cat would be the character I would nominate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Muppet Babies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, their playroom needs to be a stage and you have the nanny legs come in every now and then and change the stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nanny's gonna be a stage fatality.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, when did our game have fatalities?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, when you're fighting the boss, the screen can change.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the other thing is that like the Muppet Babies, I think the character from Muppet Babies should be Skeeter.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in every introduction, it should be, who the fuck are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, literally, they erased Skeeter from the reboot, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't they replace her with somebody else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a new character?
[SPEAKER_03]: The name Skeeter is a little bit questionable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to say that right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, the official game of Blue Sky, if we had Skeeter playable in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what about Scooter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, they could have twin tests.
[SPEAKER_03]: Scooter's actually a character in the actual level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scooter's a real person.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go back and watch Muppet Babies and pretend that Skeeter is a figment of Scooter's imagination and the show takes a whole new angle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also smoke weed beforehand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Allegedly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want you to know I do this at work on my breaks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I go on YouTube Smoke weed and watch Muppet Babies?
[SPEAKER_08]: What kind of fucking workplace are you at?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sign me up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you hiring?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a workplace where you get three weeks of mandatory PTO, just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's just those edibles, you know, when you can slide it into your lunch and nobody knows the difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are times I will sit there and watch YouTube videos of classic 80s commercials, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: and there are people who have uploaded their entire Saturday morning cartoon playlist with the commercials intact I fucking love that shit when they do that they keep the commercials intact absolutely quick what's a commercial jingle that comes to mind from the 80s oh god
[SPEAKER_05]: I try to block some of this out when I'm not at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only one for me is an extremely regional thing, like you East Coasters aren't going to get it, but it's Merry Christmas from Thrifties and Payless.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, y'all aren't going to understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had never heard that before, you know that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're never going to understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, see, Loki understands.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know what Thrifties is, but because I've had the ice cream.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the record, before Rite Aid went away to Dodo Bird, I did see a lot of thrifty stuff in my local store before it became a cheap supermarket.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because the ice cream was the ice cream of legends.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thrifty ice cream, I believe, still lives on to this day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever bought Rite Aid, Walgreens, you can still find thrifty ice cream, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: find me a fucking thrifty ice cream counter those are we have a few Rite-Aids aren't completely gone here and so we have a few Rite-Aids just a few that are left that have the counters in them that is the stuff of fucking legends right there and uh yeah Ranmari says uh thrifty cylindrical scoop that's right they had the the perfect little you can buy those on Amazon you can yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I do remember one regional jingle for New York Telephone before it became Verizon, and they would play it on all their commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I wouldn't know this, being a California kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: What, you're gonna tell us that and not sing it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're gonna tell us that and not sing it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're all connected, New York Telephone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll buy five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on, we're 80s kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're 80s kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is one jingle from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should all know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know one, though, from Mobile, and it was kind of all over the area.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was for Cockerell's Body Shop.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was very country.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cockerell's Body Shop, we love your automobile.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pussy Cow, Pussy Cow, Pussy Cow
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan has shown me these old commercials, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: The pussy cow commercials?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I barely remember he showed me one once.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, my brother in Christ
[SPEAKER_08]: You got me thinking of the Golden Girls now, because let's be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of us thought they said a heart attack, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of us thought that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, shut the fuck up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You found one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so I apologize because you guys on Discord won't hear this, but I have to play this for the live audience because this is so fucking legendary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the Pussy Cow commercial, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's Cal Worthington and his dog Spot!
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, why did you pick a commercial where Cal Worthington doesn't have a fucking shirt on?
[SPEAKER_05]: This man is like in his 70s.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the first one that was on the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: This man's in his 70s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want it better, buy Go See Cal.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're the guy we satisfy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go See Cal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give a new car to your wife.
[SPEAKER_03]: She will love you all her life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go See Cal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go See Cal.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: It says Pussy Cal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me it doesn't say Pussy Cal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I almost spit my water across my screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I almost did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pussy cow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will watch this later.
[SPEAKER_01]: The top comment on that, if you look at the top comment from three years ago on that video, for years, I always thought it was pussy cow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had no idea it was pussy cow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob is losing his shit live on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: I even have the wrong shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used the shot that took Loki out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the pussy cow of my childhood.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: You never forget your first pussy cow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that our new catchphrase?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's an unlockable character is Cal Worthington and his dog Spot.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, rest in rest in peace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rest in peace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma, where are you going to take the show next?
[SPEAKER_05]: You've made us go down the rabbit hole of pussy cow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad I called in before I decided to do an edible or something else I'm kind of glad I did Why aren't you sharing with me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I love and trust you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come to my house right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should do it because I just recently restocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should, you should, I can't say, but you should definitely try to come to Fanime next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Strong wink, strong nudge.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should definitely try to come to Fanime next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Funny you should mention that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have been saying off and on for the last few years that there are conventions 20 years ago I wanted to go to, but I could not afford them because finances.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that I'm in a position where I can take the time off that I want, and I have the money to go to these conventions, and I really haven't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I decided to do a couple of trips to Japan and still go to cons.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still putting together 2026.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think maybe a reunion tour might be in order.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you could take your bestie in the entire universe, DarkSakura, to Japan with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, I am going in 2026 because my con kid wants to go and she really loves her Kirby, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me when you do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I have the money for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me when you do that because if Shad's still there, I might go and I'll try to time it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it depends on if he's still there or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even if he's there or not, you should still go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I do want to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were looking at doing a cruise, a second cruise next year, and I don't think it's going to pan out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're on a waiting list that I hear is hundreds of people long, so I don't think that's going to pan out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we might have the bandwidth to do something big.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to get too ahead of myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just know that I want to go to Kyoto for the Miyako Odori.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Ranma, we gotta wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're making me want to spend money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is, I should let you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But do you have any other final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to grow up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a Toys R Us kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a million Toys R Us that I can play with.
[SPEAKER_05]: From book to trains to video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob doesn't remember the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in Japan, you still run the tags to the front at Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's something
[SPEAKER_03]: And in Japan, Toys R Us still exists.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was in Ikebukuro walking through Sunshine City and I saw the Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I stared and I wiped a tear away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just like... But if it doesn't smell like Toys R Us, it won't work for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm just telling you, Toys R Us had a very distinctive smell of Warehouse and Kmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma, you know the place I have to go to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Donkey?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun Dun
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me, I'm so down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to a Mega Donkey in Nagoya and found Choco Cat stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I was thinking of the Mega Donkey, because I mean, I would probably have to go to Tokyo first before I make my way to Kyoto.
[SPEAKER_08]: But on the plus side, there's hundreds of Don Quixote stores all over, most are 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to go to that one in particular.
[SPEAKER_03]: but you definitely gotta go to one Akihabara though tons of anime stuff well and then I want to go to where the luxury stores are in Shibuya, basically the pawn stores that sell luxury goods oh yes yes yes yes I mean something about getting an Hermes bag for 4 grand instead of 20 grand
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I have that money anyway, but it'd be nice to think about it for five minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Ranma, we gotta wrap it up, but do you have any final thoughts for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Toys R Us Jingle was my final thought, and then we just kind of derailed yet again, because I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I love you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, it's time for us to give our final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, let me check in real quick, Loki, with any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I looked.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you as always for listening to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you enjoyed what you heard here, please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: A nice five-star review on a site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wherever you found this show, it goes an awful long way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: with some more Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope to see some folks at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you that are spending your Labor Day in other ways, whether you're going to that other convention in Seattle or maybe the locals going to SAC Anime or whatever is in your neck of the woods, I hope you have a fantastic time this Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy the summer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope the weather isn't too crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hearing some stuff out of Burning Man and I have some friends up there that the dust storms up there are hellish this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm really keeping y'all burners in my thoughts that are up there right now and hoping y'all are hanging in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for those of you who...
[SPEAKER_03]: God's punishment for going to Burning Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you going to conventions indoors, I have friends there.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you going to conventions indoors, I hope you are hanging in there and having a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you're streaming tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to play Polya.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've actually redone my stream schedule a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's more changes I'll talk about on my channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I'm doing Polya tonight because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: My bestie sisters in Helya and I deserve a relaxing evening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun relaxing.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk to you in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, that means it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your final thought for us tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought is there's going to be a new episode on my YouTube channel hopefully tonight or tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: all right awesome i don't know why that that shot is always messed up okay sorry just twitch video things um let's see my final thought is um yeah really excited for dragon con but boy did it sneak up on me and it's so weird to think that it's been an entire year since the last dragon con that's the like time just fucking flies
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy every day you got, people, because time fucking flies.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you in two weeks on an all-new Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pacific, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week.