[SPEAKER_05]: Now that legendary games are getting good movies and TV shows, it's weird to realize how many of those games I haven't played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fallout, The Witcher, most of the Castlevanias, and now Far Cry, which is in production apparently, but given many factors, it's a good idea to wait for a series release date before too much hype.
[SPEAKER_05]: I started Far Cry two or three times, but never really made progress.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to for the narrative, but I'm only one trophy away from getting Platinum and Death Stranding 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time to get the band back together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about these stories and the rest of the week's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting right now on the show, every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is Orange Lounge Radio Live once again tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Episode number 1058 of our show for tonight, August 10th of 2025.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm here to talk about video games, very serious stuff, and never any tangents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never, never.
[SPEAKER_03]: With all of you live in our chat as we are taping live at the Voice Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm also joined by my co-host, of course, starting off with the one and only Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still go by DarkSakura, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I should say welcome back as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: brain suck sometimes uh you had a little marathon yesterday i was i was i was there for like the beginning and then i just left my computer on while i went and did other stuff yesterday but you went for a very long time i did and you know i i saw a few olr people there um not not not a lot
[SPEAKER_02]: but I did a lot of Dead by Daylight and I did some Mass Effect 2 as sort of a palate cleanser but there were some very generous people who basically paid for my hotel room at Disneyland that's good
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to make sure that I've got enough money to cover TwitchCon and still be able to pay the bills.
[SPEAKER_02]: And do some tech repairs in the local studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's practical.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing practical stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could go to TwitchCon but at this point I have a conflict that weekend now so I can't go even if I made it work out last minute but I kept telling Alan he could go but yeah I'm out unfortunately so but I'm sure it'll be a good time well my friend who we've probably seen in my chat is Mabel Von Smallcat is coming with me we have a cute little Airbnb oh fun
[SPEAKER_02]: and then we're going to Disneyland together that'll be fun and then it's gonna be pretty busy I'm going to probably be like flat on my face afterwards but I'm looking forward to it I've already started working on my cosplays and yeah well cosplay is singular since it's always the pig excited to see the latest evolution of your pig cosplay
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's also say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know you're not going to TwitchCon either.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you what, Loki, I'm skipping the party.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the same thing as last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the party sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Save yourself $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just not worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The food was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the same without a Kim Petras concert and whoever else they had that one year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I didn't go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just heard it from the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, last year was great when you had people that couldn't sing screaming at one stage and then you had a DJ just two blocks down the other way playing loud music and then the music was just...
[SPEAKER_06]: grading against each other in the middle.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: S0100, Matt, in our chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because again, we do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice Geeks Network right after the Bobby Blackwell show, twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: During the convention, it wasn't coming back to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was just it would have been a lot better if it was at one of the hotel convention centers, which I've been to a Final Fantasy 14 event at the Rio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think there's a big Star Trek convention at the Rio this weekend, actually, because I have a lot of friends there for my cruise.
[SPEAKER_03]: are there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Paris, I know one year had it.
[SPEAKER_03]: These places are fine, but yeah, TwitchCon was at the Las Vegas Convention Center, which just was really hard to get to, especially with a giant fucking concert going on that same weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then F1 Formula Racing, it was terrible to get around Vegas.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not going to miss TwitchCon Vegas at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think San Diego is a much better city for it, except the one...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hard to, like, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also hard to find lodging in that area too.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're willing to go further away and Uber in or whatever, then you might get lucky with Pacific Beach or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, that works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, probably cheaper than getting a hotel down in the grid somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how often are you staying in your hotel room?
[SPEAKER_02]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of conventions over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, Rin Mari in chat says, Anyway, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went to MAGFest this weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a ribbon for playing a rhythm game, meme song in 15 games, and no, it's not flower.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm glad you had fun at MAG West.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of those conventions I always mean to get to, but it's just like such a busy time of year for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I've always been curious about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm glad you had a good time there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have a couple other friends that go, and yeah, I need to get out there one year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I had a lot of fun at MAG Fest the couple times that I went, and I'd love to go again, but again...
[SPEAKER_03]: since they don't do it in February.
[SPEAKER_03]: The times they did it in February were a fluke and that made it much easier to get to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that it's like early January, it's harder for me to go cross-country to a thing like MAGFest as much as I'd love to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, never say never.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will say...
[SPEAKER_03]: DragonCon, DragonCon, DragonCon
[SPEAKER_03]: When I do have my final schedule, I'm not going to have time to meet people with these... Unfortunately, the types of panels these are, I'm not going to be able to meet and greet people from the show then.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's really best if you want to say hi, and I'm certainly happy to say hi, give you a little FaceTime, see how you're doing, whatever, unless you try to find me impromptu during the convention, which it does...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Animes down there, BritTracks, we're right next door to BritTracks so there's a lot of tracks down there so in Galleria 6 we're going to be having a big meet and greet for content creators you do not have to be a content creator to be there you can just be an aspiring content creator or somebody that supports content creators and wants to find new ones that is A-OK so I encourage you to come down there and it's on a Thursday
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: And I can tell you what one of her cosplays is because she's posted about it on her TikTok and her Instagram.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I know it's not a secret.
[SPEAKER_03]: She is dressing as Parker Posey's character from Josie and the Pussycats in the scene with the Mega Records dress, which took her four.
[SPEAKER_03]: She had to make 400 vinyl stickers that say Mega Records on them to make this dress.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's incredible.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly not, you know, 13 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we actually have something about music games to start us off tonight how lovely because I'm sure y'all know by now but if you don't Orange Lounge Radio started because we all met playing DDR and that's pretty much exclusively what we used to talk about was music based games whether it was Konami's Bimani series or other you know adjacent games in that space but interesting blast from the past potentially coming back yeah Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was many, many years ago that we met up with the people from Red Octane to actually play... We were just talking about that like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were just talking about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting back up where they left off, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's going to be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is I don't remember if it's the same folks behind it, but it basically Charles and Kai Huang, who were formerly part of Harmonix Music System.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those names do sound familiar, like super familiar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't claim I know everybody there, but like those names, I was like, I feel like those were some of the minds back in the day that were running Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Hero, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just that it's different when you can have these songs that people instantly recognize from Journey or whatever bands that people turns their heads and makes them want to see, well, what's this going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's why Guitar Hero did as well as it did, especially versus something like Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to take a step back once upon a time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami also was extremely risk adverse in America.
[SPEAKER_03]: Extremely risk adverse.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did not want to put out DDR in the US and they quite frankly resisted it for an awful long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know if that was the music licensing or trying to do the peripheral and their data told them that a peripheral wouldn't work well here in the US or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they were quite frankly resistant to it for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that's why DDR did pretty good for them because they had a
[SPEAKER_03]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Just shit the bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: They gave the Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, what the hell were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the beginning of a really dark era for Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to be fair, Konami, I think we would all agree, especially post-pandemic.
[SPEAKER_00]: They turned it around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seems to be in a much better place than they were.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have other people to run their license.
[SPEAKER_03]: Suikoden recently came back, and the HD remaster was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silent Hill, the 2 remake, a lot better than people were expecting, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I know people are still on the fence about this new one, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does seem like Konami is in a better place.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also, this isn't about Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have the exclusive...
[SPEAKER_03]: you know, on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they will have nothing to do with this game besides maybe some type of fee that has to be paid for trade.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how all that legal stuff works.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, Konami otherwise has very little to do with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranmari in chat says, American rhythm games don't appeal to me for a lot of the reasons they succeed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Long songs, songs just not my taste, super modes for scoring, so I just accept that I'll be a socially unacceptable rhythm gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always had room in my heart for both.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always felt I was discovering more music in the Japanese games, but I could get my... Fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just spilled a soda, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta go AFK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody take over.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could get your fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I will put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: What other people like isn't any of my business.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad if they like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad if they don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I enjoy what I enjoy, and what other people do or don't enjoy doesn't affect what I enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That being said, give me more rhythm games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Expand it, make more space for it, and we will start to see more of the niche stuff, I hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least that's my theory.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so it's going to be interesting to see what they actually come out with with this, since they said that they're going to be announcing their first rhythm game later this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a rather large team.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is still within free mode of Embracer Group, so they're a subsidiary of Embracer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully it doesn't mean that they're going to get sold off mid-development, but yeah, it'd be interesting to see what happens with this, because certainly there's been a
[SPEAKER_06]: Quite the break in rhythm games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that they've kind of brought some of that back a little bit with the Fortnite Music Fest stuff, but it would be interesting to see kind of a resurgence.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if something like say that they put out that's similar to like a Guitar Hero, but maybe not quite, you know, takes off, maybe Activision, Microsoft revisits Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's always possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although they tried to do that and it didn't work out, but you know, I mean, it'd be interesting to see something come of this, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, in the end, I mean, we don't really know everything about it that there is to know, so I want to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking to see if the guy that came to your house at one time that was Simon Tam and no, he's not listed as one of the employees here so he has moved on he was a producer at Red Octane but yeah, it'd be interesting to see what they have in mind for the rhythm game he was pretty cool though he was a nice guy he was nice very enthusiastic about it too
[SPEAKER_06]: certainly and it it's funny and I think he was a little amused at the Bimani stuff because I actually looked back in the video and one of my Bimani things was actually still in the corner yeah and it's also funny too because like uh I think Red Octane's almost their rebirth of this I want to say that they were making even peripherals for the Fortnite stuff as well I think they were doing that either that or it was um
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Harmonix was putting out anything, but somebody was making guitars for the Fortnite Music Fest stuff, so I'm wondering if that's still Red Octane, and if that's the case, it's like restarting the company the same way it started previously, which is kind of funny.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, I'm back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: The joys of doing live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I spilled a soda and it got all over.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to change my shorts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so annoyed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now the chair is sticky, even though I toweled it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm annoyed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the chat, I see everybody in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see bits and subs to help pay for clean.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are really funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody was asking if it was orange soda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ironically...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, when bringing these in the house, dropped them.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can see the lid is a little funky because these got dropped.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like a thing from Costco and it got dropped on the ground.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I guess when I went to drink it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, I forgot how to drink.
[SPEAKER_03]: So down to the ground it went and now my legs are sticky.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll be taking a shower after the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: The joys of live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, sorry to distract from the topic of Red Octane Games, but until they actually announce what they're working on, I guess we don't have a whole lot left to say, do we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I mean, that was my point.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't really know, so we're not going to know until they...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Vecna Adept Vecna
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played Palia.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually started playing a little bit more of Avatar Frontiers of Pandora because with the next movie coming out, I've been kind of getting back into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually really enjoyed the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I didn't play much through the second DLC, so I figured I'd give it another go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so far, I'm really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: That, that was, I mean, other than like my little phone dealy bobs, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was basically Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really get to play much of Minecraft because I was busy still coding the data pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, multiple data packs because I rebuilt one that we were using this week as well, but just still working on coding the data pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: for our PvE arena that we're going to have.
[SPEAKER_06]: So still working on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, we got that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I got my MCC TCG cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still have to crack open on a stream or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of fun having some of the Minecraft event cards and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I picked up a few more games that I don't know what I'm going to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one behind me, of course, is called The RPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like a spoof of Skyrim, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can side with the king or you can side with the monsters and actually try to take over the kingdom and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got a funny art style that kind of reminds me of Job Simulator or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I thought it looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I forgot to ask what that game was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks really cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a headache.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fell back down the Final Fantasy XI rabbit hole hard last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thanks to Retro Achievements, I learned about this private Final Fantasy XI thing called Horizon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't feel bad playing on a private server because I still pay Square Enix every month and I bought Final Fantasy XI twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So talk to the wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it doesn't even have Otter gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: He can't even be a Blue Mage or a Corsair or whatever else they added in that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're only limited to the first couple expansions and level 75.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the interesting thing is the client still has some...
[SPEAKER_03]: of the modern quality of life things, but not a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does level sync, which is huge for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does have level sync, but that's the only thing as opposed to, you know, like there's no book burning.
[SPEAKER_03]: You still have to do dunes parties and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but it's like, I feel like this, it's scratching a nostalgia bone for me hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, y'all know how long, how much we used to play fucking Final Fantasy XI back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: But like already in the scope of what, a week and a half that I've been playing this,
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a level 22 Red Mage with a level 10... I need to work on a level 10 White Mage subjob.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I finished the subjob class.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did the run to Juno this morning and got my Chocobo because that's another thing they sped up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have to wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: You used to have to do the Chocobo quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would take you like six hours because you had to wait an in-game day.
[SPEAKER_03]: They compressed it so that every in-game hour you can feed the Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it goes by a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get it done in 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, it's been interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, I was able to get to Juno and talk to the thing that unlocks more of my retro achievements for leveling and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I can actually see the little progress I'm making.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I'm doing it for achievements, because now it's just like scratching this nostalgia bone where I'm like, God, playing in parties was actually really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: The modern MMOs don't have the same feel to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's slower, but that was part of the charm of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing things like magic bursts and skill chains and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Horizon, for the most part, embraces add-ons.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some that are on their ban list, but their client has a bunch pre-installed if you want to use them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some of them will tell you what skill chains to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have to memorize everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, I think for all those reasons, it's moving a little faster than it did when I first played the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, but yeah, just enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I am recognizing like, wow, I'm like playing nothing else because I'm too much in this nostalgia hole right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But sometimes, sometimes you just want to eat comfort food.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you're going to eat pizza and ice cream every day for a week until you get sick of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you go, oh, I should stop eating this.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, I'm surprised you haven't tried and fallen down that hole yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really surprised.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know what you would do.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I haven't tried.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have 11 more than anyone, so all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I downloaded 11 again the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just have...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what you'd have to do differently because I bought it a long time ago back on like was it the Amazon game store or something like that so I still have like an installation like a key that's still valid Horizon's a whole separate thing and it doesn't use play online so they have a whole separate installer and the game client is so it's an all-in-one pack you don't have to do anything special you just download it and there it is so yeah it's kind of nice so but again I probably shouldn't be enabling you
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, but that is my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should get back to, I still want to beat fantasy life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have games on the switch to play, but you know, you know, some, sometimes after a long day at work, you just want to join a Valcrum Dunes party and skill chain lizards for three hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, just what you want to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I want to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Farm, and Pallia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and that's kind of a comfort food sort of game, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I get that, because I play Pallia now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's my cozy vibe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's cozy vibe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, the only thing that's not cozy vibe about Final Fantasy XI, running away from goblin tinkers that you accidentally aggroed, because that's also still a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You still gotta zone the goblins.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't do that because in the old XI, they used to run back and they would attack all the other parties as they're running back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now once they get zoned, they fade.
[SPEAKER_03]: They fade away and they don't run back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can't grief parties or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They changed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was not long into the game that they changed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say they changed that with the Treasures of Ottergon expansion or something.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's talk about more going on in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of Nintendo, a lot out of their camp this week yet again going into the holidays, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they did their Nintendo Indie World Showcase.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're announcing a bunch of different indie games that are coming out on the different Switch platforms and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of these we've heard of before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of these were new.
[SPEAKER_06]: So kind of just we'll go over these really quickly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the stuff that's a little more familiar.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we had Mina the Hollow Word, which of course is from the Shovel Knight folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they showed off a new uh gameplay trailer and also that now so that demo is available for that uh there's uh Well Dweller which looks pretty cool it's kind of a dark fantasy metroidvania game that's coming out next year uh Neverway which is like a it almost reminds me of a um
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't Starve type game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically a nightmarish life sim or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's supposed to be coming out next year as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hurtling, I think I've seen a trailer for this before.
[SPEAKER_06]: The folks behind Firewatch, that's coming out in about a week or two on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_06]: is this seat taken that's a cool puzzle game that was released that day they announced a new update for big kitty uh little kitty big city and they're going to be getting this uh a perfect picture update that's also going to have new areas new friends that you can meet new skills and uh of course a camera mode because
[SPEAKER_06]: why the game didn't have a photo mode with cats that's what we use the internet for anyways um so yeah and that's coming out later this year that free content update uh speaking of content content warning is going to be coming to the Switch and Switch 2 as well sometime next year um Ball X Pit or Ball Pit from Devolver Digital looked pretty awesome it's kind of like a
[SPEAKER_06]: Roguelike with Arkanoid style gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can now pay to spend extra time in the ball pit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's launching on the Switch October 15th and on the Switch 2 sometime later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then we have Ultimate Sheep Raccoon, which is the sequel to Ultimate Chicken Horse.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a racing platformer game instead of the traditional one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's going to be coming out a little bit later this year, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Glaciered
[SPEAKER_06]: is a, it almost looks like a Subnautica type thing, but it's a RPG with aquatic monsters.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's going to be coming out this holiday on Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they showed off just some quick trailers as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we had a trailer for Winter Burrow, which is a kind of a cool looking survival game where you play a mouse living in the snow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had Undusted Letters from the Past, Tiny Bookshop, Caves of... I have no idea how to pronounce that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cud?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Q-U-D?
[SPEAKER_06]: Coode?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Strange Antiquities, Opus, Prism Peak, Go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Town, UFO 50, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That actually was launching that day as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: UFO 50 is a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, Demon's School and Go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Town.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, lots of indie games we're checking out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice to see Nintendo sort of dedicate a little time because I think sometimes, at least with the original Switch shop, it really felt overloaded and burdened.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess this is true to some extent with the Switch 2 shop too.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know there's a bunch of shovelware on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know where there is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's nice of Nintendo to spend some of their official time really highlighting some things that are kind of worth a second look that can get lost.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of wish they did these maybe once a month and a little more often.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I guess maybe they seem to do them about once every other month.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe it's not as bad as I'm thinking in my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's nice that they highlight those types of things because it's, you know, it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to some comments over in our chat room over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network about some of the games in the pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says I admit most of these aren't really in my wheelhouse but I did notice UFO 50 so hope to pick that one up at some point Bobby Blackwolf also commenting on UFO 50 saying UFO 50 was the best announcement of the day and it was buried in a sizzle reel well that happens sometimes you know what what might not be a big deal to you is a big deal to someone else and then of course the whole infamous they spend too much time talking about this sports game I don't give a fuck about like that happens a lot too right so
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, not in this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not in the indie thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, indie sports games tend to be the best ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I will say, one of our local little bars did their gamer night this week, and some of my friends were playing Windjammer for like an hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, although, is that really an indie?
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of think it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, another comment here from Seeger Starzik, who says...
[SPEAKER_03]: is this seat taken is pretty good picked it up that day and have had a really good time with it so far seems like it could be very short though yeah sometimes those indie games especially if they're low cost may be kind of cheaper so there's that all right well uh hopefully y'all saw at least one thing in that showcase that you liked uh meanwhile a lot of people telling Nintendo what they like or don't like about a certain system that they have set up with their
[SPEAKER_03]: Digital Game Keycards
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, I'm going to assume that people really jumped on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, because the whole game key card thing has garnered a lot of negative attention, like at least, you know, if the temperature on social media, on places like Blue Sky, Facebook, whatever TikToks to be believed, people don't really like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm sure there were plenty of people that were jumping at the opportunity to give some feedback on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the questions that they were asking were, in general, when it comes to games for a Nintendo Switch system, do you prefer purchasing games in physical format or in digital formats?
[SPEAKER_03]: And for which of the following reasons would you consider purchasing physical versions of Nintendo Switch games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you never fucking discount them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a valid response?
[SPEAKER_03]: It seems like that actually is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Physical games tend to go on sale from the retailer and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If nothing else, it shows that Nintendo is looking at this and is taking an interest in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm left to believe they have to be hearing what people on the internet are saying even if they're not directly doing anything about it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I doubt they will for quite some time because I'm sure they have people are saying things they don't like well but there is another thing that could be playing into this as well and that could be the fact that physical games versus digital games is going to get more complicated because of tariffs
[SPEAKER_03]: and all that stupidity that is now enacted is that it's going to make the cost of physical games more expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So digital game for that reason is going to be more alluring.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think there's some advantage to maybe having that data as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that may be completely outside the discussion of the game key cards, which actually, I mean, again, in the wake of tariffs, those game key cards are even like 10 times worse because now it's like you're paying more for a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: For what?
[SPEAKER_03]: for nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So like, you know, I, I just, a lot is pretty screwy with all that system right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, we'll see what comes of it for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but no, no, obviously no word on what's going to be done with the survey results yet, but Nintendo has obviously made it very clear.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have enough data.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drive through.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's something new from the Video Game History Foundation.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know, they're not just looking at games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're looking at anything related to games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they have got the rights to release a computer entertainer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it started as a video game update, which was a newsletter for U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: mail order retailer Video Takeout, which I had never heard of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think we had one where I lived.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it ran from 1982 to 1990 and it actually was co-edited by Mary Lou Badeau and Celeste Dolan and means it is also one of the earliest console video game magazines run by women and so every issue of it is available through the Video Game History Foundation That's cool
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think that's really neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And certainly I'm glad that they are looking at, you know, not just the games, but anything related to the culture, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is a very important piece of women's history as well.
Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it is important to also have that sort of like snapshot in time because, you know, just being able to kind of explain to people what gaming was like in a different era.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, sometimes people don't really have that reference, you know, not to sound like the old man on the block, but it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, people that didn't grow up on Atari 2600 don't have a sense of just how it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's going to come a time when, you know, the gamers are like, oh, what was an instruction manual?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: You just go on the internet to find whatever you needed?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, the art of the instruction manual is sadly going to be long gone, except for, I guess, niche collector's editions and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's definitely preserving a moment in time, which I think is really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, this is all what we grew up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I don't recall this particular magazine, so I'm excited to see more about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, you used to have to buy those magazines and we couldn't afford them all.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's cool that we can sort of go back and revisit that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTC in chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network says, definitely appreciate their preservation efforts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we talk about games preservation, it needs to be all of it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Questbuster says, I was curious and took a look and I found a Dragon Stomper release in their January 83 issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, January 83.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a throwback.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on, I guess, to more modern sensibilities.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: So definitely...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there comes a time that companies have to reflect upon their decisions and realize that maybe it wasn't the kids that are wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I was a bit wrong, but not too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't want to take full responsibility, obviously.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, this focus with a lot of companies focusing on live service games, Sony being one of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Run into some hiccups, obviously, with some games like Concord and the like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically saying during a, you know, financial Q&A that, yeah, it's not going entirely smoothly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somewhat negative news has been coming out if we look at the past five years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Five years ago, live service games were almost non-existent from PlayStation Studios.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Helldivers 2, MLB The Show, Gran Turismo 7, and Destiny's 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: um so we have four live service or four live services contributing to sales and profits in a stable manner but you know it's I think a little bit harder to get another like kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it says, of course, we recognize there are still many issues, so we should learn the lessons from our mistakes and make sure that we introduce live service content where there's less waste and it's more smooth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's also something that people want because, you know, Concord sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and they are so nervous about Marathon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, the early testing of Marathon, I don't think went super great.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's still a lot to be cooked with that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that game has so much writing on it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know if the gaming population is in the same space that they were for a game like Marathon to be truly successful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I worry for that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because they focus more on the like, how are we going to monetize this?
[SPEAKER_06]: How is this going to be, you know, how are we going to profit from this versus making a good game?
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's the problem with like Concord.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the problem with Marathon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like,
[SPEAKER_06]: you take the live service part out of it if it was just hey here's a game we're going to release later this year and we're going to show it off to you in like a demo and the demo plays like garbage you're going to be like whoa hold on I don't want to purchase this and so that's the thing it's like it doesn't you can take the live service out of the equation stop putting out unfinished games
[SPEAKER_06]: from anybody that goes to a lot of different companies stop putting out unfinished games and then when you do decide to not listen to the audience and do it anyways don't be surprised when it bites you in the ass
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and I think gamers are also just becoming a lot more aware that like video games are, you know, PlayStation 5 games are $70.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you're going to come out with a game that asks you for more money on top of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I think gamers are becoming more and more aware, like it's going to take a really special kind of game for me to plunk down that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have to either, you know, have a story that really fucking moves me or like a player versus player type of mode that really entices me to come back over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I think that's just a riskier and riskier thing to do you know when games were $50 you know I think people are just becoming more and more aware especially and then versus of course the free to play games because I think the biggest competitor for a game like Marathon ends up being Fortnite because at the end of the day Fortnite is still free to put on your PlayStation and is a shooty bang bang game
[SPEAKER_03]: so you have to give people that premium experience especially I would argue in a single player mode that that $70 is going to justify but I worry that especially in that single player mode it's not going to be there
[SPEAKER_03]: Questbuster in chat over twitch.tv slash VOG Network says, Sony's efforts gave me the impression that they thought they couldn't fail by doing things like buying Bungie without realizing the luck part of success.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one expected Helldivers 2 to explode the way it did, but there you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: While Concord, which was created to bring that kind of success home, utterly collapsed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how's Overwatch 2 doing these days in that space?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I feel like the team shooters in general are sort of declining.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess Marvel Rivals is still kind of holding its own, especially with such a recognizable IP.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know, y'all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Marathon's a different kind of game, but I am worried.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to be proven wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really do hope they take the time to get it right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I also know the budget to make a game like this isn't limitless.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the longer it goes on, the more they're going to feel the need to nickel and dime the players to try to make the money back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: SD100 Matt in chat says, I sadly haven't gone back to Overwatch 2 since Marvel Rivals came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's just you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not think it's just you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a very interesting patent that Nintendo has put out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is for a crank.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and perhaps the crank could be used in something like, I don't know, Animal Crossing when people go fishing or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe there's some Dreamcast games they could bring back with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or the interesting thing about a crank, maybe try to lure some ports of Playdate games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, granted, the Playdate is a very different type of system.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't run things on the same level.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even think they considered Playdate to be any sort of competition whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so either, but certainly, you know, like, hey, we have the ability to put this game on our store too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if the Playdate is as serious of a thing as it is, you know, some type of just new control accessory or maybe inspired by the Playdate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, hey, what if we took that crank idea the Playdate has and put it on the Nintendo console?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if we patent it and then we sue them for using the crank?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we're evil.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the patent is for the Switch 2 and the way it interfaces with the Switch 2 controller specifically.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you know, I don't put anything past Nintendo, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a reminder, there were a lot of wild accessories during the Wii because that Wiimote would click into a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: The plastic steering wheel, hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember there was a fishing rod for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember that being a thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was an official Mario Kart thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was day one for the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see if anything comes to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because again, just because it gets trademarked, it doesn't mean it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it might.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some exciting stuff in retro news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, DarkSakura?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sorry, I had to swallow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for fans of Evercade, there is a new release coming out, which is the Rare Collection 1 and a ZX Spectrum set.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually looking pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually says it's the debut of ZX Spectrum emulation on Evercade.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is also going to include some of the early NES games, Cobra Triangle, RC Pro-Am, and Battletoads, and the arcade version of Battletoads, and then Conker's Pocket Tales from Game Boy Color.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I want to pick up one of those rare cartridges.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we got good news that Digital Foundry is now going to be going independent.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've decided to leave IGN and have, I think, purchased back their company to be able to actually take it independent.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, of course, if you're not familiar with Digital Foundry, they do a lot of these different kind of evaluations of games and see how well the visuals and everything run.
[SPEAKER_06]: and like you'll even look at like frame timings and stuff like that it's where you get a lot of this news about oh yeah this Switch game was it was basically a postage stamp that they're upscaling to 1080p you know that type of stuff but it is exciting to see you know them out from underneath IGN and yeah so they announced that to everybody on their podcast and going forward they're going to be operating independently so that's
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the first company in the media space to go independent.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like there's been quite a few this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a little bit of a theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: So congrats.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's almost always good news for these companies in these situations.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: A new trailer was released this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we don't know all the details.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just know what's in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was also, I guess, a cannibalism update that was done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we talked about that on a prior episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that was last week, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: that you have to avoid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas the game has, for example, a jungle with rain that makes the surfaces slippery, the snow that has cold air or wind that you have to avoid and otherwise you freeze to death, the lava one that
[SPEAKER_03]: you know don't fall into lava where the mountains will burst in the fire and that type of stuff so yeah it's it'll be interesting glad to see that they're still supporting it now for those of you that like to do your quests on discord because that's a thing now you play certain games you get little limited time things or little currency to buy you know flair on discord or what have you
[SPEAKER_03]: Peak will be having a limited time exclusive quest in Discord or with Discord.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be live just for next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So between August 11th and August 17th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you get a Bing Bong avatar for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bing Bong.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think that's what the little characters are called in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also new achievements apparently are coming as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is all happening tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please look forward to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I thought this is not directly related to the expansion, but I thought this was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Death by Daylight Death by Daylight
[SPEAKER_03]: But then the most important Roblox game that is an original, at least as far as I know, is the fashion dress up game.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, why can't I remember the name of that game?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's so good.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's Grow a Garden.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's but there's knockoffs of other games all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I know I've seen the Dead by Daylight one, you know, so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, of course, there is a peak as in the game we were just talking about a copy on Roblox.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not even a knockoff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've ripped off full... The assets look the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just straight up ripping it off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, on the official X account, because unfortunately some companies still use X and support its current owner, but I realize there's a lot of companies doing it, so it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: AgroCrab Games put out a very interesting post on X saying, TBH would rather you pirate our game than play this microtransaction-riddled Roblox slop ripoff.
[SPEAKER_03]: so we're hearing that word slop a lot with AI related things in this day and age but now it's being thrown at this too like Roblox knockoffs being slop which I mean I could see that they kind of are I am like honestly so surprised that they haven't cracked that copyright holders haven't cracked down on Roblox like yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: it's like the largest gaming platform right now and there is so much rampant copyright theft just so much some of it is unintentional because it's kids making the game but that said, there's a lot of it that is adults making these games full well understanding that yeah, I'm ripping off the copyright for this so it's unfortunate
[SPEAKER_03]: and apparently Cliff in the screenshot that was shared on social media already had 160,000 visits.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not like this is some underground thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's already very much out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting point also made along these same lines about slop and AI.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I know this we talked about this a couple weeks ago the PlayStation store AI generated bullshit that is meant to cash in on different trends in gaming right now so that's another you know place so yeah I I feel like this is all gonna come to an apex legally at some point so we'll see interesting interesting uh and a lot of folks comment giving the sorry a lot of folks in chat giving the appropriate comment here which is oof
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that would be the appropriate comment to this story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to our next segment and take a trip down memory lane, shall we?
[SPEAKER_00]: and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And once a month, DarkSakura puts a little twist on things and she picks a game that for 2025, it is a classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a game and now it's in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what is the classic game to arcade of the month, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, it's been in the arcade for a hot minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the game is Injustice Gods Among Us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this segment doesn't necessarily have to encompass the 10-year limit, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Although Injustice does fall in the 10-year limit since the game came out in 2013.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in 2017, the arcade version came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and uh you uh I mean it's a full-on arcade port of wait why is this saying the mobile game yeah of the mobile game interesting I didn't realize that part but it was made by Raw Thrills working with NetherRealm Studio and it first came out in Dave and Buster's before a worldwide release so um
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is weird because it says that you have cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you have cards that you scan for your character.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it plays like the mobile version with the push and hold buttons.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's six buttons all together.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have quick attack block and a strong attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you have a special attack button.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally, you have your start and buy a card without playing the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it also is your tag-in button during the battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can't choose what attack you want to use.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just have to use the special button to do your special, no matter how much your bar is filled up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like weird mini-game-ish sort of shenanigans going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had remembered that there was some catch to this game because I saw it and really didn't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, this is really the mobile version, just a lot more scaled.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Series 4 update had an instant super move that you can use when the battle begins, and you do need an additional credit to use it, and it'll give you a bonus card with an additional reward.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to basically spend twice as much on a single match.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely something to suck up money, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: um as for um the game uh beneath uh actually where your character's name is a player uh the character's name
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: um you have many swapping games for different special attacks and you will always have a countdown um and then you have a single player ladder a medium ladder and a hard ladder um and then of course there's a
[SPEAKER_02]: Your cards will also be different outfits for some of the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get the same character just with different outfits.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have different power levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, in the Silver set, if you had Bane, there's a Nightfall and then there's a Regime version.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Nightfall has 65 power levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: and 81 Defense.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Regime one has 63 power and 73 defense, so it's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it has higher speed than the Nightfall one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, there's different trade-offs and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems pretty balanced.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get all kinds of different versions of the characters that way in different outfits.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: The cards themselves, of course, have different stats.
[SPEAKER_02]: So like for the odds of pulling a card.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for bronze, it's 20%, silver 26%, gold 46%, which is pretty good because the gold I think is the one that's got like Batman and all of that on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The team cards are 3%, boss cards are 2.5%, gear is 2.5%, and the foil cards are 33% overall split between bronze, silver, gold, team, and boss and gear.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, this is a game that's definitely designed to suck up money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I just say play at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: that's more like the Dragon Ball Z game where you actually have your own character in the universe who goes on the different adventures trying to fix weird universal stuff but it's a lot more of an adventure game and I think a little bit less of a money sink yeah
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely a lot more involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just fighting where that one is, I think, fighting and adventure and full story and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this looks like a mobile game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw this not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have one of these at Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: My work had a thingy thing at Roseville Golf Land a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, oh, it's an Injustice game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it uses cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I thought, oh, the cards look like they might be neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then I looked at the price and I was like, hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the game looked bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they had it when we all went there before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, true, true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if, I mean, Roosevelt Golf Land with money gobblers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never gasp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gasp, I say gasp.
[SPEAKER_03]: There it is, your classic game to arcade, because not all of them are upgrades necessarily, of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Injustice.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: With that, we have some more things to get into.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before we wrap up tonight, we have some rapid fire news, some quick headlines to talk about here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll go over to Loki with some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't forget the other Ubisoft project on Apple TV, Mythic Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: So obviously having several successful seasons of that series, it only makes sense that they would want to have him adapt one of their actual properties instead of just coming up with something brand new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then, of course, they're also going to feature Noah Hawley of Fargo, that series.
[SPEAKER_06]: and apparently the collaboration they said is an embarrassment of riches because Far Cry you know they feel that it will let itself well to TV and yeah so interesting to see and it's apparently supposed to be on FX is where they're targeting that I don't know we'll see I'll be interested to check it out I do like some Far Cry early Far Cry so much newer stuff but
[SPEAKER_06]: and then also really cool and kind of unexpected we got an announcement that Heretic and Hexen have been updated and then of course re-released now as part yep as part of this was a QuakeCon 2025 announcement finally so finally yep so um
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they're basically getting the full treatment, being updated and remastered for modern consoles and Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also, along with that, they even have more campaigns as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's, I think, a new campaign for both games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have, of course, online cross-platform deathmatch co-op for up to 16 players, split-screen deathmatch and co-op for up to 8 players.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Toggleable soundtrack, they have an enhanced soundtrack, plus you have the original soundtrack as well 4K, 120 FPS, lots of accessibility stuff added into the game as well Modern controller support, widescreen support, save load All the bells and whistles Yeah, that's pretty cool, and it's on Game Pass, so if you have Game Pass, you can just pick it up Yep I totally forgot that this came out, and I need to check it out
[SPEAKER_03]: well ain't this something because it's already in my library oh apparently if you had an earlier version of it you got the upgrade for free I heard it was they've done this with Doom and stuff before like when they recently if you had bought Doom previously that you got the new one for free so maybe you uh
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not at all sad about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know if you would ever have a scenario where you would need this, but they did include the original DOS versions of the game with the purchase of it as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you do pick up that collection on Steam or something like that, you still get the DOS versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you have a DOS machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have an old DOS machine that you want to play it on, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: DOS emulator for Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: The DOS emulator for Mac.
[SPEAKER_02]: The irony is not lost.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotta get my config sys and auto exec set up and I'll be ready to game soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: As soon as I figure out how to allocate all that RAM.
[SPEAKER_06]: All that 4 megabytes of RAM.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't actually know what this is.
[SPEAKER_06]: This may have been 8 or 16 megabytes at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of it misreading the RAM and just going fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the game's already done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Right and Chat says, check my GOG library.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the new remaster.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know those attention whores were not going to be left out.
[SPEAKER_03]: As I've called them last week, girl, oh girl, they're not going to miss that boat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Girl, oh girl, get on that trend.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one of my personal heroes, Hip Tanaka, also real name Tanaka Hirokazu, is interested in doing video game soundtracks again.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's one of the absolute legends of chiptune music.
[SPEAKER_02]: started with Nintendo in 1980 as an in-house composer during the 8-bit and 16-bit era.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he actually helped design and program the audio hardware for the Famicom slash NES and the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's also done the soundtracks for Super Mario Land, Metroid, Kid Icarus, Balloon Fight, Dr. Mario, the Game Boy version of Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Co-composed the soundtracks for Mother and for Mother 2 or Earthbound with Suzuki Keiichi.
[SPEAKER_02]: and he wrote songs for the Pokemon anime and Nintendo said he wasn't allowed to do it anymore because it said he was working for another company so he resigned from Nintendo and worked with Creatures Inc.
[SPEAKER_02]: instead and now he was the president of the company.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now he's wanting to get back into game music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: He made a soundtrack for a game called Oasis from a studio called 17-Bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I have to find that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, oh, it looks cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, yeah, he's ready to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excited to see what he comes up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 4, Diablo 2 Remaster Diablo 3, Diablo 4 Remaster
[SPEAKER_03]: Immortal, for better or worse, was under his launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he's done a lot with driving the Diablo franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he says, after five years driving the Diablo franchise with four big launches, it's time to step away from Blizzard and Microsoft, sword in hand, and see what's next.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm proud of what we've built and excited of what's ahead for Diablo and for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was his post over on Blue Sky at rodferguson.bsky.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also of note, this comes right after a bunch of layoffs were done by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was not technically part of the layoffs, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Phil Spencer did reply and said you brought strength, hellfire, and vision to one of gaming's most iconic franchises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playing Diablo 4 with you was a blast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for everything you gave to the game and the community.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we will see where he pops up next.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt there's a new Diablo game coming out this week, but maybe there is something else you want to check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's go to the US, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's coming out?
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have a whole lot this week, but we've got Ra Ra Boom on PC, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got Senua's Saga Hellblade 2 on PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, Dwarf Romantic on PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drag X Drive on Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Madden NFL 26 on PC, Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series Midnight Murder Club on PC and PlayStation 5 Relic Hunters Legends on PC and Xbox Series Warhammer 40k Dawn of War Definitive Edition on PC
[SPEAKER_06]: Bendy Lone Wolf on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series and finally on PC, Nintendo Switch, off
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna play off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not on, but off.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bug off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's quickly, I wanted to mention before I go to Japanese releases, QuestBuster in chat made a comment about the Rod Ferguson bit that I thought was a really interesting prediction saying, there's speculation from some corners that Ferguson might go over to help Bioshock 4 after its recent shakeup given what he's done before.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a very...
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to have to bring out the wheel of plausibility for that one because I would rank that high on the wheel of plausibility, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a really good guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you for bringing that one to my attention, Quest Buster.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's go to Japan and check out the releases in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I will say on the PlayStation 5 and the Switch 2, it seems to be very quiet in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure what the reason for that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the only releases I have are on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have a quiet week in Japan for releases for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there anything like on PlayStation 4?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Golden Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know when that is now.
[SPEAKER_03]: After all these years, I figured that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... It's April and May.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, not a big release week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then we'll go to Europe, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually double-checking holidays for August.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 11th, we have Madden NFL 26 for PC Switch 2, PS5, Xboxes, Whisper Mountain Outbreak for PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 12th, Abyssus on PC, also Fallen City Brawl, RaRaBoom PC, PS5, Xboxes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Viewfinder for Xbox's World War Z VR from MetaQuest PC Senua's Saga Hellblade 2 for PS5 EA Sports Med and NFL 26 for Switch 2 A Fistful of Yankees for PC
[SPEAKER_02]: Iwakura Aria for PC and Switch, Beneath the Six for PC, Warhammer 40k, Dawn of War Definitive Edition for PC, Kevin Tom's Football Star Manager PC, and I am reckoning that this is real football and not American football, Ovis Loop for PC, Voxelgram 2 for PC, Drag X Drive for Switch 2 on the 15th, Robert on Earth for PC, and Off for PC and Switch.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was a comment in chat about, could it be back to school week in Japan?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was my initial thought, but it turns out, yeah, Japan's on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The culture in Japan is more spring-oriented for school starts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Today is Mountain Day, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I am one of those people that loves pretty much anything dropout, but Game Changer especially.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big fan of Sam Reich.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Sam Reich sat down for an interview with Kotaku talking about Game Changer and their seventh season, but one of the topics that got brought up was because they've been starting to implement video games into some of their challenges that they do on Game Changer that
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, well, hey, would you like to just adapt one of your dropout properties into a game?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, yeah, for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: The, I think, issue, and like most things with dropout, because it is a small independent company making all this stuff, it's just a matter of the time it would take to do all that and the resources it would take to do all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's kind of what Sam is saying here, basically, that...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we would be into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've talked about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it's like at this point, it's honestly more than anything just the bandwidth issue, which is if we're going to do it, we want it to feel like us, which means we need to work on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and we're not going to farm out the IP to some third party.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want it to feel personal and it needs to be something therefore that we're excited about that feels different enough from what's out there and feels worth our time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that basically the two series that Sam at least envisions that could possibly be converted into a game would be Dimension 20 and of course Game Changer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could absolutely see Dimension 20 since it's rooted in kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: High Fantasy Dungeons and Dragons type stuff so there's a lot you could do there with that but yeah I'd be excited to see that and they had some of the previous stuff with Game Changer they've done simple things like a maze game that they had and then a ski free clone that they featured in that as well so it's it'd be interesting to see if they did something with that interesting alright
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that was our last... I now have the weenus running through my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, Nick!
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, like, you know, the dropout is just great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just go subscribe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only see the little clips that come through on TikTok, but it seems pretty humorous.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like $7 a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like the, you know, Game Changer is a really fun series.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a Twitch site.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dimension 20, you know, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dimension 20 is just absolutely worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just anywhere where Burnley Mulligan is going to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, absolutely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is our last slotted story for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have some time for some last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always like to check in with the mailbag as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I saw anything in there, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We ain't got shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if you want to add shit, participate at Orangelandradar.com is the place where you can send us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was already shit in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cleaned it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, all the fucking spam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Annoyed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I was checking the blue sky as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't really get any questions on blue sky, which you can follow us on blue sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want at orange on trader.com, we use our domain as our blue sky handle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I will shout out our buddies over at game buoy.org because they always are so nice to shout us out and leave us a little tag on social media.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I just want to shout out our friends over at game buoy.org video game podcast, another show here at the voice geeks network.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have, I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't checked out their latest episode yet, but I know it just went up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that will be probably something I'll listen to on my drive up to Oregon.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, this is where we can open up for some calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to join our Discord over at vognetwork.com slash Discord, which I would encourage you to join anyway and talk with us throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also throw out some random questions in chat if you would like.
[SPEAKER_03]: But otherwise, I will check with Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like there's a few stories that didn't make the cut tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that game you were thinking of Dressed to Impress?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Dressed to Impress was the Roblox game I was trying to think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a little teeny news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a World of Warcraft thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did a new patch and you can lean on a wall now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wall leaning.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can look brooding and nonchalant.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they did also add new dungeons, a new raid, a new delve, new story stuff, new zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can lean against a wall now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to see Sassy Pants do that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, my old character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did play World of Warcraft not that long ago I checked out the most recent expansion it was fine I just I don't really have interest in the long term like the rating and all that stuff going on to be fair Final Fantasy 14 I haven't really cared about this most recent patch like I'm I'm really done with this expansion I just want them to move on to the next one which I guess this patch finishes the story of the current expansion I know but I I'm just gonna be honest I've been a fan of 14 for over a decade I just don't care about this story I'm done
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: for, you know, especially that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also in Modern WoW, they really have added, I think because of 14, you know, they've added a lot to WoW that, you know, the UI is extremely customizable now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really like the Delves, which are kind of like their solo or small party content that they have in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, there's plenty to do in Modern WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: retail wow it's just it's weird to get caught up with it I mean you you level a character through like a new tutorial island and then like you do like one expansion worth of content you pick where Chromie sends you or you do the most recent expansion if you don't have Chromie sends you somewhere else um and then like you get into the newest expansion from there but it's just it's it's interesting how contained the expansions are now I don't know
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think they have to because they've moved the story so far ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Joe and Hunter Matt says Rob, did you see or watch the new season of Wednesday?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see who was cast as Grandmama?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I didn't, but was that where Joanna Lumley was supposed to be in it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that who plays Grandmama?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to see it for that reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I haven't had Netflix in years, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I need to see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard good things about Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you seen the new season?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I need to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually didn't even watch the first season.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'd watch the first season still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I've been spoiled on enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still need to watch Stranger Things Season 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to love that show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I still do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you need to come over and watch Ghosts with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghosts?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's such a good show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, is that the comedy show on CBS?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I watched the British one for a while, and then I actually kind of like the US one better, which is weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: That I have, because I have Paramount+, that's all the CBS stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have Ghost UK on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got it all on my Apple TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is so good!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know me, I don't really watch shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very little I watch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, because I'm too busy sitting in dunes parties in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me run back to Loki and see if there's any last-minute stories we want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we can talk about Battlefield 6's open beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's been very successful.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had almost half a million players, nearly five times that of Battlefield 2042.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, along with those players, they also managed to swat away 300,000 of them that were cheating.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, you know, it's good at least that they're catching cheaters now and they can adapt it for the final game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, there'll be less cheaters in it, right, Larry?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thought process at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, cheaters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, we talked about Bioshock 4 and how there was some issues with it, you know, coming out in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully, it has not been canceled.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it is still in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the clarification is that, you know, it is...
[SPEAKER_06]: still having some trouble but they are working on getting that resolved so we shall see I hope so because I like Bioshock and I want a new one it's been too long it has alright well with that I think we're going to wrap up tonight's show DarkSakura I know you were on the fence about streaming tonight do you decide if you're going to do that or not I'm going to do it I said I would I'm just going to play some Mass Effect just you know maybe an hour or so cool
[SPEAKER_02]: Might do Zaid's loyalty mission.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me do my typical spiel and then I'll turn it over to you for a final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: But thank you as always for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell a friend or two about the show because we are the show where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: A nice five-star review wherever you found this goes an awful long way, whether that was Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for all the kind words and comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see an occasional YouTube comment pop in.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you for all of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And please keep that coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, let's get those final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: So DarkSakura, before you head off to space, your final thoughts tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too old for 13 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a long marathon.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thoughts tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another week's going to go by and another week that I'm hoping I can finish the data pack that I've been working on for now five weeks, four weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought tonight is I downloaded this puzzle game on my phone that's pretty cute that one of my friends on Blue Sky was playing and I was like, I want to try that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Puzmo.
[SPEAKER_03]: So shout out to Puzmo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got all these weird... There's a crossword thing in it, which is actually my least favorite thing, but then they have other word games that are... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got sick of Wordle after six months.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how some of you are still playing it, but there's other types of word games in there I think are really interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a poker game too that was kind of fun, so I'm going to give a shout out to Puzmo.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have a lot of other thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my other thought would be I'm going to try to play something besides Nostalgia this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we won't be here next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've got two weeks to do it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm leaving town this Friday and I won't be back until Sunday night, which is why I'm missing a alarm.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I hope you guys have a great gaming two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back in two weeks to recap just before I leave again for DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So sorry about it, but August is busy and people have trips.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hope you all have a wonderful night.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_05]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week.