[SPEAKER_04]: ... ... ... ... ...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're live once again for tonight, August the 20th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me, not August the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about August the 3rd?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fast forwarding time.
[SPEAKER_02]: August the 3rd of 2025 with episode number 1057 of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'm joined every week by my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're stepping into the future, or maybe that's just like poop that we're stepping into now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the future of the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of smells like great now.
[SPEAKER_02]: D, all of the above.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I hope you're having a good week, despite all the poop going on in the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that Twisted Metal playing behind you tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a brand new game called Fumes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you are a fan of like Vigilante 8 or Twisted Metal, Interstate 76 maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember if that game was like Vigilante 8 or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's the same universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: But essentially it's like a PlayStation-esque...
[SPEAKER_02]: Car Combat Game
[SPEAKER_02]: Which you can feel free to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I should always shill for the Twitch because we do tape live every Sunday night at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's VOG Network, 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific, right after the Bobby Blackwell show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we don't really run ads in the middle of the show because we're trying to do a live thing that goes to our podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you do have Twitch Turbo and we do run ads, like we do at the very beginning before we run live, we still get a cut of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: I get my money's worth out of Twitch Turbo because I watch enough Twitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watch as much Twitch as I do Paramount Plus or any of those subscription networks, so I get my money's worth.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, we certainly would not say no to your subscription money either over at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: It helps us stay legal, which is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, yeah, we got the new season of Twisted Metals coming up on Peacock, so I thought that might have been it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I love that you're supporting the indie games and the up-and-coming stuff, so that's
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've been looking forward to this one for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't picked it up just yet, but I'm probably going to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, it just came out, and it's like 10% off right now, but we're checking it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breakman is asking, this looks fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it on Steam?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is on Steam, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Fumes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smelling the paint fumes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, going to the gas station and getting high off of the... Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, SS2100 Matt in chat made a comment earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki is wearing glasses tonight, so he's bringing the Distinguished vibe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do it when I'm so, like, I've been trying to get myself in the mindset of, like, because I've been working on, not to get so much into my gaming week, but working on coding a data pack for Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's your coding glasses.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I try to associate it with myself that when I put the glasses on, I'm going to be focused and not get distracted by literally all of the other tabs I have open right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kids, don't bother me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Daddy's got his coding glasses on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not even the kids, it's just the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just like, uh, this is... Oh, YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Reddit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Blue Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just constant distractions.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need a pair of coding glasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have an eaten dress, but I don't have a pair of coding glasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: and not an actual address.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some folks are commenting on other car destruction types of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: QuestBuster saying I miss Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_02]: PodCulture says Red Asphalt was a good combat game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember that being a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that being a horrifying...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was both.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, yeah, it looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is funny because, well, it is funny to me because everybody was like, oh, the first season looked like garbage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like people were not ready for that first season, but it did fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get fine enough to warrant a second season that apparently people are anticipating a lot more than the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, here, I'm going to link the... Oh, someone already linked it in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, you guys are on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never underestimate the power of chat oogle, or chat GPT, literally.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyway, let's get into some kickoff topics for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into what is going on in the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to take it over to you, Loki, to start us off tonight, because Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so just keep that in mind when you're looking for Switch games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make sure that you're aware what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, that said, there were quite a few trailers shown off for different games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, starting off, we had Monster Hunter Stories 3 Twisted Reflection, which looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's expected to come out on the Switch 2 next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game I'm literally most excited about from the entire Direct whatsoever is Once Upon a Katamari.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a brand new Katamari
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you catch the screenshot in part of the trailer that said, they're 69 cousins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a lot more subtle than that, but it said something about collect all 69 cousins.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I died.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love humor that only potty humor minded people are going to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm down for a brand new Katamari game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That announcement doesn't mean talked about enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's going to be out on consoles and Steam, so check it out wherever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've already pre-ordered that stuff, but yeah, I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fifth dream in chat with a fair point, saying, I bet Keita Takahashi has nothing to do with it this time, and I think that's an extremely safe bet.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's moved on a long time ago, so I think this really is a classic IP in new hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, the Superman movie...
[SPEAKER_02]: People seem to like Pretty Good, and that's an old IP in new hands, and people seem to be fine with it, for the most part.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, I'm open to where this Katamari game might go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like by them advertising the soundtrack, by what they're showing in the trailer, by making those little tongue-in-cheek sort of jokes that they said in there...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that they understand the spirit of why people love the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I sort of like trust them enough to be able to do it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Although sometimes you see people get an IP and it's like, what in the fuck are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Bomberman Act Zero?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that what it was?
[SPEAKER_00]: X-Zero, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: The one that was all futuristic?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's take cutesy little Bomberman and make him fucking steampunk and see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: So when you sort of see that the IP is in good hands, you are a little more open to what they're going to come up with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Konami is not... Konami had a rough patch where they tried to spin off... For like 20 years!
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like Konami is finally getting out of their rough patch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're smart enough now to where they're pulling the Disney route is like...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we can't trust ourselves to make these games, so we're just going to license the IP to more competent studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what another great example.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bloober team doing Silent Hill, and a lot of people were skeptical about that, but it turned out, hey, this is actually pretty good, and now they're going to do another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Metal Gear Solid 3 remake looks pretty good, whereas Metal Gear Solid Survive sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: or Melga, yeah, was it five?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Survive?
[SPEAKER_05]: The one with the weird crystal zombies?
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't talk about that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Remaria points out M2 doing Salamander 3, Dark Tooth Seism hyped for Gradius' 40th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, like, there's a lot going on in that space, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's lots of, like, I want to see, I think, was Mega Man 11 without the folks behind Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because there was the whole, yeah, he went and made, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the other game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mighty No.
[SPEAKER_02]: 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the infamous divorce from Capcom and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes studios can carry on with the same style of game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did notice that the art style looks a little bit more detailed this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I remember with Katamari, it was very flat, cel-shaded almost to the...
[SPEAKER_05]: for all of the artwork.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a little bit of details here and there, but it's similar enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be fair, Katamari, the original, was a PlayStation 2 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are now in the era where... I'm assuming this is targeted at the original Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's both Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: The original Switch is still comparable to about a PS4, a little under a PS4.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's it's you should see some even if it's cel shaded, you should see some graphical, you know, and I imagine what they were showing was probably switch to footage, which is going to run probably a better frame rate.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it looks good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's supposed to be out October 24th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited for Bobby Blackwolf to have more break music from the Katamari soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, he only does Overclock remixes, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: More music, more remixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm still happy for the Overclock remix people to have more stuff to remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Literally, not a surprise whatsoever, Just Dance 2026 edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, yeah, every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, no shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like...
[SPEAKER_02]: if there wasn't a Just Dance game coming out this year I would say what's happening I want to be interested in Just Dance but I'm going to be honest it's connection to Ubisoft right now and everything that's going on at Ubisoft kind of makes me go it's got the ick like Just Dance has the ick right now I would rather picked up like a used copy of Just Dance for the PS3 or something than get this new thing I'm sorry but I'm also not sorry like there's just a lot of ick with Ubisoft right now
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has nothing to do with the hardworking people actually putting on their coding glasses and making the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all the fuckery going on at the top.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need to get like a Fortnite Dance Central game now that they own, you know, Harmonix essentially.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we just get Dance Central and spend that off into something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that I can go for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Rock Band essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rock Band 5 is in Fortnite essentially.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, if it didn't need to connect, I think Dance Central is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played Just Dance before like a lot of years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't feel like you're getting much each year, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: If people enjoy it, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not here to
[SPEAKER_05]: Judge what you enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon Ball Sparking Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: So brand new fighting game coming to both the Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting ported over there November 14th.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a brand new remake of Plants vs. Zombies with Plants vs. Zombies Replanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's also out on both systems as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of wondering what happened to this franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking about PopCap the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how epic all those PopCap games used to be, and then EA kind of bought them, and they were going for a little bit, and we had the whole, it's Peggle 2, or was it Peggle 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did a little dance on stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised there hasn't been another Peggle yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's Peggle 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: PopCap's kind of faded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I think Plant vs. Zombies, like, all just left.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, they have the IP for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you can't tell me that they couldn't get, like, a B or C team to put out another Peggle game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like...
[SPEAKER_02]: And why did we stop PopCap in the first place?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, those games were really addictive and fun, and you would think a lot of it would translate well to mobile.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand what happened there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe because they weren't built... I'm thinking back to Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know about 2 too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they turned it into a first-person shooter?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Garden Warfare?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Garden Warfare is that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm saying those games are meant to be more of that business model where...
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: would have like a crap ton of monetization in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But like, yeah, they could.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure there's like three versions of Bejeweled on mobile.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm almost positive that's a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bejeweled for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, because I can see that people would, they would want to keep that going because of the Candy Crush, you know, phenomenon and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's very similar.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I could see them doing that in like Zuma and I don't even know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh man, Zuma, what a throwback.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we still have those old games on Steam, so that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, this looks pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited to check this out again.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be coming out October 23rd for both Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: This I just didn't give a crap about because, you know, cool, it's coming to another console.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA Sports FC26.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hey, cool, you're going to get it for the Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully they don't treat it like they did with the previous Nintendo systems where you get this
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: We got another trailer for Final Fantasy Tactics, the Evil Ace Chronicles And that's going to be coming out September 30th as well on Switch and Switch 2 I think it's also coming out on PlayStation Systems Oh yeah, that's been announced quite some time ago Yeah, for a while ago, yeah Persona 3 Reload coming to the Switch 2 as well, that's October 23rd Right in time for that to be delisted off Game Pass, by the way
[SPEAKER_02]: That's getting removed from Game Pass this month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if it's related.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have another trailer for Hyrule Warriors Age of Imprisonment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know when that's coming out yet, but at least we got a little bit more footage of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like Hyrule Warriors, so it should be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Madden 2026 coming out to the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one was very strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game called Chillin' by the Fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a game where you make campfires.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then just the camera support with it feels like... It honestly feels like an early Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the way that it...
[SPEAKER_05]: it's just weird like I don't know um like why I would hang out with people in front of like a campfire over a camera but okay it's a thing so you know that is out now you can check that out um Apex Legends coming to the Switch 2 as well so that's kind of a big deal I hope more of those free-to-play shooty bang bang games that's out uh this week so on the 5th
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like I should try that, but I'm terrible at that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks kind of intense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hila, which is this mouse with a frog backpack.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you kind of do a lot of platforming and exploring.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's coming out on, looks like, 2026.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looked pretty cool, based on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Wars Outlaws getting ported to the Switch 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's coming out September 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Chronos The New Dawn is going to be coming out September 5th.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of a Dead Space-looking game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Yakuza Kiwami 2 being ported to the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's coming out November 13th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, apparently, the first Kiwami game as well is going to be coming out on that same day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Borderlands 4 being ported as well to the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also had some other games they showed off.
[SPEAKER_05]: NBA Bounce, Hello Kitty Island Adventure, Romancing Saga 2, and Shinobi Art of Vengeance all being ported to the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then kind of the last bit that we saw that was shown off by Square Enix are new games using that HD 2D engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have a brand new series that looks like The Adventures of Elliot.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Millennium Tales That's on the Switch 2 next year But they have a demo out You can check that out I don't like that name at all With the double the I don't think it's a good name I think they should have just called the game Elliot It's just It's a weird name
[SPEAKER_02]: Octopath Traveler Zero
[SPEAKER_02]: I would really love to see that Final Fantasy series any of it just put into this engine
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, any of, like, the one through six.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we just had, well, we just had the pixel remasters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, that stopped anybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I mean, how many times have we had, was it, The Last of Us remade the last five years or whatever?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, that's not a reason not to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say either another sequel...
[SPEAKER_02]: And that, like, we had a Final Fantasy IV The After Years.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think people would eat the fuck up out of a Final Fantasy VI too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think people would lose their fucking minds if Square ever did a Final Fantasy VI too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that seems the most obvious.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, II and III just weren't really released in America and have that same sort of, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't grow up on those games as much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy V kind of falls to the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And IV already had a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the original is really hard to do a direct sequel to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, we already had Strangers of Paradise, spoiler alert, and some other things that were really in that same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say Final Fantasy VI is most prime for a pixel sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's Chrono Trigger's turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the game that makes the most sense to do in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm saying this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you know what I would really want?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I would really want from the Enix catalog?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about the Terranigma trilogy?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about that whole stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Illusion of Gaia and those guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're action-based, so it'd be a little different.
[SPEAKER_02]: But those are the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brain Lord, Terranigma, that's the series I would love to see in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we got Live Alive, anything's possible, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is the 30th anniversary of Chrono Trigger, so... It seems like it's time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go into chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: S2100 Matt says, can't wait for Legend of Octopath, Octopath to the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Adventures of Elliot.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looked great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dark2CS says, highly recommend the Shinobi demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby pointing out that the Final Fantasy 6 pixel remaster did have one scene in that engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looked great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fifth Dream says, the same guy who localized Pokemon, the English, did Terranigma 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: that's pretty cool how about um Secret of Mana already I guess those games I guess we got Secrets of the Secret of Mana and then we had Visions of Mana right which was second to third I guess maybe uh no I'm Secret of Evermore that's what I meant Secret of Evermore is what I want to see but again I think that was a different engine they used for all that so yeah um yeah right Quest Buster, Soul Blazer, Illusion of Gaia, Terranigma in one package would rock absolutely
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you think of the direct overall?
[SPEAKER_02]: My Blue Sky feed was kind of filled with very tepid sort of... It wasn't a great... I don't think people loved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't really have high expectations for the partner directs usually, so it wasn't like I was expecting anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just more of... I think I was just more excited about the whole Kanamari announcement, and then the rest was like, okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing really else I'm excited about.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I wasn't looking to be excited by anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it was bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it just maybe lacked a lot of real surprises, and that is due to the nature of the Switch 2 being announced sort of off-cycle with all the other industry announcements, so this felt like there was a lot of catching up for
[SPEAKER_02]: are games coming out to other platforms that will also be coming out to Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it took a little bit of the, ooh, this is a new thing, shiny, sort of factor out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And therefore, I think it lost a little bit of steam for some people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think now that we've had this, the Switch 2 has kind of caught up with everybody else at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now maybe when we get to things like the Game Awards in December, which I guess would probably be our next big announcement set, unless Nintendo does a first party thing for...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So, and I would assume that Metroid Prime 4 is going to be that, you know, Friday before Thanksgiving week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we already have a date for Legends ZA, which I agree is going to be a huge title and it's going to be, you know, one of the reasons to own a Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except that, actually, that game is on Switch and Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess, to be fair, so would Metroid Prime 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have the bundle for that as well, for the Switch 2, where they're doing the same thing that they did with Mario Kart 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: so it's hard to say, it'll be interesting to see what Nintendo chooses to announce but I think then we'll get a lot more big games next year so we'll see
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, okay, let's move on to our gaming weeks and the types of games that we have been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki, you were kind of referencing your gaming week earlier, but how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, I mean, it's basically the same as last week, so it's just been Minecraft and coding my data pack in Minecraft, so still working on that, slowly going along.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost have the entire game loop done, I still have to debug everything, and
[SPEAKER_05]: Then add all this stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem is I keep taking stuff in there and I'm like, oh, hey, cool, I can do this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it gets even more complicated and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I was watching different Minecraft events that some of the people I know were in this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, wow, the stuff that they're doing in those data packs is even less advanced than the stuff I'm doing in this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to get it done sooner than later because it's been like 30...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week, honestly, truly, I have almost exclusively been playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when I brought that up last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, so here's the thing, and I've learned a little more about this whole setup.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm playing on a – and this is because of retro achievements.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like – I discovered randomly one day that they had retro achievements for Final Fantasy XI, and I kind of was laughing going, oh, they've got to be impossible, like they were on the Xbox, like get to level 75 at every job and that sort of thing, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I was looking and I was like, well, how are they doing that anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it through like a PS2 emulator, but the servers are down?
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it's actually this private system called Horizon.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Horizon is actually kind of trying to do its own thing with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very big, I guess, sort of private server.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: instead of doing one damage a tick, it does four damage a tick to make it a little bit more of a viable spell.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they adjusted some levels of some spells.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just some little things just to try to bring, I think, a little bit of balance to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm shocked at how many people are actively playing like the servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like the old days and all those sorts of things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm just very impressed at kind of what they built.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the interesting thing is, even though it's a 75 experience, they do have some features that are from the newer expansions like level sync.
[SPEAKER_02]: Level sync didn't happen until like Abyssia.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was when they bumped to 99 that they brought in level sync.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do think that makes the game better, really, because it makes it more people.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I thought I had my client in Steam but I got it through Amazon a long time ago and so I have the Final Fantasy XI Ultimate Collection Abyssia Edition yeah yeah that's what Alan bought me years ago because I was like I don't remember my play online login and it's tied to an email I can't access anymore so I don't know how the fuck I'm ever going to get these characters back and so he just bought me the Steam Edition because it was on sale for like 20 bucks for like everything and so I played to experience the book burning and everything new in the game but none of that is in
[SPEAKER_02]: This Horizon experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just really neat to see what the community has built.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Discord is extremely active.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it's... Loki, I know you and I burned a lot of hours on that game back in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is such a different experience when you have a Discord where the entire server is basically tied together, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So people can do shouts and asks in Discord.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, like, it's not... You can find things a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Wiki...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and the official strategy guide, it was a lot harder.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, my nostalgia is definitely strong with Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how long it'll last, but I'm enjoying it this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually did get an achievement because there is an achievement for getting a crystal for the Krags.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember the Krags?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Dem, Mea, what's the other one called?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, Hala, Hala, those crags, you get a crystal at the crag so you can teleport there, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So I got my, I got a crystal crag and I got an achievement.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, with everybody like, teleport, teleport, teleport, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: SJ100Matt says, so is it more doable solo or do you still need to depend on parties?
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to depend on parties.
[SPEAKER_02]: But people are a lot easier to find because they have the Discord and they have other sort of ways to try to find people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And keep in mind...
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't ran into toxic people yet, but I haven't done a lot of partying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing to keep in mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of the audience that's going to be into Final Fantasy XI are people that were playing it originally when they were teenagers or in their 20s.
[SPEAKER_02]: So most of the player base is like grown the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's people in their late 30s and 40s that are mostly playing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not all, but mostly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think by nature with that, you get rid of a lot of the edgelords.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not completely, but mostly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I would say, though, if you do want to do the solo type thing, then by all means, the original Final Fantasy XI is still a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can solo it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just has a monthly fee, which again, Square, Square, Square, Enix, Enix, Enix, Square, Enix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just bundle the XIV and the XI fees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paying for XIV should also give you access to XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would do you so much better in these times when Final Fantasy XIV has been losing a little bit of steam lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Just, you know, just do a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just, you know, accomplish a little bit and just, you know, kind of explore and just go back to remembering what the game is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just know that when they changed everything, like the meta as far as like where to level up, like completely changed when they did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I remember like it was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, you... I mean, the first part's still okay, where you go, like, to... You have rabbits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Near your starter towns, and then the desert, but then it's like, then you go to a cave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you go to Gusken Mines and burn books.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gusken Mines, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't how it was in the original.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no, it's way different now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: but uh um I was gonna say with Horizon one of the other things I think is really interesting is that they actually have a remixed version of the soundtrack which I can kind of give or take the remixes of the city music and the music that was there originally and like um you know the starting zones like I'm just gonna be honest I maybe that my nostalgia bone kind of
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if I didn't really care for the remix, I do like what they did to their all-original songs to add a little something in the areas that didn't have them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I would still have to go back and get that sound replacer thing to put the battle music in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I think is really easy to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's as hard as it was when PlayOnline... Because this whole thing strips out PlayOnline.
[SPEAKER_02]: You make your character on the web, and then it's waiting for you in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it strips out PlayOnline completely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: so I think it's a little easier to do that stuff oh and this thing embraces most add-ons there's like there's white listed add-ons and there's banned add-ons but all the white listed things are like mini maps things that are like quality of life that you know are not hurting the game to have it's like notorious monster snipers are the things that are in the banned add-ons they're very strict on real money trading so which of course they should be
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, okay, that's enough about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will say I did play a couple other games this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went to my friend's house the other night, and he has this really cool setup where he has two big TVs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have not ever really experimented with this, but he does emulators and he'll do multiple emulators all running at the same time to play multiplayer online experiences.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we were playing Resident Evil Outlast.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Disney.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Outbreak, not Outlast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Outbreak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resident Evil Outbreak.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We cleared two scenarios and had fun doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we went over to the Dolphin emulator, which I never realized.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know Dolphin has Game Boy Advance emulators built into it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I never realized.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I could see that because it's got the Game Boy player.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they come up in separate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just never realized that was in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should have
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I should have figured that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, they're going to have something to address that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: My brain was always, oh, Dolphin's just focused on the emulation of like the, you know, GameCube and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the, you know, the Wii and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, didn't know Dolphin did that either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to the controllers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's like a native...
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Boy Advance emulator built in.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so now I'm like, ooh, I want to play Animal Crossing and go to the island on that thing because that was always fun.
All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to get into some news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a reminder, we will not be here in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will be out of town on the 17th, but we will be back next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura ought to be back as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll talk about all the gaming news that comes back in the next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But until then, let's get to the news from this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, in this ongoing saga, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so we have more updates regarding the whole Visa MasterCard blocking not safe for work games through the payment processors.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's a little bit kind of a he said, she said type thing going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So essentially, you've got MasterCard, which put out a thing on their social media saying...
[SPEAKER_05]: clarifying recent headlines on gaming content and saying that MasterCard has not evaluated any game or required restrictions of any activity on game creator sites and platforms contrary to media reports and allegations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our payment networks follow a standard base of rules of law.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put simply, we allow all lawful purchases on our network.
[SPEAKER_05]: At the same time, we require merchants to have appropriate controls to ensure
[SPEAKER_05]: MasterCard cards and, you know, that they'd hear to that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing is, though, Valve then elaborated on that as well, saying, well, hold on, that may not entirely be true.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: MasterCard did not communicate with Valve directly despite our request to do so.
[SPEAKER_05]: MasterCard communicated with our payment processor through and their acquiring banks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Payment processors communicated with this with Valve and we replied by outlining Steam's policy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since 2018 of attempting to distribute games that are legal for distribution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Payment processors rejected this and specifically cited MasterCard's rule 5.12.7 and the risk to MasterCard brand.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently that rule states a merchant must not submit to its acquirer and a customer must not submit to interchange systems and transaction that is illegal in the sole discretion of the corporation may
[SPEAKER_05]: Damage the goodwill of corporations or reflect negatively on the marks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Essentially saying that they can't sell a game that's going to make MasterCard look bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I don't think anyone knows that MasterCard's behind a lot of this stuff anyways, and I don't think it really matters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's great that Valve spoke up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's great that Valve spoke up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So y'all need to figure your morals out because it's not okay that books and movies and violence can play by one set of rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: But these other games that may have themes, which if it's a gross game to you, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's for you to be able to make that – or a parent to be able to make that determination about because for some people – some people find –
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't expect everybody to understand this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people find release and therapy in working through difficult themes that may or may not have impacted them personally.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not your decision what to spend your money on at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that at the core is like the problem here is that it definitely has that appearance.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked about this a lot, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter what the facts are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything in gaming is going to be what is perceived.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the perception that's happening here is that the credit card companies control what we can and can't buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people are not taking that anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, MissingNo says you don't see them blocking payments on OnlyFans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, or guns.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I use my visa at the gun show?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure I can.
Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have to ask yourself what is a shitting table, it's not for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go chasing waterfalls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stick to the rivers and the lakes that you're used to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But trust me, organizations like the one in Australia that got this ban would probably be horrified at these types of things and tell you that you can't have them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jay Helinski in chat says, Man, Rob, what are you into?
[SPEAKER_02]: I am into going to the hard places to find the facts and analysis for you, the viewer and listener here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't fucking get it twisted, y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, where were we at, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, so not only Steam, of course, was affected by all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: HIO, of course, was removing games off or delisting games and even blocking payments.
[SPEAKER_05]: they're still kind of doing that but they are at least re-indexing the adult games that are free so they're doing that right now and they also said that they're working on getting a different payment processor
[SPEAKER_05]: Strype is currently unable to support sexually explicit content due to restrictions placed on them by their banking partners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Despite card networks generally supporting adult content with the appropriate registrations, Strype has indicated that they'll hope to be able to support adult content in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, I think then if it isn't MasterCard, then you start naming names.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this case, Stripe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, now we start calling their customer service.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, they shouldn't be able to dictate speech.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay in your lane.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Blake, once again, who pays attention to payment processors?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, unless it's PayPal, because PayPal sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, like, nobody is paying attention to, hmm, who are their payment processors on this website?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, as a bit of, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: ProTest for this whole thing as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good Old Games is basically launching a website called FreedomToBuy.Games to raise awareness on censorship in gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: And with that, they have offered up 15 games for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will say that GOG is kind of the ambulance chaser of the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And get your coin, do what you need to do, but GOG is kind of the ambulance chaser.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what I mean, you know, they're the lawyers behind the ambulance trying to, you know, something wrong, call Anne Fong, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, you know, what they're...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we are talking about them and giving them a free ad.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing what they need to do, but like, girl, I see you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, oh girl, GOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, oh girl, I see you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, oh girl, she's at it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, oh girl, she saw a headline and now she's got to do something about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's GOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so... So basically, you know, yeah, it does seem like there's a lot of, like, grasping for attention, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Free is free.
[SPEAKER_02]: But free is free.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want Postal 2 and a bunch of anime booby games, they're free for another three hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, three hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you got to get them now on those of you that are listening live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those of you listening on the podcast feed, you're probably out of time, but stay tuned for whatever Girl, Oh Girl does next because, you know, they're going to chase the headlines.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to chase the clout.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, oh, she's making a scene again?
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, oh girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about what's going on at EVO.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, EVO is the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: EVO is going on right now, and there are some updates going on over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's talk about some things that have happened at the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some of you in chat might have some other updates for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are the things I have so far, but some stuff may have come up tonight as we're taping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Virtua Fighter 5
[SPEAKER_02]: VIRTUA FIGHTER 5 REVO
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be automatically updated if you own that to the world stage version.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you own Virtua Fighter Ultimate Showdown on PlayStation 4, you can update for a discounted price of $9.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is just, you know, this is the ultimate edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: As we see oftentimes in the fighting game world, this should not really be new information to anybody that follows fighting games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thank you, TigerClaw says, they say it's the PlayStation 2 version of the Mortal Kombat trilogy.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about the Capcom Fighting Collection 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty fun, a good collection, and they're going to be doing a free title update, and it's going live this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: New content and improvements, including some remix tracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter Alpha 3 Upper is also getting four new characters, and of course the collection itself already has eight games in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're late to the party, then take note that you'll be getting some extra little upgrades with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter 6 DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: A brand new character was announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably the biggest non-surprise ever because they've been hinting at this for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Crimson Viper, Sea Viper, is going to be added to the roster for Street Fighter 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone surprised?
[SPEAKER_02]: Me neither.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Fatal Fury, City of the Wolves.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fatal Fury is getting Ken, as in Street Fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ken is coming to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, not Barbie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, now that you said that...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger Claw also points out one of the main things they talked about with Mortal Kombat Trilogy is Shang Tsung's morphine will be fixed because in the original it was causing lag because it was loading from the disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus the souped up system probably helps as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger Claw also wants to point out they revealed Battle Beast as a playable character in Invincible Versus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of new character announcements.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there may be more before the show is done because I think Evo is still going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it wraps up tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we may get a couple big announcements or two still before it's all done.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if we hear anything live, we'll break in and announce it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, we'll go to our next story, which is...
[SPEAKER_02]: We all knew it was coming, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we've already seen this before the Switch 2 launched, but now we're getting more updates as, of course, tariffs and all that stuff change.
[SPEAKER_05]: So because of that, prices are going up on Switch accessories, Alarmo, Amiibo, but not the Switch 2 system, at least.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, basically all of the accessories and whatnot are going up in price.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which would include Switch 2 accessories.
[SPEAKER_02]: So like Joy-Con and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So even though we're saying the Switch 2 system isn't going up in price, the accessories are, which still does have an impact.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so these include, was it the Nintendo Switch OLED model, the Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch Lite, select Nintendo Switch accessories, Nintendo Switch 2 accessories, select Amiibo, the Alarmo, and yeah, I think that... I thought Alarmo was one of those things that they only put out limited time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize you could even still get one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was like those game watches and the classic consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I never realized they were still selling them, to be quite honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: um yeah so they had they had all that and of course uh they i think they released that information via the nintendo today app so i gotta you know control that narrative but i mean we know why it's not a surprise it's not like they're trying to be greedy here it's just
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, prices of other consoles went up too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we ever get Sony prices?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we got Microsoft prices in Greece.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we get Sony ones?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they did it before all that tariff stuff started happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Certain countries.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but still, I mean, we knew this was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's, you know, elections, consequences, etc, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, if you don't like it, let your representative know not that it's going to change a damn thing, but it's nice to think it might.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they've already sold 6 million Switch 2s.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, pricing isn't necessarily slowing people down from getting a Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're hoping to sell 15 by the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the Switch 1 prices going up, they're just going to sell more Switch 2s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because at this point, why would you get an OLED Switch when you can just get a Switch 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess it does have a better screen, but I just don't... For now.
[SPEAKER_02]: For now, it's not a deal breaker for me, but maybe a deal breaker for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, so they're hoping to sell 50 million by March 2026, so the end of the financial year.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll probably do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it'll sell lots this holiday, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless something really insane happens or like 500 million percent tariffs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, as long as nothing stupid like that happens, I think they should be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think is ever a guarantee that it won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about the PlayStation 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go ahead and talk about the PlayStation 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumors and speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumors and speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_02]: MorsLawIsDead
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's apparently information that came from a leaked AMD presentation to Sony back in 2023 so because it's a couple years old some of this may still have changed it's not all necessarily set in stone it's all rumors in the first place but so so take it with the gigantic um salt that it's needs to be um
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So the leaks in this are saying that the company is going to be prioritizing lower power output to keep costs in line with previous generations for the PlayStation 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're trying to not up the price for this and they're going to lower the power output because the older PlayStations can be a little bit of jet engine sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, they're saying that in the PlayStation 6, there will be three times the rasterization.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's 3D rendering.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's in comparison to the base PlayStation 5 and twice what the PlayStation 5 Pro has right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're also saying that there will be backwards compatibility with PS5 and PS4, which makes sense because I think that was the last time they changed the main chipset, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're not having the same...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So apparently indicating that they want to tap into success that the PlayStation 4 had, and part of that was because of the lower price that it had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here's where things get interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, Sony is also working on a handheld.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've heard this before, that Sony may be coming back into the handheld game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently, this PlayStation 6 handheld will have a microSD slot, a touchscreen, haptic vibrations, and dual microphones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the PlayStation 6 handheld would be better than what we see with the Xbox Ally X. And there'll also be a USB-C port for video out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it almost sounds like maybe some type of like Switch adjacent sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, technology in this thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, especially with cloud and all this, who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, I'm not surprised to hear that PlayStation might try to get back into this handheld thing a little bit, especially considering the success that Nintendo's had on that front and that the Switch system works for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I just, I hope...
[SPEAKER_02]: as Jonah and Matt says.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, OLR, PSP, HD remake?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that depends on what they let people build for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Sony would have to support the hardware a little longer than they usually do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We all know Sony's track record with supporting hardware is mediocre at best.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also need to come up with things that make a lot more fucking sense than PSNear
[SPEAKER_02]: and some of these things that they tried to do with the handhelds that were like you had to have a manual to explain it to somebody and that didn't work in their favor.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think it's an interesting direction especially when technologically we may have hit the point about as far as we can go with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, PlayStation 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think we need to say much more about it now because it's too early.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see the facts later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's interesting to hear what they might be doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the handheld thing is fascinating to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of people would love for Sony to get back into the handheld business.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: As critical as I am of how they handled some things, I'd love to see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, another direct this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so THQ Nordic had their direct showcase showing off some of the stuff coming out in 2025.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they have a few games that look pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had Spongebob Squarepants Titans of the Tide with David Hasselhoff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty awesome, just like the movie in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tides of Tomorrow Wreck Nation Wreck Nation
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: that they're going to be releasing, Gothic 1 Remake, and I believe they said Gothic 1 through 3 is going to be hitting Game Pass pretty soon, so look for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really cool looking game called The Eternal Life of Goldman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of like a twisted looking thing, but it's a 2D platformer that blends, I guess, dark fairy tales, myths, and mystery, they say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It reminded me a lot of... Oh gosh, what was the old...
[SPEAKER_05]: 2D platforming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was one on Xbox Live Arcade that was pretty similar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It reminded me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Titan Quest 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said early access is now starting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the Guild Europa 1410.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a world building dynasty sim game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Re-Animal looks very strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is from the creators of Little Nightmares and Little Nightmares 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a co-op horror adventure game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, it's creepy looking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, like Little Nightmares, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Traumatizing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Fate Keeper that looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of an Elder Scrolls type RPG game.
[SPEAKER_05]: First person.
[SPEAKER_05]: It almost looks like they mixed a little bit of Souls-like into it as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, Darksiders 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: That should be pretty incredible as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fate Keeper looks interesting, Re-Animal, and I think the Eternal Life of Goldman are ones I'd be checking out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We mentioned a few games in there coming to Game Pass pretty soon, and as we know, Game Pass has been having a lot of big hits that have made its way to Game Pass lately, and Game Pass is making money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently in the latest fiscal year, Game Pass hit $5 billion in revenue.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's 500 million active users.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty
[SPEAKER_02]: Wild, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a whole revenue from Microsoft of $76.4 billion.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's up 18% over last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, this all is coming after the fact that Microsoft has laid off a shitload of people, which is really unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of makes this news kind of fucked up, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That like, look at all this money Game Pass is making.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we had to let people go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a form that they file called a 10K that talks about how the money is coming out of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they've added another $2 billion on gaming revenue, and this is being credited to growth in Xbox content and services and offset by a decline in Xbox hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though console sales have fallen 25%, Microsoft is seeing increases from gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, you know, it should be noted that is coming alongside the news that they canceled game project.
[SPEAKER_02]: They laid off people that were working on games.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are things to keep in mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, in their statement, they do say we continue to invest in gaming studios and content to expand our intellectual property roadmap and leverage new content creators.
[SPEAKER_02]: These unique gaming experiences are the cornerstone of Xbox Game Pass, a subscription service and gaming community with access to a curated library of first and third party titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, they're not going to tell you about all the stuff they canceled and closed.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what we're here to do to remind you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, it is, again, an interesting sort of side by side that is kind of fucked up, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, I guess, where this leads.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, as frustrating as all this news is about the layoffs and the canceled game projects, it's hard to deny that Game Pass is on fire right now, which is what Microsoft wants.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it could be interesting for what will be in the future for Game Pass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just kind of sucks that certain projects that were in Game Pass's future will no longer be coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess these numbers are maybe making Microsoft feel that they aren't needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get to the bumper.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's time for the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except Jamie is not going to do it tonight because she's not here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know who is here is Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's Loki's turn to pick a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really overdue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we had enough notice this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Loki was able to pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all I can say about this pick is it is something I am not surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm more surprised that this game is 10 years old than the fact that Loki picked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is the greatest of all time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Goat Simulator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, as with that, they released the trailer kind of showing off some of the stupid things that they were doing with this concept.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everyone's like, I need this now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're like, oh, okay, well...
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the Goat Mayhem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's kind of like a Tony Hawk Pro Skater type scoring system with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically you play a goat named Pilgor and you are in charge of making everybody's lives miserable.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a giant tongue that you can stick the things and pull things around.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can bounce off of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can crash into things.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can explode and ragdoll.
[SPEAKER_05]: All sorts of craziness.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then throughout the game, of course, you can unlock different mutators that give you different powers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So some of those, of course, there's a demon goat, which causes these goats to fall from the sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get different animals you can play as.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all called goats.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, for example, there's Tall Goat, which is just a giraffe.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Ostrich, which I think is like the feathered goat.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have another one that's a whale.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it kept going on and on.
[SPEAKER_05]: They kept adding different expansions to it as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they did everything from...
[SPEAKER_05]: releasing like a Skyrim type piece of content that you can play.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the RPG simulator thing where you can be a microwave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you Fus Ro Dah with a goat?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's actually one of them that's in there that you can get.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's in the Vanilla game, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get that mutator.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had, was it the Queen of Goats?
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a Sonic the Hedgehog spin thing that you could do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember there was one that was like a Yoshi mutator that you could eat things and then make eggs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's lots of crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jetpacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, but it was a fun game where there's lots of collectibles, lots of, like, stuff to try to compete.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and it was buggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was extremely buggy and crashed a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thankfully, they just recently remade that, so you can check out the remake, which came out last November, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd highly recommend playing that version over the original because the original very, very, very, very buggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was very easy to break that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But very fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I highly recommend you check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, of course, their second game, Goat Simulator 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The joke is there isn't a 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a big expansion that they put out for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's another expansion for that coming very soon as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll have to look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic game of the week, Goat Simulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: You sound so giddy to finally be able to add that one to the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is such a good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have wasted a lot of time in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the best part about the original one on Steam has Steam Workshop support.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: What makes a buggy game even better?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mods.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tons of mods.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Alan loves mods too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was watching him mod.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was he modding this last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have actually been Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he's back on that now that we got the new video cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it's like, I want to throw all the things at Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you know, because someone brought up, oh, aka the Asshole Goat game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you know that the Untitled Goose game was going to have an animated series?
[SPEAKER_05]: They even did a pilot for it
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I really wish they had gone through with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it on YouTube or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is on YouTube, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of pilots on YouTube that are fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Elvira TV show has a pilot on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is really funny, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I really wish that there was the Untitled Goose thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we'll get a new Untitled Goose game at some point, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think of what other random ass pilots I've seen on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw the absolutely fabulous American version because I did not realize that what's her name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Catherine Han from...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wanda, Agatha, Agatha Long, WandaVision.
[SPEAKER_02]: Agatha Long was in that with Kristen Johnston.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not realize it was her in the American pilot, but it was bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was not because of her.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just, that's a very hard thing to Americanize.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I saw a pilot for, you know, Clarissa Explains It All.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know they were going to turn that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like they were going to do like a Clarissa is an adult ABC series?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, all this chat, SJ100Mass says, I remember that series.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: All those pilots are there, unless they finally copyrighted them down, but I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of pilots and things you can find on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went on a YouTube rabbit hole this week, and there was some internet commentators that were making fun of it, but apparently Six Flags tried to do their own 90s show.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: is the cringiest thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like an MTV News type thing, but just it's so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fifth Dream in chat says, two words, American Red Dwarf pilot.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's four words, Fifth Dream.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll do you one worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: American IT crowd remake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even Joel McHale couldn't save that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: A rapid fire answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Peak just got a recent update.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Peak is that kind of mountain climbing co-op game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But to be silly, because it is a mountain climbing survival game, you're supposed to be like a troop of like Boy Scouts or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they put out a release.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, hey guys, totally normal update to the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing to see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then one of the...
[SPEAKER_05]: The list of changes is added cannibalism.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now apparently if you are your stamina is just, you know, pretty empty, you're going to start hallucinating.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so you'll do the whole Looney Tunes thing where the other players start looking like walking like pieces of meat or chicken or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can eat them and you get all your stamina back.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is so disgusting but funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, so, yes, as if players, they start hallucinating.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to get on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to buy this Peek game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who do I want to play Peek with?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwolf for sure because he'll get so frustrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll rage quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who else do I want to play Peak with?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need some... Oh, if Extifer is willing to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need people that scream when they play their video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe Extifer would be a good one if he's willing to make a return to the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's tricky.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does get pretty hard, but it is funny trying to help your friends and then stuff goes wrong, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then along with that other great news kind of just shadow dropped but Mario Paint made it out onto the Nintendo Switch Online SNES library it is on both the Switch and Switch 2 what is unique about this though is on the Switch 2 obviously it uses the mouse support that the Joy-Cons can do on the Switch 1 you have to use a USB mouse
[SPEAKER_05]: So you actually plug in a USB mouse into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if there's more games that support mouse controls using a USB mouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny you say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did add it to other games later in the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might not be in whatever you're looking at, but they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how they had put out a few things like Nobunaga's Ambition on Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: They put out a few games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did add it for those games too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That came later in the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so yeah, you can play Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's my question for you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you love this Rob Stradamus meme we have here in the show that the chat has going about these predictions that I make.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I did say that Mario Paint, I did say it would be a good launch title, like a new Mario Paint would be a good packing game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did say as part of that, that Mario Paint should come out on the Switch, you know, Nintendo Switch Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I get credit when it's six minutes, or not six minutes, six weeks past
[SPEAKER_02]: The Switch's launch?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think it's still close enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, it feels like they should be making a second Mario Paint game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see a Switch 2 Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, it seems like such an obvious thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they do end up announcing one for next year, I'm taking the full point, even if I miss the launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: PodCulture says it's still the launch window.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good point, PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just watch my wording next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's close enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, what, a month out?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll take the point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob has gained one point in ego.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, and if you think about it, what it's only been two weeks since the whole Donkey Kong game came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And technically that was advertised as kind of a launch window game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like it's not too far out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we love to move the goalposts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did I want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, how about PlayStation Plus games?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you are a PlayStation Plus subscriber, you know, you get free games every month.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what are you getting starting August 5th for the months of August?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're getting DayZ on PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Survival games.
[SPEAKER_02]: 60 players have to endure together, you know, except there's zombies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So be careful because there are no checkpoints and no save points.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you die, you are dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of bang your head against the wall, difficult...
[SPEAKER_02]: Grind Games, Lies of P for PlayStation 5 and 4 is also coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know you love Souls-like games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy Lies of P for free with your PlayStation Plus subscription.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we also have, if you want something a little bit, I guess, on the lighter side, My Hero 1's Justice 2 for the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, of course, the follow-up to the Arena Fighter, My Hero 1's Justice, and you get character quirks and you go head-to-head in battles in big arenas.
[SPEAKER_02]: so check that out or just don't forget to add them to your library and you know just an FYI that means last month's games are almost out the door so if you've not yet added like Diablo 4 was is one of the games for this month if you did not yet add those to your library you're literally on your last chance get on that before Tuesday so all right well if the PlayStation Plus games aren't of interest to you maybe you can go buy yourself a new game let's check out world release dates Loki what's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: this week
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a ton this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got Demon Slayer, Kimetsu no Yabai.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, Yaba.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Hinokami Chronicles 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wander Stars on PC and Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apex Legends on Nintendo Switch 2, as we talked about earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello Kitty Island Adventure on PlayStation 5 and then this is going to be the segment where I once again recommend highly highly highly recommend that you pick this game up on any platform because I think it is also on other console platforms as well Turbo Kid on Nintendo Switch I thought you meant the other one
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you meant Hello Kitty.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you were endorsing Hello Kitty.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck yeah, Loki plus Hello Kitty forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm sure that game's good too, but no, I'm talking about Turbo Kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turbo Kid is a Metroidvania game based off of the cult film Turbo Kid, which is like an 80s post-apocalyptic movie with BMX bikes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Such a good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's it for this week well let's go to Japan right now get in the car alright Nintendo Switch 2 releases we still have quite a few things in Japan this week Operation Night Strikers out in Japan this week UQ No Tear Blade for Nintendo Switch in a regular and special edition the Gradius Origin Collection is also out in Japan this week you can get a premium box version of that if you want we also have a special edition of Operation Night Strikers Faith the Unholy Trinity also released in Japan
[SPEAKER_02]: Okayu Nuyumu is also out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hybrid Adventure Neptunia Rebirth 1 in a limited edition also out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Behind the Frame and the Star named EOS also out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have two ACA Neo Geo selections coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's of course Arcade Archive and their Neo Geo partnership.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to pick up Volume 5, that has Arrow Fighters 2, Aggressors of Dark Combat, Art of Fighting 2, Burning Fight, Cyber Lip, King of Fighters 2002, Real Bout, Fatal Fury, Super Sidekicks, Thrash Rally, and Twinkle Star Sprites.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Volume 6...
[SPEAKER_02]: All of that coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Corpse Party, Tetralogy Pack
[SPEAKER_02]: Snow Brothers Wonderland and Fantasy Life 1 The Girl Who Steals Time I thought that had already come out in Japan but this is noted as a multi-language edition and it is a game cart not a key card so maybe that's worth mentioning I'm not sure so anyway that is also out in Japan let's check out the PlayStation 5
[SPEAKER_02]: Ghost Simulator Remastered is out in Japan on PlayStation 5 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gradius Origin Collection also making its way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rinmari, hopefully prepping their skills in that game because I know they love shmups.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Gradius Origin Collection is on its way to PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I might pick that up actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Salamander123, Gradius123, Lifeforce
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, so we also have Gradius Origins coming out over here as well on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_05]: The House of the Dead 2 remake on PC, Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had Fate, Hollow, Atarixia remastered on PC and Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Operation Night Strikers on PC and Nintendo Switch Ritual of Raven on PC and Nintendo Switch And finally, last but not least, Mafia The Old Country on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, UK?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because we still haven't finished Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: You cut me off, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a few more on PlayStation 5 in Japan, and then we're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robocop, Rogue City, Unfinished Business, Basureros is out in a regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Mafia, the old country, is also out in Japan, same date as the rest of the world, on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now we can go to the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, UK we've got Apex Legends on Switch 2 And Demon Slayer, the Hinokami Chronicles 2 is also going to be out as well on PC Switch 1 and 2, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series Gradius Origins on Switch And we've got Tiny Bookshop on PC And then finally Mafia The Old Country on PC, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_02]: Any interest in that mafia, the old country?
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks a little weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't really played the mafia game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not into Grand Theft Auto period peace games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of what that is, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need modern Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like if somebody would take that idea and lean into it and take it one step forward to a comedy type of thing like a Grand Theft Auto, which I guess maybe is Red Dead Redemption.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also have, was it, there was like, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Horse or something like that was one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a GOG game.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Grand Theft Amish?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grand Theft Amish?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about games that are taking a long time to develop?
[SPEAKER_02]: And when our last story here before we get to the listener roundtable, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a series that we haven't seen anything from in a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, they are working on Bioshock 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, apparently it's been restarted a few times with different game engines But yeah, 12 years since the last Bioshock game And apparently Bioshock 4 has been in development since even before that came out Yeah, I'm trying to remember what it said It's been like 15 years that they've been working on this essentially Because the development on this new game started before Infinite came out
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, now, of course, though, because of that, they're saying that there's been some, you know, the Bioshock failed to review by executives the new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then also that there's been layoffs with the developers that have been working on it as well, so they can be more agile and efficient.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you got to be agile when you're down people, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: that game has taken a long time to cook though it has taken a long time I kind of forgot that they're doing stuff there's other Ken Levine games though if I remember correctly there's that one that was in space when did that ever did that ever come out I don't think it did I honestly don't remember yeah so
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well let's go to the listener roundtable where you all can interact with our show every week You can send us emails over at participate at orangeloungeradio.com You can also send us messages on BlueSky You can follow us on BlueSky at orangeloungeradio.com We are verified by domain over on BlueSky I don't think we got anything this last week on BlueSky, no we didn't So, you know, maybe that's just a sign I need to post more, I don't know But yeah, check that out
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to open up the mailbag here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think we had anything, Loki, but I'm just going to verify that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you wouldn't mind, do you have any last-minute stories to throw at us while I pull up the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_02]: Since we're down a person tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, I don't think we have any other last minute news, but certainly I'm curious to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're like should be not that far away from Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's like within a week or two.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's real soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's right after.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's right after Evo, I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like we should be seeing some more news coming out here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: August 20th to 24th is Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_05]: OK, so a few more weeks, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: but yeah expecting to hear some more news regarding that stuff um be curious to see whether games are coming like honestly like uh I don't even know what the fourth quarter looks like right now I know that this year we've got was it Battlefield 6 and Call of Duty and you know some other mainline uh temple titles and stuff but I'd be curious to see how those all do
[SPEAKER_02]: The timing of Gamescom reminded me I have not yet plugged DragonCon yet on tonight's show I've been pretty good about pumping that up but just one more reminder I will be at DragonCon out in Atlanta over Labor Day weekend so DragonCon runs from officially it runs from August 28th Thursday through September 1st Monday but unofficially Wednesday's the new Thursday and some people stay around later too so I'm looking forward to being a part of the show again this year
[SPEAKER_02]: My lineup is still being finalized at the show, but the only thing that I know that is on lock is that Thursday night, and I think it was 7.30, but don't quote me on that time, we are going to be having a content creator mixer, and that is in the digital media room in the basement of the Hilton where the digital media events almost always are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Galleria 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very easy to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just go to the bottom of the escalator and it's right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to be having a content... Thank you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be having the content creator mixer down there at 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm expecting it to be bigger this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma
[SPEAKER_02]: content creator mixer meet your next collaborator to try to like really entice because we want that's actually what we want it isn't to put ourselves out there I mean sure our business cards and flyers will be in the lobby but we want to invite people to come in meet people learn about platforms other than their own that's the thing I get out of it I love talking to YouTubers because I don't do enough on YouTube and I really love talking to TikTokers
[SPEAKER_02]: because I've been consuming more TikTok, but I haven't been really creating a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm still kind of trying to find my rhythm with TikTok.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I'd be interested in mingling with people that work in different areas than necessarily Twitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I'm opposed to meeting Twitch streamers too, but just to like hear about that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, meet, connect, and network.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is absolutely it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwell says, I keep worrying that once I get good at TikTok, it'll be gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: The skills are adaptable to Instagram Reels and YouTube Shorts, which honestly, any content you make for TikTok ought to go on those two platforms as well before somebody copy pastes it over there if you ever get something viral.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think part of the trick with the short videos is you have to take a multi-platform approach almost.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's something we're going to talk about on some of the panels this year over at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So really excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can confirm I am involved with main programming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cannot confirm what that's going to mean yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I won't know until the app releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is maybe that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of different modalities, Loki would love more YouTube viewers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So keep that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, always.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over at LokiOLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you don't do the TikTok thing, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nah, I've tried a few and they just don't take off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to still figure out the right way to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then short form, I've done long form because I was like, oh, you know, some of these, they like long.
[SPEAKER_05]: For them, it's almost like long form is kind of like YouTube shorts in the sense that it's like different, but you could put stuff over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, nothing to get confused, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: you know I have been consuming more TikTok lately and I bet I'll name a couple creators that I bet some of you in chat will pick up on and it does relate to some of the stories we talked about tonight since we don't have a lot of other comments I'll just kind of go on this tangent is that that Switch story about the inflated Switch prices Aaron Parnas actually did a
[SPEAKER_02]: TikTok on that, which is the breaking news guy, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're ever scrolling through TikTok for you, Paige, and you ever get that young kid that's always like, we got some breaking news here out of Washington.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that crossed his feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that kind of shows, because I think it's one of the first major companies that has announced that they're doing tariffs or what the impact is actually going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Rimari says, I don't like TikTok because it's such a noisy app.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually, I get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm not sure I can sit here and say there's an easy alternative in YouTube or no, they're all just as noisy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you get something that might be a little more calm?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not saying that like I know people that love to watch ASMR videos, but I feel like you've said you're not a fan of those either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: But see, sometimes I will also open TikTok
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll open up TikTok and it will be this beautiful ocean view with the beach and it'll have this really uplifting sound that's playing like a happy little Enya song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sail away, sail away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the little caption on it says this and waking up to the headline that he died.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't say who.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all know who.
[SPEAKER_02]: But just to be clear.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not saying who.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we can neither confirm nor deny who.
[SPEAKER_02]: But your instinct is probably correct.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that is a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you allow the TikTok algorithm to sort of fall down that rabbit hole, you can get those uplifting sort of messages.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a hard thing to do, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, Aaron Parnas covered the Switch thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then what I thought was interesting, this is an interesting creator.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think their name is SilentMiddleChild.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm curious if any of you have ever seen this creator because they seem to get a lot of views.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there'll be a girl in the background that you never see that'll be like, hey, Anthony, tell me about this particular type.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's this guy that's very, he sits there and he's playing video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like it looks like he's playing Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_02]: And while he's playing Fortnite, he just effortlessly explains
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a big enough headline.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's showing up on the massive TikTok creator accounts and becoming content for them to explain as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I thought that was really interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, and I actually think that's like legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That guy does a very good job explaining things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm almost, and SSJ100Matt says, I still never download TikTok.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just scroll reels on Insta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guarantee both of these creators have shown up on Insta and YouTube, whether it's official or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, if you don't copy your content and put it over there, somebody else will.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, I would assume you've seen that guy on some platform at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you consume that stuff at all, if you don't spend enough time consuming that crap, then maybe you haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway, I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really have a lot else to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've gone on a tangent enough and we don't have any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that means we wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get the hell out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well then, let's get final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, I'm going to say thank you as always for downloading our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell a friend or two, because we are the show where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: A site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, YouTube, a nice five-star review, a comment, a like, all that stuff goes an awful long way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you get sick of hearing creators say it, but they say it for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really does help.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't ask for your money here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But a like can do more than throwing us, you know, a dollar, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: So please do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and I do see Dark Tetsuya has now shouted it out twice in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I meant to say something, sorry, saying I have to shout out Earthion that just dropped on Steam, Yuzo Koshiro, and Ancient's new Genesis shmup also drops on consoles next month.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I meant to give you a plug a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to check that out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, spread the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I said it all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So final thoughts then.
[SPEAKER_02]: No Jamie tonight, but she'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That means no Jamie streaming after the show tonight, but I believe somebody else is going to.
[SPEAKER_02]: So stick with us for those of you that are listening live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, we'll go to you for your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once again, I'm still hoping that I get my data pack done.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was hoping to have it done last week, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Progress is being made.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just taking forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, you got this.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought tonight is I hate technical glitches, but I love Final Fantasy XI, and I love other games too, and I'm going to play more of them this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a great night everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much for watching.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully Jamie will be with us and thank you all for your participation tonight whether online with us here in chat as we're live or on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Appreciate you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_04]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next week.