This week, a bunch of Nintendo emulation rumors made the rounds.
This is your reminder that Nintendo has done emulation multiple times already and the slowness
of rolling out games is less technical, though programming is always some part of it but
more often licensing.
The Nintendo Switch Online SP games are a cute addition that is most thoroughly technical
and I appreciate Nintendo's effort to add a new twist into these games as well.
This is just one throwback content headline.
Now it's time for your hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about
this rumor and the rest of the week's gaming news starting right now in the show where
every gamer has a voice.
Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live once again with episode number 911 of our show for tonight, April the 24th
of 2022.
And as I was as was pointed out to me on the Bobby Blackwell show before our show tonight,
apparently the 10 year anniversary of VOG Network which soft launched about what April
26th or so in 2012.
How about that?
My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always say hello to Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers.
Oh, hi.
Hi Dark Sakura.
How are you?
I'm all right.
I'm doing well.
Let me just take a quick minute to point out not joining us tonight.
Unfortunately, Tech Master Loki, as mentioned on a previous episode of Orange Lounge Radio,
Loki had surgery earlier this week.
He's been giving updates through his Twitter account at Loki O-L-R.
And I am pleased to report he is out of surgery doing fine.
And I think in one of his tweets, he said it was getting better every hour.
So he's just he's just at that point where he's got to let the body heal.
So I would imagine instead of doing the show tonight, he's sleeping.
And quite frankly, what a great thing to be doing.
I think, you know, and Dark Sakura, myself perfectly healthy, but a nap sounds great,
to be honest.
So anyway,
Honestly, many naps sound great.
I we're going I start back in the office one day a week, starting tomorrow.
And the whole thought is just filling me with like bits and pieces of dread.
Because the moment if I if I get sick, I'm taking it to HR.
Is everybody going back the same day or are they staggering it?
I think you get to pick your one day a week out of like, Monday, Tuesday, Thursday.
Okay, so there's a chance not everybody will be there the same day.
So it's a little bit Yeah, but still, now.
Now that you know, really, vaccinated or boosted status really isn't doing a whole lot to,
to starve off who gets sick, just the severity of it.
Um, I've got concerns then again, I came back from Disneyland just fine.
I was gonna say let's talk about the happy stuff.
You weren't here last week.
No, no surgery.
It was a birthday thing that you were doing last week.
Yeah, it was my birthday.
My birthday is very important holiday.
But you you went to Disneyland.
I did.
I am I had a very, very good time, although my body certainly reminded me that it it's
it's not a teenager, even though I tried to run around like I was so, so it actually my
whole thing started before then because Sunday I wasn't I wasn't here.
So what I ended up doing is I drove down on Sunday kind of rushed my way down and stayed
with Marissa, and Chris is our lovely friend, Marissa, who has been on the show a few times
and been in chat does some voice acting stuff, which is Yeah, I haven't seen Marissa in years.
So it was a really pleasant visit.
So you had a good time.
And then, and the area that that the two of them live in is actually really pretty.
I'd never been to the Moorpark before.
And it's sort of up in the hills.
And it was a little bit harrowing of a drive because my maps took me kind of a backwards
way.
But I'm glad it did because it was really pretty.
And then the next day, I went to pick up Tiara, which cements how much I hate LAX.
And so I managed to get Tiara out of the clutches of the the worldway traffic.
And we went to Anaheim and had sort of a late lunch at this place called Requiem, which
is a Final Fantasy themed coffee bar.
I had no idea there was a place like that.
That's cool.
It's beautiful.
Oh, awesome.
It's not far from the park, you know, so it's near where our hotel was, even though I got
bad directions because I put in the wrong days in.
There's like 50 million days in.
Oh, yeah.
They're all days in by the park, need to specify which ones which.
So so we spent a really decent amount of time there.
It was really, really, you know, and they serve you like these little toasties.
I had a Caprice one, which was, you know, basil and mozzarella and tomato, and it had
this like really good balsamic glaze on it.
And I laughed because Tiara had edamame toast, and I was calling it Japanese beans on toast
because edamame beans, you know, and and then we went to the hotel.
We had like dinner at Shakey's, which I've never been to Shakey's Dan thinks that I didn't
even know they still existed.
That's what blew my because you texted me that right next door to our hotel.
Yeah, you texted me that you were a tiara at Shakey's and I was like, they're still
around.
Like they all the Did you know the original I mean, you probably didn't but I'm gonna
share it anyway.
The original Shakey's pizza was in Sacramento.
The very first Shakey's pizza was Sacramento.
It's now the mimosa house down on 65th.
That was the original Shakey's.
So I and I remember Dan telling me about it before.
Yeah, and it's it's it's wild that like they're still open because they are they're all gone
here.
I haven't seen one in years.
But yeah, the the big wooden doors.
Yeah.
And the arcade they always had a really big arcade area like most roundtables games there.
I really wanted to play like like a deer hunting and some Oh, like, well, it's a Walmart arcade
at this point.
Gross.
Kind of.
Um, but they put way too much basil on my pizza.
I was like, I love basil and this is excessive.
So and so the next day we went in for opening and our mutual friend Nick was came to meet
us and I he actually ran into traffic so it was a little bit late but then he hung out
for a decent time traffic in LA what no no Nick straight next streamer here on Twitch
you and I have both rated him a million times yeah so really just just a cool guy all together
really sweet really fun to hang out with and then after after a little bit he rode a California
screaming with us or not screaming it's a credit coaster yeah credit coaster yeah and
and we we we just had a really good time and then he had to go off and it was me and tiara
for a while and we had dinner at Carthay circle I got a really delicious drink it's
like branding creme de cacao and coffee and cream but it like it kind of got my stomach
funny and I had Moroccan meatballs which I should have realized that there was going
to be something spicy in it so I ended up like having a slight allergic reaction but
it wasn't bad but I mean I got to pilot the Millennium Falcon I wish I had been right
pilot next time I want to be a gunner the gunners look like they had a lot more fun
is the gunner the one that just pushes the button the whole time because I think that's
what I did that's the engineer okay that's why I just yeah I just kept pushing a button
in the back row you're an engineer I thought I was in the middle but I it was a while ago
then you're a gunner okay I don't remember it was a while ago the pilots had a decent
amount of stuff to do but I I wanted to do the hyperdrive so I'm gonna wait and do that
next time it was really really cool I I had a good time with that one I really enjoyed
it the sense of motion was fairly realistic too and we did you know we did Haunted Mansion
we did Indy we did Jungle Cruise we had a really really good tour guide who I'm fairly
certain was non-binary and had some really funny Mean Girls oriented jokes fun did you
get to do Rise of the Resistance or too crazy I didn't do Rise of the Resistance it had
I didn't put in for the thing and honestly I was like it's a hassle the only thing I
really wanted to do was with Smugglers Run okay I had blue milk I will go on record right
now saying that if your throat is sore drink the blue milk it is somewhat coating and very
relaxing but the other good news it's been a week now since you've been back and no symptoms
of the big C so and I did a rapid test oh good good and so my rapid test was negative I also
though on the way out after I took Tiara to LAX I had lunch with Nick again and I was supposed to
meet Isaac oh but work got in the way of that so it was just me and Nick and we went to really good
yakiniku place hmm it's like the Japanese version of Korean barbecue yummy so um really good and
then I had I stopped at the grapevine after the grapevine to get myself a massage and one of those
like beat-you-up massage chairs because they're great and then I was checking the time for the
Bravo cheese farm which is my other resort that I go to 99 or 5 version 99 okay because I always
take 99 back that's the one for me is the one I go to that has the llama that gives no fucks
because you know they built one like at the exact same place on i-5 yeah it's funny it's yeah two
of them I know but I have to go to the one on 99 that's the one hmm and so I thought oh no they
close at seven so I booked it I like was doing a hundred in my Fiat TV I made it on 99 like I
there's a part so so for those not from the area there's two major freeways 99 with me you know I
know but I was to say for those not from from the California there's two major freeways that connect
like Sacramento NorCal and LA you can take 99 or the five it's it's and five is usually like
trucker route cows nothing there 99 goes through all the towns like Stockton Modesto Fresno Bakersfield
like all the towns in the valley you're going through on 99 so there's more to do on 99 but
five is the one where you can drive a little faster because there's like no but less people
on it but truckers and you know cows inside of the road now more cops on five now it doesn't
totally surprise me people people do drive crazy on five like not just me they were doing some
construction though on 99 but I was I was pretty I mean I drive a Fiat so when the lanes went narrow
I could still maintain speed and it was it wasn't that bad but when I got there they're like oh no
we're open till eight we changed it we just didn't do it on our website and I'm like fuck's sake so I
hung around and they have more animals there but that that alpaca still gives no fucks he was just
like I'm just gonna sit here whatever I'm bored I made friends with a goat and then I watched the
funniest thing I actually have this little video of it where there's a bunny hutch now oh by the
way I played with Marissa's bunny Snoopy who I I'm in love with that rabbit I'm gonna go back and
steal him but the bunnies in the hutch like I caught two of them they look like they were
just cuddling so they like a little video of the bunnies cuddling and then the other bunnies okay
it's time to fuck and the girl bunnies like fuck you I'm not into this and she like bounces off and
the bunnies following or trying to mount again over and over and finally she just like turns
around at him and then she bounces off and he finally gets the idea but I'm like you tell him
you tell him little girl bunny tell him you are not down you tell him to take no for an answer
lady bunny all right not being lady bunny I didn't mean that in lady bunny way she didn't
have on nearly enough wigs let me let me go to the chat believe it or not it's a video game podcast
we'll get into that too but I do want to go to the chat over at twitch.tv slash of hog network
where we do tape live every Sunday night nine o'clock Eastern six o'clock Pacific right after
the Bobby Blackwell show and Mike Deft is asking the five covers the whole state doesn't it
yeah it ends in TJ it like the San Diego and Mexico border that's where five starts in the
south and it goes all the way it goes through Portland through Seattle all the way and ends
in Canada at that that town I can't remember the name of the town way up there in North
Washington but basically Vancouver because they change the freeway changes names you get into
Canada but basically it takes you to Vancouver Bellevue no Bellevues before now it's another
B name but I can't remember the name off top my head but way up way up it's not far north of
Seattle it's only like as I think the Canadian border is only like an hour or two north of
Seattle if that so yeah but anyway yeah five five is preferred I still prefer 99 it goes three lanes
more often you've got more truck stops you know yeah there's more to do there's more to see
exactly and for me given that I'm still having that issue with you know my alertness
for me being able to stop like that it was a good idea sorry I have cat drama going on behind me
like smoosh always arguing yeah smoosh just chased cheddar in here I'm trying to see
I can't even see where cheddar ended up he must have went behind the couch they ran in here so
fast don't worry I'm sure folks in chat are dying to see the cats if I if I catch one of them I'll
show them on stream don't worry so but yeah they're still they're still getting used to
they're still getting used to each other so is cheddar coming out of his uh little shell a bit
more he is oh he's at my feet he's he's getting better he's less shy than he was but like smoosh
will pick on him like smoosh is starting to be an aggressor smoosh will like follow him around and
then like do this thing where he goes and like snort like right at him like he's and then cheddar
just books it and smoosh will follow him like that's their way of like playing lately now
cheddar's like at my feet and refuses to move super adorable so anyway you hear any meowing
that's what's going on is they're basically taunting each other so all right wait cheddar
cheddar hold on buy me time dark sagra okay um I have five dollars and that will buy you two
seconds of time haha um I don't know if smoosh is trying to be dominant though it just doesn't seem
cheddar didn't like that oh yeah well cheddar is a very shy boy yeah he is
so he let me he let me uh boop his nose he's super adorable like whenever I'm napping or
I'm asleep cheddar will run in and like wants to like lie on top of me and purrs really loud he's
just I think he's very very happy to be um indoors because we were it's interesting so I started
cheddar and instagram and just through the whole process the people that found cheddar actually
follow him on instagram because the adoption agency like you know we were we were fine with
the link being given out or whatever so they they put him in touch and so we got to see because I
I looked at one of the instagram and I got I could see um that uh I could see a picture of cheddar
when he was found and they really cleaned him up like he he was not in good shape when he was found
so but he's so adorable now you have to send me that link later yeah I will for sure
so uh pod culture and chat says so is one more each dad's kitty it does seem right now anyway
that smoosh follows alan around a little more and cheddar follows me around a little more but
I don't like I also really don't want to play favorites like I love them both um it's just you
know whatever it's what it is so yeah all right uh let's get into some video game news I mean we
could have a cat podcast tonight I suppose you know considering that Pax East was this weekend
I feel like the news is still a little bit light all things considered so you know what we probably
could fill up three hours about cats but we will get into the news and we're going to start tonight
talking about Nintendo and you know uh workers rights in the video game industry is something
that's really been a theme on our show for the past couple years honestly and everything really
came to a climax when we were talking about Activision Blizzard and still everything that's
going on there I know you have an update on that later in the show um but this week the eye of
workers rights in the industry has turned to Nintendo um there's a lot of game blogs are
are talking about a Nintendo staffer who says that their right to unionize was violated and this is
per a complaint that was filed with the national labor relations board um this also it should should
be very important to point out this is a lot to do with contractors rights as well because
contractors are really used a lot in the gaming industry I think more than is talked about quite
honestly um contractors sometimes known as like temp agencies is another you know big thing
contractors are a way to find labor very fast because a lot of your contractors have already
done things like screening interviewing and so forth so they know that somebody's like ready to
go um and you it's it's a good way a lot of times for companies to find uh folks to hire long term
as well I got my job that I was at for 14 years through through a contractor temp temp agency
yeah I'm heading on nine years so it's it you know for first but of course dark soccer and I
also don't work in the games industry so it's uh you know um but this uh uh contracting company
that Nintendo uses um Aston Carter which is a global hiring firm uh the uh worker is uh
basically claiming the both of them violated their legal legally protected right to unionize and this
was a complaint that was made with the national labor relations board on Friday what happens is
that this contractor alleges that Nintendo of America and Aston Carter said they did concerted
activities and quote coercive actions to interfere with their right to organize um now the
filing only has broad charges so we don't know like who was involved what was involved we don't
know any of the specifics but per report from Axios quote the allegations were likely to include
claims of surveillance threats retaliation and either a layoff or refusal to hire um that's also
mentioned in a similar article from protocol um there will be an investigation but a lot of folks
saying you know what probably not nothing's going to happen uh a University of California Berkeley
professor and labor expert Harley Shaken said in an interview if the NLRB is listing these
allegations it's pretty serious and their ability to act is very real after these allegations came
out a twitter user known as the boy came out and said they worked at Nintendo and said working for
Nintendo contract for three years was one of the most stressful and awful experiences of my life
co-workers were great but i was constantly under pressure of being let go for little things like
going to the bathroom or being stuck in traffic an extra two minutes before work additionally they
have an awful practice of dangling the carrot a full-time employee to contract so they almost
universally never hire on just to keep exploiting them and keep them quiet i spoke up to try and
better things for co-workers main reason i was let go tbh um again a lot of this to me speaks
to contractors rights i mean there's a few things going on with this story right number one we've
said from the very beginning since these Activision Blizzard reports came out and even before that
this is an industry problem right so if you thought Nintendo was immune from this type of
stuff i mean surprise now i get Nintendo of America i guess we could be thankful for a moment
at least we're not hearing anything about sexism or you know some of those more serious things
we've heard coming out of the activisions and like you know uh that that whole he was gonna
kill his secretary or something allegedly i'm sorry i'm totally butchering the quotes but there
was some really messed up stuff that came out of the activision stuff right you know i i feel
awkward sitting here going at least it's just contractors rights but i don't i don't want to
diminish the situation either i mean this whole thing about they could get fired for the littlest
thing this is why a lot of companies and not just the tech industry quite frankly go to contractor
agencies because yeah it is really easy to let somebody go sometimes i think the contractor
agencies are predatory practice i see but it's it's weird because i also feel like it's biting
the hands that feed me a little bit because sometimes it's worked out my favor in the past
you know as far as like getting in with a big company um it just felt though for some of us
i would expect the majority don't work out yeah no and i i'm i'm all for like this whole
practice of how this works getting scrutinized and getting looked at and contractors rights
being taken seriously please don't misunderstand me with what i'm saying um but i just say this
a lot of these things that are being talked about i don't think are unique to tech either i think
this is a lot with contractors and you know just in general how that all works so uh going to the
chat because you know our chat is going to light up at this uh over at twitch.tv slash vog network
deejirama says i kind of think that this person is mad that nintendo wouldn't flip their contract
over to fte maybe so i mean but you know we talked about like the dangling carrot and all
of that stuff maybe there is a frustration there you give and give and give and you expect that you
know maybe you're going to move up the ladder maybe get some of the benefits you know and
stuff that comes with being a full-time employee maybe it does get frustrating when time and again
that doesn't happen for whatever so uh fanara in chat says contractors equals first one out the
door yes as well like if there's ever a layoff or something like that almost always yeah contractors
like unless they're highly specialized almost always yeah um deejirama s also says well even
as a contractor you have to still follow the handbook of the company but they really can't
fire you over silly stuff um quest bus they can reach out to the the contracting company and say
that you're not a good fit i i have seen it and i i'll speak openly about this because it's not
my current company and it's not you know anything where any of us are affiliated with currently but
i've absolutely seen it where a person didn't show up to work for two days in a row and somebody
would call the contract agency and say could you just let them know we don't need them back
and send somebody else and it didn't even it didn't even really matter what the reason is
just they they we needed them they weren't here let's do somebody else and that's what you know
happens with contractors um and they can totally do it as retaliation i i was working with a
mortgage company once that they were violating several federal laws and i called them on it
and i told them why and i showed them the laws and like when i do this work i'm going to be
documenting every piece of it i'm not going to have anything that i do come back and bite me
and they let me go and yeah and then i filed it and then i filed a complaint and the company
was gone a year later yeah and you know you know she just doesn't fit in with the culture here
yeah i'm not gonna break the law for you
anyway well they didn't last the the year because i'm not the only one that filed the complaint too
yeah so anyway um just that's you know uh what's going on at uh nintendo uh is under oops sorry um
i'm having problems with my computer over here where did discord go okay there we go
okay um but uh another thing i wanted to say about this whole nintendo uh news is that nintendo did
comment on the situation um so nintendo said we are aware of the claim which was filed with the
national labor relations board by a contractor who has previously terminated for the disclosure
of confidential information and for no other reason but that see i kind of like i get what
nintendo's doing here and covering their butt but i kind of think that reason like they were watching
him and he said something to somebody and they just they jumped on it you know what i mean like
i i don't know this seems a little bit of a stretch to me but whatever i'm not i'm not there
i don't know the specifics whatever uh nintendo is not aware of any attempts to unionize or related
activity and intends to cooperate with the investigation conducted by the nlrb
nintendo is fully committed to providing a welcoming and supportive work environment for
all our employees and contractors we take matters of employment very seriously well then i would be
curious what they have to say about the twitter user i talked about as well and other former
employees whether they be full-time or contractor i've heard other stuff as well that wasn't posted
as publicly um that's rather interesting so uh you know it was really just a matter of time
before your fav in the industry had a good good look at it as well and so here's now you know
nintendo's turn to look at what are they doing right what are they doing wrong so interesting
anyhow let's move on and talk about the types of games that we have been playing this week
in how was your gaming week dark soccer i know you were at disneyland but did you
fit in any uh video gaming in your week um yeah i mean i i streamed so i played dead by daylight
and i played second and said to three um i have four of the mana beasts down or whatever they're
calling them the the nevadons i think is what they're calling them i i just think of them as
the mana beast um so um halfway through them and then i think after that after the other four then
i have the last fight so and then i've beaten the game and i'm moving on to tear enigma probably
whoa yeah um and dead by daylight i'm kind of i don't know i just like i didn't have any
concentration yesterday so i was just sort of being you know whatever about the game
it's just sort of like i don't care all right they won yeah whatever okay good sure yeah you
can boop my demo dog i'm still going to tear you to pieces i actually played demo it was kind of
fun he's a cute puppy i i didn't i haven't touched it by daylight all week i don't know what it is
i'm not like consciously trying to avoid it or anything i just kind of feel like the game's in
a bit of a lull for me right now i still play regularly for consistency it's also like double
experience yeah i heard that was going on this weekend the eerie shards yeah but um um i'm still
i still have fun i get frustrated sometimes and yeah like fanara just said new rift comes out on
the 27th oh that's right it's a twins rift yeah twins and david maybe i'll log in for that yeah
yeah so i have to see if there's anything you know worthwhile in it that i want that would
make it worth paying for so i mean i like i who am i kidding i like all the cosmetics so
i already have enough of a what is the orange shards i forget what they're called the oric
cells that's it i have enough of those on my account to buy the rift i probably will whatever
who cares i've actually i once paid for a whole rift as in like paid to advance on it oh wow
okay and that was for all the pig stuff uh okay got it because i'm sorry i'm the pig mane
um but no other other than that uh those are you know that my my wordscapes i'm still kind
of addicted um didn't really do much else um yeah right just i didn't even play astro blasters
um my gaming week uh honestly not a lot of new stuff it's it's two of my standbys i played a
lot of both i played more no man's sky i actually was really good with my streaming this week i
you know ever since the move and my life getting you know the raid turned upside down yeah you're
welcome um it's since all that kind of turned things upside down um i've been getting back
into streaming more regularly so i stream monday tuesday wednesday and one other day whatever day
i rated you friday maybe so um yeah i've been streaming more it's weird um but i played no man
sky on monday and i think friday stream the night i rated you i think i was playing that too
um and uh yeah no man's sky i i beat expedition six so i cleared everything with that expedition
and as annoying as it was with the increased pirate raids i think it made me a better no man's
sky player for one it forced me to do an element of the game i don't normally you know pay attention
to which is the combat stuff i would actually say it's probably the easiest expedition well
the normandy one was probably the easiest and that was more because of the length it was designed to
only be like a two-week expedition so you had to beat it in like five hours of game time um so that
was probably the easiest one but i would say six was probably the second easiest one uh if you're
willing to do the combat fights now i know bobby's talked about this on his show he really does not
like to do the fighting he's more of a pacifist player and i get it like if you don't like to do
the combat this latest patch is kind of annoying because they added
more opportunities to get fights picked with you but another thing i learned is that you can pretty
much run away from anything as long as you don't engage if you keep running one direction long
enough or flying long enough in one direction you can get out of it without engaging it's just
annoying because you know like a lot of things no man's sky you're doing one thing and then squirrel
something else comes up uh that's just how the game goes but i enjoyed my experience in the
expedition so much that like friday i was just like you know what i want to continue in this
new game that i started because um i beat the beat the expedition like an hour into monday's stream
and it was the last day for twitch drops and twitch drops take about three hours so i was like
you know i'm gonna try to do a three hour stream let's just start a new game let's do a new game
with all these rewards i've been collecting through twitch drops and everything so i started
the game and then i kind of found like i was missing it i kind of want to play that game again
um so i did on friday and um advanced my game and i probably will stream that a couple more
days this week so i just i like no man's sky is just a relaxing game and the nice thing about
streaming it is that you know enough especially with the twitch drops a lot more people were
coming into chat but even on friday when there were no drops you know some some of the peeps
that i've known for a long time thanks to olr and hanging in other communities just coming in just
chilling out hey what's up you know this game is still pretty but just talking about stuff while
i'm blasting rocks for dust so um yeah quest buster says i just found out that you can make
squadrons and have a wingman warp in when you get into a fight they're not that great but they give
the pirate something else to shoot at yes you don't really learn about that until the very end
of expedition six but as soon as you get your freighter which in the main story or any time
really it's in the game's code if you do five warps galaxy warps your fifth galaxy warp you
will always warp into a freighter fight if you kill the pirates which isn't that hard you the
freighter will invite you aboard and the captain will be like i'm sick of this why don't you take
my freighter and you can get the freighter the minute you get that you can unlock at one of the
panels squadron mates and they cost nanites like most things in the game does um but they're it's
pretty easy to recruit at least one and uh yeah they'll fight by your side in some of those battles
which is uh pretty nice so something to think about um anyway also i've been playing follow
fantasy 14 because i was sidetracked by no man's sky with the expedition that was timed over easter
weekend i um was neglecting the 6.1 patch in follow fantasy 14 which i finally caught up with this
week so i streamed on tuesday and wednesday night shane joined me we did some dungeons i've done
the new dungeon i did the new raid i didn't do that on stream i ended up doing that um like
yesterday saturday or something i don't remember uh so yeah so uh been enjoying the patch in 6.1
final fantasy i'm playing sage for the first time which is one of the new classes that came out with
endwalker and it's funny because i i played it for the very first time on stream on wednesday
and i think you hear me sitting there kind of going none of these words make sense none of this
thing makes sense none of but now that i've played it and i'm up to like level 76 now um i actually
really enjoy the rhythm of sage it's a very like fast pace there's always something going on type
of healer where you're doing damage and healing and barriering and so it's very like satisfying
when you do it well but it can be tricky to get the hang of it first but i'm enjoying my adventure
in sage right now in final fantasy and i'll probably take it to 90 honestly so that'll
probably be the next class i get to the end game i still have yet to look at the pvp in final fantasy
but that's kind of on like my list of things to do hopefully in this next week so that's pretty much
my gaming week uh mike deft in our chat talks about most of my gaming this week has been pokemon
either go or unite which some kirby thrown in there and that does remind me you know i don't
talk about the um gps games but i should because they do take a lot of my attention yesterday was
like niantic community day where they were doing stuff in all three games so pokemon go had the
stuff old debut and all that stuff in the shinies um and pikmin had a you know their community day
for tulips so i walked 17 000 steps yesterday because in the morning i was walking with my
pic my ingress friends although there was a thing going on in ingress but it was kind of like
very passive and not like so we we weren't even playing ingress we were doing pikmin and walking
that and i got like 9 000 steps just walking with my friends and then i went back to the i had to
pick up my sister at the airport i went back downtown after all that and i went out for
stuffle community day and walked another like 8 000 steps walking around the capital several times
so but i caught 19 shiny stuffles like it was again and i only blew i only bluetooth caught
the whole time um it was one of those things where i was like i i after an hour and a half i was like
i don't need this many stuffles i have 19 what am i going to do with these uh i'm done i have
1200 candies i'm kind of done so but i had a very productive day so that was my like niantic day so
i always forget to talk about the gps games but i play plenty of those as well it's not always just
final fantasy and no man's sky whatever standbys i have also i played my burger time machine
a little bit today really yeah i was trying to see if i could get the if i could get cheddar
to be interested in it because smush really likes the light and the noise and i was trying to see if
i could get cheddar interested in it so i played it a little bit to get the noise and all that
he didn't care he didn't care so it's interesting how cats like different things that's for sure
yeah midna would rather just like sit at the at the glass door and just watch everything outside
you know cat tv no smush used to like get up on top of it and all that stuff too but now the
cheddar's here he's his pastime is very much watching and patrolling whatever cheddar does
so anyway all right let's get into some more video game headlines for this week i hope you all had a
good week uh whether it was you know playing video games uh or going to something like pax east was
this weekend um i know that was the first convention um in a long time for a lot of people
i also know pax east did hecka precautions uh with mandated vaccines and masking so hopefully
everything is okay i always think it's a good idea if you're going to go to a convention like
that or whatever at least take a rapid test honestly just take the the nose swab test from
uh a medical provider like three days don't do it the day after do it like three four days
after just to make sure i think it's just always a good idea um i plan on going to dragon con over
labor day i'm sure there will be precautions that's fine and i will take a test as soon as i
get back just just to make sure just to be thorough but the reality is in this day and age
you go anywhere with a lot of people covet's going to be there somewhere you know you everybody
heard the story uninvited guest yeah everybody heard the story at gdc about the person who knew
they had covid and went to the industry parties anyway and that's just the reality is that's the
grocery store that's transit that's the airport that's a restaurant that is anywhere a lot of
people hang out somebody is going to go full well knowing that they have covid so if you're going
to be in close proximity with people in any of those situations look out for yourself you know
just unless unless you truly don't care then i hope you have a speedy recovery that's that's uh
like those people yeah it's that's all i got so all right moving on let's talk about in games
uh headline from ubisoft you know ubisoft not only in the working conditions uh environment but in the
nft's environment has been in headlines a lot lately which makes this headline very
interesting about a new project they are working on called project q and a tweet for ubisoft wrote
introducing code name project q a team battle arena letting players truly own the experience
the game is an early development and we will keep testing so for now all you can do is register for
upcoming tests well you see they kind of were forced their hand on sharing this because a
leaker out there actually shared footage of the game uh saying that it looked a little bit like
overwatch meets fortnite uh it's kind of what it looked like there was a mode called showdown where
four teams of two go against one another to decide the winner and battle zone sees two teams of four
going against each other to see who gets 100 points first but even though folks are saying
oh it's overwatch meets fortnite ubisoft was quick to say this isn't a battle royale game
which is so it's interesting to see ubisoft saying no it's not that not that by the way this
is not a battle royale the game will feature a variety of pvp modes with one single goal in mind
fun fun is the goal
yeah i like fun too we'll see we'll see if it passes the the rob roberts and dark sakura fun
test to be determined at a later date um also and i what also kind of cracks me up about this
ubisoft also went to say there are no nfts in project q um because selling point ubisoft has
been known to promote well it also goes to show what a big company ubisoft is you have different
developers within ubisoft so i think this team is probably trying to separate itself from some
of the other things ubisoft is known for which i think is very interesting so uh again if you want
to what was that oh i said let's hope yeah if you want to uh sign up to uh check out project q you
can do that over at register.ubisoft.com slash project q dash sign up uh and uh the project is
coming out for xbox one xbox series playstation four and five and pc uh let's hope this one lasts
and uh doesn't go the way of hyperscape which was a battle royale but apparently was not fun for
enough people because uh nobody was playing it and so they shut it down or they're shutting it down
but it is uh being uh and dated uh orange right is awarding one pat on the back for no nfts um
s2100 matt says letting us know there are no nfts gets one clap fifth fifth dream says a loud one
just sort of like a bad muted one like a like a golf clap no it was like this oh the hands just
there was an attempt at clapping um fifth dream in chat says pick a pick a better letter ubi
what's wrong with q what's what's your hatred with the letter q fifth dream
q's probably an amazing character i was just gonna say q's my favorite character and bond
what's wrong with that i i was actually talking about star trek oh that too star trek too
yeah let's remember some famous cues in history
anyway all right let's move on to our next story dark sakura what do you have for us next
well nintendo is doing something ahead of schedule um you know we often hear about like games being
delayed but we rarely hear about them coming out early and it looks that uh zenoblade chronicles
3 um is actually coming out two months ahead of schedule on july 29th um but it looks like that
instead of using whatever that early finish time you know to do more play testing and a
little bit more work on it they're just bringing it out so who knows what that's gonna mean but
we it's not like we haven't had games released early before uh like the upcoming game uh well
not upcoming it's already out but the sifu that came out um it was due february 22nd it came out
on february 8th and assassins creed 4 dropped early as well so it's not like we haven't had
a few come out earlier but i still think that the date should be maintained so that
again they can make sure that they have a good product here's why i'm gonna tell you 100 why
because it relates to something bobby blackwolf said they bobby blackwolf in our chat says they
probably have another game that will come out when xc3 was originally going to come out so they
rearrange things also in the news this week splatoon 3 which hadn't been dated yet but was
generally considered to be a summer game was given a date 9 9 2022 so it's going to get the dreamcast
day of 9 9 so that's getting a september release they're calling it a summer release because
technically you know summer runs through september 21st right so it's a summer release but it's it's
september summer so um that comment from bobby i think is 100 on the nose splatoon ended up taking
this i think i think splatoon got delayed but since they never said it was going to come out
on a certain day it's not a delay but i think the fact they're rearranging the calendar i think
goes to show that splatoon was probably originally going to be the july game
and ended up getting pushed back to september which you know if it needs more time than fine
whatever i think but it's it also interesting i just think xc3 has probably been done it's
probably been done and they're they're in the final stages of it and it was completely about
release strategy going into the holiday season and all of that absolutely but um
especially when it was already out there that xc2 and three were in development side by side so
three's probably been done for a few months now and it's really just a release release strategy
thing at this point and so now they don't want to compete against themselves although splatoon and
xenoblade are very different genres you're still asking nintendo fans who are probably interested
in both to plunk down 60 and another 60 so it's best if they space them out a little bit so that
they space them out a little bit so that you you know you'll pay 60 in july and then 60 in
september um on a somewhat related note i thought it was very interesting you know uh it was there
was a tweet going around earlier today that came across my timeline and it didn't make me stop and
go that is interesting that we're talking about xenoblade chronicles 3 being a tent pole release
essentially for the switch at this point right do you remember folks think back think back about 10
a little more think back to the wii era like 2008 2009 do you remember the first xenoblade chronicles
game and how nintendo wouldn't put it out in america and yeah how it took a little operation
rainfall to finally get that game to get released uh along with some other there were some other
games involved with that as well um but that game finally got released it was a gamestop exclusive
which i still to this day say was garbage but whatever at least it was released um and you know
because many people were just pirating it at that point i may or may not be one of them but that
game was so good uh at least it finally got in front of the eyes of other people and it's just
interesting to me how far we've come because since then then we had xenoblades chronicles x
on the wii u which you know it was wii u but i think it was still very well received as a wii u
title um and then of course the remaster came out for the switch and i i believe it did pretty well
uh well enough anyway to necessitate xenoblade chronicles two and three now so this is very
interesting that like this series is causing release strategy shifts in the u.s when nintendo
didn't even want to do this game in the u.s originally so can all of the supporters of
operation rainfall please just take a moment to say we were right and doesn't that feel good
doesn't that feel good uh bobby blackwolf says the lost story was the other one i think yes
there was that there was one other pandora something was the other there was one other
uh there was because there were three and they all did get released eventually um yeah so yeah
it was uh pandora's tower thank you orange right that was the other one so um they all did of
course the other two i don't think ever did get follow-ups uh was lost story a mistwalker title
there was it was from a studio everybody wanted to play it because it was from a particular studio
um but it never ended up yeah it was mistwalker so mistwalker kind of went a different direction and
now um fantasion is the most recent thing they've done right so um yeah so uh but last story i i kind
of Asian is great just you know annoying i wish they would revisit some of these you know it's
such a fascinating studio because they keep doing these rpgs that just don't stick for whatever
reason that's not i'm not talking about fantasion i'm talking about before that blue dragon i lost
odyssey so kind of turned a little bit weird did it yeah the thing the thing is is that like
playing through the game is easy the boss battles are harder than the advertised level
hmm uh and bobby blackwolf says it was the last story not the lost story you're probably mind
melding with lost odyssey which was also a mistwalker title it happens that was ways back
anyway i'm sorry i just had to point that out as i was like here we are talking about release date
strategies around zw a chronicles 3 when nintendo didn't even want to release the first one in the
us so i just think how far we've come and kudos to the fans for speaking up you know as much as we
talk about you know angry fanboys when it comes to nintendo i think operation rainfall did did
it appropriately and look at the look at the big victory here all these years later now we just
need the xenoblade chronicles x re-release on switch because a lot of people missed it on weu
and it had great music all right anyhow when before xenogears came out that they had a mention
of it in final fantasy 7 and no one got it because of how they spelled it right it was
when cloud was in the the wheelchair and not himself and one of the things he would mumble
was xenogias which is a literal romanization of how it would be spelled in katakana i love when
games subtly reference each other i love it it's like this little inside joke that only we get
i also i also love the concept of video games being set in like the same universe
evil is in final fantasy i love the concept of like tactics and final fantasy 12 and in my brain
in my head canon and i know i know yoshi p has come out and said no but in my head canon final
fantasy 14 is an evil is game um and i i i realize there are elements about the story that definitely
differentiate it from evil is but i it's it's uh it's an evil is in a different part of the
multiverse game to me and i think i think 16 will be an evil is game too to be quite honest i just
don't think that's been confirmed yet but that's that's maybe wishful thinking on my part but it
is creative unit 3 doing it and it's those are a lot of the people that worked on those games
so i think uh i think there's a strong chance 16 is an evil is game and i hope so so all right
moving on speaking of great things from the past dark soccer well um oh am i i'm sorry am i next
oh my bad i'm sorry you see you see what happens we lose one person for the night and the entire
rotation gets screwed up well you still left him in in the show role for another segment
well you know things happen that's right you were on last week's show always a part of the
show yeah i was like you were in last week's show even though you're at disneyland so
all right let's talk about this instead let's talk about nintendo uh and the nintendo switch
online and uh there's been a leak of the nintendo switch online uh because it includes unreleased
nes games um this was apparently something that was leaked over to um because this has to do with
another thing i'm going to talk about here uh oh this doesn't have the piece on the um gameboy
advance part hold on sorry i was looking at a story that talked about the nes titles that
have been discovered in the emulator as well but it all started with a gameboy gameboy color game
boy advance switch online emulator pack uh that was originally posted to 4chan sigh but leaks
happened there uh four files popped up on there and some twitter users braved 4chan to get in
there and talk and like see what's there uh there was a uh 7z archive that had loose nca's it was a
gameboy emulator uh made by nerd it's nintendo's team that works on other classics for switch
online the gameboy advance emulator calls sloop um so now some folks are saying you know 4chan
it's got a hit and miss type of track record but the consensus right now is that this one's legit
because builds of three nintendo switch online apps they're usable and they're playable
and they're a source code that has identifying information from nintendo devs so all the signs
point to this is legit otherwise this wouldn't catch fire the way it did um so we have news
that a gameboy advance emulator is being worked on uh for the uh nintendo switch and there are
games like pokemon pinball that show up in the list uh which i think are things that i would
love to play all over again i checked something trying to follow back a link on one of those
tweets and the account is dead the account's gone oh really yeah the one who was talking about the
analog support and the helco emulator i wonder if there was an nda so because i wonder if nintendo
maybe tried to shut it down or something who knows so that account is gone i wonder if this
other one is anyway the other one is still there that's very interesting some sometimes people
don't like the attention either and they might have changed their name to break all the links
or something i don't know so anyway um but this doesn't mean that it's coming tomorrow it doesn't
mean it's coming in june even it does it just means nintendo's working on it um but that could
be working out in the way future i thought it showed interesting things about um uh like how
they use save states to really practice some things in emulators and they actually had save
states that talked about like you know there's a certain texture used in this part of the game
and that they'll use those to test certain part of the emulators and that kind of made me click
and go aha that's where those sp releases are coming from you know how on the nso they
apparently like you know every other month or so they'll release like a kid Icarus sp edition
and all it is is basically a safe state that takes you directly to the last level in the game
so you can see how the very last level in kid Icarus is nothing like the rest of the game
it's it's very unique i i feel like those safe states some of them are just becoming the sp
edition of the game um or uh the other one that comes to mind it was one of the first ones they
ever did it was the legend of zelda um i don't remember what they called it but it was the money
filled edition it already had like every item 255 rupees it had like everything already unlocked and
i was like that was just a safe state for nintendo to test things in that game that's what that was
then they ended up releasing it as like a bonus game that's clever anyway the leak didn't just
leak that this gameboy advance uh emulators being worked on is that there was also unreleased nes
games including pac-man tetris galaga mega man castlevania lots of games that make you go wow
this really is missing it's also interesting to note the build date for the application october
2019 so they've been on this for a minute uh-huh now of course just because now see here's where
my brain goes i don't think just because the games were in the emulator they were ever being planned
on coming out because that's a licensing thing especially because this has all these mega man
games in there well hello capcom released a mega man's collection for the switch already they don't
want to just give these games to nintendo for free unless i mean maybe they'll they'll get a
money sharing thing later on but they're probably holding out but my guess is nintendo was probably
internally testing these to test the emulator to make sure that it was still good in case either
these games were ever just gonna you know they get the deal inked out these games come out someday
or um and i think this is the case with xbox or emulation in general and i know we have an
emulation expert in our discord server and i may or may not get corrected but just following this
over the years when you get a certain thing in emulation to work it usually causes other similar
games to work for example in the nintendo universe you hear a lot about mappers right you get one
mapper carpetridge type to work it usually means others that also run on that mapper will also work
i say xbox because i think back to that story when remember when like barbie dream adventures
ended up becoming a backwards compatible xbox 360 title everybody was like why did microsoft waste
their fucking time making that barbie game backwards compatible and i've been saying since
the beginning they didn't it's just another game that we don't know of that they did want to get
backwards compatible ran on a very similar type of coding structure engine something that the barbie
game did and so you know look at look at other games of that developer or that publisher did
and whatever microsoft did to get that game running also made barbie work and so i think
and that's my long-winded way of saying these mega man games showing up in this emulator build
may not really be about mega man it's probably more about the emulator because i i again i don't
see what capcom has to gain when they're selling these games independently for their own money
to just say okay nsl go ahead and release them on your service until they're sure that they're not
going to make any more money off that game and nintendo opens up their wallet enough so what do
you want to bet if these mega man games do show up it's going to be on the plus service expansion
pack whatever the fuck they call it because they need that extra money so that they can funnel some
of it over to capcom tetris i'm sure is a legal issue at this point um can they re-release the
old tetris i'm sure it's complicated granted they have tetris 99 but tetris 99 and the original
tetris on india they are different games and legally have to be treated differently
castlevania and simon's quest same logic why would konami just suddenly open those
up on nintendo switch online when they're trying to sell you the castlevania collection
so i i think some blogs and some people on twitter are reading too much into this and i
think maybe need to take a step back and go oh this is just more about testing the emulator or
maybe these games are ready to come out as soon as the deal gets inked legally but i don't know
if it will ever get inked legally pac-man um i hate to sound like a broken record but like
literally in the next two weeks there's a pac-man museum game coming out why does why does namco
want to put pac-man out on nso why they're trying to sell pac-man museum now i do look
at other games in here like kung fu the original kung fu on the nes which was an arcade game as
well i'm not sure why that game can't be released unless like was there an actual tie-in to
something that i'm just missing in the moment with that game legally but yeah that's interesting
i actually love that game by the way they must have some reasons yeah so i mean they
there's they don't have to tell us what the reasons are that's just the thing they don't
have to tell us but it's interesting the more people speculate on it that just generates more
publicity for them oh sure sure uh now this is interesting over in chat ah thank thank you
orange right kung fu was based on an iram arcade game kung fu master ding ding that's it that's
why it's legally still tied up i remember the arcade game being awesome and then they they
ported it pretty well to the nes so thank you everybody uh and dgrms says iram is too busy
milking r-type to deal with kung fu well yeah how many r-type finals have we um s2100 matt says i
remember when folks hacked the playstation classic and folks saw that they had tested a ton of other
games on it including anime fighting games the whole list of games they used to test on it would
have made that thing better than a dust collector for sure uh fifth dream in chat says maybe that
contract worker at nintendo from earlier leaked the emulators i don't think the contractor would
have access to those files but it's it's cute fanfic but probably not rooted in reality i'm
sorry to say yeah all right uh let's go on to our next story now we can go to dark sakura's story
so um well activision blizzard is doing something right um i mean then again they're kind of having
to do it they have to yeah yeah um so they are adding two uh women senior executives to the
board um they are announcing that uh lulu cheng miss messervay i guess that's how it's pronounced
is uh joining immediately and then they're nominating carrie kar for election in their
annual meeting in june um which so far they've actually uh activision blizzard has been in
violation of law that requires uh publicly traded companies with six or more people on the board
to have at least three women directors um and then half of activision's 10 person board has been
together for nearly uh two decades um eight men and two women currently sit on the board
um two however uh hendrick hart hartung the third and casey washerman have chosen not to go for
re-election so um so uh messervay is uh the vp of communication at substack and car is uh svp with
bacardi and an alum of the walt disney company so interesting there you go well the representation
is important it's interesting that there's you know the law and all that as well with the board
that's that's pretty neat um so it's good but um also i hope i hope these folks have been vetted
um because that's still important as well because the next story we have is about an executive who
is a woman who um maybe i don't allegedly not so great i don't know i've heard a lot of things
about this woman uh and she's on facebooks i actually have one more little thing to add on
please please if you don't mind yeah of course the soc investment group is actually urging investors
to vote against uh the activision blizzard acquisition the merger so um they own a small
percentage of activision stock um and they are calling for them to elect a new competent and
dedicated board of directors that's my quote um before it's going to go through and so i think
that this might be part of that this was announced uh last week i have heard of them going that in
there yeah no that's perfect i've heard of a lot of pushback to bobby kotex payout too you know
a lot of senators were voicing their opinions on that as well as that uh the deal shouldn't go
through because of bobby kotex payout his ass needs to be kicked to the curb paid out in rotten
prunes he needs to be paid out in a pink slip in a cardboard box like his contractors have he
should be given a bunch of prunes and be forced to eat it before he leaves well wait until you
hear what i have next dark sakura because it involves the tale of bobby kotek and the coo
or chief operating officer of facebook excuse me meta cheryl sandberg that's who i was referencing
a moment ago meta is under an investigation if cheryl sandberg broke company rules by um act by
uh basically trying to do a favor for activision ceo bobby kotek who she was dating at the time
oh how the world fuck i mean i just these bobby kotex stories anyone want to date him other than
maybe having him be a sugar daddy but she would have she would have enough money yeah like she's
i'm exhausted even just after the first sentence of this article but let me continue
according to a report in the wall street journal who keeps breaking these stories that going on
in the game industry so snaps and actual claps to the wall street journal and journalists who
are getting getting it fucking done uh when it comes to holding these companies accountable
uh according to this report so i have to say allegedly bold underlying italicize but according
to the report cheryl sandberg used company resources to kill negative reporting about
kotek so due to this meta is conducting a review and whether she violated the company's rules
the british tabloid mail online was pursuing is that the daily fail it must be it must be
the daily fails online the daily actually yeah the daily mail um yeah everybody calls it the
daily fail they're listed by by that name so the daily fail was working on a story
uh based on allegations from a former girlfriend of bobby kotex and a temporary restraining order
that she got against him but cheryl sandberg and kotek worked together in 2016 and 2019 according
to this report to strategize on how to persuade the daily mail to not report on the restraining
order facebook and activision staff were both directly involved with this and the concern at
facebook was that the story would quote reflect negatively on her reputation as an advocate for
women because remember she's dating him at the time wall street she's really an advocate for
women she wouldn't have been dating the shit yes i don't know what else to say uh the wall
street journal also openly questions if sandberg inappropriately used her influence as facebook
coo in dealing with mail online's management an unnamed source told that or said that kotek
quote told people that miss sandberg threatened the mail in 2016 by saying that such an article
published could damage the news organization's business relationship with facebook
why is the daily mail called the daily fail because of all their fucking clickbait headlines
and clickbait articles that they write on a regular basis who is the number one peddler
of those headlines but they do have a big readership oh sure people and people believe
stupid tabloids people especially if there's a grain of truth in it are you telling me dark
sakura here on this day on episode 911 of orange luxury are you telling me
that stupid people click stupid links are you telling me
my point is that if they have a concern about this affecting public opinion of the piece of shit
and her association with the piece of shit then it's a valid concern i mean they're both pieces
of shit but now more people will know how much shitty they are uh pele hanumea and chat says
bat boy marries princess diana that's the daily mail no that was weekly world news i'm almost
positive daily mail will post like legit stuff every so often what does it what does it say
what does it say about my sad brain that i knew which tabloid it was and to correct this
well-intentioned listener on their comment i have i will be taking no i have no further comment at
this time let's go back to uh uh this saga going on over here it should be pointed out the mail
online never published its story on kotak uh a meta spokesperson denied that sandberg threatened
uh mail online saying cheryl sandberg never threatened the mail online's business relationship
with facebook in order to influence an editorial decision this story attempts to make connections
that don't exist uh bobby kotak said to the journal he never said anything like that
activisions board of directors said it did a thorough investigation into an incident in 2014
and that they have full confidence in mr kotak's leadership holy shit is that a lot to unpack
right there because um i mean how many times has the activision board of directors come to say
we have confidence in bobby kotak we have confidence in what's going on here when
when honestly truly there is no reason to have that type of trust in bobby kotak
they did a thorough investigation in 2014 what can you detail for me activision what that
investigation was because it sounds like that investigation was throwing it a deep doc drawer
locking it and throwing away the key
if you would care to hear another quote boy do i have one for you the board has been aware of the
circumstances reporting involving an incident in 2014 around the time of the incident in 2014
mr kotak notified the senior independent director of the board has subsequently updated the full
board and has been fully transparent with the board the board through its council scadden arps
has done a thorough and what a name i'm probably mispronouncing it but do i really care at this
point has done a thorough examination of the facts and circumstances of the event satisfied
itself that there was no merit to the allegations and notes that they concern a personal relationship
that has nothing to do with the business of the company the board continues to have full confidence
in mr kotak's leadership and his ability to run the company i'm exhausted
anyway uh before we get to our next story i see the raid there from bromigos so i want to say
thank you thank you for that usually uh we're recording a podcast and so we sometimes are
really bad about doing the twitch things of acknowledging all the things when they happen
because our podcast listeners can't see that or any of that but i do want to say thank you thank
you for that it is appreciated and hope you guys are having a wonderful night um hi and welcome to
orange launch radio we've been doing this far too long uh if i had justice the scrolls on the bottom
our first episode was back in 2002 so i want to thank you all for being here for um our episode
tonight uh dark sakura and myself here loki with the night off as he had just had surgery earlier
this week and is recovering uh let's get into some more stories uh especially after that last story
about really it's it's honestly it's rich executives scratching each other on the back
literally and figuratively in this particular case and it just it's just exhausting to hear about
and why mr kotak is still employed in this industry i will never understand never understand
i i hope that once he's out the door that that's the last we hear of him
i hope that door gives him a swallow a solid thwack in the buttocks on his way out
all right let's i need happy news dark sakura make me happy make me happy only you can make
yourself happy rob is it the same anyway um sega is doing something cool they are uh doing reboots
of crazy taxi and just their radio and it's going to be big budget stuff too they are uh
the projects are part of something called super game initiative it's a plan that sega sammy has
had since last year so they wanted uh the the quote is um they want to develop all new and
innovative titles with a focus on global reach online interactivity community building and ip
utilization um and that's where the working with microsoft for the azure cloud platform comes in
so they want to uh use some of its dormant ip's for remakes remasters and reboots and by name
they said crazy taxi and jet set radio as candidates um other games on the list of space
channel 5 res panzer dragoon knight shinobi um virtue fighter and altered beast yes to literally
everything on this list literally everything crazy taxi and jet set radio were up on the top of the
list according to bloomberg um they have um done remasters remakes things for other dreamcast era
properties um crazy taxi and jet set radio were on the sega 2011 dreamcast collection
there were more i actually have crazy taxi for ipad which is actually not bad um uh there's also
uh crazy taxi ty tycoon which was originally called uh crazy taxi gazillionaire which is a
business management sim slash idol game um they've outsourced a lot of their ip revivals though
including streets of rage 4 panzer dragoon remake alex kid miracle world dx and house of the dead
remake to indie developers so we'll see what happens but right now sega is kind of riding
high on the the sonic revenue and um they're also looking into adapting uh yakuza and streets of
rage so we'll see how that goes i want a streets of rage music uh the movie if the soundtrack is
done by yuzo koshido well you may be in luck uh elsewhere in the industry this week apparently
this i i swear i read this somewhere the sonic director is interested in streets of rage
so but i knew about that yeah so but because i i actually brought that up two weeks ago oh okay uh
yuzo koshiro said somewhere that he wanted to be involved that doesn't mean his phone's ringing yet
yeah i hadn't seen anything about about that but i mean could you imagine if he did
like modern mixes of the original music that would be rad um in our chat they're talking
about like crazy taxi and these remixes um dark tetsuya says i saw someone on twitter
suggests a battle royale style take on crazy taxi and it sounds ridiculous enough to be fun
i actually think that would be awesome um like not necessarily 100 people but just even like that
sense of like 10 people all playing on the same map at the same time trying to pick up the same
people and get to the same spots i think that actually would be really funny that sounds really
funny it's only fun to me really i think it'd be fun i don't like i i i wouldn't like that i
like to get in and play it solo and be done it's it's always a solo game well it's not always be
as an option maybe i don't even i know but i when they when they put options in games like that
they have some sort of reward that forces you to play it and no um i also think um
crazy taxi is not crazy taxi uh unless it has that offspring song in it because only sometimes
they've been able to to get that you know yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah like it's it's just not for
me it was more about the the um bad religion music i whenever 10 in 2010 came on that was my song
uh tiger cloud points out that whole soundtrack yeah sorry tiger points out it wasn't the sonic
director for streets of rage it was the writer for john wick my bad um the other one i wanted
to point out they were talking about panzer dragoon so quest buster says um as mike deaf
pointed out panzer dragoon had a remake unless they're talking about rebooting a new chapter
or the series which i'd love to see yeah i think that remake kind of had a soft land um it
definitely needed a patch to get to the place where it needed to be so i'm wondering if it
isn't maybe a new game or the reality is it's on the list but it's not at the top of the list
and you know at the top of the list they've already done that that third party remake yeah
as i mentioned so i i i would doubt very seriously i mean what i would actually like them to do
is if they did remake anything is if they did a remake of a panzer dragoon rpg or what was it
here panzer dragoon saga i think i i've got a copy somewhere all right um but that would be
nice because that game is is pretty amazing all right well let's talk about about what's excuse
me i have the hiccups you guys the worst thing that can happen to me when trying to do a show
um let's move on and talk about uh something that sega is doing which is sonic origins and we got
some new information on that this week so sonic origins uh is going to be coming to the the switch
but i believe it's coming to other platforms as well i just happen to be looking at a story on a
nintendo-based website um but it's a remastered collection of the original sonic the hedgehog
titles um so sonic did announce that the release date is june 23rd hey just in time for my birthday
and by the way it is the switch it's ps5 for xbox series and xbox one so it's you know most
of the normal areas you'd expect um sega's announced it's coming out on june 23rd and it's
going to be available in these different editions it's based basically standard digital deluxe and
three different dlcs with it which is uh yeah that's a lot it is a lot there's a start dash
pack uh with 100 bonus coins mirror mode already unlocked in a letterbox background there's a
premium fun pack with hard missions letterbox animations in the main menu and camera controls
in the main menu islands there is a classic music track with additional music tracks from
the mega drive and genesis titles so i i don't know if all this is really necessary um but okay
go off and honestly i'm gonna be honest when i first saw this trailer i was like
what these games have been released so many times they re-released rather so many times
you know we've had sonic one two and three and knuckles every more like since the playstation
3 xbox 360 there's been a sega collection that has had it in it i could swear sonic 3 has been in that
too but maybe maybe not the current like genesis emulation or whatever all right they're saying in
chat that sonic 3 has not been released in a long time i'll believe them that's fine but even then
it's you know just sonic 3 i guess sonic 1 and 2 of you'll come out a million times um some people
people also say it's because of the michael jackson involvement with the sonic 3 that that
one's kind of the the harder one to get re-done for whatever reason but it's not just and to be
fair it's not just that the games are re-releasing it's that they are done in the higher resolution
so it's you know crisp pixels i guess there is new opening and ending animations for each title
there are unlockables to get new content and special stages and then there's classic and
anniversary mode which basically the anniversary mode is a full screen so it uses wide screen
play the old games but in widescreen which is kind of interesting uh and as chat is pointing
out basically they're doing these games in the sonic mania engine which is interesting but i'm
not sure that dlc is a smart thing to do with this especially right out the gate to announce that all
this is there they probably should have released it and then trickled out the dlc probably would
have been a smarter way to do it but they really want to lock in those pre-orders that's for sure
so but i don't know i think i think they're asking a little much for it considering how many times
i've played played sonic the hedgehog in recent years but i do think that the widescreen mode
it's interesting but is it 30 interesting i don't know so all right well let's travel back and
revisit a classic game in our next segment and dark sakura what did you pick for the classic
game tonight i picked tetranet yeah we've talked about it many many a time a lot of us have
memories of it well i'm bringing it up now tetranet um and tetranet i apologize i need
to step away for just one minute to deal with the hiccups i'll be back sorry all right tetranet is
an online multiplayer version of tetris that supports up to six people and has team play so
it first came out in 1997 it had releases for microsoft windows unix mac os 10 and bayos
um it was developed by stormcat and the o is a zero because it was um the last official version
is version 1.13 and it was originally developed for windows and later ported to the other systems
stormcat also released tetranet 2 in 2000 that has improved graphics uh different types of special
blocks more types and additional features like a hold piece and block shadows and a master server
so um as far as um the game it basically is a standard multiplayer tetris with a twist
if you clear a row it will cause special blocks to appear in your field if a line containing a
special block is cleared then that block is added to your inventory clearing those lines at once
multiple lines at once increases the number of special blocks that you get so at any point you
can use a special block um at the at the start of your inventory on one of the six fields which is
one of your uh either your own or other people's uh or your opponents excuse me so it depends on
which type of block you're going to use so a is add a line where it adds a broken line
c is clear line which clears the line on the bottom of the field uh b is clear special blocks
which causes all special blocks to return to normal blocks r is random blocks clear so random
blocks are removed from the target field so that gives you gaps in your lines um o is a bomb block
which uh causes uh block bombs to explode and scatters uh other blocks throughout your play
field q is block quake which causes blocks on each line to shift and sort of like an earthquake
effect uh g is block gravity where the blocks on the field just immediately fall into whatever
gap happens to be there and deletes the completed line um s is to switch fields so you actually
switch your play field with somebody else and n is nuke field which removes all blocks from the
target field the last player to still be able to place pieces in their field is the winner
um and depending on the server use there are alternate rules sometimes there is pure
where special blocks are disabled so it's just everyone is playing multiplayer tetris
and then seven tetris where the first player to make seven seven tetrises is the winner so
there are those modes um the music in this one um it it's it's called the dance of the spheres
it's been everywhere like they made a step mania chart for this um what i don't remember that
that's awesome yeah um it's the authorship is claimed by someone named uh david is it might be
although there are other sources that say davy m carlson is the composer um
back in the day we thought this was hot shit today i can't stand listening to it i mean i i was like
okay jamming for a little bit a little bit nostalgia then after i was like okay i'm done
um so there are also um different variables you can add to the tetranet uh 1.13 client
different variables um one is called tetra tetra fast which removes the one second delay between
the pieces that you find and the standard tetranet gameplay um after uh when the police
sorry police piece delay is implemented on the client side it's just a modification that keeps
clients from from having it happen to the you know you basically there's you only connect
to people playing tetra fast um there's also uh one called tetranet slash tetra fast 1.14 with
the 1.14 protocol is a variant where everyone receives the same sequence of pieces there's
block tris um that's for the windows client um where it also supports the tetranet and tetra
fast protocols but it also has additional special block types one is for left gravity which pulls
the blocks to the left as far as possible piece change that changes your current piece and zebra
field which clears every second column on the field um then for tetranet 2 um it's another
multiplayer tetris done by the original creator um the five new blocks it adds is immunity where
the target cannot be affected by any special uh for 15 seconds clear column that deletes a column
from the field mutate pieces that causes um the target's next pieces a default of three to become
large and awkwardly shaped darkness where you can't see anything on the field beside your
current piece and its immediate surroundings for 10 seconds confusion that causes your controls to
get mixed up for 10 seconds um and then of course there were other other clone you know the other
uh tetranet 2 got closed down by the tetris company just like other ones did um the website
and servers were unavailable for several years as of early 2010 tetranet 2 is back up and running
uh and that's uh i kind of want to play yeah um the tetranet 2 website and servers have been
recovered relocated and restored um this the with all of the you know various versions it was really
well received especially by the linux community the uh linux conference uh linux.com.au um even
had a programming contest where they tried to uh program tetranet playing bots that would connect
to the server and play the game and the prize for best spot was forty thousand australian
uh was sorry a forty thousand australian dollar ibm p-series server and there's also land parties
um game revolution said tetranet was an affordable alternative to tetris and then in a review in 1999
of the next tetris game revolution said that tetranet was truer to the tetris roots and if
you want multiplayer a multiplayer tetris the network-based tetranet is more fun
i'm wondering if the existence of tetranet is what led to tetris 99
oh i'm i'm sure it's in part inspired by it for sure absolutely yeah you know when they were
trying to think of like how do we do tetris as a battle royale somebody probably thought of
tetranet you know and and you know how could we model it after that in some capacity oh for sure
for sure really care by the way for the way that tetranet 2.0 looks yeah i like the way the first
one looks better yeah but i like the overlaying grid over the pieces so for people who have like
some issues with uh the perception of space and i'm not saying next necessarily depth perception
but just more like spatial awareness having the the segments to the blocks make it easier
and more accessible well we didn't uh in chat they're talking about a vog tetris night and
def says uh tetris 99 has private lobbies you know uh a tetranet or a tetris 99 i think i'd actually
like super be down for that i think that would be a lot of fun uh i think we should invite kevin ddr
uh from who used to listen to olr years ago to just come and slaughter us all
so if you don't know he's he's uh was quite memorable in the tetra scene for a while so
i don't know if he still plays regularly but yeah that would be very funny all right all right well
there it is uh i think that's all you have to say right that's your classic game of the week
tetranet that'll do it that'll do it but that's that's such a good pick i love i love tetranet
and you're right it's come up on the show i don't know how many times before so uh it only makes
sense we spotlight it as a classic game of the week eventually around these parts right so all
right um anyhow let's wonder why okay my discord was taking forever to kick back in jamie was a
gray square for a minute there all right that's right um a lot a lot of ellos i have more stuff
to do in a row so i'll get right into it are we really okay oh yeah it's rapid fire news hey
when loki's not about to eat myself some rose jelly bellies okay when loki's not here we all
got to pick up the slack but these are rapid fire news so you can talk about them rapidly well i'll
let you chew that jelly bean and just mention in chat lol lol and dark tissue says idk how badly
do you want to lose um excellent question i'll probably lose anyway i'm not that good at tetris
um you know another tetris game that isn't played online enough is tetris effect it had a pretty
neat multiplayer mode in it i don't know how many of you actually have it we should do a
tetris effect night one night that would be fun i think so all right um i still like giant tetris
which one the giant oh isn't that a sega machine the arcade i think it is yeah that's fun all
right uh let's get anyway rapid fire news star sakura so um i'm sure we've we've covered this
before the tmnt uh shredder's revenge this retro style beat him up that you can play as the four
turtles or as april or s splinter well as long as as long as tiger claws here we'll always get
the latest teenage mutant ninja turtles news well uh the game is actually going to feature
the 1987 tv series voice actors you know cam clark and all of them are revising their roles
that's legit pretty rad it is pretty rad and uh it doesn't have a release date yet um
it has a window dot emu the the publisher working with tribute games
confirms this summer for switch so it's gonna be pretty cool i've watched the trailer i'm pretty
down for it also um press release time uh battle toes versus double dragon i'm sure we remember
that back in the day on on the uh the nintendo entertainment system um it's actually going to
have a physical uh reprint of it there's a pre-order window from april 19th which is my
birthday through may 22nd um at 59.99 or uh 64.99 euro um put out by retro bit publishing
and then they are planning on releasing the 16-bit version later this year that's awesome and that
also i i real quick before we get into our next segment some of you were talking about
that on our discord server this week and i always want to promote our discord server
vog network.com that's vognetwork.com discord we'll get you an invite to the server and many
of you post stories there throughout the week and sometimes we pull from that uh for stories
that we're going to talk about on the show and i'm i'm always happy somebody sometimes people
ask me my opinion on things throughout the week i'm if i'm surprised people care but i'm surprised
or i'm always uh happy to drop my opinion on whatever you just tagged me over on our discord
server so um dart to see us says i never got around to that one officially i'm assuming that's
the battle toads and double dragon game but playing a bit of the rom it seemed kind of fun
yeah all right uh we are now going always annoyed the shit out of me so i'm not buying it
all right we are going to travel around the world and check out some release dates um
loki is not here tonight so i will take up the us release dates and talk about uh what is coming
out in the us so let's see today is the 24th so this week on the 26 demon gaze extra for windows
zombie army 4 dead war is coming out on the nintendo switch and then we've talked about
this on the show prior the stanley parable the ultra deluxe edition is out pretty much
everywhere uh vampire the masquerade blood hunt i know we've seen some previews of that uh that
is out on windows and playstation 5 so if that's up your alley you have that and then on the 28th
bug snacks uh makes its debut on the xbox platforms as well as windows and nintendo
switch so bug snacks is no longer a playstation exclusive as of the 28th for you cricket fans
out there cricket 22 is coming out on the nintendo switch but i'm just i'm just gonna guess
i don't it's listed in my american release dates although i can't imagine it's actually coming out
in america but that's that's awesome if it does there's a somewhat cricket falling in the us
that's true there's there's people who play rugby here too i know some gay rugby players
they love it rugby is is preferable i think uh then we have rogue legacy 2 i think that game's
been in early access for a little bit but it's coming out of early access for windows xbox uh
won an xbox series uh that is all on the 28th uh tasomachi behind the twilight for nintendo switch
and playstation 4 and uh quite a big release this week on april the 29th so uh just before we get to
our next show nintendo switch sports that is we sports but nintendo switch sports um and that's
uh one that we've had on our our ion for a little bit ever since nintendo kind of surprised announced
this but should it be a surprise should it because this is a we sports was a huge selling game
nintendo switch sports will have tennis bowling and sword play or chambara is what it's called
in the game and three new sports soccer volleyball and badminton so uh you can uh hit around the
shuttlecock in the privacy of your own home on nintendo switch sports i want to fence people as
you play badminton so enjoy playing with your shuttlecock that is what and if you didn't know
that is what they call the little thing in bat badminton it's the shuttlecock all right i think
all of us learned that in high school playing badminton all right moving on to japan and
checking out the japanese release dates looking on the nintendo switch uh pretty similar story uh we
have um ike men sengoku toki o kakaru koi aratanaru day uh comes out in regular and limited edition
from idea factory uh and that is uh where you are a fashion designer who goes back in time to
an alternate version of sengoku era japan you have accidentally changed history and earned the favor
of nobunaga oda by saving him from death so you must survive three months surrounded by famous
and handsome sengoku warlords before your next chance to make it back home
this game sounds too ridiculous to be true but it's true but it's but it's it's notable because
it's you're it's like a men dating simulator you're dating uh sengoku so um that's kind of fun
all right let's see what else uh food girls 2 civil war
what the fuck is up with the releases this week
um a popularity voting bet based on your dignity win or leave the street market
the second major game in the cuisine personification simulation series
what i'm sorry can we unpack that statement for a minute the cuisine personification simulation
series please look forward to it we do have i am toast um he shows sami sami sami is out in japan
this week as well uh tasumachi behind the twilight is also out and oshi no love yori koi no love plus
love or die so a dual pack also out in japan this week and if you've wanted a min min amiibo that is
released in japan this week as well um you can also look forward to nintendo switch sports also
releasing in japan this week on the playstation 5 this week uh moto gp22 is released on the 28th
there you go let's go over to the uk dark sakura so in the uk uh god this thing is asking me
questions now um in the uk we only have four uh on the 26th for switch we have zombie army uh
zombie army for dead war um on the 28th we have cricket 22 the official games of the ashes
also for switch actually everything on this list is for switch um uh nintendo switch sports on the
29th and also in the 29th metal tails overkill all right that that would do it uh we will soon
get to the listener round table your emails your calls and all that good stuff if you want to join
us in our discord for a call vog network.com discord by the way i i have a special need tonight
i'm hoping somebody will call in because i'm gonna need help wrapping up the show tonight
because dark sakura as you know she tends to go out the door before the credits roll because
she's trying to set up for her own little thing uh going on after the show the after party
that's going to leave me here all by my lonesome self so what you're what was you saying i was
singing that song all by myself by myself yeah so that will leave me all by myself if nobody
calls in tonight but if we get a phone call tonight i can let that person close down the
show with me tonight so that'll be fun all right um but first intern yeah an intern tonight so
let's uh we do have some stories to get to before we get to the listener round table so let's get to
this uh first story from dark sakura so um uh wisconsin video game workers uh at raven software
um as we know they are the arm of activision blizzard that works on call of duty
um they and i believe that we've talked about raven before in this uh in this whole uh concept
here but they have a unionization campaign by 21 of their employees in middleton wisconsin
um as just trying to shake more of this up going on i mean they're working you know to really put
it in there um but at this point um their regional uh nlrb director in minneapolis rejected
um activision's push to have the election encompass a wider category of raven workers
that would dilute the unionizing vote so um at this point um it looks like that the union
the unionizing may be good to go
so you know we we hypothesize this would probably start at activision and this would be one of the
first to uh break the dam so to speak on the unionization in the game industry efforts and
that might be uh coming to i mean we it's not the first time we've heard of the uni because we've
had stories on the show weeks before there's been other smaller developers but for this to happen
within activision would be something another thing too earlier this month um activision
blizzard also announced that they would be converting nearly 1100 part-time quality
assurance jobs to full-time jobs and raising hourly wages to at least 20 bucks so there's that
all right and uh if you've gotten if you're getting a raise at your job and you want to
waste your money on something uh boy do i have the prospect for you and that is more legos because
an official lego atari 2600 is supposed to be launching this august um this is by promo bricks
who kind of leaked this i guess um because uh this you know these things tend to leak out in catalogs
and um you know uh industry ordering and things like that um so an official lego version of the
2600 console uh will be coming back coming out in august as part of the 50th anniversary for
atari as a company uh the set will have a lego rendition of the console itself and also the
joystick and a cartridge of pitfall which is interesting because that's not an atari game that
was an activision game but that will be the game that will be made from plastic bricks of course
very very similar to the nes system that's out there that you can make a little mario on the tv
that runs it's super cute i don't have one because i was able to hold on to my money but i've seen it
i think bobby blackwolf had one at his house and i was looking at it it's cute um and uh yeah it's
a cute little system so uh that'll uh if the atari 2600 one has the tv and everything too that would
be pretty cool so uh promo bricks is saying that the atari 2600 will be 200 i'm sorry 199.99 but
let's just say 200 uh when it is a timed exclusive on lego's website this august and a general retail
release in january of 2023 dark to see it says well i guess it would be either that et or pac-man
uh i think atari wants to forget those two
so it's probably yeah combat would have probably been the game for that oh hey loki's in chat
shouldn't you be lucky shouldn't you be resting loki all right i knew he wouldn't be able to stay
away all night but i was actually gonna say tune in next week to find out when loki plans to get
his because i'm sure he's gonna get uh his own version of that but um i would also expect so so
i also saw in chat uh they're saying that seems kind of cheap it says nothing about the operational
tv with the game on it we know there's a pitfall cartridge that doesn't mean there's a pitfall game
on the tv so i would imagine that piece of it probably actually isn't there um unless they you
know unless again we're hearing this uh from a second-hand source i imagine when uh atari or
excuse me lego and atari decide to officially unveil it we'll find out for sure but i wouldn't
count on the tv being a part of it so all right that is it believe it or not for the stories that
we had on deck for tonight so we're going to get into the listener round table we'll take your
questions uh over at twitch.tv slash vog network but also we welcome your emails every week
participate at orange lounge radio.com and as i mentioned earlier we will take your calls on the
discord vognetwork.com slash discord i believe we have one email tonight so i will turn it
over emails oh same person snap or i may have not thrown out last week's email check the date
um you know i'm notoriously bad at that yeah yeah sorry last week that was last week's you know i
rely on a clean inbox you are more than welcome to log in before sunday night to take a take a peek
all right let's get to tonight's email hello lr i was not expecting the reaction that i got
to my email last week ha as always thank you for your support of my games and i'm including
the listeners in that as well rob mentioned that unlike with xbox live indie games falling plus is
displayed on the proper xbox store unfortunately this isn't 100 true because although you can
search for it and find it easily you cannot browse the store for it games included in the
creators collection as it is called cannot be browsed you may recall that the store got a
complete visual overhaul back in 2020 this collection had a browsable section on the store
before that but now that is gone several folks have opened tickets or made complaints about this
but unfortunately microsoft is not acknowledging or responding to these oh well i will also mention
that falling plus is unfortunately not a play anywhere title meaning you cannot also play it
on windows but if um if you buy it on xbox to anyone who would have utilized this i apologize
but it's already available on steam and my audience is small enough that i didn't want
to split it across the two different pc versions but if you post a score to leaderboards on xbox
email me at yyr at yyrgames.com with your xbox gamer tag and they'll send you a free steam key
that's good guy yyr he doesn't have to do that at all but that's just good guy yyr
i'll end with a quick correction forza horizon 4 is actually still available on xbox game pass
so if you just discovered forza horizon with the fifth game but would like to try the same game on
a different map then give it a try while you can i happen to really like the version of the uk that
they created thanks again for the show and have a great week looking forward to seeing peppy the
penguin again erin yyr all right i'm i'm so glad uh you're happy with the reaction because i was
happy to see it and that's a bummer that there isn't like a store like a way to like look it
up in the store by hand you know a store page kind of like you were explaining there i just assumed
because i could search for it and it had like you you were in the template in the store like you had
screenshots you had all that other stuff i just kind of assumed oh okay it's in the store because
here it all is but you have to search for it that's interesting um ssj100 matt also notes uh
you can link directly to it because he just dropped the link in our chat room so you can
actually just tap the link and buy it there that way if you want um it's it's too long of a link
for me to read on air so i can't really do it that way um but i can just say search for falling plus
or you can probably search for yyr uh and you'll find it that way too but if for whatever reason
that doesn't work dude just do falling plus and you'll find the game i did play it earlier this
week but i i didn't i was playing for so long i got to a point i had to leave i had to leave and
i couldn't finish the game and upload my high score i should have just purposely died a bunch
of times to get my high score up there but i'll do that i'll do that later this week maybe i'll do
a stream who knows but kudos again yyr for the release of falling plus and um my bad on forest
horizon four i guess it was three they must have delisted not that long ago i'm just getting lost
amongst all those numbers can you blame me i'm not sure all right thank you dark soccer for that
email reading uh participate at orange launch radio.com if you would like to send an email for
a future week in the meantime let's welcome a special guest onto the show because i see
someone in our green room so hello you are you are on orange launch radio who's this
hey what's going on everyone it is ron well long time no talk i know right you know i had no i
wasn't planning on calling in until that first article popped up i'm like yeah which article
oh about about about the person working at nintendo that's oh basically mad they didn't
get flipped to full-time employment what's your thoughts on that well i've been in it
basically 20 something oh yeah it and contractors oh yes yes and the bulk of that has basically has
been me as a contractor and the main reason you want to go fte is for the benefits and the
discounts and all that cool stuff that's the main reason why but sometimes you'll have to
be there anywhere from like three days to five years until a position opens up that you can get
in there or if the budget is big enough where oh they could add another spot for you and that's
it and contracting specifically is a very interesting world because you get a lot of
temporary people that are brought in for transition work like we're moving from one
cloud to another so we're going to hire contractors that are experts in this to help us with this
transition and then we're going to let them go because they're only they're literally contractors
they're here for this length of time it does a lot of stuff like that that i i would say is
nefarious but it's oh it stinks and i'm sure i'm sure nefarious shit happens don't don't get me
wrong yeah it basically depends on the company now i i will put this out there you know i
was a contractor with nbc universal for about a year until covid happened now we had two separate
it departments they merged them so the next open spot went to somebody in the other department
because he had seniority over me and the main reason why i was putting my head down doing what
i had to do is because i wanted those discounted tickets to universal studios and for the record
i was going to universal studios japan so that was that was my main goal you got to see you
got to see super mario world i don't blame you at all yeah that well yeah that and the sailor moon
4d uh experience oh shit that's a thing oh my god i want to see i want to take alan alan loves
yeah yeah i i will find you information and i'll send it to you do you know how many bootleg vhs
sailor moon tapes alan has in his closet i know i had over 150 bootleg vhs tapes until i had to
toss them when i moved believe you me and when i switched to digital a couple terabytes of fan
subs which i slowly deleted as i went to purchase legal titles and stuff like that but i've worked
for a company called fresh direct where i was a contractor there and i ended up long term because
i knew how to run help desk and do technical support besides loading windows or mac onto
a computer and handing it to the user and what they did was they had a contracting division
for those for union for the truckers you were contracting with them for x amount of weeks
till you got flipped over to the union where you had all the benefits and so forth and one thing
that some people don't realize is that when the company when the agency pays you x amount they
charge that company double the amount to have you there which is why nine times out of ten you'll be
at that same rate for more than one or two years because they'll be like oh we don't have that type
of money because it's coming out of their bonus and that's why you work hard to show it you can
do so that the manager of this company be like you know what this person's good i like them
let's convert them you know and right now the company i'm currently working with
i got the call about a month ago saying that my contract is getting converted so i'm basically
waiting for the hr paperwork and so forth so in a way i do understand where this person is coming
from but sometimes you you've got to you always got to watch your back because even though you
are still an employee of the company you got to follow the rules and so forth the littlest stuff
they will ping you for and what's interesting in some cases the littlest stuff they don't they
just let that slide and they expect everybody else to set the proper example you know
it's uh the contracting world is very interesting stuff and it's it's it's far beyond video games as
well but it's interesting to see um how video games kind of play into that and how the industry
you know really uses contractors to do um a lot of work that we don't always think about that goes
into making games i mean it's not even sorry it's not even just like the testing of games and these
are that but like we've talked about trade shows packs right now i don't know what big names are
still doing packs east right now um but you know when it was you know nintendo and sony that were
doing these shows the booths that were the people that were staffing the boost contractors yeah
booth babes i'm using my quotey fingers at e3 in the pat contractors yeah so i mean
and wait this happens at regular anime conventions too it's like you can be you go to a con and be
like you can work a booth and get for 20 hours and get reimbursed for your badge and you still
get to go enjoy something like that that happens yeah and the thing is it's like
like nintendo can sit there and curate all these resumes and go through the whole kit and caboodle
of the multi-tier interviews to see if they want you or not they'll let the third party company
be like you know what we're gonna call all these people in they're gonna put them through those
interviews it used to be where the agency will call you back we got your position you report
here now it's like we have your position you're gonna interview with the agency to see if you are
fit and if they like you you're going to interview with the company and so on and so forth that way
in the event you do get converted to full-time you've already done those interviews all you
gotta do is sign the paperwork and that's that um speaking of conventions i know you were somewhere
this weekend because you sent me a picture with another blast from olr's past where were you at
this weekend i was actually in the bronx i went to go visit j j vmont at his job oh you were at
the store oh i thought you were at a convention okay you were in the actual store oh okay no i'm
i have a convention this weekend i'm still catching up from the last con uh i i pre-ordered
a pop from his store because you know even though that same pot was available at game stop i decided
to cancel that pre-order in order from his comic book shop to support small independent shops good
for you especially especially his our old friend there so even if i haven't seen him in a while he
used to call her right once in a while but i i know business has been very busy so i forget
i went there to pick up a pop and he walked and he he walked away with a hundred extra dollars
of my money i bought comic book boxes and more pops okay aka shit you don't need you still
walked out of there with it hey look today today was our weekly cost or no actually more
our every three weeks or so costco trip i have no room to talk about buying extra shit you don't need
look behind my head is a mini is a makeshift shelf that sits on my storage bins of all the
figurines i have purchased that i have not taken out because i realized i don't have room for them
in the display case but they're great deals at cons and it's like well it's within the seven
to ten dollar amazon let me buy this you know i love it uh yeah i'll be filling up this place
soon enough with that same stuff so yeah i'll say as much about one thing about contracting that i've
gained from is the fact that every place i've worked at is same yet different i've gained a
lot of valuable knowledge and training and skill but what sucks is when you're trying to go full
time somewhere they look at your resume and see all these places and it's like well how come you
haven't stayed here how come you're like my contract ended that was it that's all it was
yeah i was up for a role i didn't get it because i had too many contracting positions and in a way
i'm kind of glad i didn't get that role because i'm happier where i am now that's a weird thing
to dq someone over for sure the person believes that when you're in it you shouldn't have all
these multiple positions these roles i i know multiple people in it where that's the norm
couldn't you just list your role as the contractor company and the whole time you've been there or
are you going back and forth between different contractor companies just because i know when
i was like that by the way well when i was doing contract stuff i was signed up with like three of
them and i'm like whichever of you hose gets me a job burst is the one i'm sticking with
i i do that that's exactly what it is yeah i sent my my my resume out next thing you know i'm
getting all these texts emails and phone calls you know yeah it's for sure i will put it this
way though when i started with where i am i um i started there with the intention that they would
hire me because that's just how it works if you really suck you don't you don't stay on
and i had my first interview for a completely different department and where i work they
encourage you to wear different hats and diversify yourself and build a bigger portfolio and learn
more and incorporate that into newer and newer newer roles so i know that where i work is also
a unicorn uh rama i want to get your reaction to this quote in our chat over at twitch.tv
network quest buster says a co-worker once told me that you can't spell shit without it
look there is a reason why there is a flask on my desk
it's regularly have a gimlet lunch break
i i'm glad that they care lunch for us every single day and i'm glad of the fact that the
one block over sells beer okay i love it all right well uh hey rama why don't you hang out
with me for a minute here and help close down turn off the lights with me here tonight because
we are getting to the end of the show uh and it's about time to wrap up but that means we're going
to be saying bye to dark soccer in a moment but before we do that i'm eating my cheese from the
bravo cheese farm rob oh yum is that um this is sage oh like a sage cheddar and this is a garlic
jack that's that sounds tasty they're delightful that sounds wow um before we get to that though
i do want to say thank you of course as always for listening to orange launch radio thank you for
tuning in uh thanks for being here uh if you enjoyed what you heard here at orange launch
radio tell a friend or two about the show help us spread the word because we are the show where
every gamer has a voice but we need the voices here to put out on air um a nice five-star review
on a site like itunes spotify google play wherever it is i mean there's a million places that podcast
these days wherever you found this particular program uh please leave a nice review uh social
media shares are huge as well all of it we'll take it all uh raids on on twitch uh as bromigos
did earlier thanks again folks uh or anybody uh and hosting uh all all very good stuff so thank
you thank you for all of it it is appreciated um before we close up shop here tonight let's
go around and get everybody's final thoughts um dark soccer i hate to interrupt the cheese eating
and self oh no that's you getting your phone up there i was like and selfie taking um but what is
your final thought tonight um damn this cheese is good all right have a good stream and we'll see
you next week see you soon all right uh let's see so uh rama thanks for being here with me
and closing down the shop tonight everybody listen to anime jam session tuesday nights over
at twitch.tv slash anime jam session you should just follow it right now while it's on your mind
so you'll always be notified yes please do um well rama i i get to extend the courtesy to you
as well do you have a final thought you'd like to share with listeners tonight
drink more sparkling water because this cherry limeade is the bomb that i i've had that
particular brand and it is good it's good stuff there's like nine cases sitting over here so i'm
like i'm good for the next like three months i'm not the only one that stocked up at costco clearly
so all right anyway uh my final thought tonight is you know what i need costco to carry and i've
already talked about this on a previous episode of the show is this fucking quote coke starlight
shit that's a zero it's so good i think so some people some people think it tastes like ass i
think it's delicious and uh it was tasty i kind of felt a taste a hint of caramel while i was
drinking i'm like it's lighter than normal coke this is good it tastes like raspberry to me it
tastes like specifically this black and red raspberry gummies that's what this tastes like
to me some people say cotton candy ah yes i don't know and apparently there's a new uh they're doing
something like pixels i think is you know here i am giving coke free ad dollars but you know what
here's the downside because i like this because i like this i drew this i'm already not able to
find the 12 packs anymore and it's just i know it's going to disappear shit i love always goes
away i feel your pain on that because there are certain flavors of coke and pepsi i cannot get
here in brooklyn but if i cross the bridge to jersey it's right there but i'm just like i
don't believe this actually happens this this fictional land of not having to pump my own gas
and finding new flavors of pepsi all right that is it that is going to do it for another episode
here of orange launch radio hey thank you so much for being here and participating with the show
uh we will see you next week we'll be uh here to do it again next week hopefully loki will be back
but if he needs another week and then he's going to get another week but seeing as i saw him in
chat earlier he seems to be well enough to sit at the computer and is thinking about the show
so thinking of you loki get better soon have a great night night everybody we'll see you next
time and thanks rama thanks for being here and closing down shop with me tonight so i'm not so
alone bye everyone oh we love you rob come on you've been listening to orange lounge radio
orange lounge radio is a production of olr studios to join us for our live show tune into
vog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m eastern the views and opinions expressed
in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio
nor vog network but you know they were all still true
you know they were all still true
see you next week