Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Tonight, the PlayStation 4 Pro is officially unveiled
Sony makes the case for 4K and HDR to gamers
Was it enough to convince you you need one?
We find out tonight on the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio
Live tonight, episode number 657
for this September the 11th of 2016
My name is Rob Roberts joining you here in Studio N7
in Sacramento, California
Here with you over the next few hours to talk about
video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
and with me in studio, as he always is, say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hi
Hi Loki, how are you doing?
I'm alright
Happy birthday! Today is your birthday
Thank you
I know there's other historical events weighing heavy on people's minds today for good reason
and you know, obviously our thoughts go out to those that are affected all these years later
but, you know, things go on and we still do our podcast
and you still celebrate birthdays
which is today
Yeah
And what did you do to celebrate? How was your day?
Well, I...
This does not sound like a happy birthday
I'd like to say I did something fun
but it really was just the wife was stressed out about the kids all day long
so she was in a really fantastic mood this morning
so I went out and got breakfast for her
and then we went grocery shopping
and the kids were just acting up like they usually do
and then we bought stuff to make food
she wanted me to make salmon wellingtons
so I made salmon wellingtons
and then she didn't want to buy, this week for some reason, the frozen macaroni
or not macaroni cheese, spaghetti and meat sauce for our kids
because it has MSG in it
so I also had to make spaghetti with a meat sauce
for two hours standing up, didn't eat lunch
felt like shit until I had some cereal
so I wouldn't pass out from stress
which we'll get into in a little bit
why I'm so fucking stressed
and then...
Don't worry about this, alright
I mean, I guess we could talk about it now, why not?
Why not? Let's talk briefly about why are you so stressed out?
Do you need a hug?
Yes, so here's what happened
Yes, you need a hug?
No
What happened?
So, obviously it's my birthday today
and so I typically every year
because I'm weird like this
I buy myself something for my birthday
Why not?
Because everybody else is the excuse
I don't know what they get you, you know, whatever
so that's fine
I get myself awesome birthday presents
I treat myself the way I deserve to be treated
Exactly
My friends are very generous too
but I know I'm gonna buy myself something
And just on a whim
and I don't even know what prompted it
it was just like I was at work one day and I was on a whim
and I was like, you know
I haven't checked eBay in a while
because I used to go on eBay and I used to go look at DDR stuff
just for the hell of it
Okay
And this is where it started
So in Rancho Cordova there was a guy selling a TechnoMotion machine
for $99 starting
and I was like, holy shit
I'm never gonna be able to find something this perfect
I feel like I already know the punchline that's coming
and I'm really worried
Go ahead
No, it gets worse
Oh, it gets worse
I'm already upset about it
So anyways, the whole week I'm stressing out
I'm like, oh, I can't possibly do this
My wife would kill me if I got this
There's no way
So we were just at Best Buy yesterday
because we went out to dinner
because we have to kill time because the kids are there
and she's like, well, let's go get you something at Best Buy
I'm like, okay, we'll go walk around, look at stuff
and I didn't know what I really wanted, so whatever
and so I brought up, I'm like, well, you know
it'd be cool if I could get this, this cabinet
I mean, it's really huge
and she's constantly complaining, stressed out about how our house is a mess
because there's just clutter everywhere
which happens when you have kids, but yeah
and she wants to get rid of it
and I've already set up to throw away some of that
but I still wanted this cabinet and stuff
so earlier today I was talking with her about it
and I'm like, at that point it was up to, I think, 102.50 or something like that
or no, 205 is what it was sitting at
and it was sitting at that for a few days
and so I was like, okay
so I gotta run this by the wife and see if I can get an okay
and if it's okay, maybe I'll try, you know, bidding on it
so reluctantly after, you know, she's very not happy with this idea
she's like, fine, whatever, just do whatever you want
and so, and then she finally kind of warmed up to it a little bit
after she was like, you know, once she got in the car and drove away with the kids
so I got basically the green light to go ahead and bid on this
and I was gonna basically cap it at about $300
I may have gone a little higher than that just to see if I could, you know, get it
so I'm getting everything ready
I've got my computer up on the eBay page, ready to go
and I'm putting away clothes and stuff
and I'm watching the clock and the clock in our room's not right
so it's about three minutes before I need to get there
so I'm going to the living room
I notice the clock in the kitchen says it's one minute before, not three minutes before
I look at my computer, it's 30 seconds before the auction ends
so it's like, oh shit, put in my bid, highest bidder
but the problem was I put it in about 10 seconds too early
I got outbid
so I had it for $250
I had it for $250 for 10 seconds
and then I got outbid and if I only fucking waited a few more seconds
I would have had a fucking DDR machine
whatever
well sorry to hear it
it's so frustrating though
I always thought eBay worked
like you're supposed to put in the most you're going to pay anyway
no, it's bid sniping, it's always bid sniping
you always got to bid snipe
I decided to shop eBay
I remember doing eBay
but it was so perfect, like it was cheap
I bought a copy of Super Metroid on the Super Nintendo
it was cheap and it was fucking local
like cheap and local and it was a Technomotion machine
and the screen, the monitor didn't work on it
or it may have not worked, something didn't work
like the hardware for the Technomotion didn't work
but it's a fucking seller on PC
is basically what Technomotion is
it's a seller on PC with an old ass video card
I'm like, that's fucking perfect
just rip it out, throw a new PC in there
step mania done
and then you know, fix up the pads
you know, possibly put metal over the other pads
or you know, we're golden
it just wasn't to be, unfortunately
and it would have been so fucking perfect
but I was so stressed out because I had to talk to my wife about it
and it's, you know, a big auction lady
and it's so stressed out
but now, okay, so you lost this one
okay, caeser-a-ser-a
but now, like, don't you kind of have like this pass
like, don't you get to put that card in your pocket
like, hey honey, remember when you said I could get the machine
no, it doesn't work that way
it doesn't work that way at all
but it's fine, you know, because like
you know, we're throwing away stuff in the garage
and I gotta move my arcade cabinet out there anyways
because, you know, the kids
and originally I wanted to like set up
you know, dance pads with it
but it would have been so perfect not having to build
because it was the same price to build those pads
as it is to buy a whole fucking machine
so, it's like
you know, why not
I mean, I wouldn't have picked Technomotion as my first choice
but
whatever, it's basically DDR machines
some folks in our chat
let me, of course, formally introduce the chat room
hello chatters, and you can chat along with our show live
we do tape live every Sunday night
at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com
live Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
and if you are listening live
participating with our show, you can join our chat
over at live.vognetwork.com
so, real quick
so I, here's what it actually went for
so I bid $350
even though we agreed on $300, I still wanted to have a margin
okay, because some folks wanted to know
what does a little higher mean, so
and I really should have counterbid
but who knows if I would even want it
it went for $366
it's still not that much
no, it's not
but whatever, I mean
it's techno motion though
it's a copy of a copy
but it doesn't matter, I wanted it for the hardware
I don't give a shit about that
you deserve a prime DDR machine
you deserve something legit
I didn't, I mean, it's basically
the pads are exactly the same, you just
cover up the other
the other buttons
Tech 2030 in our chat wants to know a little more
if eBay automatically lets the highest bidder win
at the end of the auction
how do you still snipe people?
because what it is, is you put in basically
say
say someone wants to pay
$250 for something
and yes, you could think, okay
$250 is all I can pay, you know, here's what I'm going to put in
but
you know,
I would have paid
a few extra, if I knew it was going to go for $366
I would put $367 in
I mean, obviously, that's what it would have done
and so, it would have stated that
because, see, the problem was he had
the person that had time to respond
to, he saw I got outbid, and he had
time to put in another bid
the trick, when an early bid on that stuff, is you wait
until like, there's 10 seconds left
and there's no time, you, if you're lucky
enough to be high enough, then you get it
and there's no time for them to react
it's all some damn psychological game
you guys turned it into something way sicker
but that's how you
get stuff for cheaper though, because
if you just put in, I want to pay $250
for it, then it's going to sit at $250
and someone's just going to pay $250
but it's all psychological, because you're like
$250 is the most I'm willing to pay
but then when you see somebody, some little fucker snipes you
and gets $251, then you're like
well shit, I'd pay $252
so, aha, $250 isn't the most
you'd pay, you're actually willing to pay more
that's the psychological game
is, how much are you
willing to pay for this shit
is, how much are you really willing to pay for this
it's a sick game
it is, but see, I'm out of practice
it's been several, it's been at least a couple
of years since I've actually bit sniped somebody
and I was panicked because
I almost missed it, because I was putting away clothes
from the laundry
and I was like, shit, there's like 28 seconds
left, I'm like holy fuck, I'm glad
I got you here in time, I just like
I put stuff in and I was like, worried
because sometimes you put in a bid, they're like
oh, please sign back in again, you know, because
make sure that you're signed in
or some shit, and you know, if that
comes in there with 10 seconds left, it could fuck you
with, you know, not being able to actually place a bid
I do want to introduce our guest
who's been sitting here very patiently listening
to the horrors of your
eBay day, but I do
want to quickly acknowledge some folks may have
forgot, where's DarkSakura?
Remember DarkSakura, this is her first
week of her hiatus from the show, she will
be gone from the show for a couple of months
due to an arrangement
with her day job, she's just unable to
make the show for a couple of months, however
we will be hearing her a little later on
during the Classic Game of the Week through the Magic Radio
she will still be joining us every week for that
and she did confirm to me this week
she got November 20th off
so she can be here for episode 666
so at least she's making sure that the important
stuff is covered, so
yeah, that's, literally, hell yeah
so, anyway
meanwhile, we
have a guest here in studio with us and it's
a friend of the show who's been here a couple of times before
but we're really excited to welcome him back, it's always
a good time to welcome to the show
Gabe from Nascent Games
creators of Crumple
Kinship and whatever
other projects this man takes on
because he does games like I do podcasts
and also
involved with Sacramento
IGDA, what's your role with
SACIGDA? I'm the founder and chair of
IGDA, you're the Grand Pooba
basically, you are
you are SACIGDA
so I put it like
I'm the face of
IGDA Sacramento and then I have my
vice chair of Brianna who's the
voice of IGDA
Sacramento because she's the vice chair
that's a very good way of putting it because I know Brianna works her little
fanny off for IGDA, she does
great work, and hello Brianna
if you're listening out there
so I definitely want to talk to you a little
bit about what's going on with Nascent Games and Crumple
and all that, we're going to get to our kickoff topic
first, I'm sure you have some things to say about this
as well, one or two
Loki, let's talk about
what Sony unveiled this week in our kickoff topic
so Sony had their little
press conference if you will
they unveiled basically
hey, you know that Playstation Slim
that came out, or that got leaked out and had
reviewed and all that stuff, yeah it's real
basically going to be replacing
the Playstation 4 that's
available now
and I want to say that it was
$2.99, and then
they've got the
Playstation Pro
which is basically their
Playstation Neo, it's what they're calling it now
it's sponsored by GameStop
well
is it?
no, because that's just the first
thing I thought of when they announced that
would you like a Pro card instead?
that's a page out of
Microsoft's playbook right there
the Xbox Elite
and the Xbox Pro system
everything is Pro
I'm okay with the name
I didn't think it was actually going to be called Neo
it's basically $3.99
it's more powerful
it will do
output to 4K
not natively
up res stuff, but it will be
better looking than
the other stuff is now
and will supposedly
help enhance
VR
and stuff like that
not even you can say it in a complete
sentence without just
foaming at the mouth
and that's precisely how Sony sounded
because not even they can be like
they just used a bunch of technobabble
no one gave a shit about it
it's just like
talking about
all this stuff and how they're gonna
maybe at the end of the day it's like
how much better are these games gonna look
and a lot of these games are gonna be supporting
these enhancements including
starting off with Call of Duty for third party
Call of Duty
and even Black Ops 3 that came out last year
will get a patch to support
the higher resolution
gameplay
but will they be free?
yes
I heard that some publishers
are gonna be free
there's a story out there somewhere
that Sony's saying
that publishers can essentially set
whatever price they want for it
no they retracted that
oh okay well that's good
I think the first company to do it would have gotten
a lot of internet BS
yeah I can see them doing that
so it's gonna be something
that's gonna be available
coming out in October
and
I'm not really interested in picking it up
because I have a system
already and I don't
have a 4K TV although I did look at 4K TVs
yesterday because I was at Best Buy
and there's some pretty nice 4K TVs that aren't too expensive
so
you know what caught my eye amongst that whole
press conference was the fact that they actually
showed the first Mass Effect Andromeda
like in-game footage and so
that definitely had me laying on the couch
going awwww
I didn't know what any of it meant
it didn't look interesting at all
I was living for it
every minute I was very happy
it's very pretty
oh my god and they're purposely obscuring
some of the characters and so forth
but I thought it looked great and so
I'm certainly sitting there going okay
well if Andromeda
is gonna look better
on a pro
maybe I do need to get a PlayStation 4
pro but now
here's where I'm stuck now is because
okay yes
these games like Final Fantasy 15 even
I think they showed in the sizzle footage
a lot of games coming up that people are
very hyped for that will supposedly look
better on the pro but then I worry
my television even though I bought it
last year as a 2014
model it doesn't do 4K
and I don't think it does this
other coloring stuff they were talking about
so am I gonna get any benefit
from the PlayStation Pro
and I kind of feel like that message
was garbled like I
know they said oh yes conventional
TVs will also see a benefit
because down sampling
I think is what they're talking about
basically it's gonna be a little bit clearer of a picture
but is that really
worth selling your system and buying another
system for $100 more?
No it's not and honestly
cause it's not just the system it's the
TV too you gotta get a TV
and that's gonna
display that kind of content
and there just isn't sufficient content
right now period other than Netflix
but even the discs
it won't play 4K Blu-ray disc
which was the dumbest
thing ever because Sony came up with
Blu-ray and they're the
ones and oh yeah we beat HD DVD
but now here you are coming out
with PlayStation 4.5
instead of waiting like you should
and they just
they put the limitation
on their own format
which is ridiculous
for them to have left
the door open for Microsoft
to be able to say hey our
entry level Xbox One S system
will do that that was a
real faux pas
Microsoft jumped
on that like I mean they jumped on
that it was that was hilarious
yeah not this in particular
but there's other things that have really gotten me
like pro Microsoft camp now
mainly one thing
and we'll get to that later but
there's one thing I'm like really
you can't do this like this bullshit
you can't fucking handle this
Microsoft can do this no problem
but Sony oh poor Sony can't fucking
handle this shit and on top of
like all this other nonsense
I'm like maybe I should get an Xbox One
then I can get this game on there instead
because I would be purchasing all my games
on Xbox One instead of PlayStation 4
with their multi-platform you know we asked our
users on Facebook in our community
over at Facebook.com slash Orange
Lounge Radio about the PlayStation 4 Pro
and here's some of the responses we got from our listeners
about what they feel about
this whole you know press
conference and if they want a PlayStation 4
Pro or not our pal Critical Myth
said it's not clear to me what the benefit
of this console would be versus the
existing PlayStation 4 they have a
long way to go before I'm sold on the
need for it you know I'm kind of in a similar
spot with that because
what really got me was when
I went back to go watch the
Mass Effect footage on YouTube
or whatever it actually
the president of BioWare or whoever
it was sorry I forget who it was in the video actually
said if you're not on a 4K
TV to see this
go to one and
replay this or you know it's kind of like
stop now and go to a 4K TV and I'm
sitting here like oh okay
let me just run to Best Buy and get one
yeah let me just drop eight nine hundred
thousand dollars you know because that's you know
because you know you're the one percent
so thank you in a weird way
actually have them down about like four
dollars yeah I kind of feel like if you bought a TV
in the past maybe two years
that was one of the past two years model you
probably got I mean TVs are
getting more reasonable yeah I'm surprised how
cheap they were I mean they had those
all did HDR and all that stuff but even
I'm not gonna go drop a grand on a new TV
just for this right and so
you know and honestly I think it was
that more than anything for
me that said
maybe I don't need this PlayStation
Pro because I'm not gonna drop the money
on a 4K TV then this guy is
actually saying I'm gonna need one to
see the difference
so is Andromeda coming out whether
that was the message Sony wanted to convey
or not I'm sorry but that dude from BioWare
that's how he phrased it Andromeda coming out on
PC it is
and don't don't think
I haven't thought that exactly I need to
go to that's like my thing right there
like I actually started thinking about like
why do I have a PlayStation 4
is it because of you know Sony
first party exclusives that were like I
was really interested in and I started thinking
what Sony first party exclusives do I have
that was really interested in oh no man
sky well that came out of fucking PC anyways
so
ah infamous
yeah that wasn't very good
um
nope don't have anything so
I was like well
why I forgot a war
got a war is alright but
you don't buy a system for one game
Zelda so
I don't know we'll have to see
let me get through a couple other
comments on this from Facebook
some different perspectives here Tiger
Claude said I currently own the regular
PlayStation 4 and don't have a 4K TV
so I don't need it however
I heard that the PS4 Pro does not
support 4K Blu-ray media
so it's going to be a deal breaker for those who
want to watch their 4K Blu-ray disc
on the 4K TVs
Degenerate Johnny had a very similar response
to that talking about that 4K
digital content from Netflix and Hulu but
not physical content from 4K
Blu-ray you know
wasn't Microsoft placed in the hot seat years
ago for doing something similar favoring
digital content over physical content
digital content's all good and stuff if you
have the fucking bandwidth to do it
yeah and we've already hearing what
you know we hear what um
our home IPs you know the
ISPs are doing like Comcast and stuff
they're putting a cap
on bandwidth
you know on a monthly basis already too
so what's you know so now we
so now we run into this
conundrum of you know
this rapid fire advancement
in technology and
and clarity in gaming and
movies but now you've got you know
the ISP saying well
we're only going to let you enjoy it for a limited
amount of bandwidth before we kind of start capping
you so we're running
into a problem here so it's like
yeah it you know so
we've become so obsessed and dependent on
the streaming aspect of it you know
um yeah
but here we are you know
you know questioning are we
willing to drop another four hundred dollars
on essentially minuscule
upgrades well and then there's this thing
about one more one more response from Facebook
um Andy Ard said since I don't have
a 4K TV I don't see too much
of a reason to get one sure we'll have some
improvements for 1080 TVs but not
enough in my opinion plus I'd
rather get PlayStation VR this
fall and I don't have the funds to drop
on two four hundred dollar boxes
and that for me puts the nail
in the coffin of why I think this it's
this was not the right time well here's
the other thing too now it has been wondering
how well is this running on
how well is PlayStation VR running on the
regular PlayStation 4 I
don't know yet well like how
what they're demoing it and best buys
on a regular yes I know I got there a few
minutes too late yesterday so
I was like oh hey oh
man yeah but I
mean I think for the most part I
feel like I actually feel okay
that the PlayStation 4 is going to be able to
support the VR stuff okay
but um you know I think that's a very
good point is that Sony's putting out
two new four hundred dollar products
this year and I'm not sure that's the
brightest thing to do especially
when it seems too early for this
4K thing exactly and Microsoft's
coming out with theirs probably I'd say next fall
so
already I mean technology is going
to be so much better like or at least
cheaper than what they've got there
and they can put out a system that's more
powerful same price
when actually more people have content
and like the devices actually
watch this stuff on I just don't
I it's too damn early
it's like when they try to push that fucking 3D
TV shit they actually had hey look
it's the PlayStation TV and it's
you know got fucking 3D
you know TV and something it's a
shitty
small TV that did their 3D
stuff and then they're like ah
fuck 3D you know VR
but do you want to hear the hilarious part of this
I pre-ordered one on
Amazon anyway you can because
as you said
you can just go on there and click
pre-order I don't have to give them any money or commitment
or anything and I can go in and cancel
if I change my mind which I
kind of think I'm going to do but Sony
has 30 months to make
me change my or 30 months 30 days or so
to make me change my mind I just
I still maybe change my mind on PlayStation
VR yeah because the more I think
about it I'm like what am I really getting
out of this and I'm kind of wondering
maybe if I should just wait and see
if
there's something if they're going to you know handle
this like they did 3D
I was hoping to hear a little
more you know a lot of folks had said that this
PlayStation conference they did this week felt
very short and I was surprised
they didn't talk more about VR
considering that is coming out in a
month you know
obviously they talked about it in conjunction
with the pro but they didn't really
talk a lot about that kind of
surprised me how is it better though is it just
you know a higher frame rate and even still
it's like that's kind of
lame I think it's the same sort of
textures improved and you know
those sorts of like I don't
understand why I would drop that kind of
money for that I just
I don't know it's just
that's all you've got
for me is that your games aren't
that innovative it's just it's slightly
prettier it's going to look much
brighter you're going to be able to see the details
but that's on any system though HDR
is going to be supported you know
on anything but
we'll get into that a little bit later but I'm just
saying what's the point in dropping money for
this pro thing because you're not going to
I don't know I don't really think there's any
immediate
needs for that and look at the titles
that are going to support it yeah Call of Duty
is going to support it but is it everything out of the
gate I mean how many titles are going to be supporting
this right away and not everybody
has to support it
I'm really curious what's going to happen
for those households that don't have
PlayStation 4s at all right now because
I mean at first glance you would think oh
well if I didn't have a PlayStation 4
at all then great I'm just going to buy the pro
because it just makes sense but at the same
time does it because now these households
are faced with do I get
the PlayStation 4 pro or do I
save a hundred bucks and get a slim
is this worth a hundred dollars
that's going to be the question that these
holiday sales numbers are going to be very interesting
and for most families yes it is going to be a huge
huge difference because I mean
that's why Nintendo meanwhile
Nintendo's in the background in the
in the darkness just laughing
maniacally like haha we're still going to be
cheaper than all of you
it does
really feel like Nintendo is just riding
off this well I shouldn't say they're riding off this holiday
they're riding off the Wii U
for this holiday but you're starting to see
all these other plans
like it's like okay well since
our mega beast won't be available
we're going to send all these other
little gremlins out you know between
the classic NES and the
the thing we'll get into with the iPhone later
on that I'm sure you all already know about
with that and
what else
the physical Pokemon Go thing
you know they're going to start attacking holiday
from all these other angles I think instead
and I think Wii U is just kind of like
you know well
come on down to your old
old Wii U saloon
not so much the Wii U just Nintendo in general
with their next announcement
and I mean because I think that's what
more I was referring to just because
you know they did pretty well last
year you know with them being
the cheapest at the time even though it didn't make
a huge difference
now but
you know but still
I think that you know Sony shot themselves
in the foot majorly with this
Microsoft's going to do
a lot better which is kind of sad
because the slim wasn't really necessary to begin
with anyway but
you know but yeah so we'll see
yeah we will definitely see especially
you know the games are going to be very
important I know the last month
of sales figures showed that
Xbox One outsold PlayStation
4 now to be fair
Xbox One put out that new S
and that figure is
the old one and the new one
combined
but still
you know that is not
a trend that Sony would want to see continue
and here's the thing what's really amazing about the Pro
is it's able to output
you know 4K images
you know upscaled but it's
you know higher than 1080p
greater detail
more fidelity in the picture
but
still can't fucking run PlayStation
1 games or can't run
PlayStation 2 games yet a
fucking PSP can
run a PlayStation 1 so what you're telling me
is that system is fucking weaker than a
PSP yeah the only thing yeah
what was that the emotion chip in the
PlayStation 2 that made all the difference with the
virus compatibility but they
still have now it's software emulated
stuff on the PlayStation 3 so don't tell me that
that fucking powerful ass fucking
system can't play PlayStation
2 games oh but PlayStation Now
has just no fuck you I am not buying
your fucking PlayStation now well it does play
select PlayStation 2 games available
for $9.99 I am not subscribing to PlayStation Now
ever fucking ever
I am never ever subscribing to
that more like PlayStation I'm gonna save that clip
for when he subscribes a year from now I will never
subscribe to it more like PlayStation
never all right uh let's
see Dungeon Buster in chat says
it's been barely three years since the PlayStation
4 came out this still feels
like a knee-jerk reaction to a changing
market I just okay
here's the weird thing for me I've
been following video games for
even longer than this show has
existed 15 plus years at
this point right what what
is the what is the changing market
I didn't understand that there
there isn't there isn't they believe
that there isn't there absolutely isn't
and and it's the cell phones are fucking everything
yeah I think I think it's the
advancements of the smartphones and
and you know the you know the the bigger
publishers are like uh we can't we need
to keep them at home we can't let them go
out people think because
people drop hundreds of dollars every other year
on a nominal cell phone upgrade they're gonna do
the same thing right they have the
apple mentality and they like they think that that's
okay but even we're seeing with Apple themselves
it's like it's Apple's losing sales
from the subs from the six because of
you know these sort of things and you know
it's gonna change it's it's gonna change
after a while people are gonna get tired
of spending five six hundred dollars
a year because it's gonna it's gonna happen to Xbox
as well that's that project Scorpio
that better be something crazy
good because because we're hyping
the slim but now we're gonna have
extra you know an
xxl version of the
one next year and it's like
well rumor is and take
this with a giant salt lick because
rumor doesn't mean much but
that Scorpio's like an expensive
motherfucker like it's gonna be a seven hundred dollar thing
like it is for gamers
that are dedicated and need the power
but you know we laugh but
check out how much steam boxes cost
you know like there's people willing to pay the
higher end power and you want to play Xbox games
buy a PC
I mean seriously that they were
fucking pimping that shit
all fucking E3
Windows 10 and Xbox One
exclusive then fuck you
don't need them if you want a more powerful
system why are you gonna drop money
on an Xbox that you can't fucking upgrade
unless you buy a brand new system
buy a PC that's probably that's the
thing is like that's why I was like oh I'll buy an Xbox
One no way actually no I will
buy a PC because why would
I buy an Xbox One that you're gonna
try to sell me a new one later on and I don't understand
the point of this new PlayStation
system because
once again what is it
what are they meeting I mean are there people
out there going well that PlayStation 4 just
doesn't look good enough I'm not buying it
no one is saying that
nobody is doing that
I mean people might be like oh yeah
I wish it was 4K well
it fucking isn't and you know what it's still
not fucking 4K it just
outputs upscales to 4K
it's not 4K but there's just still not enough
content to justify you know 4K
like that again other than Netflix and such but
that's it like it's just it's like
we all said earlier it's just too soon
and you know who I pity the most and you know
of course this is gonna come from me
of course it's the developers
the developers who've been so focused on
even developing for the PlayStation
platform as it is and then
to hear now you're
getting two different hardware upgrades
or options and I remember hearing
some point earlier this year that
I remember
I don't know if it was Game of Sutra
or somewhere else were saying
that for any
new developers on Sony
Sony
made the developer sign this like
exclusivity thing where it's like
your games have to be
4K ready as an option
like it can't just not
have 4K option and
you know or something along those lines
it was very concerning
because as a developer making
a game in even
1080 is tough
because you know because it's like you know there's so many
limitations you know whatever you know
as powerful as the consoles are you know
we as indie developers
only have such
a limited amount of budget you know
to make a game as pretty as possible
I mean you know
I mean for God's sake look at what happened to No Man's
Sky as pretty as it was
you know what I'm saying and the approach that they made with it
they have a long way to go but they
but they fell big time because
of all the crap that they went through
and they barely got by on the
PC version but look what happened
between PC and Playstation 4
all that stuff but my point is that
there's
there's a cost there's a huge
cost to creating
4K textures
1080p textures and of course
the people who are playing they're not thinking
about that but people like
myself that's a huge
that's a huge hit on our
budget because it's like we
budget our games you know
hopefully to get it right
we hope to get it right and
you know let's put our game in
1080p but now we're in 4K
and it's so difficult
to get 4K textures
you know 4K textures
implemented properly especially when
we've never made you know
huge games we don't have the support
we don't have the size of a
AAA studio and that's the other
big problem too like that's where I was concerned
with Sony announcing this
because it's like how many developers
are actually going to utilize
that 4K?
Can I tinfoil hat something for a minute because
no just your line of thinking
here kind of made me think of something
is it possible that No Man's
Sky you know because
obviously people have their issues with
some of the quality checks and things like that
is it possible that No Man's Sky
was rushed to market try not
to laugh because I realized the game was delayed like five
times but was it
possible that No Man's Sky had
to release now to
get around this 4K directive? I think
they did but I do
think
I think where they failed the most
is that they
they tried to
they were trying to create an imagination
imaginary world this massive
not even world universe they were trying to create
this imaginary universe and
the procedural generation approach
in the on the development
side that's a really inexpensive
way to create a massive
to create a massive world a massive
universe because procedural generation
it's all in programming it's just all in programming
but the problem the problem with them
is I think partly you're right
about that you know on the on the back
end because they're like you know because even with
myself with my kinship game kinship
when I started kinship kinship was initially
going to be on the 360 and then
we hear about when they when Microsoft
moved to Xbox One and they weren't bringing
it wasn't supposed to be backward compatible
so anything coming out on Xbox
Indie wasn't going to be able to be played
because they changed the whole architecture for
Xbox One then the Nintendo opportunity
came up with you know for Wii U we were like
alright great you know you know this is our
second chance but now Wii U is dissolving
into the nether
and now here we are again like
well what's going to happen with NX
let's see what happens with NX so now we've
I've just ultimately decided we're just going to make it for PC
and see what happens from that point
but you come to the you know
it is an extremely frustrating process
because you know yeah
at some point you know
they No Man's Sky was so
far in especially with the size
of their game if their game
was just a regular you know 10
level game you know couple worlds game maybe
a six eight hour game they
probably would have delayed it again but they were
they were in too deep with No Man's Sky
and they were like and they knew
they didn't want to become
and again this is
I'm probably putting my tinfoil hat on myself
but they probably didn't want to be a star citizen
Well I still like
No Man's Sky for what it is
and you know I stand by my early impressions and review
of that game but what I don't
like is all of a sudden there's like some
massive radio silence coming out of that company
like after they patched the PC thing
then like you check the Twitter
it's like dead like and I
realize okay you put out a game that you've been
working on for years maybe you need a little vacation
but you rotate
that vacation so somebody can
keep us in the loop of what the hell's going on
Not for that kind and that's what I'm saying
not for that kind of game they
try to be and that's one you know even
even when I do my meetups
this is why I'm really
proud to be to have
founded the chapter because that's one of the
things we talk about in our different chapter
meetup sessions the one thing you
don't ever want to do
as your first game is
make an MMO
that's like game development
101 your first game should
never be a World of Warcraft
you just don't do that unless you're an
inheritance baby but even then
you still have to know what you're doing
It's too much to chew
It's huge and you don't have
it's not just the skill
set because one can have the skill set
to make that scale
of a game but you have to
the one thing you know nerds
a lot of nerds and especially
developers don't have
especially at the start of all this
is discipline you need
a mental discipline to make
that to make a game of that scale
and with everything those guys went
through with No Man's Sky yeah they
they should have
they should have brought it out and you know they should have
brought it on bits and pieces they would have been so much
better off I think they kind of did
well well
I mean efficiently not just
not just sloppy but you know
okay well okay let's let's
shift a little bit to talking a little more about you and what
you're involved with and all this stuff so obviously you
are you know founder and such
as the Sakai GDA how are things going has
there been growth here locally with developers
absolutely yeah absolutely I mean
we you know the
the proof is always in
you know our indie arcade event
you know we we the I
founded the chapter three and a half years
ago and the whole point of the chapter
founding the chapter was
we needed
I needed our game our
Sacramento game developer group to be taken seriously
I was tired of us getting laughed
at by by our neighbors
why would you laugh because we're Sacramento
because we're Sacramento we we
we are we are the red-headed
stepchild of of California because we're also
like if I'm not mistaken we are a
top 20 media market right top 25 media
market right but it's something something
like that but I mean again but she's still on
gigabit earn it though yeah but
like San Francisco is right next to us sorry
our houses are affordable right well
yeah they won't be for long no we won't be really because
all the Bay Area people are coming here no it's the
fucking arena's fault yeah it is the arena's
fault and and and you know and that's how
you talk like a Sacramento
playing everything on that goddamn arena well that's what I do
and I'm from New Jersey and I already know better
it's like no will the arena make them
play better no it won't and
and my and and I'm only I'm
not going any further with the king's stuff other than
in the arena suffer than this statement and
I've said it a few times and it's racing my
brows and I'm gonna do it again because I don't care my
opinion on it is that the Kings the
new arena should not have been a bit should not have
been built until the Kings won something
period so no arena should
have been built for an average team period
win a championship and then you get then you get a
great Christmas gift a newer well
to be fair counterpoint they've promised
to bring the Monarchs back yeah
Monarchs were able to win a champ yeah
and God promised me to be six three with
six pack sometimes that hasn't happened
sometimes you need a woman to get it done
well
anyway
I just showed you
receipts
right so but
so nonetheless like
so one of the biggest things was making
sure that our game developer group was taken seriously
and more importantly we weren't losing
great talent you know
you know a lot of talent leaving Sacramento
to go to all the you know to go to all these
different locations and such which I again
I respect that you know they want to work you know
they want to work for you know insert you know
triple big triple A studio here whatever
but if we had an opportunity to
to create a job
market here at SAC and
make them be like whoa I don't have
to leave home I can stay and
not have to worry about paying three thousand
dollars a month for a studio in San Francisco
if I get lucky and
excuse me so we'd like so that the idea was
was that you know we
have been nurturing and developing this chapter
and it has
expanded into wonderful proportions
I just put out a newsletter last
week and on our meetup group
we we are over
a thousand members now now it
is both and I said this in the newsletter
it is both a very interesting milestone
but it's also a concerning
one because we don't see a thousand
members at a time ever but
we have seen a lot more I will say
that in our newest indie arcade
oh yeah
yeah see the next event
that might change but for the moment
we'll see what happens but with our most
recent indie arcade back in April
in West Sacramento you know
we had about five hundred fifty attendees
which was more than double
the other two indie arcades
I told you this
I told Bree this you guys are sitting on the next
big sack gaming con and it's
it I would say it's going to happen but it
is happening well I'm gonna
I'm very proud
I'm very proud of this number one
I'm very proud of the people that have helped
make this happen in the first place you you are
part of this you know what I'm saying you guys were a part of this
we just showed up and told you no you
did more than that thank you
so you did more than that
with this microphone cord I'm just telling you you've
done so much more than that because
no no seriously because and
because it's not just us our chapters defined
by everybody I just
host I just host and I try to
and I try to be the push for everybody
especially this man over here Loki
trying to get his shit done you know what I'm saying
that's what we do that's what that's that's what we try to
do you can find a way for me to get more than
four hours of sleep at night which is just
I hear sedatives are pretty good
but anyway I digress so the idea
is is that have you
got just quickly have you guys had some games
that have that like people might
recognize like the downloaded that have come out
of Sac IG members oh my god
the one I think of I just
saw because Monsters and Monocles
that guy in Davis
that put that together in fact I need to invite him
on the show that
that just released on the
steam early access and I know he was at
the arcade event a couple years ago so
you're starting to see and they were at PAX
they went to PAX West while I was at Dragon Con
and I know they had a lot of success there
so I mean that's a really great success story
and I'm sure you've got more because based on
the games I saw at arcade
yeah Venture 4th almost
Venture 4th is done
Venture 4th is done Venture 4th was out and actually
I'm actually glad you said that because we're actually doing
a meetup later this month in
Elk Grove I believe it's in Elk Grove
at Elk Grove and Ed at the
Innogrove co-working space where we're going to
do a Q&A for
Skirmish Studios
as well as ArcLight for the Venture
4th game and because they did very
they both ran recently very successful
Kickstarter campaigns and
we're going to be talking to them and
interviewing them to see why
what went right what went
wrong and what they could have done better so on and so forth
but yeah I mean Monsters and Monocles is
definitely one of those games
that's done so well and
yeah we've had a slew
more and in fact we had
we had a mystery
judge who she used to work at Xbox
I don't know if you were there for that
but she came through
and was like
you know I'm going to look around I want to see what's
going on but no one knew that someone from
that used to work for Xbox she works for
a subsidiary of Wargaming and
she came through and was like
here's you know I'm going to tap
you guys and I feel so horrible I cannot
remember the name of the game if Bree's in the chat
I don't know if she's listening or in the chat right now
Was that the one that was like a runner with polarity
type of thing like it was black and white?
Yes absolutely and I feel
so bad we have the studios listening
I'm so sorry guys because my mind
my mind is just upon the mess
Which one? The one that won that prize
from the Microsoft developer that was
that was really good it was the
like you had like a
it was like a black and white type of game
and then like in the white spots would be the black
character that's running through and then the white
spots would be the white character
I got the demo for that it was like the
rabbit and the owl
rabbit and the owl that's it
yeah they
they have been kicking butt
they've been doing great they got selected
Bree's actually in our chat I just realized
she's the anonymous chatter in there
she's like screaming at the top of her lungs
Thanks Bree
Thank you Bree so
but again ultimately
there's been a ton of growth here and
we've started our most
recent progressive game jam
and a slew of new teams
a slew of new faces as well as
as well as the veterans that were there last year
and the year before that
it's been a tremendous
tremendous thing and
even now with myself I'm proud to say that now
I can finally be a part of that with my crumple
game coming out within the next
month and a half-ish
I'm so happy for you
I was starting to
wonder if your game was kind of like one of Loki's games
we were going to see it come out
I don't release stuff that's not fun
and I am so mentally working on
stuff so every day
I think about my game and every day
you know jot stuff down
and I do research every day
well maybe that's the problem
every day I think about mowing the lawn
alright
no I don't actually
who really does that?
that's alright I'm one step ahead of you
I just don't water the lawn so it doesn't grow
well technically you're obeying the law
because we're in California
so fuck the lawn
so yeah with crumple
yeah
I announced it
maybe even 3-4 weeks ago
that crumple's over
90% done now
we're working on
90% left now
the actual ending for the first
episode since crumple for some
who've been keeping
close lock on our game
crumple's going to be released in episodes
and so the first episode is
like I mentioned a little over 90% done
we're working on the ending to how episode 1 will
end it's going to be really
pretty intense and
we're just putting the final touches of any
bugs squashing in the code but
yeah we're almost done
you wouldn't think a game starring an envelope would be intense
but
see one thing about me
and this is something that
this is another reason why I started this chapter
because I came in as the
idea guy I do not
have any art skill I do not have
any coding skill but I could tell a
story because I've done poetry and I
have a wacky imagination the thing
with me it's about what's on the inside
and that's anthrax
let him finish
shut up
so what happens
is
you know what's on your inside? pepperoni
I don't eat pepperoni it's all
garlic and parmesan
so what happens is
that for me it was
you know even if you have the imagination
and the idea you can make something
beautiful you can make something very intense
and I mean I think we've seen
I mean you know
a lot of games that seem
simple on the surface are actually very
very intense Limbo which was part
inspiration for Crumple comes to mind
like okay a 10 year old boy black and white
silhouette okay what's why
and that game turned out to be incredibly
intense and atmospheric so
to be able to achieve that on
Crumple knowing we were making it on
a flash
it's like how are we going to pull this off but
we've been able to do it and I can't wait
when we show the little
progression reel of how Crumple
started how it looked when it first started
as compared to how it looks now with all
the sounds and you know the
attention to detail I'm excited to play it again
I think the last time I played it was almost a year ago
at that Reno thing oh my goodness
yeah yeah you can
actually play the demo now
there's been a demo for probably
near a year now on Newgrounds
and well as a listener of this fine program
please tell me where I can get this demo
so oh man I
did you have something on good old games
though I thought or no
I'm thinking of the other one Desura
so the demo started on Desura
went just dissipated into
had some problems yes dissipated
quietly so yes
we'll call it um but yeah we
so there's actually a demo on itch itch.io
as well but I don't really remember
but so it but on Newgrounds
and they've been super supportive Newgrounds have
actually been retweeting and liking my stuff
as well which is pretty cool but on new
but I don't have the exact link off the top of my
head because it's like numerical so just
Newgrounds go on Newgrounds.com
on the search type Crumple
it'll be the first link you'll see it
you don't need to sign up for an account
on Newgrounds you can just play it and
yeah it's it's not the newest
newest version but it
it's pretty it's it's
generally pretty close to where we're at we've made
a number of upgrades and touch-ups
since then but you'll still be able to give
it a shot there's a link uh just given in
our chat room too by Bree for all the
listeners yes there you
go thank you so much on Newgrounds yep
that's yeah that's the link so for those listening
on the podcast though you'll have to search for it but it's crumple
yeah absolutely and and and I cannot
stress this enough I talk about this on my
Twitter on the time and for those who are not following me already
on Twitter it's at nascent
games so please
please follow us say hi
say what's up but feedback
we always need your
feedback we need to know what's
right what's not so right
we need to hear this stuff and
and we recommend that for any
developer you give feedback to
don't be a poo-poo head about
it you know be constructive
you know give us give us good
feedback because um
if you this sucks doesn't tell me how to make it yeah
this sucks you're never gonna play this again
this game is so hard it's not gonna tell me anything it's like
okay why we need to understand why
so definitely when you play
it give us that feedback we we
would love to have that feedback um we need
it we need the feedback because I don't
know a damn thing but I know I know I
want to make you want that feedback from the O.L.R. listeners
before the rest of the internet we're
very we're very fortunate here at O.L.R.
that we have some pretty pretty decent minded
people in this program thank you decent
minded adults or children whichever
that's great glad to glad to
hear that well a lot of them did start off as children
and now we're adults
you have to have a little bit of a thick skin to put up a
Loki's crap three hours three hours a week I have
four sisters man he does not need they
know he can do that hasn't already happened
uh tell us briefly about kinship what what is
kinship where's where's this at kinship
right now um it you know just
like any almost anything in the game development it has
suffered its setbacks um
you know both on a technological tech
uh tech standpoint you know as
well as um who
who's able to help and and and you
know so on and so forth and it's
kinship is um it's
funny because kinship initially started as
a the original idea with kinship was
that it was going to be a fan remake
of Gradius 3 and
I then I decided no fan remakes
I can't be doing that I need to do
something original if I'm going to spend three years making
something might as well make something new and original
you can come up with something Gabriel do
something so I did so so here we
are now again you know as we
talked earlier kinship started as a 360
game you know was becoming
what's going to hopefully be a Wii U game
that's not going to happen now so now
we we look at just PC for the moment
and then console wise see what
what comes from that um
on the I've do you have
your 4k textures ready to go hell no
4k you know
can whatever so anyway so 4k
this so the idea is is that
um you know I've
involved myself more in the
development side I've actually learned
how to do environments
and build levels out so I'm not
I was gonna I was gonna say and I just to back up
a little bit I was very blown away when you
just said now because I didn't even realize
this you said that you didn't code
crumple and I always had this
thing in my mind that oh you you coded
right in there with the best of them but you you're
more of like a project manager is kind of what you're
doing right you're making you see the plan
and you're making sure all the moving parts
are doing this but it sounds like you got your
hands a little dirtier with kinship you actually
got in there and and did some more
of the environments yeah I've been
developing more of the environments um if
you look at it's not it's not
a very very recent trailer but well
actually no I actually posted a gameplay
trailer back in March before the indie arcade
event I posted a game our first gameplay
trailer on our YouTube channel um
youtube.com slash nascent games
go there and and look up the
stage three for kinship
gameplay I actually created that
that that it was a space
you know just kind of the easiest thing to create
first but I did but yeah it was
a great place to start and you're gonna get to see
get an idea of what kinship
looks like how it feels so on and so forth
and I I saw Bree's comment about the soundtrack
yes uh we have
definitely check our soundtrack on Bandcamp
we have um a compilation soundtrack
um and I just released a demo track on
there now um yeah nascent games
dot com dot excuse me nascent games
dot bandcamp dot
com yes definitely thank you
so anyway so kinship um
kinship is gonna end up
I'm working on the next trailer now for kinship
uh it's going to be
it's gonna become much more
personal for me because I've gone through
both the technical setbacks
as well as the personal setbacks
with with with the development of this game
when this game comes out
it's probably gonna piss off a couple
of people who know they were involved with
it and were no longer involved with it
and there's gonna be messages to them
in very subtle subtle ways
wait whoa whoa whoa whoa
what fucking dynasty unfolding
here dynasty in space unfolding here
so you're are you wearing dirty laundry
here on this project you did so you had
people that you were working on this game with
that are no longer a part of the project
for I'm assuming creative differences
is always politically correct yeah
those two words but you are you're flat out saying
listen listen all y'all
I've left I left I left you bitches
some messages in my game
yeah the idea here yeah
you're like the fucking Taylor Swift of
video games
I I hopefully don't want to go
that way yeah snake
game some more like a solid snake
a sneaky snake fuck you
so any good
thank you good so here's
so here's my whole thing with with that I
don't I I I'm always
grateful for both the good and the bad
experiences whatever whatever we go through
the one thing I mean
we've seen it happen to so many game
developers you know especially those
who kind of
kind of had their hands you know
just by themselves and then they decide to sneak
one more person in you know
and I mean we won't you know I'm sure we can
all we can all think of immediately who
who we think of when I when I say that
um you know uh
anyway so nonetheless it's like we think
about what we think about what happened
you know what happened with
those challenges with me
it's not it with me
it was more you
it was a couple of things you had
you had those who
had the drive but
didn't you know they they had the drive
but their ego got in the way
but then you had those who
you know who were very humble
but not
not at all confident in their skill
set and it affects you during your
game development and after a while
you know you try to
you try to empower them
there's one thing I learned
very early on with this is that because
I don't know anything about development
you know I had to make sure
I came at this from a very
from you know from a very reasonable point
of view and very empowering point of view
and you know this
year you know
and I've run into the issue a few times
I mean you know to the point where someone
and this was very early on in development not
recently but to the point where
someone actually sat down with me
and asked me to make them
the producer of my game
they asked me to make them a producer of my game
and they hadn't actually made anything for me yet
and they hadn't even graduated school yet
I said why would I make you that
why would I make you that at all
because they were like well I need to have that on my resume
I'm like no you need to earn it
and we run into
those egos and that's part of the
biggest problem one of the biggest problems with
this is that
you know we
you know I run into those things and
I'm left speechless like what the hell do I
how do I even respond to this sort of thing
so for me you know it became
and it's very frustrating because
it's like again with the ton of other
setbacks that I already had
you know now that
becomes you don't want to take it personal
but it's like I don't share
my story with why I'm
making my games to just anybody
you know unless I'm selling
you the game and you want to understand
why but if I'm asking you to help me make this game
and I share my story it's for real
and to just kind of for those
things to happen is a big slap
in the face but I
don't vent about that sort of thing
online I'm not typing multiple messages online
or anything like that here
us as friends we talk
about that because and it's something I share
with the people in my chapter too when we talk about
that it's you know
it's a thing was you have to be ready for
that you're going to come across people like that
and you have to know how to handle yourself
when something like that happens
that's part of life and also part of business is that
there's going to be people that you have unfortunate
you know run-ins with and circumstances
with and you you know you
learn from every experience
so what I'm understanding here is I'm going to be the executive producer
on this game that's fantastic
but what I
but what I do like about this and you know
well I mean not that this
story is unfortunate and everything but
what I do like about what you know you're talking
about with the story and how you
were not really coding for crumple but you got
in there a little more with kinship and I think this is a
very very very important point that we don't always
talk about but it does seem
to come up whenever you or Brie
are on the show and it's it's definitely
worth repeating is that you don't
necessarily have to be a and I'm gonna use
my quote-y fingers code monkey right
to get and no offense to the code monkeys
of the world we wouldn't have gaming
for y'all but here's
the and it's a great Jonathan Colton song it is
however
however you don't necessarily have to
already know
unity you don't know
uh
c++ you don't have to know
visual game makers on sale this week
you don't have to know one dollar in order
to make a game because sometimes the key
part to making a game is networking
with the right people that you want
to make a game with but then that turns
into a family and sometimes you get
family problems right game
development is all about
chemistry no matter no
no coding no coding skill
no art skill no
animation skill no 3d modeling skill
or two or you know 2d or 2d
our art assets go describing me right now
none of that is gonna matter
if you don't have the chemistry with
your people and you know
and that has to come from both ends and
and and with that chemistry has to come
accountability and part of the issue
um with my with my past
uh with the past issues I've run into
has mainly been between
you know the the just filthy
arrogance and the and the filthy lack
of accountability because it's
you know you you know
I myself start questioning
my own capabilities
on what what I can what
I've been doing and the impact
I've been leaving with both the community and my
own games and it took me long
it took me so long
to finally decide
what part of game development was I
gonna do because I tried to get into
animation back in the late 90s you know or
mid 90s when when Donkey Kong Country
came out on the Super Nintendo how
inspired I was to like oh my god
I want to do this seeing what they did
to make that silicone graphics was my friend
I wanted them I wanted to marry
them and but as I got
doesn't right well of course
indeed but the idea was is that
I as I learned more and more about animation
what it took I like I can't
draw so for the next
15 years I gave
up on myself and just
went with a regular life and I was part of
the sheep and just worked and then
and put my dreams aside and now
here I am at this point where I'm so close
now and I've got crumple coming
out and and I
turned 40 at the end of November
and November 28th
that crumple
is going to be out through
hell or high water before
I turn 40 and
and I'm telling you with all these things that I've
gone through that you know
that's why it's like we learn from this
we chalk it up to the experience and
when we put the credits when the
when kinship finally is done
and we put those credits up and in
that special thanks section you know how you see
the special thanks and all these different
the special thanks are going to be to all those people
who didn't do an effing thing for me
and I can't wait I can't wait but it's also
going to be mixed with the good people who were supportive
and all that stuff but it's going to be a great guessing game
because it's going to be like wow wow
which one of them really pissed him off and which one
actually supported him you'll never know
and it's a beautiful thing so
but anyway all that aside so
I don't know how to follow that up
but I'm excited to play
that game
and kinship which will be out
so come hell or high water
before your 40th birthday
what's interesting in hearing you talk and say all that story
is it was so funny to me in a way
not funny haha but ironic
is you could just replace like everything you said
with radio and hey it's me
because that's what I went to college to do
was to do radio well originally
it started that originally
originally it started I was going to be a weatherman
so was when I was a little kid
when the weather channel came out oh my
god I was so obsessed with that so you're not alone
can you imagine Rob Roberts with the weather
so there was and then I actually
I did broadcast journalism
I actually interned at a television
station in the town where I went to school
and I learned about how fucking miserable
everybody was there
and I started to realize like I don't know
if this is really for me and then you start to get into
radio and this was right
when the internet was starting to boom and all this other stuff
and there's this very like ho-hum
attitude in radio and it's like you know
you can work your way
you can work and work and work and work all these hours
but if you don't suck the right dick you're just not
going to get anywhere with radio and I'm just kind of like
I don't know if this is
I don't know if this is the life I son of
but here we are
Bree who's big in radio
now in TV she could totally
tell you all you just got called out Rob Roberts
Roker that's what he put
you know and I have
mad respect for people
like Bree who stayed in
that industry and have really
worked on that from the inside
for me I was like
eh I'm going to just
go work a temp job and see
what I can do with my life and figure this out
another way and started
radio as a fun little thing on the side
and shit here we are
I'm going to be turning 40 in a couple years and
we got some podcasts
but I love it you know
I've been able to do all this on my terms
Absolutely and no one can
ever take that away from you and that
is the same thing with game development and that's the same
thing that I have to tell myself
everyday and that's the same thing I have to
tell other people like this is going to probably be
the one and only platform
that I'm going to share kind of the more
personal stuff that I kind of did here
no one's ever going to hear this again because I got to
keep going forward but I think this was healthy
for me because I haven't really been able to
share this because
I'm glad we can be your psychological outlet
you like how we have a couch here in the studio?
I just, I'm not, should I put my feet up?
If you want, make some home
Put my feet up and lay back, that's just awesome
Definitely, so thank you
for that by the way
I just feel a little weird that you
talk about some of those difficulties and we
follow that up with, hey but you should all try
to get into game development
No they have to be ready for that
you have to be ready for the good and bad
And that is life, you could be involved
in sports, you could be involved
in podcasting
you could be involved, and there's going to be
people that are
great, that you work with great like Loki and
Dark Soccer and there's going to be people in your life
that you don't work with so well, greatly
and that's just going to happen
although honestly, like I don't want to
I've made it sound shady
like everybody's going to go try to figure out who does
Rob Roberts not work well with, actually I've been
pretty fortunate in the podcasting thing that everybody's
been pretty decent, so I can't
Yeah and I've
had my, again I've had
dealing with my bad eggs and you know
it's good, the important thing is that
I can complain about that and this is why I don't really
ever talk about it, this way today was kind of the
exception and I'm happy I was able to
but once it happens
I chalk it up to the experience
and I just simply ask myself who
am I not going to, what type of personality
am I not going to deal with going ahead
because they're not going to stop me
from going forward in what I've got to do
I've got a game to make and I've got games to release
and I've got people waiting to play my game
and no one is going to remove
that dream of mine because I
I'm the only one in control of that whether I decide
to stop it or not and I'm not
because as I said I did that for 20 years and that's
not happening again so and I've got
a community rooting me on
waiting for me to get this
done so, like you guys
so hell yeah
Well that's one of the most raw interviews we've probably had here on Orange
Lawn Radio but I, no I appreciate it
I love it, you know
I appreciate it more, man
If people want to get involved with making
games, you know, again, and we just want to
emphasize, you know, even though
Gabe's talking about some dramatic experiences
that he's had, you're going to get that
with anything and you have to be prepared for it
but there's a lot of great rewards
I've gotten great rewards from podcasting
you've gotten great rewards from
making games and the best is yet to come
when these things actually release, so keep
an eye out at Nascent Games on
Twitter and
websites, nascentgames.net, right?
nascentgames.net, that's our new website
you can actually see the most
up-to-date crumple gameplay trailer
first thing on the video there, there's a lot
more I'm going to be doing to that website
I had to revamp it from the ground up
but it's nice for what it is
right now at the time, for the time being
our YouTube, we're
going to be posting more on that soon
youtube.com slash nascentgames
our Bandcamp where
again, we have a compilation album right now
to hear the different
music tracks that we're making for the couple
different games we're working on
nascentgames.bandcamp.com
I also posted a new demo track
for our Kinship game
it's free, so be sure to, I just posted
I think a week or so ago, so be sure
to have a listen to that, it's a demo
track, but it's a good track, so be
able to, be sure to catch that
and then
we're on Twitch, and we're actually going to
be doing an extra
livestream on this Tuesday
at the Cafe Colonial
we're going to be doing a livestream for Extra Life
on Bioshock
the Bioshock collection which comes out on Tuesday
I'll be jamming out to Bioshock 1
because I love the hell out of that game
and so that's how
we're going to be repping the community a bit
this Tuesday, I don't know
if I'll be able to beat the whole game
oh I will, I definitely will
I don't know if I'm going to be able to beat all of Part 1
in one sitting on Tuesday, I'm going to try
but yeah
twitch.com slash nassongames
and the Extra Life
Brie if you have, thank you
Brie if you find
if you get the link for the
yeah, because we're part of the
Sac Indie Arcade team, because we have a
team on Extra Life for Sac Indie Arcade
and I'm one of the people for that
I don't know if she'll be able to pull that up
but if you're in the chat
be sure to keep an eye on that
but otherwise, yeah, so
those are all my links
two other quick questions and I've really got to move on with the show
because we're running a little long, but that's okay
so one, I'm
sitting here, I'm passionate about
games, I want to get involved with games
hearing this has made me realize
I don't necessarily have to know code to get
involved with games, I need to meet
people at my local IGDA
how do I find them? So our meetup
group, meetup.com
slash game developer
it is as easy as that, is that good anywhere
in the world? Yeah, yeah, anywhere in the world
but yeah, meetup.com slash game developer
that's our chapters meetup
group, be sure to check us out there
there's other links for
our Facebook, our Instagram and so on and so forth
but definitely go there
and yes, you
the two things I ask
for if you're going to come talk to us
you need to be in this for the
love of the development
I don't need you walking up in my group saying
I've got this great money making idea
because I've had a few people do that
I've happily showed them the door
like don't come back because this is not why
we're doing this, we hope to make money
but that's not why I need you here
we're trying to create a job market right now
and if that's how you're going to be
I can't have that right now
I'm laughing because again
the parallels to my own world are just
uncanny. Yeah, it's crazy
it's crazy stuff but I mean
and yes, the extra life link
oh man, I can't even follow that
so yeah, sorry, if you're in the chat
yeah, so extralife.org
or .org. Does that game developer
meet up, is that, like, if I
remember our audience is all over the world
let's say I've got somebody in New York City
we have a few listeners there that wants to join
the New York City IGDA of which I'm sure there's
one in every borough, how could they find
the IGDA in their area?
Yeah, so IGDA.org
and there's a section for chapters
and there's a ton
of chapters
go there, check it out
and even the, I haven't been there in a while
but the chapters list the actual
chapter head for each location
and yeah, you'll be able
to reach out to them. She posted a more
friendly link
to the Extra Life, so it's
www.extra-life.org
slash team
slash sacindiarcade
Yes, thank you. Brie's like our living
breathing Rolodex. And thank you Brie
because yeah, I know. Bring her with you next time
where is she? I know she's home
Yeah, she's home right now, but you know
with her work schedule
too, she works so much earlier
but yeah, Brie
I saw what you said, I know even though you're not here
but yes, thank you, you're still helping me out
but yeah, that's ultimately it
just come with the drive
and come with
a genuine attitude that you're
ready to make a difference
and show others what you know because we're
all about sharing knowledge
if you come with
that arrogant attitude, I'm gonna
wipe the floor with you and I'm gonna
I will ruin your day
I will be the original
ending in Mass Effect 3
and destroy many people's lives
you're gonna wish for an alternative
Let's focus on the positive
Yeah, and unlike
We're gonna make a game
I'm gonna put you in a fucking
special thanks
So
definitely come through with a great
attitude, you know, even if you're shy
I prefer shyness over nasty
arrogant crap, we don't have time
for all that, so yeah, so definitely
come through and check us out and I have to say
someone says something really really quick
then god, I don't want to take up too much
time on this one, someone says, oh, Dungeon
Buster, he made the quote, we're here to make games
not massage egos, thank you
that's it, that's precisely it
that's precisely it
That's precisely it
You want to be part of a team
Yeah, or even
feel that if you still want to be
a solo act in your
game development, that
you want to be
empowered, we talked about the feedback thing
earlier, you have to be prepared
for all this sort of thing, so we have to
be supportive and give each other that
constructive criticism, but
we're here to
empower each other, not push
each other aside, so absolutely
Alright, one last thing before
we move on with the rest of our show
Any teases for next year's indie arcade
event?
So, we will
99%
sure be
back at the West Sac Community Center
there is that 1%
opportunity
I can't say yet because
it's still early in discussion
My brain says you're going to outgrow that place by
next year
Some people have said we've already outgrown the West Sac
place, and it's like, wait, it's only our first time
They could have used the second floor, there's still more
room on the second floor they could have grown into
so I don't think you've quite filled that space
entirely, but I am worried
for you guys that you're growing
which is good, that's great
It's a great problem to have, and yeah
it's going to be interesting what happens for the next
one, we already have our keynote
speaker, she was
so you remember Michelle
Michelle the last speaker
she was on the team
that made Evolve, right?
Evolve and making Mafia 3
Michelle Smith from 2K Games
she's going to be our keynote
she was phenomenal, and she's a Sacramento
native, and there's no other
person I would ask to be our keynote for this upcoming
thing, so she's going to be our keynote
we're planning a number of other things
I will tease
I think I'm okay to say this
because it might happen
but we incorporated
the board game aspect
which had a great response for the board game
board game developers, we are planning
to incorporate pinball
for our next one
so stay tuned
Okay, I like that tease, that's good
by the way, if we want to talk about panels
maybe we want to get involved this year
I would love, it would be an honor to have you guys as a panel
please, be awesome
no pressure
I was going to ask y'all anyway
we'll be there with bells on no matter what
yes sir
let's move on, we've got plenty of news
we've got to cover, but of course we have to talk about
our gaming weeks, I was in
DragonCon last week, which is why we didn't have a show
I've got to talk a little bit about that
let's get into our gaming weeks, we'll try to
quickly move through this, but we'll see
Loki, how was your gaming week?
I wish I played a lot of stuff, but I didn't
I did stick with my I'm not playing
Tatami Katamari because it erased my progress
so I didn't, instead
I played Non-Stop Night
which is yet another mobile game
thankfully though, this is not a clicker game
because there's nothing you really click, except
for, you know, special abilities
every now and then, it's more of a
clicker game without the clicking, if that makes sense
and it's much more simplified, and it actually is
kind of fun, because it is
very easy to cheat in, so that
that's what I've
it's honestly though, the cheating
at this point, I'm like so high
level that it doesn't affect anything
but it's kind of neat
there's a little bit of strategy to it
so there's kind of that
but it's a good time waster
so I'm playing that, I played a
little bit of Ingress, not much
Pokemon Go, and
more stories later, but
I may not be playing much Pokemon Go
because I'm not too happy with Niantic right now
Alright
Hey Gabe, do you play
games besides just making them, what have you been playing?
Yeah, I've been
I've been
I've been dabbling more
again, and I seem to talk about
this every time I'm on this show
my Earth Defense 4 is 4.1 because they
just announced
unofficially part 5 is coming
out, which I expected to be a thing
and that's great, so I've been rocking
that on my PS4, I've
been playing Horizon 2
Forza Horizon 2 again because
the Horizon 3 demo came out
today, so
Yes, the demo came out, and the only reason
I know what you're going to be doing, Lee
I thought it was still in that soon area
Well, here's the thing, the only reason I knew is because
Microsoft sent me a code for the
Halo vehicle, the Warthog
They sent me a code that you could drive the Warthog
in Forza Horizon 3
It's insanity, so when I
redeemed the code, it took me to the page
that said, okay, you'll be able to use this here and here
but in the description
it said, this vehicle
will be applicable for
Forza Horizon 3
and all these different versions that they mentioned
and it said the different editions, and then at the bottom
it said a demo, I said, bullshit
what demo, so I clicked
further, and it said demo coming out
September 11th, I heard when it was coming
and I realized it was today, nice
Yeah, this evening, so I've been playing
that, and then
I've actually been, funny enough
I started playing
again, DuckTales Remastered
I was playing that again because I got stuck on the
very very last level, I just decided to start over
and then I've been playing Chrono Trigger
on my Super Nintendo
and
it's probably one of the best decisions
I've ever made, because God help me
that game, whoo, yeah
so that's what I've been rocking out
Look at you, going from new stuff to old school
love it, my gaming week
speaking of new stuff, okay, so I spent
the weekend at Dragon Con, which is why I wasn't here
which, by the way, I just want to give a quick shout out
to Dragon Con and the people that I met
there, had a great time on the podcasting
track, we did end up doing a panel
after all, on Sunday
about social media
and had a really good time, and
yeah, it was just, we have
presented the Parsec Awards, which was
great, because yet again, they gave
us the spot right at the very end
next to last
so it's really something to be on
the stage right before Richard
Garriott, aka Lord British
who like, made Ultima, which is a
series, you know, that I grew up with, it's just
an honor to be in his presence and so forth
and you know, all the great talent
that goes with podcasting and all that
so just, you know, my hat's off to
everything involved there
and Dragon Con this year, you know
that is not usually an event that's
big on gaming, you know, Dragon
Con has always been big on other types of
fandom, be it sci-fi
Dungeons and Dragons
board gaming
you know, but I was always told
ever since the first year I went, don't expect a
big video gaming presence, but I gotta say
this year, they started to step it up
quite a bit, and I think this is because of a partnership
they have with MomoCon, which also happens
in Atlanta
there's some type of strategic partnership thing going on there
so this year, they had Tokyo Attack
there, who actually had a 24-7
arcade running of
Japanese import video games
so I was playing Papa Music
over and over and over again, it was fun
they had Ubeat
like six machines, I finally got to play
a re-rave machine for the first time
so if Kyle's still out there somewhere, I finally
finally played a re-rave machine
for the first time, so yeah, that was just
that was an awesome addition to Dragon Con
did you meet dragons though?
there were definitely cosplays of dragons
they call Dragon Con
the Super Bowl of cosplay, and for good reason
there was some really just elaborate
stuff that happens there
so yeah, I
had a great time, there was also a classic gaming
arcade that was set up in the dealer hall
that wasn't 24 hour, but it was still nice to see
I got to play a
Mortal Kombat 2 machine, which I have in a
long time, and I still
remember how to chop somebody's head off with
Katana, and that felt really good
that's awesome, where you can remember and not have to
pull it up on your game FAQs, hell yeah
I actually got to beat some rando
guy, we were playing
Mortal Kombat, I think he was Johnny Cage
and I was Katana, and I remembered
block block block block block, high kick, and
bye bye, chopped off the head
I still remember that for scorpion, so kudos
to you man, that was great
alright, and let's see
JD in chat says, what do you think of the
what did you think of the re-raves guy, they have one at
Sunnyvale Golf Land by the way
I mean, if you've played the iPhone game
which, if you're a fan of music games, you
really ought to have by now, if you haven't
friendly reminder to try it, because
yeah, it's a great little
touch game, and you know, it just felt like
that, but on a much larger
touch screen, because this thing is huge
it's the size of a large television
but it's a touch pad, and so for that
it makes it almost harder for your eyes
to get a sense of what all is on
the play field at once, but
I'd like
to touch the big button, I like to
touch the big screen and touch it, it's fun
so yeah, I enjoyed it
let's see,
okay, so also at DragonCon, so Bobby
you know, he does a lot with
VR and AR and all that development
so our pal Bobby Blackwolf was there
and we had for the first time this year
what we were calling the VoG Suite
because we actually had a suite at one
of the host hotels, and so Bobby brought
his toys
and we all got to try them
so for the first time ever I got to
try the Vive, the HTC Vive
and I got to see some demos and that
that was cool, I mean
I was a fan of VR since I checked out
Oculus Rift for the first time, so it was just cool to see
some of the stuff in that, I watched other
people play Job Simulator, which was
cracking me up, we were laughing
until three in the morning playing Job Simulator
and I really like the
Angry Birds type thing they had, but it was
all Portal characters, which I think is a game
called The Lab that has, it's like
Valve's, you know, kind of
VR playground game, a la
Wii Sports sort of thing, so
that was cool to see, but I was really all about
because I got to try for the first time HoloLens
because he actually has a HoloLens dev kit
so for the first time I got to try HoloLens
and the game
that he had me play on HoloLens was called
Fragments and
it's pretty fucking cool, like
I'm smiling because one of our developers
actually has lent me
the HoloLens because he
got it, he got it as part of the pre-order
That's not a cheap blend by the way, I was told
how much those things cost and yes
Your life
It cost you your life
Well here's the thing, so the
HoloLens, you configure it
and it actually scans the room, so it knows
where couches are, it knows where tables are
it knows where things are, so this game
Fragments is like a crime scene
type game, so it's like a frozen moment
in time of a crime scene of a
kidnapping basically, I'm not going to spoil too much
but it's like a kidnapping basically, and so
you look, what you're trying to do is determine
where are they, because you can
see the kid and the
kidnapper and you're trying to determine where do you send
the cops, so you're investigating
things in the room and suddenly you might look at the
wall and oh there's a brick sticking out of the wall
so you actually pick up the brick
and turn it around and you might see that
it's N-O something
so it's New Orleans is where you're
supposed to go, type of thing is N-O
or you might find that
lying on the couch is a ticket
for the ferry or something
so you actually kind of have to look around the room
looking for things, and you even look up at the
ceiling and you can see that it's raining
so you know that the scene is happening somewhere
in the US right now
or it's raining, so there's little clues
like that that you have to put together, so I thought that that was
really cool, that was like playing like a
90's adventure game, but instead
of clicking on things that are
in the scene, you're looking around you
at the scene and actually touching
them and interacting with them, and I just thought that was
such a neat, that was
such a cool use, and then when you're actually watching
the cutscenes, here's the crazy shit, so
since it scanned the room already
you'll be watching like the chief and her
two assistants or whatever, they're all talking and having
conversation, one of them will be sitting on your
couch and then suddenly stand up
as part of the scene and stuff, it's like, okay
so like it knew that you had a couch
because it put this character on the couch and
so I just thought that was so rad, how like it
actually used the room
so I would, now here's
the thing, the one drawback to Hololens is that
the field of vision
very very small, it's like
sitting right in front of a big screen TV
type of thing, and
so you, you know, it's very
obvious where the
holographic stuff begins and where it ends
so I don't think it's ready for primetime
so to speak? Oh definitely not,
the plan with the Hololens was gonna be
that, and this is
why they released it now, and
the release is not because
the idea is that for the next
probably three years, three or
so years, we're gonna be, we're supposed to
us as developers are supposed to get completely
comfortable with the Hololens, and the
goal right now from what I've learned again,
this will obviously change
it's to be earlier or later, but
2019 is supposed to be
the year that the first actual
full on
games for the commercial
or consumer version
of the Hololens is supposed to be for 2019
at some point, so
I'm not totally, you know, the experience
I played was neat, I don't know
what other types of games are gonna be
doable on this, I mean it's
I already have one I'm gonna make for it, so yeah
it's, you have to think about
games differently, I think in order to
make for the Hololens, and you know, Bobby's
had this conversation about, well he sees it more as
something that's gonna benefit
in non-gaming types of areas
just like Kinect kinda had
some of its biggest successes
in hospitals and things like that, you know, things that had
nothing to do with games, and Hololens may end up
being very similar, and that may be true
but I think there's going to be some great gaming
experiences in this thing, and I think you're right, by them
getting it out so early at least, people
can really think about, you know, have plenty of time to
consider what's that game gonna look like, but I gotta say
I kinda, like
everything I had heard about Hololens
was pretty tepid, because I think
they were showing things, like here's the Halo experience
and everybody's too focused on, well you
can't see, I mean the field of vision sucks
da da da da, but this concept
for this game that I saw was like
okay, this shows me
something that you can't, you can't
even do this in VR
Right, no you can't, right, absolutely
and definitely sells the difference between
here's the difference between holographic gaming
and virtual reality, so I thought that was just,
I thought it was neat. Absolutely, and I saw the
I see the Hololens as a great, just like
VR, I see the Hololens as a great
supplemental piece for
game development and gaming, not
so much primary, which I think
that's what a lot of people are
quick, so quickly impulsively jumping
to, it's like, oh this is going to be the next great gaming
experience, I know, I think it's going to be a good supplemental
gaming experience, as an
as an add-on, but it, you know
Virtual Boy tried, and we
already saw what happened with that, so just don't
just don't do that. We've come a long way since then.
We've come a long way since then, yeah.
Quickly, I want to talk about some other games I've played this week
Overwatch is having a free weekend on
PlayStation 4, so I finally got to play
with some of my pals, like Exeter and Flaco Jones
on PlayStation
Xbox also. It is so, yeah, it is
on Xbox One, it is so fucking
hard to play on a controller when you've been playing on keyboard
and mouse for so long, like
it's just, it feels weird, especially
playing something like Pharah, where I'm used to using
the right mouse button to levitate, like
now in this, it's like, okay, I have to use L1
to fly up, and then L2 to
levitate, it's just, it took me a long time
to get used to, and my aim still feels
ridiculous, but, you know
playing with friends has been
fun. Am I going to double dip the $50
to buy it again? No, I'm sorry to my
friends on console, which is, I can't justify that.
And I think it's just, it's a little ridiculous
that Blizzard knows it's me.
No, because I tied my battle
tag to it a long time ago with
Diablo or something, which I
guess I did kind of double dip on, but in my
defense, the PC version had been free with
World of Warcraft, so.
So, but I'm not going to double dip on
Overwatch. If they knock the price down to 20 bucks,
maybe, but it's Blizzard, that's not going to happen
for a good long time.
But it was still fun to check out.
Speaking of World of Warcraft, I've been playing Legion
now that I'm back from Dragon Con.
Hey, the new expansion, pretty darn
good, I gotta say. And it
brought back, I think, 3
million new people
because of that expansion. You know,
it's very interesting how they've really
taken out a lot of the, you go
to this zone to do these levels,
and you go to this zone to do these levels,
and they've kind of taken more of an approach of, nah,
everything scales. Everything scales
until you get to 110, so you do things
in the order that you want to do for the story.
And that alone is really,
I don't know, it's just really changed a lot of the feel
of the game, and it kind of gets you more into the quests
and, you know, the dungeons
really feel now more like an end piece
to a storyline in a zone.
It's just, it's very, very interesting the way they've
done it. I'm into it. But isn't that,
and maybe this is a dumb question,
I apologize if this almost sounds ignorant,
but isn't that the point? Isn't that,
wasn't that what they should, what is, I don't,
again, I don't know what, how it was initially,
because I haven't touched, I've played,
I've played two hours of
WoW at the start, and that was, I couldn't do it anymore.
No, because you would kind of feel
this pressure to just, you know,
you know, fuck how you get there, you just need to
get to the max level as fast as you can.
So once you're ready to go to a new zone, you just
kind of stop where you're at and you go to that next zone.
That's been a lot of how you've
been playing MMOs in general
till today. This one kind of
stops, says, you know what, there's
no, you just do whatever you want
and everything's going to scale. And so
it's really kind of changed the game in that regard.
Interesting, that's nice. So I just, if you haven't played
WoW in a little while, Legion's kind of worth
checking out. I gotta say, I've been enjoying
it. I've enjoyed it more than Draenor
for sure.
Pandaria, I think
it's probably a better expansion than Pandaria,
probably a better expansion than Cataclysm.
It's a little early to say for sure, because I need to play
more of it and see what the end game looks like, and more importantly
what the support looks like.
But I'm very encouraged,
I'm very encouraged that they're already talking about
7.1. That's very
encouraging, that Blizzard may be remedying
what was their weakest point.
Still trying to play Final Fantasy 14
though, even with WoW, because Final Fantasy
14 had an anniversary event going on
and I had to check that out.
So, I'm a little MMO'd
out almost, but never, never.
Okay, one more thing I gotta talk about.
Luminous is out
on iPhone.
So, do you remember last week, or two weeks
ago we talked about Luminous and we were like, oh it's
new portrait mode, and we're like, no, that can't,
that's not the orientation. No, it is.
Portrait mode is the new orientation. You now play vertically
with Luminous, which was
kind of weird to see at first.
It works, but
oh, and Luminous on mobile phones
has Shinen. They've got the
classic pack that has all the old school
songs, very, very cool.
Here's the biggest problem with Luminous,
it's on a touch phone. That's the
biggest problem with Luminous, because again,
the direction,
the left-right movements and down
to move the piece down a touch, it's just not
responsive enough. And I need to remind
myself, any time that I think
a console experience is gonna make for
a good iPhone experience, it's
not. If it's just gonna be a port
or vice versa, which
y'all are gonna try to get me
in a few minutes here when we talk about one of the big stories
of the week from me just saying that, but
there's a big difference between porting
something that was originally on consoles
and designing something with
the mobile space in mind.
So, that
being said, I still think if you're a
fan of Luminous, it's what, three bucks?
It's worth checking out. It's far better than the one
they put out years ago
when I think the 4 was the iPhone that was
going around. It's far better and more responsive
than that, but from a
precision standpoint, I just think
if you're good at Luminous and you need the
precision that comes with being good, you're gonna get
really fucking frustrated that
it's touch controls. But
Shinen, that song
rocks!
That's a good call. That's a good call on that.
So yeah, good look on that.
So there you go. That was my gaming
week. Some quick announcements,
then we gotta get into the news. I gotta plug
GamerX4. We're gonna be there. We're gonna be at
GamerX4 at a table
in like three weeks. I can't believe
it's coming up that soon, but VOG Network will be
there at a table. Myself, Dark
Sakura, Shane now telling me he might go,
so that's pretty cool. And
a panel
Sunday, 2 o'clock,
the Indie Gamer Super Show with
myself, Dark Sakura, Captain Spike from
Gameboi.org, and whoever
else we pull onto our thing at the last minute.
Oh, congrats, man. That's gonna be
fun. Wonderful. I'm very excited.
Are you going? Because I know IGDA has a presence
this year. I've
heard bits and pieces
a bit about it, but I don't know. I tried
to myself get a table for NASA games, but
budget-wise, it was out of my budget at the time.
So I mean, I don't know
too much about that. I know there's been
a little more talk about the MagWest thing,
because apparently MagWest is doing, they're
having a gathering
later this month in San Jose. I think
they're doing the arcade
portion of whatever's going on at GamerX
too, so I think the early scenes. Oh, that makes sense.
Yeah. Which, by the way, I
don't know, since I haven't seen you in a little while,
I already have my hotel and tickets for
MagFest 2017, just so you know.
Nice. I'm gonna be there. I don't know if you're going back, but
I'm hoping they'll go back. I've reconnected with them
recently, so we're hoping.
Good. Good. Sounds good.
Alright, and then
the DragonCon Super Show. So we did
have a new show on VoG last
week. We actually taped in the VoG
suite. We did a special show
with hosts from this show,
Bobby Blackwolf, Pod Culture,
British Invaders, Critical Myth.
I'm leaving somebody out, and I'm gonna
hate myself for it later, but people came
together from all those shows, and
we did this Super Show
that's gonna be available.
Here's the thing, since it wasn't really something to
it's not gonna be on the podcast feed, it's gonna be on
YouTube. So Bobby's putting
that all together right now, putting on the B-roll
in. I don't know when, but it will be
on YouTube for you guys.
Yeah, I know, we're trying to get our
trying to warm up to that a little more. Do it!
I've been only pushing you since the day I met
you. I thought I said British
Invaders. Did I not say British Invaders? You said British Invaders.
I thought I did. That's what Brad from
Pod Culture said. So anyway, hopefully I didn't
leave anybody out, but yeah, we
did a fun little show there.
And that's probably a tradition we'll
continue next year. We'll see.
Okay, we gotta get to some gamer news. We're only
what, an hour and a half into the show? Let's get to some news.
Loki. So
Apple had their conference where they
talked about the new phone
and everything, but one of the announcements that they had
which was kind of odd was
Nintendo was there. It was like,
what the fuck? Why is Nintendo here?
And so they had some game announcements. The first
one is Super Mario Run,
which is going to be coming to iOS first.
It's a mobile game of Endless Runner,
if you will, where you're Mario
and you jump on platforms
and... Or you could just play
New Super Mario Brothers on the Wii U
and have a better experience.
Anyway, I'm done. I don't know.
I'm not so
ready to write it off because one of
Nintendo's biggest strengths, always has been,
always will be, is level design.
And so even though we're calling this
an Endless Runner, it's
not really endless because it looks like there's
definitely these setup stages and so forth
and it just looks like the way things are set up
there's going to be a definite, you know,
there's the obvious path and then there'll be
the path that includes all the red coins
and all that other fun stuff. And so I just
feel like there'll probably be more depth to this
than your typical quote-unquote
Endless Runner. So I'm curious,
I want to know what the price is going to be.
That's the big thing for me. Is this going to
be a $3 game? If so, fuck
yeah. It's going to have in-app purchases
though. Or is, no it's not. They've, they've
come, well, they wrote that off. It's a
free demo and the in-app purchase
is the game. That's it.
Yeah, they wrote off the in-app purchase
thing. They say we're not going to do that.
That's what the description said. Yeah, no, the description
says that because the game will be the one
level demo and then the in-app purchase is the rest
of it. Which a lot of other games do.
Yeah. But here's, you know, could it be
a $20 game? Because honest,
honestly, Nintendo could get away
with it. No. Square Enix
does. Yeah, and that's funny. You said
that I was going to actually, I was going to say they pulled it off
they did it with Final Fantasy. Yeah.
And everybody loves Square Enix for that. Be prepared.
I think they're going to charge $19.99
for it. I think they will. I think they're
going to be that bold. My hope is $9.99
but I fear you might be right
but I hope $9.99.
Yeah. Well that's good. They can charge rid of the
fuck they want for it. I'll still buy it. I will.
Part of the problem.
I will. I don't, I just, I know
it's going to be solid. Part of the problem, man. I know.
I know. However,
other things that were kind of in little footnotes
there, they're going to have a Fire Emblem game
and Animal Crossing.
Animal Crossing.
Well that's going to do
pretty well. Well
actually those games though, even though they
talked about those games, those games are supposed
to be out I believe by this holiday.
Yeah. And they just, they suddenly
put in there that Fire Emblem and
Animal Crossing are now going to be coming out before
the end of March 2017.
So those games quietly
getting delayed in favor of Super Mario.
Will mobile games be for the NX?
Could be. Well, who knows?
I think there's going to be, I made
I made a, I don't like, I hate
speculation but I had to have a little fun
with it anyway. I think there's going to be
I think whatever the NX
is going to be is going to have a straight up
tie into why they're
releasing the games on the iPhone.
I think they're going to try to pull almost
and please forgive
me for those who, please forgive
me guys, but I almost smell
the same approach that Ouya did
where the next console
is going to be, yeah you can play it on our console
you know, but you'll also be able to download it here
and play it here and there will be some maybe crossplay
or something like that. Yeah, it kind of vomited in my mouth
a little bit when you said that. That's why I
apologize in advance but I'm just saying because
like just these announcements are really
really weird. I gotta say, the
Mario thing, it did throw me
for a loop a little bit. I wasn't
yep, props to Apple, props to Nintendo.
I wasn't expecting that. Sorry Black Wolf
I see you're here. It was courageous of them
to put it on the platform.
Yeah it was, yeah.
Well just so you know though, they
did say it's coming to Android as well.
So you're not going to get left in the cold if you're on
Android. Thank God. It's just
iPhone first or something like that, right?
Who cares? But then
that raises the question about what happens
with the next DS.
That's what I want to know. That's why this
surprised me because I was like well wait, hold
hold up, hold up. If
the NX is going to be
portable then why
is suddenly Nintendo going
third party on another platform
and all of a sudden all this
endless ocean of wank
that we have on Twitter about
Nintendo should put Super Mario
on the PlayStation 4. It's like
shut up, that's never going to happen but it's like
it kind of just fucking did this week. If you
ever write a book you need to call it that.
My endless ocean of wank.
I thought that's what I tell the boys
on Grindr.
But we already had a similar title for that. Remember
it was like pissing in
an ocean of piss or something like that.
That's right.
That'll be the OLR documentary
or the Behind the
Music on the Making of Kinship.
Anyway, no. If they
ever did a documentary on the making of kinship you know
it's going to be called Special Thanks.
Word up.
You heard that fools.
Now here's the thing.
They made it very clear
it's not a traditional
Mario game because Mario is
obviously doing the endless running thing. You don't have to do
the left and right controls.
Having played Luminous let me tell you
it's not going to fucking work and I'm glad
they don't have Mario going left and right
and all that. This is how you make it work.
You have one
button. This game is played with one
button. Touch. Touch.
Touch. Touch. That's how the game
works. That's it. So if you want
a more in-depth Mario experience you're
going to have to go to the NX.
But at the same time
hasn't Nintendo told us that 2D Mario
is kind of like Mario Maker was
kind of the swong song for 2D Mario.
Here comes your encore during the week
we were off.
They're doing new Super Mario Brothers games
which are basically 2D Mario games.
They look dumb.
They're not 2D.
Seriously.
Fucking get the Rayman team on
a 2D Mario game or any
Zelda title.
Hand drawn, hand painted
Mario game.
I'm sorry. They did that already.
They had Wario Land shake.
Which was fantastic
looking. Just no one played it.
I put up a tweet
a couple days ago about
I know we'll talk later about this
with Interplay and them selling their
assets. And all I said
was Earthworm Jim
Ubisoft Rayman Origins
Legends team. That's what I need
to see. So yeah. That's what I want to see.
But I hope you're wrong
though. I hope the Mario
Maker is not the swong song
because I really would love to see
you know
those type of graphics
again. But yeah.
Let me go to some chat comments
over at live.vognetwork.com
Ranma in our chat says iPhone users
can lose their shit over Super Mario Run
but us Android users still have our
headphone jacks. Oh yes.
Here's the thing you Android users
get with your Note 7s. When you beat
Super Mario Run and the fireworks go off
at the end of the stage, your phone also
blows up. That's what you get
as a Note 7 user.
Well that's alright you know because at least we don't have
one of those iPhones that you can bend in half
like a cracker.
I thought
that joke is so 2014. Come on.
We're past the bendable
iPhone. Like those stupid
3.5mm
phone jacks or audio jacks.
Here's my thing. I'm actually
I have upgraded iPhone every time I'm
eligible. I'm not going to get an iPhone 7. It actually has
nothing to do with the headphone jack thing. It's just
okay. It's a new camera.
Yeah.
Yeah. My 6
My 6 is good enough for now.
It takes a better picture.
It takes a better selfie.
JD in chat says hey maybe they should port
Rhythm Tengoku Gold to touchscreen smartphones.
I'd be down with that. That would be a good franchise.
You know we know that Nintendo
was working on several. Well now we know
Mario was one of them apparently.
For whatever reason they've bumped this to the front of the line.
I'm not sure
maybe this has to do with Pokemon
and the fact that their stock went way up with Pokemon.
Namco. I could use some
Taiko no Tatujin.
All right.
Let's move on.
Loki what do you have next? Speaking of Pokemon
Go right? Yes.
Pokemon Go is getting an update.
They're updating finally to
0.37
or something. And what it's going to add is
the ability for players to turn
one of their Pokemon into a buddy. So you can basically
when you're walking or driving
or whatever they
earn candy for
the distance that you walk. Also apparently there's
a nice little easter egg where if you walk with
Pikachu for 10 kilometers he hops
on your shoulder. So that's kind of neat.
The update will
also I guess make it
easier to
choose smaller Pokemon on the map.
Also prevent eggs hatching
without animations
or something like that. And I want
to say that there was something that was supposed to make
leveling up easier. Oh
and fuck you for if you have a jailbroken
or rooted phone like my son
does because their fucking app
is not supported on that phone
despite the fact that it runs just
perfectly fine so I had to fucking root it
to get it on there. Oh but fuck him
because he must be a cheater because that's what they're assuming
because they're Niantic and don't want to fucking
fix their problems. Instead they're just going to blame
everybody that has a rooted phone for fucking
cheating. There's already a
workaround for it but it's a pain in the fucking
ass. And why should I have to
you know
spend all this effort to play your fucking
game that I paid money
for as well to
you know purchase items because I thought I would kick
you some money before making this game.
But then here's how you fucking repay
me by fucking me over.
Well what would you expect from a
studio that can't even
call its version version one?
It has to be 0.3 point
I mean what is this? I mean what
happened here? Because the game's not fucking
finished. It won't ever be done.
It's going to be another No Man's Sky.
So I mean it's like seriously.
That's unfortunate.
But you know what? You know what's good though?
I'm so glad that they focused
their shit on instead of fixing
the problems. They've got Pokemon
Go coming out for the new fucking
iWatch or
Apple thing. And oh it looks so
fucking fantastic on that tiny little fucking
screen. I'm so glad that they
could focus their fucking efforts on that.
But fuck all you guys. I guess fuck you
if you have your own stupid rooted phone.
You better fucking buy an iWatch because at least
that shit will work. Hey you want to know something fucking
funny? You're releasing this stupid
Pokemon Go Plus in what literally
days now that I'm going to fucking
hack the shit out of and there's not
a fucking thing you can do about it.
But you know go ahead and punish everybody
that has a fucking rooted phone because
they're the fucking hackers. I don't have a
rooted phone and I'm going to hack the shit out of your shit.
The following comments are not necessarily
of OLR and its affiliates.
Okay so here's the thing.
They actually counted how many fucks were in that
segment in our chat room. 15.
That's not enough.
So okay I will say this.
As cute as the Watch thing
looks and if I were into the Apple Watch
I'd probably be into the
if Jamie were here she'd be raging so hard right now.
But if I were into
the Apple Watch thing I'd probably be into
the Pokemon Go thing because it did look cute
you know for what the Watch does. That's awesome.
I can take both hands off the steering wheel when I play in the car.
Okay that's funny.
Okay but
it does seem a little bit reductive
to the
physical Pokemon Go
thing that Nintendo's trying to make money
off of that's coming out next week.
Like I don't fucking need that now
if I have an Apple Watch it sure seems like.
Well no you still do because you play the Apple Watch
one just like you do the actual game.
So you actually I think you throw balls and stuff like that.
No you still hatch eggs and all that stuff.
Yeah you still do all that.
Here's the thing is like I mean seriously like
like I've heard
rumors that one of the other reasons that they may have
you know blocked it for rooted people is
because they're going to like somehow abuse
the device. I'm like dude you don't even need a
rooted device. Hello look at
okay the way this device works is
it indicates any time that you have to
push the button. It flashes a light or
rumbles. There's electricity going
to that light there's electricity going to that rumble
motor. You fucking just
solder a goddamn wire from
that to the switch. Bada bing
eight fucking auto hacks your stupid
fucking pokey stops and auto catches
fucking Pokemon by one
fucking wire. He just went
sopranos on us. I'm with
William Murderface in our chat. Loki dropped out of
rant space. Someone vent the rant core
breach.
Good lord.
It's fucking disappointing.
Now I gotta explain to my son who fucking
loves playing Pokemon Go. I'm sorry
Niantic fucking hates you because you're a cheater
so you can't play anymore. You're not worthy
son. I mean
seriously he is fucking in the
Pokemon like crazy now because of Pokemon
Go and now sorry
fuck you. You don't get the play because
you're a fucking cheater. Thank you.
He's almost at 20. JD with the obvious question
in chat that I have to ask as well
live.vognorant.com just don't update the app
on his phone. Oh
I'm glad you thought of that except
Niantic also fucking thinks about that because
see I have this other app called Ingress
and if you don't fucking update it it doesn't
fucking work.
So that's what's gonna fucking happen is because
they'll check your version of it and I'm sorry
you need to update your fucking app to play this.
This is great.
Wow. And the most important
about what he just said
for those new to counting
numbers you've
just received a great lesson
on how to count. I'll put it in the review
of the app.
Oh my god.
Alright. Let's talk about something that
God I just wish he'd won
the goddamn techno motion machine.
It would have been half
the fucks. You'd be like I don't give
a fuck about it. I don't give a fuck but life
is great. I got a machine.
Alright. Let's talk about
Interplay. Gabe mentioned this earlier.
They are going to be selling their games
and intellectual property so
if you want to buy an intellectual
property such as Earthworm Jim
or MDK or Clay Fighter
fuck yeah. Oh my god.
Clay Fighter was awesome. Or Descent
or Battle Chess
get to it. You can
actually do that.
Let's see. Wedbush
Securities is going to be assisting Interplay with
the sales of the IP so I'm
very curious to see what happens in a couple months with
who buys what.
See it's moments like this
that I as a startup indie studio
wish I could afford to get something
like that because I know
that would be so beneficial for
my team. Especially for some of my team where
they're kind of the younger generation so they
don't know. They aren't familiar
with those older games back in the
early mid 90s
and so on and so forth. It'd be great to be like you have
no idea. Earthworm Jim
no idea. Clay Fighter
I need you to write me a theme
song like the Clay Fighter song
which actually if you remember on the
Super Nintendo I think had the vocal
Yeah it did.
It's like
everybody remembers that because like
when did the fucking new Super Nintendo talk
to you during Super Metroid and
during Clay Fighter. Well NBA Jam.
Ok one or two other times too.
Right.
Very true. Very true.
To register participation for this week's episode
of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com
use the passphrase
wolf. Anyhow, Loki what do you have
next for us. Alright
so the next thing I have we're going to talk a little
bit about is
Mario games
and Miyamoto basically saying
hey you know what
Mario's just not going to really work
out for VR. Damn right. It's not
going to be a good fit and I kind of I could see
that because I mean think
about it. It's platforming. It's lots of
movement. That's going to make people sick.
Basically saying you know I agree
that adapting Mario to new platforms is key
to keeping him relevant but we want families
to play together and virtual reality
which requires players to be closed off
from the real world doesn't really
fit in there. We also like people
playing for a long time and it's hard to do
that with VR. You don't need
VR to be closed off from the real world.
That's been happening since
the Atari days. That's an interesting statement.
I don't know if that's a good reason why not to do
it because if you think about it they can still
do like you know
like Sony's doing where they have you know
the multi-screenplay thing where it's
almost just like the Wii U where you add one person
on a gamepad. Everybody else is on the
TV. You know you could do that with VR.
Don't put Mario on VR. Yeah I was going to say but they're still
stationary and there
isn't the restriction other than
if you really want to vomit
fast you put Sonic in VR.
Like here's the thing.
That's just punishment. Holy shit. And this
goes back to what I was saying about you know
fragments and the AR space and
everything is that you know it's going to change the way
the game developers think about
games. It's like telling
a painter that now instead of
oil paints they have to paint with watercolor.
It's a whole new canvas so that doesn't mean
the same old ideas are going to necessarily work. I don't really
take a lot of this you know what he
says right now for
I don't know like how much of it
is just kind of a thing that he's saying right now because
if you think about it like if VR
becomes like the Del facto thing
of course they're going to put fucking Mario in VR.
I mean just like how they probably were saying oh
well we're not developing
mobile games because our games are too fucking awesome
for that and here they are developing a mobile
game so
I don't know. Did you say
Rob did you did I
maybe I was just
high but did you just say Mario
Paint by any chance?
No but I was comparing this to
painting so I can see why somebody would actually
come at the conclusion of Mario Paint. So okay
cool. So I wasn't entirely losing my mind
because I just had this wild thought like God
Mario Paint in VR which
that would be that would be freaking
awesome. By the way
perfect iOS Android
opportunity for Nintendo
just bring
back Mario Paint
and that most of all most
importantly that music generator thing they had
in Mario Paint. Oh my goodness yes.
And use the magic of the interwebs that
we can send our little Mario Paint
creations as text messages
and those silly little songs that we do in the
music generator we can send those
to each other somehow. Just food for thought.
And that'll never happen because it's too brilliant of a night.
Alright.
Anyhow speaking of VR
experiences this one would be worthy
of VR by the way. Space
Channel 5
Sega announced that there is
a Space Channel 5
VR called Ooki Ooki
Viewing Show and when I heard that Space Channel
5 was coming to
VR I about made an Ooki Ooki
in my pants because
I fucking love Space Channel 5
and so the thought of just getting
to you know strut along with
choo choo right along that
just I was so excited about that
um but
unfortunately it's actually not
the game the key word is
viewing show so you get to be
a program viewer of the report
show sadly it's not something
that lets you play the rhythm game. However
but see I still go
okay but it seems like they're testing
the waters if this does well
that's that right there though
see this type of thing is why I'm
hesitant with jumping
in on like Playstation VR because
all these games that come out are experiences
they're not a game
it's just like it's a thing
it's a small portion of what could be
a game it's basically like a
tech demo
that's just why
am I dropping $500
a platform for fucking tech demos
it's gonna be a Tokyo game show
so some folks will get to try that out
first hand and here's the interesting part
I just assumed it was Playstation VR
right it's actually not it's a Vive
um title so that kind of
surprised me but then again Sega's been doing
stuff for Steam so I guess it's
not as surprising but uh yeah
so it's actually an experience that's gonna be on the Vive
so some folks that are going to Tokyo Game
Show will get to check that out I don't know
if Akuma JP is going this year but if you are
you need to check that out for me please
alright
uh let's go to Loki
with another news story
so once again you know another reason like I'm
I bought Fallout
on Playstation 4 it's like sweet
cause I can my laptop
doesn't run these games that great
and you know I can also
do mods it's gonna be fucking awesome because
they talked about it at E3 and everything
yeah
unfortunately that's not gonna happen on Playstation 4
they did get they ended up releasing
mod support on Xbox
um back I wanna say in May
um it was supposed to be coming later
for Playstation 4 but
it's just not gonna happen anymore basically
as Bethesda put it on their website
after months of discussion with Sony we regret
to say that while we have long been
ready to offer mod support
on Playstation 4
Sony has informed us they will not approve
user mods the way they should work
where users can do anything they want
for either Fallout 4 or
Skyrim Special Edition
like you we are disappointed by Sony's decision
to give uh given the considerable
amount of time and effort we put into
the project and the amount
of time our fans have waited for mod
support to arrive we consider this
important initiative and we hope to find
other ways um user mods can be
available for the Playstation audience
however until Sony will allow us to
offer proper mod support for Playstation 4
that content for Fallout 4 and Skyrim
on Playstation 4 will not be available
thank you Sony
I appreciate this is really making me
warm up to your Playstation
platform
Sony's not having a good PR week
they kick so much ass
at E3 and god
help us with this
seriously though the ball is in their core for
a lot of shit that's just not fucking
working like Microsoft
saying hey you know what we would do
cross platform multiplayer
balls in your court Sony
fuck nothing
ok and then like
then this shit is just
oh I'm sorry we promised this
for our players you bought the game based
on this promise yeah
we're just not going to let you do that either
they're like so worried that their console is
going to get hacked or something or that this game would make
you know the game crash or something like that
who cares if it makes the game crash it's a mod
it may do that put a
fucking you know
someone might put
titties in the game
and then there would be titties
on your Playstation
and then somebody calls
channel 10 news because the
kindergartner at home saw titties
oh no they
saw titties what
god of war is fucking around the corner anyways
there's always titties in god of war I mean who cares
or there's titties in grand theft auto 4
right now or 5 I mean
so you know
what's the big deal there's titties already on there
it's a mature rated game
well we're not a mature rated
society that's the problem
so that's a good retort
I already have most of my people
in my you know settlements
without clothing anyways because
you can glitch it to do that
it's just a thing you do
so who cares I just think it's
stupid and this right here I'm not
buying Skyrim for Playstation 4
and if I do get an Xbox 1 I will be
buying multi platform games on
Xbox 1 because apparently they have their shit together
where Sony can't fucking
even emulate god damn Playstation 1 games
yet on their powerful fucking hardware
backwards compatibility folks remember that
it's stupid it's Playstation now
oh we got Playstation now no fuck
you I don't want Playstation now
I want this shit to fucking work because I bought it already
well Sony screwed themselves up anyway
because they built that Playstation 4 so
advanced thinking oh Xbox 1
they changed their architecture and they
essentially fell for the bluff
if you will saying oh well
Xbox 1 is not going to be able to play backwards compatibility
that means we're in the clear now because
Xbox because Microsoft said no
our next system is not going to be able to play 360 games
and then Microsoft went on Ninja
on Sony and said
hey surprise
through a nice software update and
Windows 10 we've just
not made a couple hundred games and that just screwed
Sony up it's sad they're doing backwards compatibility
better they're doing multiplayer
support better they're
supporting you know innovative
things on their platform it's just
weird that that's happening
it's also directly correlated
to when they threw one president out and got
another one yeah so
that's right knock down the 1%
fools all right DungeonBuster
in chat
saying Bethesda
pretty much threw Sony under the bus
yeah they did hell yeah that was
that was air that Bethesda put
Sony in the special thanks yes
they did there
were so because they put the
effort into it and Sony's like yeah
we're not doing it there were a bunch of issues
such as mods not having any sound because the
PlayStation 4 uses a proprietary sound format
that they needed to work around so
all
right anyhow uh
how would you like speaking of Microsoft
I mean how crazy would it be if suddenly
a Nintendo emulator came out
for the Xbox one then
boy Nintendo or excuse me
Microsoft even more fans if
they were to do that and it looked like
for a little bit this week that it might be happening
through the emulator
nest box actually
said on Twitter that their application
had passed Microsoft certification
process for the
Xbox and so it looked like
the nest box was going to be coming
out on the Xbox
one but a mere two days later
and I can't possibly imagine what happened
but a mere two days later all of a
sudden not only did this emulator get
yanked from
even potentially coming to the Xbox one
it got yanked from the mobile
phone and I think it's on the windows 10 store
or it's on one of the windows stores
fronts as well which
is interesting that okay
well we'll put emulators on those storefronts
you know nobody's paying
attention to windows phone anyway so
what the fuck we'll just let emulators on this platform
cause literally nobody's watching
so
but oh no the minute you say
you're going to put it on the Xbox now we're
going to have a problem that's what actually
happened here is that and the
reason was apps that are targeted
to Xbox one are primarily gaming
experiences must be approved
through the ID at Xbox program
and that was the excuse they used to yank it
all which makes sense because the ID at
Xbox one they only care about
the Xbox because do you know how many emulators
and roms are on the windows
mobile platform I had a windows phone I had no
idea do you know I oh my god it was so
easy to find super
mario world just a super mario world
and just play on my windows phone how is that legal
no one cared because
what because of the because what windows phone
it was a windows phone that you know two people none
of the seven people were that that were
playing it you know that have the phone
we're going to be like oh my god microsoft look what's happening
oh no so yeah no absolutely
not so I'm not yeah so that's the only reason they got
called out was because of exactly that
it you know they added it to Xbox if it was
on the windows 10 the UWP
the universal windows platform
wouldn't none would have happened none would have
happened at all that's just hilarious
all right well all this talk of emulators
and things in the past makes
me think it's time to open
the gaming vault with the classic
game of the week
every week of course dark
sakura steps into the gaming vault and
finds a game that she thinks hey
you guys should be playing this game this
week and thanks to the magic of radio
radio magic here
she is dark sakura why don't you find me
under all the stuff
it was it was a difficult task but
it had to be done I'm too busy
playing my demon hunter we we
miss you already dark sakura but I'm glad
I'm glad we can have you this like you're having fun with demon hunter
yes I am demon
hunting demon hunty yes
demon hunties you're liking the new
wow expansion I am because
I like Illidan good he
needs to be my secret demon boyfriend is that just
what they need to do more often in world of
warcraft is just bring back old stuff because it
seems to work well for them then it just needs
to be all space goats and Illidan
cause he's like my favorite
anti hero I don't think he's
a bad guy that could be the next
expansion space goats
we already had space goats well
we already had Illidan we had Draenor
that was space
goats anyway she's
gonna step into the gaming vault and find a game
for you guys to pay a little respect
to this week in
the classic game of
the week respect your motherfucking
elders and this
is an elder in video gaming
it's older than a lot of you it
actually it could have birthed some of you that is a
sad sad truth yes
what is the classic game of the week dark sakura I was
five I was two
okay you were five too
no I was two
the classic game of the week is tempest
not tempest 2000
which we've done before
not txk which is
fucking awesome and everyone needs to play it
get a vita right now it's the reason to have a vita
it's tempest
it came out in 1981
babies
oh then I was three just kidding okay whatever
let me feel old
it came out by atari
and it was designed by
some guy named dave
and my husband is texting me while
I am doing the classic game
um
dave thorough
it takes place on this kind
of tube thing
it is a three dimensional game but it
was done in vector
the original was
and so this surface
is sometimes a tube sometimes
it's planar
but you can basically move
this little claw shaped spaceship
named blaster
um around the play field
from segment to segment
um it was also
one of the first games that used atari's
color quadra scan vector
display and
you also got to choose your starting
level and it was called the skill step
that atari called it
um you also uh
could increase your maximum starting level
depending on your performance
in the previous game so you could keep
continuing from there and it was
so it was one of the first video games
that had progressive level design
um as far as the
way that the game the object of the game
you just basically have to survive as long as
possible and score as many points as
possible by cleaning off the screen
which is harder than it sounds oh my
god tempest is a whore
because you pay for it
you fucking pay for it
okay
anyway you get
who's tempest why are you calling her
such horrible things on this program dark
sagra tempest is a 50 year old drag
queen
sorry not sorry
um anyway um the players
ship uh gets to shoot
rapid fire shots down the screen
and little enemies are trying to come
up that segment that you happen to be
on you also get a thing called a
super zapper and
it destroys all the enemies on the field
um enemies will also
um have different
kinds of behaviors like one of them will leave
a spike as they travel up the
the little section um
and so when you're moving on to the next
play field the spike can impale you
impale
they also can go up to
the top of the screen and try to
capture your
little blaster ship
um and then when you
destroy all the enemies on the play field
you get warped to the next level
and so that's pretty much
tempest it has 16 screens
with different shapes on them
some like I said are closed
um and some of them are open fields
that have you know real end points
um
and each of them has a different color scheme
based on difficulty level
including invisible
which are for level 65
to 80 okay people actually
saw level 65 cause I never
I knew that there were like red
fields but like I never
saw anything but blue
stage wait I think maybe like one
time on a port of this game
maybe for like Commodore 64
I think I saw red which is
like the next highest up you see red when I play that
game
I just like playing this in the arcade
cause you have the little nub that you
would turn back and forth and you could just spin it
it felt like you liked playing
with the nub yeah I like playing with the nub
once in a while okay the nub like you played with
once in a while okay
anyway um
the game was supposed to be
in concept
a 3D remake of Space Invaders
but it had different
problems so
really cause it looks nothing like it
yeah so the um
the creator though said that
he got the design from a dream
where monsters were crawling out of a hole in the ground
so the game started off as
aliens to vortex and finally
it was Tempest and
there were different um
uh cases different
um cabinets for it
um there was the upright one
um there was also
uh a shorter
cabaret style cabinet
that um
it was a little
I don't think that they made as many of them
and then there was a cocktail style
that allowed uh two players
to play at opposite ends
um but the screen would
flip of course vertically for each of
the players not that it really mattered in this game
yeah
if the screen didn't flip oh well
except maybe left and right would kinda be
screwed up and that that would make your nub
turning a lot less fun
well Jeff Minter
um came later and created two
authorized sequels one of them was
Tempest 2000 which I have done his classic
game because it's awesome years ago
it was like one of the first classic games like years
ago yeah and um it
came out for the Atari Jaguar and
um the Playstation version was called
Tempest X3 was there anything else worth
owning on the Jaguar
what was it
besides Tempest 2000 wasn't it
like an Astol game no it was like an aliens
and predator game or something no I thought that there was
another like little 2D platformer that came
out on it was it it wasn't Astol
it was okay but seriously Tempest 2000
was the game was it Ristar maybe maybe
I don't know okay um
and then um there was Tempest 3000
uh for the new on DVD players
and then um Minter
did two more games that were inspired
by Tempest Space
Giraffe in 2007
and TXK which came out on the
Playstation Vita which
has been getting a lot of play in my house
now that I have a Playstation TV
that and Ultra Despair Girls
so um
it's had different ports it was the Atari
2600 and 5200 versions
um well
those were prototypes I actually do have
the 5200 prototype
and it's pretty pretty awesome
we play it with the trackball
um and then
um there was an Atari
Greatest Hits version
um there was also
Superior Software for the BBC Micro
and Acorn Electron
and one by
Electric Dreams for the ZX Spectrum
and Amstrad CPC
there's also been Windows versions
and different versions of the Playstation
Saturn, Super Nintendo
all kinds of different versions on it
so basically you can find
Tempest anywhere but play TXK
because it's really good and
Sony was kind of being dickish about
um wanting to sue the guy
I don't think that was Sony dear
Not Sony Atari
yeah whatever and Tempest
was actually featured in a Rush video
subdivisions
get out that's awesome
and as we know Rush is Canada's best export
that just made like an awesome game like
1.5 times as awesome
right? so that's your game
Tempest play it
right now play TXK
on all the things TXK
there it is your classic game of the week
Tempest originally in the arcade
but ported to
everything in the 1980's
everything
it's very great to have
Jamie on the show thanks to Radio Magic
so we'll see her back next week
for whatever next week's classic
game of the week might be meanwhile
we had a birthday this past week
actually just a couple
days ago which we just passed
Nine and Nine which not
only was the day for what
a new Lady Gaga single
and a Bastille album I think came out on that day
no way!
but it was also Dreamcast day
Nine Nine 99
was the big day the Dreamcast came out
in the US anyway
so a happy belated birthday to the Dreamcast
that would be 17 years ago
any Dreamcast memories from you Gabe?
I feel like we get into
Dreamcast memories every year around this time
but what about you Gabe?
I'll be honest I only
play the Dreamcast a little bit
this is probably
not the game people would expect
but Soul Calibur
when I played Soul Calibur the first time
and I heard the orchestrated music
I fell in love with that I was like oh my god
how is this playing such gorgeous
because that was N64 I was playing
Nintendo 64 and I was still so
used to music made in MIDI
and then to hear
fight music being played with
actual full CD orchestrated sound
I was like what is this?
I lost my mind
and then Virtua Fighter 2
or even 3
between those two games
there was an import game on the Dreamcast
that was partially inspired for Kinship
but I...
Border Down is what it's called but it never came to the states
it was for the Dreamcast called Border Down
thank god if someone has that game
for me the big one is going to forever and always be
Phantasy Star Online that just
blew my mind to have that type of experience
on consoles
we were kind of introduced to
the MMO experience a little bit
on PC with Ultima Online and so forth
but just to have that on
which some argue if
PSO was really an MMO or not
but at the end of the day the point is
that it was definitely something
a game that you could just
drop in at any time with other people
and experience together
it was so different for the time
that's why I had to have a Dreamcast
big social experiment and then
that game I cannot believe I forgot about
that game so yeah
my back to the PSO fans but yeah
that was a wonderful game
for it's time absolutely
you know we mentioned the Dreamcast
anniversary on our social media pages earlier
this week of course you can always follow us on
Facebook over at
facebook.com slash orange lounge radio
but you can also follow us on Google Plus
google.com slash plus orange lounge
radio and actually over on
Google Plus Act Def did mention this week
I still own one but I don't know if it
still works but I do have fond memories
of it and the games it has I
remember completing Crazy Taxi
haha yeah
of course like just a mainstay
game the first game I got for it
it took me a lot to do it but I managed
to I also remember playing
lots of fighting games with friends
lots of fun yeah wasn't
Capcom SNK 2 on Dreamcast
yes it was so fucking good god what a
great game seriously
wonderful over on
Facebook Ragenator
I think this says that I never bought a
Dreamcast something that I regret
to this day I do however have the
Dreamcast collection Nights into
Dreams Jet Set Radio all that stuff
on Steam I wish there
was more retro Sega stuff on
Steam like Mr. Bones and the Panzer
Dragoon games I've always wanted to play
those Hunter R
said I went through two different Dreamcast
consoles after dropping my original
Ray console thereby ruining the DVD
drive on the console I got the black
Sega Sports edition of the Dreamcast
remember they used to make
there was a Hello Kitty Dreamcast at one point
oh don't tell that to Brianna
Bri there's a Hello Kitty Dreamcast
out there it's probably on eBay
go quick
oh she's all about that
no it was awesome I remember I saw that
in like Japantown in LA once or something
and I was like it's cute
did that whole thing
it was awesome
long nights playing
Power Stone that was Loki's game right
Power Stone yeah Power Stone is pretty awesome
man I wish that's something that would come back
and Tony Hawk's Pro Skater
of course
good memories it's just
it's hard to kind of pinpoint
like you know we have all these fond
memories of the Dreamcast yet it sure doesn't seem like
it lasted very long you know it did not and it's
unfortunate because I think that was a
console way ahead of itself yeah and
and what I think it fell
it just it fell during this
massive transition because it came
out
because it was in between like the N64 and the
PS2 at that point I think
when the PS2 was coming out and
and yeah and because of the
impact the first Playstation
made on everybody yeah I think it was
too little too late for Sega which is very very
unfortunate Bob C in our chat
says Tekken was never on Dreamcast
but didn't they have that tricky like was it
okay speaking of like software yeah there's Blingcast
right where you could you actually
did put Tekken it was this weird thing and
like you know we were joking about the Windows phone and the emulators
earlier but it's like a lot of that stuff was going on
on Dreamcast with the Blingcast
and then like one reason I got a Dreamcast
when it was only like 40 bucks I mean obviously
there was PSO and all that stuff you could just like
burn a disc with a Nintendo emulator on Dreamcast
and it worked for the most part
that's so weird that a Dreamcast
is capable of playing Playstation
1 games oh but a Playstation
4 alright I'm sorry here we go
simmer down
Jesus
and you see Bree freaked out we told her she's like
show me
see she's freaking out already but yeah
yeah you right about
yeah you mentioned yeah not Tekken
but yeah that's why I said Soul Calibur nevermind
alright nevermind I'm just drifting away
alright that's why the chatters are here
live to set us straight yeah
gosh it's like it's that it's that instant
feedback be careful what you wish for
when you want feedback you get instant feedback
thank you chatters I love you
very much
alright let's do some rapid fire news
Loki alright
so
Bloodstained that awesome
Castlevania
Igarashi game it's been
delayed
you're gonna have to wait until 2018
to play it what a fucking shock
I'm gonna die from that surprise
and I backed the game I did I did too
I backed a huge I was a huge backer
well it looks like it would be Mighty No. 10
alright you know what you know what
I've demo already plays
better than Mighty No. 9 I'm just half kidding
if it's good
let it simmer oh definitely
let it cook take your time
make sure there's an internal temperature of 160
degrees or higher
it's safe to consume based it well
I'm fine we're waiting a little longer
it's fine definitely
Oculus had this
animated 3D like viewing
experience called Henry
and they won
they won an Emmy for it
no kidding
so that's pretty awesome
best original interactive
program
nice congratulations
breaking news do you know who else won an Emmy today
RuPaul won the
Emmy for best reality TV show
host that's fantastic work
so excited
cover girl
now the question is did Stranger Things
win any Emmys
I don't think it was nominated because I think it's too
early I think it came out too
after the like cut off or whatever
I think it'll be next year when it's eligible
yeah so how about
it could get Globes though I suppose
how about Kimmy Schmidt
I don't know if it was nominated I feel like Titus
had to get nominated again I think so yeah
but I don't know
I don't follow the Emmys that closely you know why
cause I do a show on Sunday nights
that keeps me from watching all that other crap
rock on fight the machine
alright moving on
to other rapid fire stories
Brie pay attention it's Hello Kitty
Hello Kitty is coming to
Animal Crossing New Leaf what
yeah that's right
Hello Kitty well
simmer your expectations
in Japan anyway
so the Hello Kitty characters will
be on themed items that are coming to the game
there's furniture that's gonna be
unlocked using Sanrio amiibo
cards going on sale
in Japan November 3rd
I kinda have to fucking have them like I just do
yeah she doesn't need a reason not
she doesn't need a reason to go to Japan
I just that's gonna be a reason for her to go back to Japan
okay now she's gonna go to Japan to get some
fucking cards that's pretty that's hard
more hardcore than me that's her homeland anyway
I just bat my
eyelashes if my dear friend Akuma
will help me out or I think I think Amazon Japan
did that thing a while ago where now they will
ship over here directly
Japan and China
you know you don't have to worry about that as much
anymore
anyway there was a
I guess Animal Crossing Nintendo
Direct that has a little bit more on this so that's
pretty cool
also
PlayStation 4 Arcade
Archives is growing you know these games
don't get featured a lot but essentially
arcade ports of classic
games such as Gradius 2
I think was one I did a live stream of not that
long ago you know there's actually a
growing library of really kinda like
under the I mean cause none
of the games out I can think of off the top of my head
anywhere like huge releases but
a lot of like really kinda like under the radar
stuff well some of these
releases are gonna get pretty big because
one of the games that's actually coming out for
PlayStation 4 very soon I guess
Bubble Bobble's coming out soon if it's not already
oh I used to love that game
yes that's that's
that might already be out
and I missed it I have to go back and look
The Legend of Kage was
in that list as well but this is huge
Haunted Castle
is coming now you
might not know that from the name
that is the arcade version of Castlevania
so
when you see Haunted Castle on
PlayStation 4 that's fucking Castlevania
on the PlayStation 4
that's gonna be pretty awesome that's also
gonna join some other releases
Thunder Cross, Terra Force,
Ark Area, Mutant Knight
you know again not a bunch of like
you know huge titles in name
so could we possibly get
like a Silent Hill game called like
Misty Spooky Town or something like that
you know it's
basically like the arcade version of
Silent Hill
Kaijuto in chat over at live.vognetwork.com asks
I love Bubble Bobble but do we really
spawn on PlayStation 4? As long
as the boss will spawn on level 30?
Yes. Oh snap
That was a long time ago on the end
I feel like I need one of those flowcharts
Do we need
Do we need Bubble Bobble on this
console? Next thing
Does the boss spawn on level 30?
No. If the answer is no
No we don't. Yes
Of course we do
I need a Lego one of those levels
Alright let's
travel around the world and check out some
release dates of some games coming out in a country
near you starting with the US
Alright so we're getting a little bit busier
So we've got Bioshock Collection coming out this week
on PC, PlayStation 4, Xbox One
Remember PC? You don't have to really buy it
if you already own it so it's all good
free upgrade
Dead Rising coming out on
PC, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
that's the remastered version of that
also coming out as well, PlayStation 4
and Xbox One and the Dead Rising
Triple Pack coming out on PlayStation 4
and Xbox One which makes me wonder why
isn't the
Dead Rising off the record
not by itself?
I thought that was the second one that was in there
No, off the record was the
it was the expansion of 2
Right, that's what
It wasn't a standalone though
Off the record was the alternate
Dead Rising 2 where you play
instead of
It was an alternate? I thought it was an expansion
No, it was an alternate because Dead Rising 2
you played a different dude
Right, but off the record
showed what happened to Frank
after part one
No, because the whole premise was like, here's how I would have done it
and that's basically the game
Interesting, okay
But yeah, those will be coming out this week
My Q, Labyrinth of Death
on Vita, Mystery Chronicle
One Way Heroics on PC
NASCAR Heat Evolution
on PC, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
NHL 17
on PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
Packet Man Championship Edition 2
on PC, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
and holy shit
it's a Konami game!
Pro Evolution Soccer 2017
PC, PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4
Xbox 360 and Xbox One
Psycho Pass
Mandatory Happiness
on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation Vita
mandatory happiness
that's what I want on this show
that's what I want from Loki
mandatory happiness
I feel like there should be an episode of OLR
where Loki has to
it's mandatory happiness for Loki
and we're just gonna throw fuckin' everything at him
every Apple story I've got, every Nintendo story I've got
and he has to be positive
we have to call it Happy Loki
he has to say something nice
for 15 minutes
I'm gonna do it when his kid's here
I can do it for the whole show
yeah, we can speak to him
we need to do that
okay, anyways
they're all yelling at me in chat to do it on episode 666
that would be evil
and then, let's see
we've got ReCore coming out this week
on Windows 10 and Xbox One
exclusive
Rive on PC and PlayStation 4
The Witness on Xbox One
Avadon 3
The Warborn on PC and Mac
and Conga Master
on PC
Persona 5, PlayStation 3
and PlayStation 4
just a small little game
just a small little underground title
this is kind of a cool title
Diaries of a Spaceport Janitor
I'm wondering if that's like that Visceral Cleanup
game or whatever
that's gonna be coming out on PC
Dragon Quest 7
of the Forgotten Past on 3DS
Christ, this is a big week
and finally, that's it
I want that fucking Dragon Quest game too
and I kinda want Persona
oh my god, it's a busy week
alright, let's go over to Japan
it's a busy week there too in Japan
the Bioshock Collection makes its way to Japan
the new PlayStation 4
little Slim version is out in Japan
this week on the 15th as well
and Persona 5 in a regular
20th anniversary edition and accessories set
all of that hits Japan as well on the 15th
so yeah, very busy
week in Japan, World Soccer winning 11
as well in Japan this week
so it looks like Japan kinda mirrors us a little bit this week
on the PlayStation 4
sadly, the only release on the Wii U this week
is Terraria, but you know things on the Wii U
are kinda dying down a little bit
on the PlayStation Vita
which basic question, they haven't gotten Terraria yet?
not in a retail release
that whole thing, yeah
PlayStation Vita
taken over there with Hightaka no Psychedelica
comes out in a limited edition in Japan this week
and Yunohana Spring, Cherishing Time
also out in Japan this week
lastly on the 3DS this week
there's a brand new 2DS
in both Lavender and Pink
and Red and Blue
there's lots of new 2DS colors out this week
but you can also get a price reduction
on Zelda no Densetsu
Toki no Ocarina 3D
which of course is the Ocarina of Time 3D
in Japan with a price reduction there
and
Cho Sentochu Kyokyu no Shinobu
to battle player Choju Kesenn
comes out this week
Battle for Money
is what that translates to
loosely there
so that is out on the 3DS this week
so that's what's in Japan
with Dark Soccer being absent
from the show for a little while
Loki's gonna step in and
take a trip over to Europe for us
with the UK dates
I guess I will
I guess I will if you're making me
so in the UK
let's see what we got coming out
XCOM 2
on Playstation 4 and
Xbox One
Police Tactics Empyro
on PC
and let's see
that was the 7th so that was last week
this week ReCore on
PC and Xbox One
Pro Evolution also coming out over there
as well on Xbox 360
Playstation 3, Playstation 4
Xbox One and PC
Bioshock the collection
on PC, Playstation 4
and Xbox One
and that's it
Now the chatters
are actually saying, there's a couple of people in chat saying this
that Persona 5 is actually not
out here in the
states this week Loki, your list may be wrong
because apparently it's out in Japan
this week, that part was correct but it was actually
delayed for the rest of the world until
February, several people saying that in chat
are you telling me that Wikipedia is incorrect?
I don't believe you
because even I'm looking at another Wikipedia
page that says that it's
out worldwide on Valentine's Day
it will be out multiple weeks if it has to
ok?
and listen, I am like a weatherman
I'm telling you what the weather is going to be like
and then it will be like something it decides
you know what, it probably still made your list
because there's that many people that are planning on
recording it this week over on this side
honestly, but
just want to clarify that
it will be out in a secret location that you have no access to
it's still coming out though
that list is 100%
accurate
let's get to our emails
every week you guys email us
participate at orangeloungeradio.com
and we read some of our favorite
emails here on the show and respond
to them if appropriate
is this appropriate?
for these emails?
or do you not know yet?
yes, well I've just given them the
once over
meaning I open them up to make sure they didn't say
fuck you, you fucking fuck
but that could have been from Loki though
or I had to make sure
it wasn't something that said buy Viagra
cheap
we need to talk about that
Viagra has a sponsor, FOLR
no!
hi
but we do have some fabulous emails from listeners
this week starting with Andy R
who starts us off this week saying
I'm sure you're already sick of talking about it this
late in the podcast but after replying to the
Facebook post I was musing more about the
PlayStation 4 Pro and felt like
emailing with some more thoughts
mainly because I was watching a video gamer
Eurogamer put up
a video that Eurogamer put up about the event
one guy talking had been to the event and the
other, like most of us, only saw what was streamed
the guy who only saw the stream was very much
in line with the internet consensus, namely
the I don't see the point or I don't see a huge
change sentiment that is going around
interestingly though, the guy
who had been at the event seemed fairly impressed
with what Sony had managed to coax out of a
$400 box
which got me to thinking, this reminds me a lot
of VR, in general it seems like the
people I talk to about VR tend to fall into
two camps, ones who have tried it and
think it is cool or ones that haven't tried it
and don't see what the hubble is about
in the case of PS4 Pro, watching
footage of a 4K HDR game on
a stream probably doesn't do
justice, much like not having
actually tried a VR headset
I know I personally streamed the PS4
P meeting to on my phone
over a cell signal which clearly
wouldn't hold a candle to the kind of TVs the
Pro is designed for, like VR
Sony has probably got an uphill
battle convincing people that this is the thing
they need, especially since this one
requires not only the box itself
but a TV capable of really taking
advantage of the box, maybe they're banking
on people who don't have the TV yet
future proofing and just going for the Pro
anyway, at least we've seen the
PlayStation 4's will fly off the shelves at
$399 in the past, so getting it to that price
point was a smart move, anyway
just a few thoughts for the conversation, this
holiday is going to be pretty interesting I imagine
that email again from Andiar
that is a very good point
I really like the comparison
about that VR
can be a hard sell until you've tried it
so considering that very few
of us probably watched the PlayStation
Pro thing on a
4K TV, maybe
we are not really seeing the message
whereas the people that were there
well I'm sure Sony had 4K projection
in that room taken care of, so people
were very happy with what they saw I'm sure
so very interesting perspective
although that being said
that fantastic
demo that they had of
Horizon Zero Dawn
or whatever that is
looked awesome
Shadow of the Colossus
awesome, it did look awesome
so this tells me that Sony now needs to
get PlayStation 4 Pros
running on 4K TVs in every Best Buy
around the nation, because that's really the best way
all I need to hear is, hey Grand Theft Auto 5
is going to be one of those supported
higher resolution games
would that really do it for you?
what about The Last of Us
I haven't played The Last of Us
because they're doing it with The Last of Us, they're adding
4K textures for The Last of Us
because why not
see for me, but Mass Effect, you know
that's kind of my version of Loki's Grand Theft Auto
you know, that, seeing that
as part of it does kind of make me go
maybe I do need a Pro, maybe I do need
to future proof, but maybe I am
a little worried that by the time I get a 4K TV
Sony will have another console
in three years, that's where I'm starting
to worry, that sounds like it, because if
it's a ten year cycle is what it's supposed to be
you've already, we're not even
halfway there and you're giving me a new console
you're giving me an upgraded console, so
speaking of Grand Theft Auto 5
uh huh
so how much Grand Theft Auto 5 have you?
to be fair, not a lot, it's one of those
things that I think about playing it and then
ooh, shiny, I get distracted by something else
you know how it goes, I do
alright, one more email this week
from Dark Tetsuya, who says
hey OLR, I thought I'd write you guys about a neat
new indie film that came out while you guys
were on break, it's called The Outrunners
so basically the plot is our hero
Eli was visiting the arcade with his friend
one day and got to talking to a girl
but the resident bully and his gang caught wind of it
and challenged him to a high stakes race in
Sega's The Outrunners, winner stays
loser leaves the arcade for good
it's a pretty neat film if you enjoy
classic arcades and the racing games
they had back in the 90's, because this sounds
like a plot out of the 90's to be quite honest
but um, there's
even some subtle nods to anime like
Initial D, like they actually
used some of the music in the end racing scenes
and Eli's car is the same car that
the star of the Initial D drives
the director told me on Facebook that
Initial D was one of his favorite anime
the film is available for free on YouTube
and be sure to check them out on Facebook as well
the gaming blogs haven't really said
a lot about this, but I thought if I sent you guys
an email, I could get more people to check
this out, uh, you're right
the dozens and dozens of people that listen to OLR
will hopefully check this out
so thank you for the heads up there
that is again called The Outrunners
well hey, I like old Sega 90 game
let me ask this, since it is an ode to
90's racing game classics
will we get to hear in this movie the
doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
like is that what plays
as the 20th Century Fox logo
comes, well I guess not, because it's not a 20th Century Fox movie
but you know, that's what you expect
right?
Daytona
hell yeah, heck yeah
anyway, that would be a fantastic
game for the remake
seriously
hell yeah
alright, there it is, your emails
participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
if you want to send us an email
for consideration in a future week
alright, remake Daytona
they did on the 360
and it was gorgeous
it wasn't remade
because 4k is where it's at
720p
special thanks
it was no, those are just the HD versions
of like the Dreamcast games
or whatever they had, or Saturn games
no, but they like redid that from the ground up
and they added a couple new things too
it was great game, if you want the HD
remake, play the 360 version
it was good, that's the best I can give you
I can't give you much else, so can't please you
clearly, so it's all good
alright, s2100matt posting a link there
in our chatroom by the way
some folks I'm sure will be watching that
after the show
or is Loki trying to watch it during the show
I thought that's what Gabe was
peering over and looking out of there
no, I'm looking in the chatroom, someone said
would a new EDF in 4k
there would be no frame rate
those games are so horribly optimized
it would just be like
it's just like nothing, in fact
at the very least, Playstation 4 Pro
would maybe bring it up to like
20 frames per second, I mean
the 4.1
it was way better than
the PS3 version
because the PS3 version in 2025
was terrible, so that had frame
rate issues from the 20
I like 2025 part
of the way, it's just
I don't know, it's not
the same
it was its own thing I guess
but it was nice to have the co-op
and stuff, I just haven't played co-op
alright, let's get back into some other
gaming news, Loki, that's fine
we're such nerds
anyways, so
speaking of
every
Playstation 4, this is kind of
a neat little thing to throw in there
you don't have to buy a new system to get
that wonderful HDR, so be able
to support the wider range
of color and everything
the pictures will kind of pop more
that's coming in a free update
if you already have a Playstation 4, you can enjoy
that right away, assuming
they have a TV new enough to actually take advantage
of that, which I don't
again, we face
this technical
issue, and I almost begin to
wonder if
that's the mentality
with these bigger game companies
honestly though, it's been a long time since I had a
TV, I got this TV, actually thankfully
it was a promo thing from Sony
ironically enough, it's a Sony
HDTV, but they gave that
to all of the employees
of the company I worked for, and so I had a nice
new HDTV from that, and at the time it was
cutting edge, but
now it's pretty old
so I mean, I could use a new
TV, it's just
you're justifying buying a new one
my concern is again,
is a
new console no longer enough
do we have to have
you gotta have a very powerful TV
and here's what we can provide too, because
now you're costing me
not just four or five hundred dollars
to enjoy a new gaming experience
now I gotta pay a grand
essentially, you know
and on top of that, like why should I be dropping
money on a new TV and a new
system and VR and all this stuff
for Sony, when
you know, they can't even get
like mod support working and stuff
something that was promised to people like a long time ago
well that's ultimately my point, because
invest in a PC instead, I mean
well even the original PS4 was supposed to do
4K, and
that just
disappeared into the
nothing. The menus are 4K
That's it. Right?
And again, that's a whole other thing
I appreciate the fact that these newer consoles
and I said this earlier, okay fine
you're gonna be able to display
show off 4K and things like that
but I can't wait to see how few
developers actually utilize that
that's gonna be the best part, so anyway
I digress
So, I mean
if my TV doesn't really support
this thing, then this patch does nothing for me
or will I get to see some subtle differences
or what? No. Brighter blues
brighter blues and reds
that's about it. Because I bought my, like my TV
is pretty fucking nice I think, it's a
2014 model apparently
and so it doesn't have this. Maybe it supports it.
I looked on the Amazon thing, because I actually went back
and looked at the TV I bought on Amazon
which, just an interesting
side story, I was gonna buy the TV
at Sears, and it was on the display
for it and everything, and then they told me, like, we don't have it
like, they didn't
they wanted me to go to another Sears
on the other end of town, and I was like
okay, I'll head over there now. I'm sorry, but the TV you're looking for
is at another Sears. Yeah, it's in another castle
right? So I just
I came home and I bought it on Amazon, like
anybody else would have done it
Why are department stores dying?
Or just go to Best Buy and have them
price match Amazon. Uh, yeah
I guess I could have done it, but anyway, it doesn't matter, because I got a fucking TV
like two years ago, no, last year
and it's a two year old model, but apparently, yeah, it doesn't do
but it does do 3D
Blu-rays and all that stuff
Oh, goody goody. I have, like, two movies
I can watch in 3D
Tron's one of them, so
Do you have the glasses for it? I do, but
fuck if they ever seem to work
I tried to use them on the ongoing, I was like
these don't even really work
And that's what I mean right there
like, that's what I mean, you know, the other thing
that made me push so hard on 3D
Yeah, right? Look how well that worked out
Boy oh boy
Anyhow, um, well I still
you know, I'm excited for the update to see if
it'll do anything for me, but
God, again, my TV is not that old
and it doesn't support any of this
Well, the 4K support ends are pretty nice, I mean, just even watching the little demos
walking through Best Buy and stuff like that, it's like
damn, that's a nice clear picture
but it's just like, damn, is that gonna be the
same nice clear picture when I stream it through Netflix
on this crappy boxy they have? Nope
I'm gonna need like, you know, a nicer
new platform to be able to stream in 4K
and a nicer new internet provider
that's gonna be able to handle that
bandwidth, but not Comcast
Alright, well another big birthday
that happened this week was the 50th anniversary
of Star Trek
and how appropriate that just this past week
Star Trek Online
has come out for consoles
what, came out, what is it
like January 2012
when free to play, I think it had actually been out
as a pay game maybe a year or two before that
and then it was free to play in 2012
well now it is out on PlayStation 4
and Xbox One
so it took a little while for it to come out
but what a good way to get an older
MMO some new attention
than by being right there for download
on the consoles
DC Universe Online
kind of did this same type of thing a while ago
as well, so anyhow
Star Trek Online is now available
and I think the audience over there
seems to be growing a little bit, probably
these console releases are helping
so now might be a good time to check that out
so, what's cool is that they actually have some of the
cast from the movies, it's like voice over
oh really, oh that's awesome
that's pretty cool, I wanna say
I may be wrong, I don't wanna step out of line
but I wanna say they were able to get Leonard Nimoy
in the game before he had passed
well cause again this game's been out
since 2010, so I wanna say
he was in it, and they had at one point
Zachary Kinto was in it too
because he was Spock
in the new movies, I think he was in the game when it
first came out as well, so
uh yeah, Kaijuto in chat says did they
make the game better cause on PC
it blows, and Fifth Dream confirms yes
Nimoy is in the intro in the first five
minutes, so that's pretty cool
it might be worth checking out all on its own
I'm curious if uh
any of our friends from Starboard Power Coupling
uh check that out on consoles cause I know some
of them play Star Trek Online, I don't know if they
went and checked it out on consoles though
so uh let's move on, Loki
so uh this is kinda cool
there was a slight tease or a positive
leaked tease that Earth Defense
Force 5 might be a thing
um apparently this was coming
from um a count, they had a countdown
teaser actually on
the D3 publisher site, and I wanna say that this
also leaked out from like another publication
that it was out there
um so
yeah, it'd be
interesting to check it out
the moon
hell yeah, EDF 5 baby
oh boy
you gonna pick this one up when it comes to Earth?
of course you are
alright it sounds like you and Gabe will have
something to play together cause Gabe's definitely
a fan as well
nothing, that game
just warms my soul
so much destruction
so goddamn hard
alright we are gonna open up the
pipeline to you guys, Orange Lounge Radio
all one word on Skype, if you wanna give us a call
and talk about anything that we've talked about
tonight, maybe you wanna ask Gabe a question
or uh anything else that might
be on your mind, you can go ahead and give us a call
Orange Lounge Radio, all one word on Skype
um while we wait for some calls to come in
um Gabe let me ask you about this
uh locally with Sacramento
and development and all that, I know we had talked about
earlier in the show, we mentioned that Sacramento
can be seen by those in other areas
it's kinda like, you know
not as lucrative of an area
or whatever, which seems a little silly to me
cause it seems like, you know, we're growing a little bit
with our, even our triple A game development
right, which um, you know
I forget what they were called back in the day, what, Click Play
or Click and Play or something, Click Nation
that's it, they grew into now Capital Games
EA Capital Games, which
uh I believe based on one of the trailers
they showed recently, they're doing work with the
Star Wars mobile development, right, yes they are
yes they are, so that's pretty cool, do we know of any
other like big big studios that are establishing
a presence here locally? Um, I know
so on the indie side
um, on the indie side you've got Skirmish
who just recently got a little office
uh, so I think somewhere
in Rancho or Sacramento, something like that
I wanna, yeah, somewhere nearby for here
I think, um, I know the other big one
Fifth Planet Games, they're up in Rockland
they were in Roseville, they moved up
to Rockland, um, they've uh
they've trimmed down a little bit on the size
of their studio, but they're
still a pretty significant size studio, Fifth Planet
Games, and big shout out to
Rob, um, you know, Rob Winkler
he was one of our speakers for the
first indie arcade, um, but yeah
Fifth Planet is definitely one of the other
well known studios
so with their, um, oh my goodness
I can't even think of their freaking game name right now
but yeah, you can find them on Newgrounds and so on and so forth
but, yeah, so there's a few
but we definitely need
more, I wish we connected with EA
because, you know,
that would have been great to establish
something with them more, but we'll see
alright, we'll see, well in the meantime let's get
to the phones because they are ringing, hi you're on Orange
Launch Radio, who's this?
Hey what's up guys, this is Kaijuto
Hey Kaijuto, what's on your mind buddy?
I got some game recommendations for you
First off, I just want to say that
I've been playing the
Rumble, what is it, Rumble in
the Rocket League
that thing is great, I don't know if you guys tried that
I haven't, I've heard about, God, the
Rocket League, they have really done a great job
Just continuing moving that game forward
ever since its original release, I need to check
that out
There is some trouble in paradise with that game
because now the fans
are pissed off because they decided to go
with the whole
you got unlockables, but you have a
crate that you have to open and you have to buy
keys to open that crate
Oh, pissed off
because they're claiming that they need the money
because they want to make it into an esport
but fans are not buying that
They're like pissed off
There's some real Rocket League hate going on right now
A lot of fans got that free
from Playstation Plus
but then again, Playstation Plus not really free
so, alright
Nothing ever is
My game recommendations
going to the Star Trek, the 50th
anniversary thing
I found this game, I think it just came out a couple
of days ago, it's called
Halcyon 6
and that game
is so much fun, it's fantastic
You got to think of
that game that came out for the
tablet, Trexels
remember that game?
It was like a
remake of some other game, Pixels
or some crap
Think of that game as
Trexels, but a lot better, it has a story
there's humor in there
there's base building, if you're the type of person
you're all into that base building that they did
with XCOM and that type of stuff
they have that in there, they have away missions
you can send your away team out there to have
battles, for all you Final Fantasy
fans, it has the whole
type of turn-based system that
Final Fantasy kind of invented
where you have your three party
members and then you fight either
three monsters or two monsters
they have that in there, it's all turn-based
it's a lot of fun, it's 2D, it's not
3D, but
there aren't any type of platforming
that type of crap, you don't have to run and jump on
stuff, you're basically
trying to battle
Is it space sci-fi, which is why you're tying this to
Star Trek?
No, it's basically a Star Trek, because you have
your science officer, you have your captain
your communications officer, they have the
different colored suits
you have spaceships that you're flying
it's Star Trek
Alright, I gotcha
that's a good recommendation
This is on Steam by the way
and the second game is a matter of murder
which I think is like
$2.99, really affordable game
and if you love the game Clue
you're gonna love this game because
it's basically Clue
it has endless replayability because
every time you play you can generate a new
mystery, and it plays
just like Clue, they have the mansion
you gotta investigate, you gotta find
the weapon, find the suspect, find the motive
and then when you think you have
all that together
then you go into the accusation phase and then you have
all the characters, they all come together in one room
and then you have to
retell what happened, like who committed
the murder and why and all that stuff and if you got it
right, then you get rewarded for it
it's a really fun game, it has some
really shitty art
but it makes it funny
it looks like a three year old
kid drew the game, but that's part of the trauma
I love it
and the thing with the body
it's hilarious because they don't show
the entire body, you just see
the feet
the tasteful dead person
just the legs sticking out from under the carpet
yeah, yeah
and the game makes fun of itself because when you do the
tutorial
I guess it's the maid or something
she's like, what are you freaking out about?
it's just a body, that seems to happen a lot in this place
right away
you're gonna be solving multiple murders
just people being killed in that house
so it doesn't have the board game element still
where you roll a die to move around
there's no dice
it's almost like a point and click
you're clicking the characters
you're talking to them
but the writing is done so well
that you actually get involved
they'll tell you stuff
if you ask a guy a question
he's nervously stroking his moustache
to give you little hints that he may be lying
it's a really cool deductive game
because what I found out is when I played the game
I was doing the tutorial
and the guy was like
I was in the pool room with so and so
we were playing pool, so I went to the pool room
and there was a guy in there and he confirmed
his story that his alibi was legit
because they were both playing pool
but then you speak to another guy
and that person's like, yeah, I was playing pool too
and I'm like, no, you weren't playing
it was just these two guys in there
so that's how I knew that they were the murderer
just cool stuff like that
alright, so Matter of Murder
I gotta check that out on Steam, so three bucks
alright, very cool
thanks, the one thing I'm ready to buy
alright, Kaishudo, thanks for the call
alright, later
have a good one, bye
alright
we have the phones ringing, so let's get to another call
hi, you're on Orange Mountain Radio, who's this?
hey guys, it's Jason
what up?
I am currently barreling down the east side of the Rockies
which is why your voice was missed
from the intro this evening
as you're in your car, zooming down a mountain
that is responsibly
responsibly, I am answering both hands around the wheel
I promise, alright, fair enough, fair enough
what's on your mind?
even if my car is magical enough that I technically don't have to
I still do have both hands on the wheel
you guys have brought up a couple of cons
con things and VR things
and so I just kind of wanted to chime in with my two cents
of the last couple of weeks
while you were down at Dragon Con
I was quite literally in the opposite end of the US
at PAX West
oh yes, the other thing that happened over Labor Day
how was it?
the other four days of madness
this was my first West
as many of you know, it's been called Prime
up until this year and now they're calling it West
for consistency
between East, West and South
my first West, my second PAX
I went to PAX South at the start of this year
it was definitely a lot more hectic
but at the same time
a lot bigger
a lot more events
still very social
largely to do with the fact of the
more and more people I'm meeting
in various communities
Twitch spearheaded or not, but a number of those people
are also involved with the games
with the larger gaming community
business wise
so it just kind of steamrolls from there
the show floor
itself was nice and big
very tiring
everybody had their space
you see all the
Twitch and their mammoth
streaming center and partner center
Intel, Blizzard
even
Tiny Build had a
shockingly good presence
considering their up and up over the last couple of years
but a lot of familiar faces
but still a bunch of hidden gems
and the Indie Mega Booth
Mega Box I think it technically is
and then various other locations
tying specifically to the show
there were two things that you guys have touched on
that I wanted to bring up
I don't know exactly who
the individuals are, but with the story
about Interplay going under
and selling off IPs
the founding members
the founding creators
of Descent have already moved on
from Interplay and they were
exhibiting their own game called
Overload in VR
at PAX West
I don't think it was ever really covered on the show
before, but they had a Kickstarter as
one does, they're still offering pre-orders
that count towards stretch goals
but they have very
significant plans
a very great Vive
backed demonstration of
what Overload is
going to do and it is
six degrees of freedom
multiplayer, robot
zero gravity
dogfighting
I unfortunately didn't really feel like queuing up
in the line, but watching it was
absolutely spectacular
and I absolutely am looking forward to another
Descent game as well
yeah, you're not the first one to say that logically
those guys should be the ones that
try to bid for that Descent
IP, whether they have the money to do so or not
we'll see, but
yeah, it would make a lot of sense
that they should probably try to make a play for it
that would be quite a stretch goal
fund our
IP acquisition attempt
well, you never know
there might be a magical publisher out there
who's willing to marry the two together
like will front the money
for this if
that would be
one of the better
stories, like one of the most
monumental stories that I've heard in the last
jeez, decade I guess, I don't know
if you guys
want to look up more information, media
and all that stuff, playoverload.com
plenty
plenty of media there to go up, screenshots
screenshots, a little bit of gameplay video
demonstration of what it does in and out
of VR and then the common
game's gonna have multiplayer and
epic robot battles
and huge boss battles, etc.
VR
more generally
I, prior to PAX West
I had only ever used
Oculus Dead Kit 1
I never, I didn't queue up at
E3 for
VR, I haven't seen HoloLens
and I haven't
bumped anybody nearby to see
their Vive or anything of the sort
up on the sixth floor, which is
where a lot of
indie, both publishers
and developers were exhibiting
there was a little corner for
University of Washington, UW I think
it was, their game development
program, I got
talking to a couple of people because they just had
a free throw
a three point shootout simulator game
and that was my first experience
using the Vive and it was
it was
Loki was talking earlier about how
everything with a big name attached to
is an experience and so it's
kind of less interesting
but this game, like I said
free throw or three point shootout
I'm not quite sure where on the line it was
but it was a basketball simulator running
Vive called Nothing But Net
or Nothing But Net
and
it was, I
hadn't actually really paid attention to the
controllers yet, but to extend those
as your hands and use it for
just simple
ball grabbing, basketball
grabbing, not that other
kind, basketball grabbing
oh my
basketball
grabbing, flick and release and
the world that they created
which was just like a high school
gym, fairly nondescript
but it still felt very good to be in it
it was a very limited
demo, you just had
60 or 90 seconds to
shoot
to make shots
and
but it was fun, it was cute
it reminded me
both of you
possibly all three of you have talked about
video game renaissance and
I have played basketball in real life
I played for a season in elementary
school
basketball has obviously
been a part of American media forever
and I played some basketball
games on and off, it's never been my primary sport
but it was still fun
when talking
to the developers of this Nothing But Net game
I was talking to them about
this very, very basic
arcadey
three point shootout game for DOS
called Three Point Shootout
and to see
the progression of gaming all
over again to take
basic concepts to introduce
developers, players and everybody else
to how these
things actually work out in 3D and finally
being able to put
full body motion
into this kind of thing
it really tickled me in a really
really happy way and that was
definitely one of my
underrated gems of the show
that I just enjoyed
I just kind of hovered around listening to
conversations, I had a great conversation with
the husband and wife
development pair
talked about some of their plans
what they could do, gave them reference
to prior art and plenty of things
the demo was
just a single round of shots, they talked about
a lot of other things like horse
and multiplayer and
MMO-esque simulation
because it is a gem with multiple hoops and maybe
maybe even going on into
like a two on two NBA Jam style
thing maybe
but it was fun, it was simple
it was conventional and it hit all of
the spots to be able to take
a basic
concept and apply it into the VR
world in such a
simple but
excellent way
so it sounds like you had a pretty
successful PAX West
it's no longer PAX Prime
I heard that's
because PAX East is the real PAX Prime at
this point but I won't go there
how were the panels, did you go any panels
any of that stuff? I did zero
panels, I was
incredibly line averse so
the guide book was
a map reference for me and I
just didn't pay attention to any of the panels
which is a little weird
for me I guess, sort of, but I don't know
I was there for the people
I was there for the people and friends first
that I don't get to see in person nearly enough
and in between
that I made my own adventure across
the show floor
very quickly I guess one of my
other underrated ones that I haven't even
been thinking about, talking about
for some stupid reason
if anybody knows the
old Neo Geo game
Windjammers, one of the
multi game, multi game arcade machines
we saw in
mini golf and bowling alleys and all those
kinds of things, that game is
coming back to PC and
PS4 in the form
of a disc jam by people who
also grew up with the game and loved it
and are turning it into
a little
steep down
pong that I break up a little bit
yeah you're breaking up a little bit but you're back now
that sounds
disc jam
already in some gamers hands
PC and PS4
Windjammers-esque with an updated
look and feel and
that was quite a treat to be able
to talk to other fans that
finally did something with the game and moved into it
and yeah
alright, very cool, alright well sounds like you had a
good time, TwitchCon are you doing that
in a few weeks, isn't that the same weekend
as GamerX right I heard?
it is the last, it's like September 30th
into the start of October
same weekend as
GamerX, that's some unfortunate timing
I
am
I should be doing TwitchCon, I am
tentatively doing it, I'm
actually, I wasn't supposed to be heading home
I was supposed to still be along
the Pacific Coast, quite possibly in the
studio
next weekend, but I had
a little home incident occur
so that's why I am currently barreling down
the east side of the Rockies
I hope everything's okay, so
alright, well I'm gonna go ahead and let you go, okay?
Sounds good, have a good night!
Alright, thanks for calling, take care
Alright,
OrangeLoungeRadio, all one word on Skype
Looking quickly, some chat comments
Kajuda says, OMG, Twitch has a con too?
What do they all do, meet up on
Skype and stream? No, I
went last year, actually because of Jason
Jason was like, I have an extra ticket, are you
sure you don't want to go? Because in San Francisco
it would be very easy for you to go, so I was like
sure I'll go, I thought it was interesting
I actually, I left a little
more motivated to do more streaming, which
has been hit and miss, some weeks
I'm able to do a bunch, I probably haven't done
one in a month, just because, you know, I
am doing four podcasts on
and off, so it's kind of like a lot of my creative energy
time goes into that, so
alright, let's try to sneak in at least one more quick call here
before we call it a night, hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hey, this is Akdeft
Hi Akdeft, how are you?
Really great, really great
What's on your mind?
Well, anyways, I want to talk about
the Super Mario
Run announcement
What do you think?
Well, basically, it's
not something that
necessarily
is
well, I had the idea
in my head, and
I kind of
missed my train of thought
but basically
what they're trying to do, or I think
what they're trying to do is basically
like, cross-promotion
of some sort
because they're not
and this is something I was talking
with other friends
they're not offering the full game
right now, it's
even if you see like
Super Mario Run as a full game
it kind of isn't because
it isn't like the full Super Mario
experience
and we can see it like
in stuff like Super Mario Maker or
New Super Mario Bros
and all that stuff
but something that was curious
and this relates also to
Pokmon GO
that the 3DS sales
went up
I think for July, and I don't think
for August, I don't know
but many people
pre-ordered in expectation
of Pokmon Sun and Moon
so I'm
trying to guess
here that basically they
did this
maybe because they want part of the
mobile market, maybe that's something
like
secondary
but I think
they're trying to like
promote their own stuff through
other media
I don't know if that makes sense
You know, that's something that I
this is Gabriel, good to meet you man
this is
something that I was mentioning
earlier with my little
speculation
about the NX
and me getting the
impression that
that's what I think Nintendo's trying to do
I think them releasing
this Mario game
on iOS is a hint
of what's coming for NX
to an extent, that's just my impression
of it, so I
I really just need them to fucking reveal the
NX already, get this fucking time
Tokyo Game Show is in two
weeks, I'm sick of the speculation
all this wank
you know I love that word
all this Twitter wank
granted, we've been no help either
we have the wank and the tinfoil hats on this show
as well, I'm fucking sick of it
it's after labor day
no more white shoes
and a goddamn NX announcement
let's do it
Hey Act, can I ask
that's just
by the word of Rob
can I ask you something really quick because you mentioned
something that I found
very intriguing
as a
mobile, you play games on mobile
I take it
right? Yeah. Okay. Do you
feel that
as a mobile gamer
the price
that you pay
do you feel it's fair to say that
one should still expect
the full game experience
on mobile
or should it really just be
are you really just paying for something
that's going to be a quick
time consuming thing and then we move on
I mean do you fully expect
do you fully expect the full
video game experience on a mobile, should you
expect that on a mobile phone?
I think we
should expect something like that
it's not
it's not necessarily like
exclusive to a console
or in this case to a mobile game
but I think
my point is
because we have seen runners
in consoles
we have the bit trip
runner series
like for example
maybe even Rayman
I don't consider it a runner
but they do have mobile
versions that pretty much are runners
right
but my point was
you don't get the full
experience
as in you only go
right instead of going
left to
you don't have full control over Mario
in this case
where in a console
in even a portable version
of Mario you have full control
of what you can
what Mario does
in the game
so I
I don't see like
Super Mario Run like a bad thing
at all
it seems interesting enough
but yeah
I don't think Nintendo is
putting all the
all their money into the mobile market
at least just yet
and at one point it's exactly
the next part
or point of this
yeah there's got to be a correlation
somehow and there was a comment in the chat
that I just seen when they
I didn't see who it was that mentioned
was the NX going to be running Android
hardware they were going to be using
a processor
chip that
can that fuels Android
but not necessarily
that doesn't necessarily mean you know it's going to be
an Android based thing it's just a processor
I can't remember what it was called
similar parts but not necessarily how they function
right like a Tegra or something like that
it's like a Tegra processor
but for me I think
this is a way for Nintendo to be making money
this holiday season when
the Wii U is not going to be expected to
really do anything I think this is something
Nintendo is under a lot of pressure to do
and I think again that's why you see them
coming up with all these other creative ways to make money
this holiday to keep their investors
happy is oh we have the classic NES
which we know stands to do well oh we have the
Pokemon Go bracelet oh we have
you know the mobile venture
you know we're going to put our biggest thing
on mobile so maybe this is why
they bumped Mario up to this year
was to kind of show that they're
going to still be productive through this holiday
so maybe even if the
NX tanks which you know
I don't want to see that happen I don't think
any gaming fan would want that
although I just want to know what the fuck it is already
I think
you know Nintendo can show that they as a company
could still stay afloat no matter what
definitely so anyway
I'm going to let you go so we can wrap up the show
but thanks for the call and for the insight
hey thanks for having me
alright that's going to do it for the
skype line tonight but if you didn't get through tonight
do consider sending us an email for a future week
participate at orangeloungeradio.com
alright
now before we wrap up the show
and say our good nights we have to make sure
that we get any residual angst
out of our system so that we can successfully
start a new week
nice and fresh and on a clean
slate so we empty
and reset our pallets with a segment we call
here the FUs of the week
music
low key your FUs of the week
I don't know I just have to be
myself for being 10 seconds
too early
music
there's so many jokes
I can make with that but I'm
going to be a nice person
and not make them
alright
10 seconds too early is not a bad thing
well
depends on the end goal
but yes
Gabe do you have any FUs you need to get out of your system
a special thanks you need to give tonight
ah
no not necessarily I let it out
I pretty much let it out earlier
yeah enough I can't really
think of anything right now so just you know
thanks for everything though guys
my FUs of the week goes to
fucking food poisoning
here's the fucking week I had
you ready for this? alright so I get back from
Dragon Con which was awesome no complaints
there so I get back and of course
I get sick from the plane or something
cause Bobby's like I'm not sick and nobody else I know
at Dragon Con was sick so I got something on the plane
at the airport or something so I'm sick
and I'm like out of work
Tuesday and Wednesday I usually take the day after
anyway just as like a
recuperation day when I go to a big con
but I have to take like another day I was like
you know how that kind of looks to your boss was like I need one more
day of vacation cause you know
luckily my boss is pretty understanding she's great
and everything but it's just like when you still feel
like an asshole doing it you know like
the work is piling up and I'm not coming back to do
it yet cause
so I go back to work on
Thursday I go to get lunch
on Thursday and it makes me sick
like stomach sick
I'll spare you the horror story
but it was not a pretty 24 hours
so it's like I couldn't catch a fucking break
last week it's like
it's like boy
are you enjoying that high of all that
motivation and fun times you had
at Dragon Con well let me just punch
you in the stomach literally
so you could just knock that shit off
here's all your happiness in liquid form on
the plane enjoy
so anyway
F you to that
grocery store I will not be buying lunch
from again
that's what I get for getting a fucking salad
that's what I get for getting a fucking
salad meat and potatoes all
the way meat and potatoes for life you know what
I'm just gonna be fat and not have
food poisoning that's how it's gonna be
here on out
alright well that brings us
to the end of another episode of Orange on Trader
actually quickly I should check in with Loki for any
last minute stories I forgot to do that earlier
there's a remastering
of Duke Nukem 3D it's coming out
Duke Nukem World Tour it's gonna have also new levels
awesome
Duke Nukem
I mean it would be what
the fourth time I bought a reimagining
of Duke Nukem but oh well
you can't really remaster the game too much
I mean it's
clearly they can't make a new one so
might as well keep doing what works
alright
well that is going to
bring us to the end of another episode of Orange
Lounge Radio and Gabe I want to thank you
for being here you were a lot of fun tonight
always a pleasure to have you here on the show
same here I'm not here enough seriously
I really love being here
you see we have an empty chair there so we're trying to fill the space
with some more interviews and some other
friendly faces here at OLR so
you know if you stop by anytime
look forward to seeing what IGDA brings
in 2017 I can't believe we're talking
2017 but shit it's
September and before you know it we're gonna be saying the holidays
holidays are here
hell yeah and magfest you gotta try to make that
happen it'll be so much fun if you could go
really gonna try to do that
awesome I try to get more involved with panels and stuff
this year so I should probably pick your ear on how to make that happen
absolutely so awesome
well any final things you want to get out there for our listener
base before we say goodnight?
just for everyone that
showed the support and the feedback
tonight thank you all so much
I cannot implore enough please
try our demo on Newgrounds
the game is coming out so soon
any last minute feedback suggestions
we really need it right now because it's just
one other guy and myself
making this game and
anything anything I've done
all I could to give any last minute
updates to my coder so
he's making it happen so please
give our demo a try if you're on Newgrounds
already leave some
great feedback not saying five star
review but give something
good you know some good feedback we really
really need it right now yeah
because essentially I am the marketing team
I don't have a marketing team
and so this first game is super
super you know for Breeze and Benny Hana
oh my god I want to go back there
yes that that that yes in fact
if any great help
I will take you to Benny Hana
just kidding but he's completely
kidding as much as I love that place and as much as you
probably are awesome but yes please play our demo
it's on Newgrounds.com
just go on Newgrounds.com type in
crumple on the search box and you'll see it
first and foremost please give it a shot and leave
some good feedback and follow us on Twitter let us know what
you think as well because like I said we need
all the help we can get we're not doing a
kickstarter we're doing this flat on
our own and that's the chance
we're taking right now so please we need
your help we need your help getting the word out
best of luck to you with all that keep us
in the loop here at OLR when the game is released
so we can check it out stream it and all that good stuff
and don't forget to let me know about Tuesdays I'd
love to come by yes yes the meeting is swing
by cafe colonial I'm always kind of wondering are they still doing that
thing Tuesday night oh yeah they are they're still
and it's and it's it's they got a
they got a really strong crowd because they got
following they're they're doing Smash Brothers in the back
they do the Smash Brothers tourneys in the back and then
everything else up front so yeah if you're if
you're local nearby cafe colonial
I need to show my face there more often and plug my show
you should seriously come on by
yeah come on by buy my crumple burger
they named the burger after my game so
please does it have paper crumpled up in it
did they put egg in it or something
they do it's a burger with a fried egg
and cheese and lettuce and the whole works on it
lettuce tastes like paper Loki
I know it does
so yeah so stop by
and say hi at the cafe colonial this Tuesday
night I'll probably be there early
like four o'clock to get things rolling on
on Twitch
we have playing through the Xbox one for the
Bioshock collection it's for Extra Life
so please come check us out stop by
say hi and yeah like I said I'm gonna try to beat
Bioshock 1 in one evening
I doubt it but we'll see
some very kind words for you in chat Gabe
Kaijuto saying Gabe should be third Mike until Jamie
comes back well we gotta we gotta share the love
a little bit with some other folks we know and you've got
other things you gotta do but you definitely
should come back and even when Jamie's back
you should still be we will always
make a fourth chair for you and a
fifth chair for Bree if she would like to be here too
definitely that means a lot thank you thank you so much
for that that means a lot thank you
most welcome
Loki my friend that's it we made it
to the end of an episode here it's not
longer episode but a good one uh any
final thoughts for our listeners tonight I'm just tired
now yeah I'm depressed
tired of eBay it'll be okay
well happy birthday though you know what we have some
awesome some listeners were saying we should you know what we
should all put 25 bucks in and help
Loki get the damn DDR machine that's
not the thing that's why it was such a disappointment
because those those cabinets and granted
it was slightly broken I would have needed to
you know fix up some stuff but that's
fine I mean like a new cabinet
goes for over a thousand dollars it's
like yeah that's why it stings so bad
because it's it's like that's
actually more cost effective to do it that way
than it would have been to build pads
I got build pads but now you're reminding
me like oh you know if I you know now
that I'm not upgrading my phone this year
now that it looks like I'm probably not going to get the PlayStation
4 Pro and I may not even get the VR
at this point we'll see I'm kind of on the fence with that
maybe this is the year Rob's finally
going to get his cocktail cabinet because I really I really
kind of want one I was gonna say you practically have the
money for that for a cocktail cabinet now
if you don't get those two things yeah I know you've got the
money for that now only only if
get it on Amazon you can pre-order it and then
part of me is like you should save that money to
do responsible things like home buying
oh come on who needs adulthood we need
cocktail tables come on man
priorities exactly what future you got
a bar top that I built oh
well there you go you're halfway there man I know I
know all right
my final thought tonight I
I can't think of an awful lot I'm just gonna say
I'm gonna I'm gonna try to play
more Overwatch which will make Alan very
happy because Alan plays a fucking ton of
Overwatch I think it's like all he
ever he plays that and then I'll see him play No Man's
Sky a little bit and he's back to playing Overwatch
he plays a lot of fucking Overwatch and he has like
like bro friends he made playing
Overwatch and everything that he
gets on there and he bro chats
about how you know there's a reaper back
behind the thing I just I'm like wow he's
like really really good and when I
play with him I'm fucking terrible so
I need to up a game
on Overwatch so I might be working on
that this week or I might play
Grand Theft Auto 5 to keep Loki happy
and after all it is his birthday
yes I hope you
had a good birthday all things considered
Loki indeed if not maybe maybe
this week will be good too
I have to go back to the call center
in a few weeks so that's not making me too happy
well enjoy the few weeks that you know you don't have to
be there so it's like here's how
frustrating it is yes we would love
to hire you for this department
but because of some corporate
tree bullshit we've got
to not hire people even though
we desperately need people because some higher
up person thinks it's a good
idea not to spend money of course
unlike corporate
America which is also what your wife
says it's a good idea not to spend money right
and she says that about everything
we can have like billions of dollars
like don't spend any of it it's like
I'm not I'm not gonna do that
alright alright
that's gonna do it have a great week happy gaming
everybody we will see you back here in
seven days and by the way
I don't know how many of you long time listeners notice
we kind of mix things up a little bit with our format
and our layout tonight so hopefully you guys enjoyed
that appreciate any
feedback you guys have a five star
review goes a long way in a place like
iTunes or Google podcast or wherever it is
you heard this show tell a friend about the show
we are the show where every gamer has a voice
but not unless you help us
by you know recruiting friends
and folks to listen to the program
because we don't have a million dollar
website or advertising campaign
no we still gotta keep day jobs people
we are home grown help us help
you so while we work on paying
the bills over the next seven days
and playing some games we'll be back to do it all again
in seven days goodnight everybody bye cheers guys
you've been listening to orange lounge
radio orange lounge
radio is a production of
OLR studios to join
us for a live show tune into
fog network dot com
sunday nights at six p.m. pacific
nine p.m. eastern
the views and opinions expressed
in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff of orange
lounge radio or fog
network but you know they were all
still true
see you next week
you