[SPEAKER_21]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_24]: And this is episode number 119 for this
[SPEAKER_24]: November the 21st of 2004.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scene's most interesting station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, I should have been the Internet's radio station.
[SPEAKER_24]: You'd think I'd have my script memorized by now.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just, I'm out of it.
[SPEAKER_24]: You've got to turn it on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Turn it on.
[SPEAKER_16]: But money, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: But money?
[SPEAKER_24]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me better as Skye.
[SPEAKER_24]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_24]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, say hello to Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have food, and it's yummy.
[SPEAKER_24]: What kind of food?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a low-carb tortilla with roast beef and provolone cheese and spinach.
[SPEAKER_24]: Her mic is really, really low.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can we do anything to turn up her mic over here?
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll have to look into it.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said that I'm fabulous and wonderful and the world should worship me.
[SPEAKER_24]: As always.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tell us something new.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have food.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's better than all of your food.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also joining us tonight, earning his title right now, trying to fix Jamie's mic there, Techmasa Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_24]: Right.
[SPEAKER_24]: And he can't say anything else because he's too busy working.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also joining us tonight in studio, a familiar special guest.
[SPEAKER_24]: He's here an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_24]: Say hello to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm a mouthful of spinach And I have spinach
[SPEAKER_24]: Call That Love
[SPEAKER_24]: An exclusive for you guys, the new Ultramix 2 songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not talking about the same stuff that was on the V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_24]: We already played that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm talking about the brand new songs from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: that isn't anywhere else on the internet yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: And for instance, in this first break, we're gonna hear Tengoku, or 0.59, both, both, you know the song is both names, the Jesper Kidd mix, and then we're gonna hear the DDR edit of After All, and a new song called Altitude, all from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're gonna play a whole lot of new Ultramix 2 songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ultramix 2 is on everyone's mind this weekend, I think, if you're a DDR player, you've heard about this game, and if you're an Xbox owner, you probably own this game by now.
[SPEAKER_24]: or you're getting it very soon.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, of course, on top of that, we've got all the Japanese imports as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, a lot of big news tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll get to all that after this break.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also, whoops, I gotta remember this too, the Akira Omoka signed CD giveaway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hello, we're giving away the first CD tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who?
[SPEAKER_24]: I would hope you'd know him, seeing as he did the song right before we came on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I lust after his musical talent.
[SPEAKER_24]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's the Jamie I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I lust after his body.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_24]: Tonight is the night of revelations!
[SPEAKER_25]: And that was just funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki lusts after a man.
[SPEAKER_25]: No.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's in the same way I lust after, like, Margaret Cho.
[SPEAKER_25]: You mean he's not a giant robot?
[SPEAKER_24]: In the same way I lust after... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I lust after teriyaki sauce.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, Benihana teriyaki sauce.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, the way I lust after that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, yeah, sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Break time.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll be right back after this.
[SPEAKER_24]: Music from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: Enjoy, you guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: She knows the voices in her mind
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter D, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_16]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_24]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio episode number 119 on this lovely November 21st, 2004.
[SPEAKER_24]: First off, to those of you guys that are brand new to the station, tuning in for the first time, big welcome to you guys.
[SPEAKER_24]: Welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know that our rebroadcasts that are starting now over on DDR Freak on Friday nights are getting a pretty good reception, so I think we might get some new people because of that.
[SPEAKER_24]: So a big thank you to you guys for tuning in over here and listening to the live experience.
[SPEAKER_24]: With a shotgun.
[SPEAKER_24]: with a BFG for all I care.
[SPEAKER_24]: A pretty gun.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, in there we had some songs from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: Brand new, playing them for the first time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki and I just were recording those off our Xbox not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hope you guys enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Giving you guys something to check out tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Those of you guys especially who haven't gotten a chance to check out Ultramix 2,
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what's interesting is that a lot of that same feedback in the chatroom, I'm seeing a lot of... Ziz says, it just sucks that they killed Tengoku with this remix.
[SPEAKER_24]: MPQ says, too much kid, not enough Tengoku.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or .59, however you want to say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just... It really was a lot of extraneous stuff that really didn't need to be there.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll admit, I actually kind of like it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's like one of my more favorite remixes.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's different, and I can see why people don't like it, because it is so different than the original, and a lot of people consider the original to be like one of the staple Bomani songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, honestly, it's in like every home 2DX version.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, not every, but almost damn near every.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, you know, it was a classic DDR song, so it's kind of like when somebody touches that and makes it different, people are kind of nervous.
[SPEAKER_24]: I kind of dug it, though.
[SPEAKER_24]: Certainly more so than a lot of those remixes we got on previous DDR mixes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the same thing like what they did with the Battle Royale manga.
[SPEAKER_07]: They took something that was fine the way it was, and blew it way out of proportion by Americanizing the text too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they Americanized the mixing too much in this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's too big, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fine, simple, the way it was.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, to each their own opinion, but certainly Ultramix 2 offers something for everyone, so even if you didn't really like that song, maybe you liked After All by Delirium.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would hope that you would like that song, Jamie, considering it was a former cage match pick of yours.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think she likes that song.
[SPEAKER_24]: What did you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_24]: Arcadian
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, put down the dating sim on the DS for a minute.
[SPEAKER_24]: What do you think of Altitude?
[SPEAKER_24]: That seems like the kind of song you would put in a cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: What do you think of Altitude?
[SPEAKER_24]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Have you played that one on Ultimate X2 yet?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think once.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's kind of cool because a lot of people are going, oh my god, finally we're getting a US exclusive song that's a 9-footer.
[SPEAKER_24]: Of course, not only is there nine, but there's like ten UX exclusives right now, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: What are you doing over there on the DS?
[SPEAKER_24]: You look like you're scratching off paint or something with your stylus.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's all black.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, you're doing PictoChat and you're just making all black boxes?
[SPEAKER_24]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, of course, today, the 21st, being the release of the DS as well, and not only Loki, but myself had to go pick up one of these and...
[SPEAKER_24]: I heard they were supposed to be in short supply, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: It doesn't seem like there was much of a problem.
[SPEAKER_24]: It wasn't that hard to find.
[SPEAKER_25]: You guys have DSs?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, let me get one in the back.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was difficult.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't want to get too far off base here, because we have to start off the show as we start off every week's show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did we want to talk, since we brought up Conception?
[SPEAKER_24]: Later.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll talk about it later.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, we have to get to How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day, because that's an Orange Laundry of Tradition, dammit.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, Jamie...
[SPEAKER_24]: I know you're working over there, but how was your week?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: My week was shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: My day was half shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I normally enjoy being female.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is one of the days I don't.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think I know where this is going, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to say anything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been in a crappy, crappy mood all day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I overslept, and then it took quite a bit for me to be happy again today.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I am now in a better mood than I've been all day, thanks to the power of good conversation, and coffee, and salty food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I normally hate salty food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went out and got me some hot dogs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Salty Hot Dogs from the 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, the rest of the week was kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been mostly gearing up toward my trip to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to be here next week because I'm going to be in Alabama and not here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I will have my laptop with me and there may be some Skype potential if I can find a reliable broadband.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's next week's show you're not going to be here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm sort of going to be in another state.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: That happened to me once this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to come back with like a fro because I cut my hair short.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the humidity is going to make it all poof up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Are you going to come back with a little bit of southern accent?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought I already had a bit of one.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not that strong, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never really had much of one to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now today, during the show, I'm going to be kind of quiet because I'm doing a paper on a focus on ethics for business law.
[SPEAKER_24]: You?
[SPEAKER_24]: Ethics?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you can shut up right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have ethics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have... some.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, DarkSakura has always been a really good place to go for advice, you know?
[SPEAKER_24]: Dear DarkSakura, I'm feeling a little sad today.
[SPEAKER_24]: What should I do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Get the fuck over it!
[SPEAKER_24]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_24]: Of course, that's not really ethics, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: You told me to shut the fuck up, and I feel better already.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dear DarkSakura... Okay, Dear DarkSakura, I stole a dollar out of my mommy's purse.
[SPEAKER_24]: What should I do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it to me!
[SPEAKER_24]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me and my fucked up morals.
[SPEAKER_07]: But nah, I'm gonna... It's gonna be cool because I'm gonna go see my mama's son.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm gonna see a bunch of my friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, a few people from DDR Freak are gonna be coming down to see me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, Freak!
[SPEAKER_07]: And I figure maybe I'll get some interviews or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or a statement from various people's.
[SPEAKER_24]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_24]: We do want some statements on record from some of our pals in Alabama and the surrounding areas.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I prefer to call those make fun of the customer buttons.
[SPEAKER_24]: See, unfortunately, we don't have make fun of the listener buttons.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, you know, we don't have that.
[SPEAKER_24]: We can't afford cough buttons.
[SPEAKER_24]: So if I just cough in your ear and blow out your speaker, my apologies.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I totally agree with you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_25]: Click.
[SPEAKER_25]: Those listeners are stupid.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: Click.
[SPEAKER_24]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_24]: We get a dollar for everyone that listens.
[SPEAKER_24]: Click.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_25]: My week was all right.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was pretty uneventful.
[SPEAKER_25]: I tried playing Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_25]: MyStyle, which includes cheating, and my GameShark 2 crapped out on me, so I bought a new codebreaker today.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cheaters never prosper.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, shitty software... Oh, what do you mean, cheaters never prosper?
[SPEAKER_25]: Bush got elected.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways, so... Wow.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways, so... Today, we got...
[SPEAKER_25]: DM DM DM DM DM DM
[SPEAKER_25]: Literally six feet away.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not even six feet.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki was sitting on the couch, which you can see on cam, and I was sitting in the Jamie's seat, which you can't see on cam, but it's really close.
[SPEAKER_25]: On the other side of the coffee table.
[SPEAKER_24]: We were playing PictoChat and writing dirty words like vagina and things on the PictoChat and drawing middle fingers to each other and stuff, and it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is what the DS was made for.
[SPEAKER_25]: I love the DS just for that.
[SPEAKER_25]: That is the best feature right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, actually, it was really cool, because we were playing Metroid Prime Hunters at the demo at Best Buy, and I gotta say, the control on it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's just really smart.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm having issues with it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's too much for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I miss my Atari joystick, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: One button!
[SPEAKER_24]: One button for everything!
[SPEAKER_25]: Now, now, I like it, I like it, but it cramps up my hand like a bitch because you have to hold it in a really weird way, and so, like, my finger's all fucked up from trying to reach around to the back to, you know, push the, uh, L button, and it's just like... Sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can't quite get the reach around, huh?
[SPEAKER_25]: I guess, yeah, whatever, anyways, um, so, other than that, um...
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, we went to Benny Hoff's today and that rocked.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because we were going to go to some cheapo teriyaki bowl place and they ended up not being open on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_24]: What kind of restaurant is closed on Sunday?
[SPEAKER_25]: Religious restaurants?
[SPEAKER_07]: Chick-fil-A.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_24]: I know Chick-fil-A is closed on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_24]: They don't have Chick-fil-A here though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have one in Solano.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's not here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to go eat at Chick-fil-A in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, done.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways, so... Well, yeah, well, I'm going to go to South Sac and eat at Popeye's, dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_07]: I could eat at five Popeye's in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry, Logie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, sorry, but not really.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, anyways, so, yeah, it's pretty much a lot of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've leveled my white mage up, like, five levels or so.
[SPEAKER_25]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_25]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_25]: What else?
[SPEAKER_25]: Not really much else other than that.
[SPEAKER_25]: We got Ultramix 2, so I watch people play that.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that's pretty much it for right now, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: RKDN42, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: My week was kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was sick most of the week with a cold, but it was working.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just sniffly all week and so forth, and it did work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then, went on Tuesday, went and got my smog test for my car, so I can get full registration.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then, after doing that on Thursday, I went down to the courthouse to see if I could pay off my ticket for the registration thing, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh yes, and that was the one you got after this show, a couple weeks ago, yes, alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you said that I need the final registration, or have to go to DMV or something, so they extended the date, so I have until next month to get all that done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully that will still be corrected and I only have to pay $10.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said $191, which would be a bitch if I had to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then I paid some 2DX this week and ordered 8th Style on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're going to get 8th Style before me, Cry?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well it's probably going to be like two weeks or so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I ordered from YesAsia and they don't have them in stock at the moment.
[SPEAKER_24]: I definitely want to play some of the 8th style consumer stuff tonight because there's a song on there I love so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be getting mine from PlayAsia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody's getting 8th style but me crying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just going to be getting it for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I still don't have 7th style crying.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's either 8th style or I think I'm getting a tablet because I'm changing my major to an art major.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't do much else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Played a bit more 2DX today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Came here yesterday and
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Spring of Trivia!
[SPEAKER_25]: Spike TV is the most intelligent station I've ever seen because they are bringing... You said Spike TV and intelligent in the same sentence.
[SPEAKER_25]: Listen, they have a good video game awards show and they're bringing Japanese game shows over here to America.
[SPEAKER_24]: And reruns of Blind Date 24 hours a day.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_25]: That fucking rocks!
[SPEAKER_25]: And you know what else they have?
[SPEAKER_25]: World's Wildest Police Chases.
[SPEAKER_25]: And we watch that every fucking day.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_25]: So they have really kick-ass TV.
[SPEAKER_25]: But...
[SPEAKER_25]: Hey Spring of Trivia, it's the weirdest show you'll ever see, it's just a trivia show, it's not really a game show And the winners at the end, they win bread Sounds like one of our giveaways And it's great though because one of the trivia things was Mozart wrote a song called Lick My Ass
[SPEAKER_25]: And he actually did write a song called Lick My Ass And then they performed the song Lick My Ass Which was translated into English And it was great, it was like um
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, wonderful sensation, lick my ass.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_25]: You just have to watch that show, it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, having taken quite a bit of music history, when I first started college, because I started off as a music major, that doesn't surprise me one single bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what, Vox said it right though.
[SPEAKER_24]: Lick My Ass is a wonderful sensation.
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_23]: Mozart.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, Mozart.
[SPEAKER_23]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whoever.
[SPEAKER_23]: The dead guy.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, that's what... See, Taka needs to now, you know, take that song and, you know, put it into, like, another renaissance song for, like, you know, 2DX Blue or whatever the next one's gonna be.
[SPEAKER_25]: Gold.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_25]: 2DX Yellow.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, and one more thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: This will be the last thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: DERBY OWNERS CLUB
[SPEAKER_24]: For once, we have the cool game on the block.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, we have Disney's Rave, too, for weather.
[SPEAKER_24]: But for twice, we have the cool game on the block.
[SPEAKER_24]: I really, really hope they can keep it in good shape this time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gave poop to a small child.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, the coin slots are a little iffy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_24]: How did you give poop to a small child?
[SPEAKER_07]: I bred some of Iguana Girl's horses because I missed having my specials.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first one I built was an albino, so I named it Shiroi.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a female.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it was a male, I would have named it Michael Jackson or something because I think its parent was Latoya Jackson.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was one of her half-and-halves.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, my second one came out all gray, so I named him Poop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I gave him to a small child.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then my last one was a panda, so I named it Gungurl.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here, have some poop, little child.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you should have seen the kid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, here, I named my horse Poop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can have him.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the kid just grinned.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got poop!
[SPEAKER_07]: He just had that hey, hey, hey grin.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can you imagine the parents getting the phone call?
[SPEAKER_22]: Could you tell your child not to bring poop to school again?
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: But yeah, we gotta start him young in the life of horse racing.
[SPEAKER_25]: And, you know, betting on tracks.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_24]: Go, baby, go!
[SPEAKER_24]: Explicit joined us during that first commercial break, and you know he's always got a lot to say.
[SPEAKER_24]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Had to take a few tests this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Practically passed all of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I actually finally played Derby's Owners Club at RVGL.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go, baby, go!
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's about time RVGL got onto my good side.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: I still haven't gone there yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm still a little scared.
[SPEAKER_24]: That place, Bomani Games go and they die there.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm scared that when I go there, Derby Owners Club is going to have like two monitors missing and it's going to make me cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or kids stealing the... Or kids breaking all the TV.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: Graffiti or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and finally got the DS.
[SPEAKER_24]: You too, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the pictograph.
[SPEAKER_24]: Were you here when we were talking about how Loki and I were sitting just six feet from each other, writing vagina and sending middle finger pictures back and forth?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm hiding right now with my fuck you hat.
[SPEAKER_24]: You have to put that on cam so they can see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cam over at www.orangenautorated.com If you can't see the hat that Explicit is wearing, it says fuck you in sign language.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now I have metric point hunters.
[SPEAKER_03]: It feels pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just hard to get used to, really.
[SPEAKER_24]: Are you having problems with the reach around like Loki is?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually got used to it very quickly.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can shoot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just shooting is the big problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: Does everything have to be about gay sex, really?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you're making me think DS stands for dual sexuality.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought DS stood for me!
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck y'all!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have no other real material tonight, so I resort to Dick Fargage sex jokes.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, how does it feel to have... I'm offended.
[SPEAKER_22]: I need to sue.
[SPEAKER_22]: How does...
[SPEAKER_24]: Go ahead, you ain't gonna get blood out of a turnip, honey.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, you mean the DS?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I thought you meant me, my dick and fart and gay sex jokes.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm offended!
[SPEAKER_24]: How does it feel to have a game system named after you?
[SPEAKER_07]: My ego is gargantuan, like the size of the King of All Cosmos' package.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have decided, by the way, speaking of that, that I'm going to cosplay as the Little Prince, with a big ball of stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: I should cosplay as the King, that would rock.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, actually I forgot I did do something else yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went to the Wreck-It-Con kickoff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, how was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: What is Wreck-It-Con for those who don't live in California?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a local anime con, one of the smaller ones at one of the schools in Pittsburgh, California.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a good time.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to go again this year.
[SPEAKER_24]: They moved the date though, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_07]: March, I think.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I got a fantasy star online art book.
[SPEAKER_07]: I picked up a record, which I need to bring over here to rip the audio from.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_24]: Ask Orange Lounge Live
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll talk to him.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I just, you know, seeing all the costumes, I was like, you know what, that's what I should do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And someone suggested, by the way, I got a free copy of The Sims 2, which I'm giving to Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm going to be, he gave me some ideas for a skit I can do for The Masquerade.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that would be put little Lego houses and stuff on the ground and roll over it with a giant ball.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have this big display behind me that sees legs in this humongous package.
[SPEAKER_24]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know if they do put Katamari Damacy on the DS, the king will have to be both screens.
[SPEAKER_24]: His package will take up the entire lower screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I'm wondering how one so endowed could come out with something so tiny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should be getting the game, the Japanese version, in a day or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got it off eBay for about the same price as it cost me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh wait, so you bought the Japanese version?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Of course, they didn't change much, so, except the words, but hey.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, my week and my day was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't do a whole lot of Bomani playing, well, except for Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've actually done a lot of DDR playing in the past three days, but I'll get into that a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_24]: I did not go out to Roseville Golf Land with the others on, what, like Wednesday or something?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, I was supposed to go on a date the other night and I got ditched.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, you know, life sucks sometimes, but what can you do?
[SPEAKER_24]: Although, I got an apology today, so that made me feel a little better.
[SPEAKER_24]: And one of my really, really good friends is in the hospital for the second time this week.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, Christopher, I know you're not listening, but I'm thinking about you and I hope you feel better soon.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also...
[SPEAKER_24]: I went and got the DS with Matt today and I've been really enjoying that as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Benihana is one thing that Loki didn't say about Benihana.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was only my second time there.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you know what's really weird about when you go to Benihana?
[SPEAKER_24]: When you go to most restaurants, you sit at your own table, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: But at Benihana, you kind of have to like share a table with other people because they sit like seven or eight people at a table because of the fact they only have so many chefs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: So, of course, we want to talk a whole lot about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: We want to get your input over the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you go over to www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to take some of your calls in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: But first, let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_24]: We still have a lot of music going to play for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: As I said earlier in the show, we've got so many Ultramix 2 songs we want to debut for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't think anybody else has these right now, so we're playing them for you guys and getting your thoughts on it as well over the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we'll talk about Ultramix 2 when we come back.
[SPEAKER_24]: From this, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
This is how the story goes
[SPEAKER_16]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
Let me tell you something you don't know Let me tell you something you don't know
[SPEAKER_16]: Let me tell you something you don't know
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_24]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hope you enjoyed some of the music there in that break.
[SPEAKER_24]: All from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: We had a song, you should know this one, Brick House by the Commodores.
[SPEAKER_24]: Finally making its way into a DDR game.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's a great one.
[SPEAKER_24]: After that was a group called Creo with a song called Burning For You, which is kind of a, I think it's one of the sleeper hits of the mix, honestly.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's one of those songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Catch It by Total Science
[SPEAKER_24]: which is a song I don't particularly care for so much.
[SPEAKER_24]: And DarkSakura is discovering the wonders of pictochat with Loki on the DS right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: What are you guys drawing pictures of?
[SPEAKER_07]: My artwork is pretty damn good on this thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to put it up on the cam.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can try, but it looks really blurry.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can go try to put it up on the cam, but you're going to have to chat while I do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to... I drew a picture of a toilet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you can barely see it, but it's coming out okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki sent me a picture of a turd, and I sent him a picture of my horse, and he sent me a picture of glue, and I sent him a picture of a toilet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here, take that foul thing back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm supposed to be doing my homework.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was going to say, I found a way to distract DarkSakura from her homework.
[SPEAKER_24]: Show her Pictochat.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now Loki is drawing, he's repeatedly sending me pictures of him holding a gun, shooting RVGL children.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's like the third one he sent.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I'm turning this off.
[SPEAKER_24]: We got a show to do.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm just, I'm really scared about the next, like, anime con.
[SPEAKER_24]: or better yet DDR Tournament with all these DS's.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's gonna be like every kid on the block's gonna have their DS there and drawing naughty pictures back and forth.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did you like how there's a big old warning in the DS manual about parents?
[SPEAKER_24]: You should advise your children if they're under 15 about the warnings of chatting with strangers.
[SPEAKER_25]: When picking a name, make sure it's gender neutral.
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't understand the reasoning behind that.
[SPEAKER_24]: So dirty old men can't pick up on you?
[SPEAKER_24]: With a DS.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously, if you're a dirty old man hitting on girls on a DS, you're sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Desperation.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's see, here it is.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is on page 10 of the manual.
[SPEAKER_24]: Important privacy information.
[SPEAKER_24]: Nintendo DS wireless communication, including PictoChat, is not monitored.
[SPEAKER_24]: In other words, they're saying this is not Xbox.
[SPEAKER_24]: This means PictoChat does not block messages from strangers.
[SPEAKER_24]: Similar to unmonitored internet chat rooms, children should be warned about receiving messages from or communicating with strangers.
[SPEAKER_24]: Up to 15 other DS users within range of your Nintendo DS may be able to view your nickname and messages within a selected chatroom at any one time.
[SPEAKER_25]: I hope to God, because we live in an apartment complex with four buildings around here.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's kids over there and they got video games.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mommy, Mommy, give me PiktoChat, give me DS!
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, hey, who's this chatting on here?
[SPEAKER_25]: Penis.
[SPEAKER_24]: and it goes on to say, an adult should assist children with a system setup and instruct them not to use personal information and not meet strangers.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that's the part I don't get because how far does the DS work?
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, it's only like 30 feet.
[SPEAKER_24]: So chances are you're already by the stranger.
[SPEAKER_25]: But, but, not necessarily because...
[SPEAKER_25]: 30 feet, and I think that you can ping off of each other.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think.
[SPEAKER_24]: That would be something else.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or give personal information to anyone because it could be read by a stranger.
[SPEAKER_24]: So don't put your credit card number on PictoChat, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, 15-year-olds, don't put your credit card number or your social security on PictoChat.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Let me be the first one to say this right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: You're going to see an article within, I'm going to give it like three months.
[SPEAKER_25]: Kids caught in school using the DSs to cheat on tests.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what, they could already do it though, with cell phone text messaging.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've already heard of that one.
[SPEAKER_24]: In fact, even, because it's not a huge secret, I'm a teacher in my day job, except I teach adults, and adults are just as bad as children.
[SPEAKER_24]: But they use email.
[SPEAKER_24]: They'll use their email system to email each other during tests.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have to watch them.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not everybody.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm talking about one or two bad apples spoiling the bunch, obviously.
[SPEAKER_24]: Whatever date you choose to enter as your month or day of birth, year is not asked for.
[SPEAKER_24]: An it's your birthday message will be communicated in the chat room on that date.
[SPEAKER_24]: For more information, visit Nintendo.com slash consumer slash DS privacy.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's some good reading, if you're ever really poor.
[SPEAKER_25]: I love how the little warning comes up every time you turn that on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Be sure to look into the health risks
[SPEAKER_25]: We're playing the DS.
[SPEAKER_24]: DS causes cancer.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, back to the big Bomani news from this week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ultramix 2, DDR Ultramix 2 hitting the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know a lot of us have gotten a chance to play it on yesterday, 20 November, during the special, and some of us have been playing it throughout the weekend.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, what did you think of Ultramix 2 overall?
[SPEAKER_25]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was definitely a good mix of
[SPEAKER_25]: Basically, it's almost all new stuff anyways.
[SPEAKER_25]: And they did a really good job on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Really good job putting it together.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was under the impression that there'd be more actual videos for these songs.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, you know, not this random shit, but eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: But the steps seem pretty good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Really, I didn't have too many complaints about it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Except maybe, like, you know, bomb mode was kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_25]: Some of, like, the, you know, extra party stuff's kind of, eh, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's, I mean, it's different.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's pretty much all it is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like it so far, though.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, what about Songless?
[SPEAKER_25]: Songlist was very good.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like all this stuff that you haven't heard before, like the new remixes and this stuff from a different drum.
[SPEAKER_25]: Very good decision there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, whoever decided to hook up with a different drum for the songs, bless you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bless your little heart a million times over.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was the most genius idea for DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was as good as the original idea to hook up with Toshiba EMI in Japan for Dance Mania.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I know I've said it on this show before, that all DDR needed was to hook up with another record label, just like Toshiba EMI in Japan.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hook up with a record label here and get some good songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: And thank God, somebody finally listened.
[SPEAKER_24]: Of course, I know they probably weren't really listening to me, but somebody else thought of the idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: and hooray, it had great effects on DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think the different drum stuff is the best music in the game.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, Arcadian, what are your thoughts on Ultramix 2 being a DDR mostly import fanatic, but how do you like this domestic release?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would definitely say it was probably the best US mix that I've seen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it probably is the best US mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a lot of cool new stuff and
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw on some of the videos for the new stuff, they have the website of the people.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of this stuff is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd want to actually check out the bands that did them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Which I'm sure if any bands ever heard that, they'd be very happy to hear that.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, having their songs in DDR gets them the extra exposure.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, honestly, never heard of Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_24]: Never heard of them before they were in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now, I am a huge fan of them.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know most of the people that do this show.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know we've gotten tons of listeners in on that band.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, it's great.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, it's been great promotion for not just them, but other bands too.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know there's a lot of Day Behavior fans and stuff too, so.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing, I just don't think the sentence makes sense.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, you want to read that sentence?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Mr. Sucker's contention that this violated the implied warranty of merchantability.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that sound correct?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's big words, but it sounds fine to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't mean to interrupt the Vimani discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just had an agonizing moment over my own grammar.
[SPEAKER_22]: Have you gotten a chance to play Ultramix 2 at all?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't had a chance to do anything.
[SPEAKER_24]: You'll have a chance before next week's show, or two weeks' show, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm hoping to get some time in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, it's probably going to be after I get back from Alabama.
[SPEAKER_24]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I've had other priorities.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_24]: But money can't always come first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it could.
[SPEAKER_24]: I left work early on Friday and ran over to Game Crazy to try and find the game, and all they had were the bundles, so I went over to GameStop instead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to GameStop first.
[SPEAKER_07]: You make me cry.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's just the GameStop people are always hounding me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then go to the one at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's too far of a drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then tell me and I'll go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm crying.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else you want to say about Ultramix 2, Arcadian?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and the backgrounds are seizureific.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you play it for like over an hour or so, you'll start to get a headache if you have those on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I disagree, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think in the past three days, I've played more DDR than I have since I, like, first got into the game, or, like, I would say after 4th Mix was new in arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, I have that set.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've played more DDR in the past three days than I have since I first probably played fourth or fifth mix, honestly.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's how much I'm into this mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I haven't had a seizure yet, but I agree that the backgrounds are really bright and it makes sudden mode very difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a seizure yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: They just seem to try to throw as much shit on the screen as possible so you'll screw up and miss the arrows.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll lose an arrow in all the busyness of the screen.
[SPEAKER_24]: and in challenge mode, that can be a bitch.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can trim the videos off, people.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know, but it's not, it's much fun that way.
[SPEAKER_25]: What was up with Rage?
[SPEAKER_25]: First off, having ginormous hair and second, dancing like a fucking woman.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he did in fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: He had Emmys dances.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have a feeling they only have one template for all the dance moves, so they're gender neutral dance moves.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, that was all right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Explicit, anything you wanted to share on Ultramix 2?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, he hasn't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I haven't really played it yet, but I'll probably most likely play it this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can find anyone who has Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else you wanted to say, Arcadian?
[SPEAKER_24]: You look like you had another thought you wanted to finish or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, the tournament we did on 20 November?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, unfortunately not a whole lot of people on Xbox Live just yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: We tried doing a big tournament on Xbox Live yesterday, and we managed to finally get four people, a four-person tournament.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: But here's my advice to you guys that play the tournaments on Xbox Live, change the song, or else you'll play the whole song the whole tournament.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get It All
[SPEAKER_24]: And speaking of songpacks, songpack 7 is on the way out.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we know some of the songs are going to be in that.
[SPEAKER_24]: A lot of classic DDR songs, everything from end of the century to era.
[SPEAKER_24]: And a brand new song, I feel, the Junk Circuit mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: But unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_24]: From what we understand, the song pack has been submitted, but it has not been added by Microsoft yet, which has been the case for a lot of previous song packs from DDR Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_24]: So hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would honestly check Monday, because I bet you Microsoft will add them on Monday.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_24]: As far as my personal thoughts on the mix, like I said, I've played this game more in the past three days than any DDR mix in a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_24]: I really like it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I love the fact that now it feels like DDR is not just being copies of Japanese mixes.
[SPEAKER_24]: And by that I mean, you know how when you run a copy on the copier and then you copy it again?
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: But with Ultramix 2, I think a lot of people really didn't know what to expect.
[SPEAKER_24]: It got slammed a lot after E3 because the interface was kind of weird and, you know, the song list was not all that hot at the time because they were keeping all the good stuff under wraps, but boy.
[SPEAKER_24]: When they hooked up with a different drum and got all the new songs, it's just absolutely amazing.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the Xbox Live stuff, phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_24]: Having the edit steps online is great.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would say the only downsides I've seen so far to the game is maybe I'm still noticing some frame rate issues in some songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, it's a big deal.
[SPEAKER_25]: With the videos running, it is big.
[SPEAKER_25]: But, you know, if that really bothers you, turn off the videos, and I'm sure they'll fix it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I had trouble with the controller, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd be hitting stuff, and it wouldn't register.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, that was annoying.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think a lot of people were saying that they were a little concerned about the steps when they first heard that new people are making the steps.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, longtime DDR fans, and oh, who knows what that could be.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I think there were some people out there that were even dogging on it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Makers of another game were dogging on the DDR Ultramix 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is really fucking unprofessional, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, yeah, we already discussed that on a previous episode.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not going to go there again.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I believe it was Cutris on DDR Freak said something about those folks are eating a nice slice of humble pie right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I thought that was a very good way of putting it because...
[SPEAKER_24]: People are just loving the steps.
[SPEAKER_24]: I honestly have not heard really bad things about the steps yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: Which, in every DDR mix, what's the first thing that people knock?
[SPEAKER_24]: Steps.
[SPEAKER_24]: Every DDR mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: But not this one so far.
[SPEAKER_24]: Granted, there's been a couple people saying, oh, you know, some of the songs are AAA-able and the timing window is meh.
[SPEAKER_24]: But that timing window and the steps aren't the same to me, you know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Clearly, the person that was working on Sound Pack 6 was not working on this game.
Ha!
[SPEAKER_24]: and thank heavens for that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it's been really neat to see the edit mode stuff online too because some folks over from the DDR Freak thread are already uploading all the Oni edits.
[SPEAKER_24]: I saw some of those on there.
[SPEAKER_24]: I downloaded a few of them.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: The only thing I had a problem with is they kind of tucked that away.
[SPEAKER_24]: I agree it was not as easy to find as it should have been, but... And plus, I think it's kind of got a lousy setup, the way that you download the songs, because you have to have the person on your friends list, or they have to be in the top 100, which right now isn't a problem, but once you get more than 100 people on there with edits, it's going to be hard to find people with edits, so I...
[SPEAKER_24]: I think that might be... It wasn't maybe the brightest way to do it, but maybe it was the only way they could.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Or even later.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, who's to say you couldn't, you know... Because they have, you know, where you can update your software and stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know if I'd ever see that happening with Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think they'll just do an Ultramix 3 and fix all those things.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, some of it's better than no it, so...
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I'm going to go ahead and open up the Skype line if some folks want to comment on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just go over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us, and you can give our show a call and let us know your thoughts on Ultramix 2 if you picked it up.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not the Japanese import games just yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll get to those in a little while.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know some of you guys want to talk about Festival and the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: We will get to those a little later.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just want to kind of talk about Ultramix 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Favorite song so far in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_25]: I love the Midi Head remix of In My Eyes.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_25]: Second favorite, Monkey Punk.
[SPEAKER_24]: Which is funny because I remember somebody saying that Monkey Punk, somebody who heard these songs before we did, saying that Monkey Punk was not that great of a song.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like it because it just feels like guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_24]: Arcadian, favorite song in the mix so far?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard him enough to really give a favorite.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like some of the new stuff, like the new sort of electronic type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, a lot of the different drum stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything that you've heard that you like so far?
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie, anything you've heard yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been overly displeased except for the Tengoku.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was just crappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jonas, anything you... Well, I didn't really hear much of the songs, but some of the stuff I would consider my favorites so far until I actually play the game would be like Jam On It or... The booty ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Burn For You.
[SPEAKER_24]: Burn For You, yeah, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, those are my top two so far.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would say my top three, Skulk, Love Skulk, Love Skulk, Wherever You Are by Lava, and Tough Enough by Vanilla Ninja.
[SPEAKER_24]: Love that song, and the video is cheesy-rific.
[SPEAKER_25]: Love Skulk, but hate the cut of Skulk.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're kind of mad because they took out the vocals.
[SPEAKER_25]: Horrible edit of Skulk, but other than that, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_25]: Once you hear the original, you're just like, ugh.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know so much, because the part with the female vocals is my favorite part of the whole song, and that's in there, so I'm okay with the cut that they used.
[SPEAKER_24]: I agree it's kind of sad that the male vocal couldn't be in there too, but I don't know how they could have cut it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But they need to definitely make sure that this... Stick with a different drum for the next mix.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just establish yourselves with a different drum, because obviously it's bringing them a lot of, you know...
[SPEAKER_25]: and it's just, you know, it's a very good deal, I think, because you're going to hear all these artists you've never heard before and you're going to kind of get these brand new artists coming out just because of this.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkTetsuya DarkTetsuya
[SPEAKER_24]: Awesome video.
[SPEAKER_24]: Love the gyrus full tilt video because it actually has screens from the old school gyrus and a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: So anyway, I guess what we'll do is take a break.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then we're going to come back and talk a little more about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: Looks like folks are shy tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't really want to talk to us on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: See if we care.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's just fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll sit here and talk for you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Close Your Eyes
[SPEAKER_16]: Close your eyes and let us fly, you and I
[SPEAKER_16]: Together we can touch the sky I was walking down the street You came like the summer breeze Sweeping my breath away It doesn't happen every day You and I together in the sky Forever young, we can have a time of our lives
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Close your eyes and let us fly You and I, together we can touch the sky Close your eyes, close your eyes and let us fly You and I, together we can touch the sky
Thank you for watching!
Yes, Marty Gantz, go ahead, play me something new right now.
You're so smart.
Go ahead, play me something I haven't heard before.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 119 in progress.
[SPEAKER_24]: And somebody in chat said that they wanted to call on the Skype line, so I'm going to go ahead and open up the Skype line back one more time, see if we get a call.
[SPEAKER_24]: So you can go ahead and call in our skyline right now if you want, www.orangeauntradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_24]: While we're waiting for that call, Loki has some exciting news he wants to share with you guys about something we've got set up for next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh wait, never mind, we're getting that call.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll get back to that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, you're on Orange Haunt Radio.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey Rob.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, who's this?
[SPEAKER_26]: Jazz.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi Jazz, how are you?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm good, how are you?
[SPEAKER_24]: Good!
[SPEAKER_24]: So you've been playing a lot of Ultramix too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_24]: And what do you think so far?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: You think it's awesome?
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, you're somebody... How long have you been playing DDR?
1999.
[SPEAKER_24]: 1999.
[SPEAKER_24]: And would you... You're old school like us.
[SPEAKER_24]: Would you like me... Now, you don't have to agree with me, but would you say, along with me, that this is the best home mix they've ever released?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_24]: What is it that makes this mix so damn beautiful?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because they took it in a whole new different direction and gave us Americans something that hasn't been rehashed from Japan a million times over.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's the copy of a copy thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd say a different drum is the best thing that happened to Ultimix 2, honestly, my opinion.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Xbox Live, because I love Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_24]: I never thought two, three years ago... How long ago did Xbox first come out?
[SPEAKER_24]: Three years ago or so?
[SPEAKER_24]: I never thought I would be sitting here saying I actually love an Xbox game, but it's true.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have to eat my words.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_24]: A lot of people are doing that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: So how's the competition going on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_24]: Aren't you ranked like number three or four right now on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that last time I checked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's easy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the timing is really pathetic, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like triple A'd at least ten songs last night.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm so surprised.
[SPEAKER_24]: I triple A'd ten songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, on the 20 November special yesterday, I was playing on light mode.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now shut up, because I was actually on dance pad.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got one great on four songs in a row.
[SPEAKER_24]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was so pissed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: That happened to me a lot on Heavy, and I was really mad at that for a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: Listen, you and your DDR skills.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, I don't know, any suggestions you would take to the Konami team for Ultramix 3 ideas?
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot more 2DX crossovers, a lot more B-Mani crossovers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't even know that something like Midnight Special was so awesome until I actually got to play it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Exactly, because that song was always in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is it just me, or does Sleepwalker sound like a total... Is that the name that's on Sleepwalker?
[SPEAKER_24]: Does that sound like a total Guitar Freak song?
[SPEAKER_24]: It does.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Boy Zone, or whatever that other song was.
[SPEAKER_24]: What was that other one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy Jazz?
[SPEAKER_24]: Boy Jazz.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, Boy Zone is that Europe band, huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it's something else.
[SPEAKER_24]: Euromix.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's Euromix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else you wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really, except, come on people, practice, give me a challenge.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, a call, a call to those on Xbox Live, challenge.
[SPEAKER_24]: What's your gamer tag, so folks can find you?
[SPEAKER_02]: KamikazeCat.
[SPEAKER_24]: KamikazeCat, alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Whoop some ass.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, later, bye.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now what he doesn't know is, I plan to take him over in the rankings very soon.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, maybe it's just me, but I honestly think that this DDR mix is so good that we seriously need to start hounding, and I don't mean like just writing letters and, you know, saying pretty please.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean hounding Konami, everybody, from every angle, to let Konami of Hawaii do a new arcade mix and put a new arcade mix out there in America.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anybody else feel similarly at all?
[SPEAKER_24]: Or have you guys given up on DDR in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily a having given up, just no expectation really.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's kind of where I'm at right now, which is why it would be such a pleasant surprise to see a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I think that with all this great music they're getting in DDR now, and just the way it's been presented, and the way the steps were done and everything, I think...
[SPEAKER_24]: Hostile Takeover!
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll buy 51 shares of their stock!
[SPEAKER_24]: That's a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we could do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: And honestly, as shareholders, we would have interest in the company's activity.
[SPEAKER_17]: That is a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Konami a publicly traded company, though, because it's Japanese?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do believe so, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: One second.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, she's looking it up in the business law book.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, man, we should become Konami shareholders.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's a great idea, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, Jamie's going to look that up in the business law book over there on what's going on with the possibility of buying shares in Kami.
[SPEAKER_24]: Any other methods?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just check up, make sure, see what their corporate deal is.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Any thoughts from you, Loki, about a new arcade mix?
[SPEAKER_24]: Haven't you been saying for a long time they need to do a new arcade mix?
[SPEAKER_24]: Now you're all of a sudden really quiet.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm Lovin' It!
[SPEAKER_07]: Businesses have relationships with all sorts of people, other than their stockholders, including employees, suppliers, customers, creditors, and the local community.
[SPEAKER_07]: Under the stakeholder interest theory of social responsibility, a corporation must consider the effects its actions will have on the other stakeholders.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there may actually be a legal requirement to satisfy those who have a stake in their activity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not just their shareholders, but also their customers.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a great idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm seriously going to look into buying Konami stock.
[SPEAKER_24]: You could just buy like 5-10 shares of stock on E-Trade, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also this one here.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, a corporation would violate the stakeholder interest theory if it viewed employees solely as a means of maximizing stockholder wealth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, basically, they have to treat their employees well, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: But also, that's just saying that anyone who has an interest in the activity of the company, you know, if they're not meeting the majority interest, then they're actually violating that rule.
[SPEAKER_24]: So if you love Konami and you want to see them do right, put your money where your mouth is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I have that right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Buy a piece of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that we should buy Konami stock.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to look into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a business major in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you answer this for me?
[SPEAKER_24]: I know, maybe we're just talking out our asses here.
[SPEAKER_24]: But in theory, it sounds like a good idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: It really does.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean... Oh, Zaku found the financial info.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_24]: He put a link in our chat room there over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I might have misinterpreted some of this, but let me look at this.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, okay, granted, one person couldn't just buy two shares and then expect to run the company.
[SPEAKER_24]: But if...
[SPEAKER_24]: Several people bought several shares that collectively had a say.
[SPEAKER_24]: They might listen to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we should incorporate ourselves.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I think we need to do that anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, but Orange Lawn Trading will not be a publicly traded company because nobody's going to tell us what to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be privately owned.
[SPEAKER_25]: What are our earnings for this year?
[SPEAKER_25]: One dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to thank my friend Julie who I'm on another form of chat that I'm not letting anybody know because I don't want them to send me messages all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_07]: The site, if you're ready, is konami.com slash en slash ir slash um wait
[SPEAKER_07]: Another page popped up over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me get the address again.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's konami.com slash en slash ir slash stockholder info, all one word, slash index.html.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it actually goes back to investor relations.
[SPEAKER_24]: I posted that in our chat room if folks are curious about that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a very interesting direction you've just kind of taken this program, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: As of 19 November, KNM stock is $22.09 a share.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_24]: I could buy five shares of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we as, you know, find out how many shares are available.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know the first thing about playing the stock market.
[SPEAKER_07]: But as shareholders, though, we would have a right in our voice and how the company is run.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is what it is for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_24]: My life has changed for the better in many ways because of this game.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I know that kind of sounds, you know, maybe sad to some people.
[SPEAKER_24]: But seriously, I've met a lot of great people because of this game.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've, you know...
[SPEAKER_24]: I've started, along with DarkSakura and Loki, a radio program which I love doing twice a week.
[SPEAKER_24]: This game has done so much.
[SPEAKER_24]: I believe in this game.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to see this game have a future.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to put my money where my mouth is and buy a piece of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing that I need to point out, too, who is this Primo Maggot, I guess?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can only buy as many shares are available too for purchase because they are going to take certain interest to make sure that those takeover cases... One person doesn't do a hostile takeover.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have ways of making sure that you're not... But at any rate, even if you own one share, you have basically an interest in how the company operates.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have a right to say, I am not pleased with what you are doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to listen to me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not that I would say I'm not pleased with what they're doing, but I would say...
[SPEAKER_07]: But overall, I mean in general, you know, I'm disappointed in what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's just a matter of, you know, you now actually, as you have a full, you know, an interest in their activity, not just an interest as a consumer, but an interest as someone who is making money off of this company.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think you've got a great idea on your hands, Jamie, and it is worth the hundred bucks for five shares to find out, honestly.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, if really, if you want to make your voice heard, you can write all the letters you want to until the cows come home, until they're run over by a Katamari, but if you actually go out, put the money down and say, I have interest in your company, this is what I would like to see, then this is a real definite way to make your voice heard.
[SPEAKER_24]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is going to be very interesting to see where this goes.
[SPEAKER_24]: If anything becomes of this idea, I'm very curious to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, you have a comment?
[SPEAKER_25]: Um... No, I was just thinking it'd be cool if they had DDR for the DS.
[SPEAKER_24]: Second work.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or...
[SPEAKER_24]: Now the chat room is running away with this idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: Zaku says, I propose every DDR player in the country over the age of 18 buy at least one share of Konami stock.
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe pulling legs there, but if you could get a large amount of them too, you could.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Primo Maggot says, and then show up at Konami's shareholder meeting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually seriously considering doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at this, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your school and now this are coming together.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can apply this business law knowledge.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your professor would be so proud.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though I changed my major and the class is no longer required.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: You would still make your professor proud.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do you want to send a copy of this program?
[SPEAKER_24]: Or do we say fuck too much?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we say fuck a bit too much.
[SPEAKER_25]: Would they allow me to come in wearing an eyepatch and a pirate bandana during the shareholders meeting?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm not going to do a hostile takeover.
[SPEAKER_24]: Honestly, if you want to be taken seriously, if you want this idea to be taken seriously, no, you can't come to the shareholders meeting dressed like a pirate.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I think Hell No, We Won't Go would be okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, well, to be continued.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to do something.
[SPEAKER_25]: I play party games.
[SPEAKER_25]: Come on, what were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_24]: I've got a lot of time off work this week thanks to Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have a lot of time off during work thanks to my work.
[SPEAKER_24]: So now it's on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Julie suggested we insert bleep for fuck.
[SPEAKER_24]: No way, I'm not going to bleeping censor myself.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bleep you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's change topics completely.
[SPEAKER_24]: Something we haven't talked about a whole lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn, it's a big deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: Where are we going to be talking?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh yeah, okay, sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to do the Akira Yamaoka giveaway very soon.
[SPEAKER_24]: But Loki, you have an announcement you want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways, as we were mentioning earlier about, you know...
[SPEAKER_25]: How we were going to have Conception on the show and Conceptions out there with Waldo.
[SPEAKER_25]: In the meantime, we were talking with another artist out there and I think we mentioned it on the other show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Next week, on Orange Suns Radio, coming to you live, the guy behind one of the best remixes, I think, in this new Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: In any DDR, honestly.
[SPEAKER_25]: And in any DDR, MidiHead will be on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_25]: He did actually one of the trailers for the Matrix Reloaded, I should say.
[SPEAKER_25]: One of the songs that I entered in Cage Mansion.
[SPEAKER_25]: Didn't win, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: And just a bunch of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think there's some other games also, but I don't remember offhand.
[SPEAKER_25]: But yeah, he will be on the show next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: And this one will air!
[SPEAKER_24]: For MidiHead, you can send them in.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll create a thread on our forums, or you can ask questions live during next week's show.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can't eat this microphone, I found out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, let's get to the other order of business tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's right, it is time for the very first drawing in the Akira Yamoka signed CD giveaway.
[SPEAKER_24]: We've asked you questions Monday, Tuesday, and Thursday nights.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys have entered, and we're going to pull a name out of the hat right now and find ourselves a winner right now, live on air.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't worry guys, though, if you didn't win this week, you got a whole nother chance.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're doing the whole thing, we're just rewinding and repeating, next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: And you have a chance to win Monday night, Tuesday night, and Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_24]: Monday night, Diversion, the Bomani Remix show.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tuesday night, Pump Up the Volume, Randomness with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Thursday night, Outside the Box, gaming with myself.
[SPEAKER_24]: And remember...
[SPEAKER_24]: Listen all three nights.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can enter three times.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can enter three times if you listen all three nights.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can enter chances.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I realize one of those nights is Thanksgiving, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: If I'm going to be here and do a show, we're going to do a drawing, dammit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, Jamie, you want to pick our winner?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I want to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, she's going to pick her winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: She's going to reach into the hat and pull out a... Ooh, it's the Dr. Dick hat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel dirty.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, it's the Dr. Dick hat.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, hold on.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to... I'm going to mix it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to caress the names.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can caress the lovely names and then pull one out of the hat and we're going to see who wins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pick one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jazz!
[SPEAKER_22]: Jazz is the winner!
[SPEAKER_24]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_24]: He was the one that just called, too!
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is he even listening still?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: He probably went back to playing Ultramix 2, so he probably doesn't even know he won.
[SPEAKER_25]: He's all, huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, he just went, huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: He doesn't even know why he won.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, well, he'll figure it out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_25]: He figured it out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I guess the buffer, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, Jazz, you won.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, so he's going to win that signed Akira Yamaoka, what is this here, a mini-disc from Silent Hill 4, The Room, it's a Japanese CD, here, we'll put this on cam too, and it's signed by Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_24]: Again, if you didn't win tonight, try again this week.
[SPEAKER_25]: And he gets the special copy that I scraped with iron wool.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, you did not, quit lying, quit lying.
[SPEAKER_24]: But maybe we'll send Jazz some other orange launch prizes as well.
[SPEAKER_25]: But those are speed grooves.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie's going to try and scan it so we can get a picture in.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll do that with the other disc that we're going to give away this next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can try and put this on cam, but I don't think it's going to turn out very well.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let me try.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's speed to make it play faster.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie, you know what we've missed?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: The ferrets.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me the babies!
[SPEAKER_07]: My parrots.
[SPEAKER_17]: My parrots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, don't throw that at my paper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Babies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this the retard baby?
[SPEAKER_25]: I think the retard baby is in the closet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, this is my laptop, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The retard one doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can have it back.
[SPEAKER_25]: I throw like a girl.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: The retard one died of complications.
[SPEAKER_07]: It died of crabs.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, somebody stapled this one.
[SPEAKER_25]: Somebody did an operation on this one.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was mine because I had to.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, because the geniuses that made those parrots.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to go to a break, and when we come back, I want to talk a little bit about some of those other releases that came out tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: In fact, stuff that I know nothing about, so I'm going to try and call somebody over the Skype line to kind of talk about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: But in the meantime, we're going to go to a break with some more music from Ultramix 2, DDR, and then the Cage Match as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: I Spy is the first song we're going to hear in this break, as well as I'm in Heaven and Istanbul Cafe.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll be back.
Thank you.
Music Music Music
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't wanna be the one to tell you how I feel When these feelings I have really are for real The time is right for this, a love to shine on through But you gotta tell me what you wanna do
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, did you hear about that show?
[SPEAKER_06]: What show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they play a lot of great Fermanian video game music, but if you listen to it, you have to listen to it again within seven days.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I've heard of that station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I even listened to it a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, what happens to you if you don't listen to it again?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you die.
[SPEAKER_24]: I, what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, wait, what's this crazy bitch doing coming out of my computer screen?
[SPEAKER_12]: Ahhhh!
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Listen or die!
[SPEAKER_24]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: We just heard some more songs from DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: Including I Spy, I'm in Heaven, and Istanbul Cafe.
[SPEAKER_24]: He says he's contemplating giving it away as a Christmas gift.
[SPEAKER_24]: Isn't that cute?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, we are going to get to the cage match in a little bit, but first off, I want to talk a little bit about 2DX8Style, because that's a huge thing that's coming out, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, it came out already in Japan.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's exciting because it has some 2DX Red songs that are unlockable in it, including Spiral Galaxy is one of the songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then there's these great new consumer songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: I definitely want to play one of the new consumer songs for you.
[SPEAKER_24]: But first, I thought maybe we'd give somebody a call.
[SPEAKER_24]: that knows a little bit more about this stuff than I do because I haven't really been following the 8-Style News.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie, have you been following the 8-Style News at all?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of, sort of.
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly haven't had time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, have you at all?
[SPEAKER_25]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Arcadian, I know you have a little bit, but... He's trying to find the mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I read a little bit of stuff, but... Sounds exciting from what you hear?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's see what our buddy DarkLionXVI has to say about 2DX.
[SPEAKER_24]: We've talked to him about 2DX before.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Sky.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, is this Ziggy?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Where's your copy of 2DX8Style?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's already in the UPS office here in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: They won't deliver it until tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't you just want to go break in and get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a good idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: He doesn't want to get busted.
[SPEAKER_24]: So tell us about some of the things we have to look forward to in 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_04]: The main menu's interface is like DDR Extreme US's Song Select Wheel.
[SPEAKER_24]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wait, it has the Song Select Wheel from EXUS?
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't know about that one, huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: Does it have iToy support, too?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_24]: What about some of the new unlocks, some of the new songs?
[SPEAKER_04]: About the unlocks thing, Spiral Galaxy and Taiyou.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can unlock them by playing all of the eight style songs, including the exclusives.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, there's a catch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do not use easy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, what happens if you do use easy?
[SPEAKER_24]: You're screwed?
[SPEAKER_04]: You cannot be able to unlock it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It has to be normal or hard mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I haven't heard much, even Everyday Lovely Day or Nebula Grasper.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try to get it tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, we're going to play some of them actually here right after I'm done talking to you.
[SPEAKER_24]: I absolutely love Everyday Lovely Days, so we're going to play that one.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll probably throw in Nebula Grass first as well, because I know that's one a lot of people are looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_24]: LED looks like he's back.
[SPEAKER_24]: There were rumors that he left, but he came back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do you know anything about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I haven't been browsing around Vermont-y style about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was just curious, because a lot of people were saying that LED had left, and now all of a sudden he's got all these songs again.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, if he did leave, he came back pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know what happened there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one more thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: About... On the record, it doesn't show the complete listings of your current scores, the progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami somehow removed that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_24]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, if you've beaten the song, or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just like shows your grades, just grades, grades, like the records of each individual sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: They might have taken that out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're getting some feedback in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jason says, what does he mean the EXUS song wheel?
[SPEAKER_24]: What do you mean by that?
[SPEAKER_24]: He said it's 8th style arcade authentic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me try to find that picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's in Bimani style.
[SPEAKER_24]: He found a picture of it somewhere, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, maybe, are you sure it's just not a Photoshop?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a real deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: Some of those kids over there love to Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, so Siggy's going to try and pull up that picture.
[SPEAKER_24]: When you find that link, could you post it in the chat room there?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I will.
[SPEAKER_24]: For some folks that are really curious about what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here's the thing about AI and SVGL.
[SPEAKER_04]: As of last Wednesday, they have Beatmania 2DX11, 2DX Red on their machines.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to go down to Arcade... You know what, Sad?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to be in LA tomorrow just for the day, but I'm not going to be able to go to Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I'm not going to be able to check it out for a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I do want to check the game out.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else exciting about 2DX Red that you've heard about?
[SPEAKER_24]: The new...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, by the way, on 8th style, whether regular or limited edition, you will get a goalie cover of a 2DX Red e-amusement card featuring Daruma and Tsunaru.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of those little cards you can put... Oh, that's very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we getting any... AI is working on their 2DX e-amusement readers.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is the EMU's thing, were there extra songs that were available on 2DX for the EMU's thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I never really got... Oh, they're probably from the network.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was just curious, because I know Poppin' Music usually has the e-mall songs that end up in the consumer style releases, but not so much 2DX, so I was curious.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else you want to share about what's going on in the 2DX world?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I found the picture.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, okay, found the picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to post it over.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because our chat room is seriously going WTF because some folks have played it and said it's arcade authentic.
[SPEAKER_24]: I had heard that the title screen was really weird, so maybe that has something to do with what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've linked it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, I'll have to take a look here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've got to see this for myself here.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, oh, interesting, the way it's, is kind of across the top, oh, okay, that's kind of like, okay, kind of like the title screen, I see what you're talking about, okay, that's, that's what it is, that funky new menu, like the main menu, where you choose, like, expert, beginner, how it kind of has that, yeah, this one's featured in, I think the one right here on the picture right now, it's featured, I mean, it's chosen as Danny Ninte, or Fast Course, right,
[SPEAKER_24]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, I'd heard that the title screen was a little different there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's very different now.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, but once you get in and you pick the songs, it looks like 8th style.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_24]: And no iToySupport.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's also a high-speed setting where you individually choose a song on which high-speed you want.
[SPEAKER_24]: I had heard about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's so good.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, in the expert courses and stuff, you can do a separate high-speed for each song?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do that, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, thank God, because that needed that, because I would hate having a non-stop course, and then, like, I would have, like, Dune, and then I'd have to do 250 BPM.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Expert mode.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anything else you want to share about 2DX?
[SPEAKER_24]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's the only thing I can share.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I do get my copy of 8th style, I'll give you pictures, even a clip of me playing dancer.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, yes, my favorite song.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, definitely.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we want to talk to you guys, talk to you a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_24]: When I say you guys, I mean the listeners in general about your thoughts on 8th style when you get it.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we'll give you our thoughts as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, thanks for letting us bug you, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, some information there on 2DX8style.
[SPEAKER_24]: Scared everybody a little bit with that comparison to EXUSA, but it looks like it's just the menu.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't worry, kids.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everything else is still just the same.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't freak out on me.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, speaking of 2DX8style, there's some great new consumer songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's so nice to see the return of consumer songs in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we're going to play a couple of those for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: My favorite song, Everyday Lovely Day, the LED style mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: I love this song.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Nebula Grasper, because that's a really popular one, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to play those songs, and then we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was a preview of some songs from 2DX8style, some new consumer tracks there, Everyday Lovely Day, and Nebula Grasper.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, we are back and also being released this week, DDR Festival and Poppin' Music 10.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't know a whole lot about Poppin' Music 10 yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not up on the Poppin' Music scene, to be honest, but I'm going to try and get Navi back here on the show after he's gotten a chance to play the copy.
[SPEAKER_24]: I did hear the Akumajo Dracula medleys in it, which makes me very happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That makes me go squee.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: I guess it's one of the email songs that's in there, so it's very awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: I figure there's not too much of a point.
[SPEAKER_24]: But for those people that don't have an Xbox, but they do have a JPS2, it's kind of a first chance for them to take a look at some new songs and also the new interface.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, you know, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just pros and cons.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just all depends on what you're looking for in a DDR mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll bet you anything, though, whatever they release next year will have some of the Ultramix 2 stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wouldn't be the first time.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: TACO?
[SPEAKER_24]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: I took a risk by putting in a top 40 song.
[SPEAKER_24]: And what do you know, it worked.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys voted at the winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was Gwen Stefani.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the name of the song is What You Waitin' For.
[SPEAKER_24]: And that was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: Remember the way the cage match works?
[SPEAKER_24]: You hear a clip of last week's winner and two brand new songs in their entirety as chosen by the Orange Lounge Radio hosts.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then you vote on your favorite in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's start it off with song number one tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a clip of Gwen Stefani with Whatcha Waiting For.
Thank you for watching!
Watch now, you're still a super hot female You've got your million dollar contract And they're all waiting for your hot check Watch your wedding, watch your wedding, watch your wedding, watch your wedding
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, that was a clip of song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: Gwen Stefani, what you waiting for?
[SPEAKER_24]: Last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: Song number two in tonight's cage match comes to us courtesy of DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, what did you pick out for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I picked a song that was in Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm pretty sure we haven't done this one before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so either.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would remember a band name like Manchild.
[SPEAKER_07]: Man Child Nitro Narcosis
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was Manchild with Nitro Narcosis.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's go around and see what everybody thought of that one, starting off with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that song was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually fun to listen to when you're driving.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it gives a 9 for the speed limit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going 90.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's go over to Arcadian42 and see what Arcadian thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll give it a 9, because it sounded pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, 9 from Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jonas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'll give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got a good beat to it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, a 9 from Explicit as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, then, uh, wow, everybody gave it a 9, but I'm sorry to break the trend, but I only thought it was kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, there's just songs in Amplitude I like better than that one.
[SPEAKER_24]: I give it a 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've already picked them for Cage Matches.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know, sorry, I just, I didn't dig that one as much, sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: I give it a 5.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's go on to song number 3 in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_24]: It comes to us from Loki, and Loki, what did you pick tonight?
[SPEAKER_25]: I didn't really have anything, so I just picked a song that I just happened to have lying around.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is another DM Ashura song, a remix between A and AA, so obviously this would be AAA.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, here we go, and I love how you just let our listeners know that you're just not even trying anymore.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I have another song that's decent that I could put in instead, but you already have that song, so...
[SPEAKER_24]: All righty then, here it is, DJ Amuro remixed by DM Ishura with A.A.A.
[SPEAKER_24]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Amoro remixed by DM Asherah with Triple A. Jimmy!
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounded like A to C. It wasn't bad, though, at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really hard to put my finger on it, because it's just something that...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was, you know, when you hear that fast drum beat pick up to another part that like everybody in God uses, it sort of sounded like there's just recycled tricks in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'd have to give it a 7.5.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, 7.5 from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: Arcadian?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounded pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd give it like 8.5.
[SPEAKER_24]: 8.5 from Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jonas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some flaws with it, like
[SPEAKER_03]: There's like some recycled samples and sound effects.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It also sounds like some of the elements used in previous DM Assures work as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I respect DM Assures.
[SPEAKER_03]: works a lot because he's done so much for remixing good remixes.
[SPEAKER_24]: As opposed to Paranoia, Cowgirl, Survivor, Max.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or that 1, 2, 3, 4, Max, Honeycrap that we heard somebody play at the station.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have to say, it is not a Max remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the love of God.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I might actually do a pinfall for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll just give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, an eight from Jonas.
[SPEAKER_25]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: I would pretend to be excited, but I'm not, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: It gets a triple A because, yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: Nine.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sure that made a lot of fanboys and girls very moist in their nether regions, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: It just didn't do it for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: It didn't have the same charm of the original.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: It wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I was going to give it a 6, but Jonas brought up a very good point in the fact that it's not a max 300 mix.
[SPEAKER_24]: And for that, I give it a bonus point.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I give it a 7 overall.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: It doesn't matter what we think.
[SPEAKER_24]: It matters what you think.
[SPEAKER_24]: So you guys can vote in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here are the three songs, one more time, that you can vote for tonight in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_24]: Gwen Stefani, what you waiting for?
[SPEAKER_24]: And song number two tonight, Manchild with Nitro Narcosis.
[SPEAKER_24]: And song number three tonight, DJ Amuro, remixed by DM Ashura with Triple A.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, guys, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote, and your votes will be counted up, and we will reveal the winner shortly, as soon as we get all the votes.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, in the meantime...
[SPEAKER_24]: DM Ashura
[SPEAKER_25]: Step Mania's Urbanized theme, which is a little bit different than most of the other themes out there.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's kind of a neat look to it.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's dancing characters for you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, the dancing characters there are.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's a skin edit of Emi and Halas Emi that...
[SPEAKER_25]: Master Chief from Halo
[SPEAKER_24]: Did they ever fix the Mr. Spanky dancing character?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think I remember that there were issues with it or something.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, it fixed.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was just a bad file or something.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it works now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Mr. Spanky can dance around like crazy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have there been any new skins for Step Mania recently?
[SPEAKER_24]: I notice you still hoard that Technofield one, but has there been anything new?
[SPEAKER_25]: Techno Fiend, whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know, some other ones that are being worked on.
[SPEAKER_25]: They all kind of look the same, but the Urbanized one, Technofine are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's supposedly work on Euromix 2, but I mean, that's pretty much just Max 2, so what's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_25]: Also, I forgot to mention, of course, you know, Festival, the new steps are being coded for that, and also for the new songs in Ultramix 2, and for the Dancing Sage Fusion stuff should be coming out eventually.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's a little easier to do it from Xbox because they can actually rip the steps and code them directly.
[SPEAKER_25]: So it makes it a little easier.
[SPEAKER_25]: So look for those that hit DDRUK at some point relatively soon.
[SPEAKER_25]: Other than that, really not too much else.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you want to go find some good skins for Step Maniac, go to DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_25]: Go to their Step Maniac forum.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's a whole section for themes.
[SPEAKER_25]: and there's a ton that are being worked on right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: And they even have a whole thread of ones that are finished.
[SPEAKER_25]: And there's plenty for you to choose from.
[SPEAKER_25]: So just go look over there and you'll find them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys want to know who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, it was very close.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was won by one vote.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then the other song, it beat it by two votes.
[SPEAKER_24]: So it was all very, very neck and neck tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tonight's winner, I think this is actually a bit of a surprise to me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tonight's winner is... Gwen Stefani!
[SPEAKER_24]: For the second week in a row, if you can imagine that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, Loki says it's on.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's gone next week, trust me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want four weeks in a row, man.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want Gwen Stefani to get retired, man.
[SPEAKER_24]: She's awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: By one vote.
[SPEAKER_24]: So close.
[SPEAKER_24]: Every vote counts.
[SPEAKER_24]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_24]: We could have had a tie and somebody could have broken the tie, but no.
[SPEAKER_24]: One vote decided it all.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, of course, everybody in chatroom is bitching about it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, hell no.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't tell me that song won.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, you guys voted for it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm counting the votes right here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think the people that voted for it are kind of hiding now because they see that the wrath is coming to get them.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: They want to know what came in second.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was AAA by one vote, and then the other song was down by two votes.
[SPEAKER_24]: But all pretty much across the board.
[SPEAKER_24]: All pretty much across the board.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we will see what happens next week in the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_24]: But for now, let's get back to Ultra Mix 2 songs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think we can all agree that Ultra Mix 2 songs are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: And in this break, we're going to hear... Ooh, my favorite one's in this break.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_24]: Toe Jam is in this break.
[SPEAKER_24]: This song's great.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's like a country song.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Tough Enough by Vanilla Ninja we'll hear in this break, too, as well as Wherever You Are by Lava.
[SPEAKER_25]: And for those of you that play doubles, I hear the doubles light steps have a certain way you're supposed to play them.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know what that means, but that's what I've been told.
[SPEAKER_24]: It means hoedown!
[SPEAKER_24]: Square dance!
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: We will be right back after this.
Music Music Music Music
Thanks for watching!
Baby, I'll be the strongest to survive
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_16]: and the rest of the cast.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't need you there, cause I need you there, all tonight Just keep on keeping the promise, if you don't come, don't be around, away, go for the fire, baby, that's tough enough Just keep on living strong, stop giving me doubt, don't be free, just get you in the deep of the heartbreak, baby, that's tough enough
Baby, I've had enough
[SPEAKER_24]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hope you're enjoying the Ultra Mix 2 songs we've been playing so far.
[SPEAKER_24]: What did you guys think of Toe Jam?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yee-haw, Ninja Cowboy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Which is funny because it was followed up by Vanilla Ninja.
[SPEAKER_24]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_24]: What did you think of ToeJam?
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys explicit in our Acadian?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's country gone techno.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you say, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's Earl?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yuck, yuck, yuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a ToeJam and Earl song in the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_24]: I heard that.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, El Mullet made this funny realization in our chat room before the show, during the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_24]: He was talking about the song Toe Jam and he said, it's funny because there's a pun in there because, you know, you're jamming on your toes to the steps.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get it?
Huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everybody's a comedian these days.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because we're sick and not going to take it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to offer a big F you to the Lexus van freshly purchased that was driving in front of me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doing not the normal one to two car space that you're supposed to have, but doing like five car lengths.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: My angst knows no bounds.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't have words to properly express it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, uh, oh yeah, F you to this fucking paper!
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Focus on ethics?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are those?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but that's really about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just sort of angsted out, so I'm gonna pass on the mic and release my anger in a more physical method by beating up, you know, an inanimate object.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably a fact machine office face style.
[SPEAKER_24]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just need the gangsta rap replay in the background, you know?
[SPEAKER_24]: Remember, if you guys want to send in a nephew, send a private message to Sky in our chatroom right now while we move on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck you to trees and the leaves that they drop.
[SPEAKER_25]: My God, there is literally like...
[SPEAKER_25]: A couple feet of leaves outside.
[SPEAKER_25]: We walk out there to my car, and there's literally a pile of leaves next to my car.
[SPEAKER_25]: I swear, if I leave my car there for a few more days, it's just going to be covered in leaves.
[SPEAKER_25]: But, it's fun to kick them and make lots of noise late at night.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of funny, when I came here yesterday, there wasn't any leaves on the ground, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I came in, and they were just all over the place.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, they all fell at once.
[SPEAKER_25]: So that fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_25]: Also, fuck you G4TV because you suck and your stupid attempt at doing something clever the Nintendo DS day was fucking lame, okay?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't like watching TV in a small little screen on my TV showing the show and what looks like a DS around the show and some stupid chatting
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyway, um, and finally, um, fuck you that my money isn't on my card yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: That pisses me off because I want to go spending, spending, spending, spending.
[SPEAKER_25]: And, uh, fuck you using my GameShark for breaking, especially after I spent like an hour putting all the codes in and playing with it a few days, and then all of a sudden it just stopped working.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you, Interact.
[SPEAKER_25]: Old Face Jeff
[SPEAKER_24]: No, they get worse.
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to getting stood up.
[SPEAKER_24]: That is awful.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why do you do that to people?
[SPEAKER_24]: That is rude.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's so rude.
[SPEAKER_24]: God damn you.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: I forgive, though.
[SPEAKER_24]: I forgave.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm such a sucker.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: I try to understand.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just have angst.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, maybe watching a nice episode of I Killed Your Cat would help.
[SPEAKER_24]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, didn't...
[SPEAKER_07]: On a happier note, my paper's done.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also an F you to the fact that I have to wake up at 4 in the morning to catch a flight to LA so I can do one day's worth of work in LA.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm training a whopping four people tomorrow and they're sending me all the way down there costing them I don't know how much money and the fact is I will be working from about 6 o'clock in the morning till 7 or 8 at night.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's because corporations are retarded.
[SPEAKER_24]: But they give me lots of money so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, um, F you to mail PMS, because I swear we have it.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's move on and see what some of our other folks in the room have to say, starting with Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, uh, fuck you to the, the ticket, parking ticket machine in the courthouse for eating my dollar and not giving me a ticket.
[SPEAKER_06]: Parking tickets, I had to go and park and go get the walk-up thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I lost a dollar to that damn shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, fuck you to my foot for hurting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hurting for a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, fuck you to my... Parts of it are oily and greasy and yucky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to wash it off all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then other parts are fucking dry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn winter does weird things to me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, and... Yeah, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to having too many tests for one whole week, even though I passed it all, it took me like, only giving me three hours of sleep the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU from working a 12 hour shift, starting from 7 o'clock in the morning,
[SPEAKER_03]: F you for having a 12 hour shift on a Friday working at 7 o'clock p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: till like 7 in the morning and then later on going to the barrier right after you're only giving me like 30 minutes of sleep oh wow yeah but then later on I have to sleep in the party F you for not getting WWE safety cables autographed out on Saturday
[SPEAKER_03]: A friend of mine was supposed to go, but he couldn't go because his license got stolen.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is Stacy Q the one that sang Two of Hearts?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rad!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, she's the one with the good ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's one big F you to the NBA on Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: My God, the Pacers and the Pistons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why the hell are you going to go fight over something just over a game just because someone dunked over your ass?
[SPEAKER_03]: And as for our test, why the fuck did you punch the wrong fan who you thought threw a bunch of cup of ice on you?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the wrong person, you sucked a white man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of some lady who was behind you, you actually threw it against you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, that also resolves.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the fans at the NBA, at that Detroit game, who are also causing the fight in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, why can't we all get along?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Preach on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dang, and people fighting over things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think a few people got hospitalized over the fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people get suspended indefinitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't come around blaming on...
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, it's the NBA's fault, or ooh, it's the Detroit Pistons' fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's everybody's fault in the first place.
[SPEAKER_16]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: People need to grow up, use their own common sense not to do some shit like that ever again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think, yeah, I think, well, so far they're suspended indefinitely, but most likely they're going to be suspended for the whole season.
[SPEAKER_03]: But who knows, I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you to trees for putting a goddamn tree branch under my car.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to remove that by ripping the whole branch itself from the bottom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, he's talking about more car problems and shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you to more SUVs fucking up the road again.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this time I'm having a loose tire in the fucking freeway Almost causing another accident As if I have not gone through any more car problems recently Causing me to spend hundreds of dollars off my own damn paycheck And reporting it as an insurance will cost me a damn record There's also another F.E.
[SPEAKER_03]: to my insurance God
[SPEAKER_03]: The stress is too high, I'm broke as hell, I'm going to school, how the hell am I going to spend food money?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or spend money on my DS, which now I owe money to.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, Explicit, you remind me of a...
[SPEAKER_24]: 80 year old guy who's sitting out on the front lawn drunk as fuck yelling at himself.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's going, F this, and F this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why can't we all get along?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the damn kids.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's all the damn kids fault.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just teasing you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And F you for not being able to connect two Xboxes for the Halo 2 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Figuring out that there's a broken wire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, oh well, maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, can I get to chat room now?
[SPEAKER_03]: To be continued.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, as always.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Moving on to the chat room FUs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ooh, didn't we just hear this?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it would be a good FU music, though.
[SPEAKER_24]: MPQ says, a big FU to Washington State for not having any 2DX machines.
[SPEAKER_24]: Poto says, FU to greedy repo men who steal your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_24]: No Halo 2 or Ultramix 2 for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, DS, says, F you to the dumb customers at Best Buy, I know how to fix computers, thank you, ask me one more stupid question, I'll replace your fucking Pentium 4 chip with a potato, oh yeah, F you to cock-teasing girls, you fucking suck, expect a flaming bag of shit on your front door, hey, that's one way to win the chicks over, Jamie, Jamie, chicks dig flaming bags of shit, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: I love it when you're not paying attention to this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a yeast infection.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeast is good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeast is in bread.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like bread.
[SPEAKER_25]: What's wrong there?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not candida yeast.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeast in bread is different than yeast in your vagina, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know what happens when you get a candida yeast buildup in your organs, like your stomach and your intestines?
[SPEAKER_07]: It makes you die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it turns your stomach and your intestines into bread, and then you die, because they can't digest.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ferments them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my lord.
[SPEAKER_24]: We've hit a whole new low tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_24]: Misty says, F me for falling asleep and missing part of the Ultramix 2 show.
[SPEAKER_24]: Aw, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to the fact that DDR Ultramix 2 got the better songs and DDR Extreme USA owners get in the shaft by Konami for favoring Microsoft with a dollar sign over Sony.
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to my braces for being retightened, thus making my teeth hurt.
[SPEAKER_24]: And F you to the fact that I have two hard-to-sell exams tomorrow, both of which I'm not truly prepared for.
[SPEAKER_24]: FU to the Pacers, Ron Artest for punching the wrong fan and FU to the Pistons, Ben Wallace for pushing Artest in the first place Artest got what he deserves and enjoy promoting that rap album now that you can't play this season Dark Knight says my FUs to going work especially on Friday the 25th aka Black Friday because I know that I'm going to be getting these a-hole customers that always seem to give me a total hard time nothing more
[SPEAKER_24]: Sigurd says, F you to the lackluster DS launch.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, but you had G4.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: Where the hell is my WarioWare?
[SPEAKER_24]: That isn't Field of Magic.
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to homeless people because they were chasing me in my dream before turning into Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_23]: Great.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn them.
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to DrawnTogether this past week for only being mildly funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: I agree, it was only mildly funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: More Xander and Foxy and Ling Ling and less everyone else.
[SPEAKER_24]: Final F you to people complaining about it taking too long to get G2 unlocked.
[SPEAKER_24]: I unlocked it in under a minute, so what's the problem?
[SPEAKER_24]: You know something they don't, you little jerk.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know it damn well.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, DarkPetsuya, I'm going to have to agree with Loki, F you to G4 and the stupidest publicity stunt ever.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkLionXVI says, only one F you tonight, F you to my router for suddenly disconnecting me.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you very much for playing everybody in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's do some more Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're starting to run out of show time, so I definitely want to get some more Ultramix 2 songs in before the show's over.
[SPEAKER_24]: And maybe we'll do some Ask Orange Lounge when we come back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ooh, doesn't that sound like fun?
[SPEAKER_24]: I know you kids love that segment.
[SPEAKER_24]: So in this break, Rubberneckin', the Elvis song.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to hear that along with a rock song called Sleepwalker and Tittle Tattle.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_24]: And remember, Ask Orange Lounge is coming up, so send us some questions in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: By the way, by the way, I'm not okay By the way, by the way, I'm not okay By the way, by the way, I'm not okay To be awake is the only thing I want With you, I'm just walking in my sleep To be awake is the only thing I want
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
TonePone Dreams, Alpha Perfection, So Very Hard To Reach Harmony Machine, Tormenting The Sensory Deliciously Evolved, And Yet Nobody Knows Tittle Tattle, Chit And Chat, Shoots In The Breeze, Platter, Clack, Neat And Splatter, There's A Synchronicity
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Gaming Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: So uncensored.
[SPEAKER_23]: and even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio and having a little too much fun with PictoChat, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: I found a way that you could pull down the last image that was drawn or scroll up so you can erase things and change things in the image.
[SPEAKER_24]: It makes a fun game.
[SPEAKER_24]: The DS never knew that they had in there.
[SPEAKER_24]: And you know what else?
[SPEAKER_24]: This is why the N-Gage never worked, because it didn't have PictoChat, honestly.
[SPEAKER_24]: Imagine if you could have PictoChat and send those little pictograms anywhere in the USA.
[SPEAKER_24]: Even to random phone numbers.
[SPEAKER_24]: That'd be the best.
[SPEAKER_10]: What does this cock?
[SPEAKER_16]: What does this cock on the cell phone?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why you call me a cock?
[SPEAKER_10]: I am no rooster.
[SPEAKER_24]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's get to some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: Remember, if you guys have a question, send it in over private message right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also, we'll open up the Skype line in a little bit if you guys want to call in and you have a comment or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, but here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: some stupid question what will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio all I really know is that it's a really good thing that you guys can't see our picto chats cause then you'd think we're perverts as if you didn't already know extra verse tonight alright uh Flair O'Day
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, isn't it a bit strange that they put a good chunk of the unlocks for Ultramix 2 on the V-Rare?
[SPEAKER_24]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: Come to think of it, a good half of the extreme V-Rare songs are unlocks too.
[SPEAKER_24]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_24]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_24]: It kind of took a little bit of the thrill out of the unlocks, the fact that they were all already on the V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_24]: But at the same time, it was some of the best stuff on the mix, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would have liked to have seen more of the different drum songs, but I just thought the V-Rare was great because it had Skulk and Superstar.
[SPEAKER_24]: I thought that was neat.
[SPEAKER_24]: Any other comments, thoughts on the Ultimix 2 VRare?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was just weird that they put so many unlocks on it.
[SPEAKER_24]: You pretty much knew 9 of the unlocks, or was it 9 or 10?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_24]: A whole lot of the unlocks just by picking yourself up a copy of the VRare.
[SPEAKER_24]: Which, by the way, I'm trying to snag us some extra copies so that we can give them away on the show.
[SPEAKER_24]: So even after the Kiryamaoka giveaway is done, we'll do hopefully another giveaway, some Ultramix 2 VRares, maybe for much easier things, just like calling in at a certain time or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's see what Dark Knight has to say.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: If a tree falls in the woods, does it make a sound?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: The real question is, how much of a lifespan will the DS have before Nintendo decides to make a new handheld?
[SPEAKER_24]: Any thoughts on this?
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I do half-hell deeming another color.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously, I give it February.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll have new DS colors, honestly.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then there will be some kind of Super DS or like DS Extreme or something where you're going to have to re-buy the DS because they did the same damn thing with the Game Boy when they did the little... They're going to do DS NES colors and DS Famicom colors and... I mean, they had Game Boy and then they had Game Boy Pocket.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then they had Game Boy Color.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then they had all the fucking colored Game Boy colors.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to be as much crap as the PSP will be.
[SPEAKER_24]: Siegert in our chatroom says, People!
[SPEAKER_24]: There are no color combinations that will work besides the silver and black.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have thought about this for hours.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get a life.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, the QS.
[SPEAKER_25]: Quad screen.
[SPEAKER_25]: Let's see how many screens we can cram into this thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: To be honest, I think the next thing you're going to hear about DS is going to be a Bluetooth network where you can actually play online internet games.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it'll be a peripheral, though.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_25]: Warp Pipe is working on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're not saying that's what they're working on, but that's what they're working on.
[SPEAKER_25]: So you'll see that at E3 this year, though, because they're going to be at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_25]: But not until then.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Doe
[SPEAKER_24]: How did you get the music from Ultramix on the Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_24]: The reason I'm asking is because I like to make a music CD out of the songs from Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very carefully.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, we rip them ourselves, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: We have the soundboard hooked up through the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's how we got tonight's songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I know they're not like 100% perfect quality, so honestly, you may not want to burn them to CD.
[SPEAKER_24]: But honestly, just keep looking around there on some of the different forums out there on the net.
[SPEAKER_24]: Something will turn up soon enough.
[SPEAKER_24]: Always does.
[SPEAKER_24]: Any advice, Loki?
[SPEAKER_25]: DDRUK, once the sim files are out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why are DDR Extreme USA owners getting the shaft now that Ultramix 2 came out and got the better of the songs?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think they just tried to do something different with Extreme, with the whole eye toy thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, you could argue, well, you know, Xbox doesn't have hands and feet mode, and I know that makes a lot of you guys go, big fucking deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, they tried to do something different with the PlayStation, just like they were doing different things with Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I don't want to knock the PlayStation 2 for at least trying something different that wasn't there before.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it wasn't just the eye toy things, but, you know, some new interface, new songs, things like that.
[SPEAKER_24]: It just, you know...
[SPEAKER_24]: Buy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Purchase.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, how many crappy songs can you find in Extreme USA versus how many can you find in Ultramix 2?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, I believe, if I'm not mistaking, it's kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everybody thinks they know, but I think Japan, for the most part, did Extreme.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Hawaii, well, we know Hawaii pretty much, for the most part, did Ultramix 2 with some help from their staff in the Bay.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_24]: They tried something different, and for some folks it didn't work.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_24]: For the most part, people are taking very well to the new music, and hopefully it'll continue.
[SPEAKER_24]: MPQ wants to know, which is better, paying $400 for a Japanese PlayStation 2, 2DX and controller, or driving 14 hours to Ventura, California to play 2DX?
[SPEAKER_24]: I've done both, sadly enough, although my drive was only 8 hours.
[SPEAKER_24]: But...
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: Even when you get it at home, it doesn't quite compare to the arcade, especially because the consumer releases are a little bit behind the arcade releases.
[SPEAKER_24]: So honestly, I wish I could tell you one or the other was better, but face it, you're going to end up doing both, just like I did.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like masturbation and sex.
[SPEAKER_24]: D.D.Arcoholic says, Hi Rob, Jamie, and Matt.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just thought of a super idea and wondered what you thought.
[SPEAKER_24]: Would you do an all night Orange Lounge Radio Marathon live show like on a Saturday night?
[SPEAKER_24]: You could do it for charity even.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be like a slumber party with vodka.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, with one condition.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want an arcade to host it.
[SPEAKER_24]: If we're going to do it overnight, I'm not going to do it in this little apartment.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want arcade games and things to do.
[SPEAKER_24]: So if we could get an arcade in the Sacramento area to agree to it, and I think if we work the charity angle, yes, I'm all down for it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it could be fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or maybe we could talk to our buddy at the theater.
[SPEAKER_23]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_24]: That might be an idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: On the big screen.
[SPEAKER_24]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's an idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll have to think about that one.
[SPEAKER_25]: Can you imagine if we could get PictoChat on that giant screen?
[SPEAKER_25]: That would be so cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Orange Lounge lock-in.
[SPEAKER_24]: I like the idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: I like the charity angle, especially with Christmas coming up.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Asylum.
What?
[SPEAKER_25]: The Asylum.
[SPEAKER_25]: We lock you in.
[SPEAKER_24]: Great.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I'm like, the Asylum is a dance club.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't get it confused.
[SPEAKER_24]: I really do like that idea.
[SPEAKER_24]: And in fact, I want to get in touch with you later about that, DDArcoholic, because maybe you can help me approach some arcades about it.
[SPEAKER_24]: See if anybody would be willing to do it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: If not, we could just always bring our shit to Country Club Lanes, because they're open 24 hours anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I'm all down for it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Misty says, What do you guys want for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I'm so glad she's asking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some spinach.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want sex.
[SPEAKER_23]: But not from Santa.
[SPEAKER_07]: Santa's got years of experience.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Santa would be quite the sugar daddy if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want someone to pay for my plane ticket home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: And I know some friends of mine are going to host them, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: It works out.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not really big on material things.
[SPEAKER_24]: Pretty much like if I want something bad enough, I just go and get it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Honestly, I think the best gifts I've gotten in the past were like things that people made.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like one year, Shark Scroll made me this collage for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_24]: Look at you a sugar mama.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, DS says, My question, will you and the rest of Orange Lounge Radio be suicidal enough to go shopping on Black Friday, which is, of course, the day after Thanksgiving, biggest shopping day of the year?
[SPEAKER_24]: Any plans to go shopping?
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, yeah, actually, I am.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you're going to be in Alabama then, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, I'm still going to be doing some shopping.
[SPEAKER_24]: Still pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, that's that Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually going to be in Dothan.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god, that's where my boss is from.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's so funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll go bomb them for you.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, not my boss's house.
[SPEAKER_24]: What Loki said.
[SPEAKER_24]: I love my boss.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: As far as shopping, no, I don't plan on going to the mall that day.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's nothing that exciting about it for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to stay home and masturbate all day.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_25]: I may make it out.
[SPEAKER_25]: If I have stuff to buy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: I have to think of what I want to buy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Depends if I have my money by then, which I hopefully will.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just want to sleep and play Final Fantasy and Ultramix, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: Is that so wrong?
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, I don't want to go shopping.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to stay home.
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe get Mongolian barbecue.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mmm, Mongolian.
[SPEAKER_24]: Legend of Zaku says, so what do you think might be on your Thanksgiving Day table, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_24]: unique side dishes out of the norm?
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie, what do you think might be a unique dish on your table?
[SPEAKER_07]: Haggis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that for real?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, for real.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't really have many out of the ordinary things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know who's going to be cooking Thanksgiving dinner when I'm there, so I'm just going to say, put food in front of me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm off the diet today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feed me.
[SPEAKER_24]: And remember, don't eat in DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, but I should take a minute to plug the special that our buddies over on DDR Freak Radio are doing on Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_24]: They're doing like an all-day marathon of DDR, like back-to-back, like non-stop till your brain explodes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously, it's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_24]: Second mix, third mix, fourth mix, all of it back-to-back.
[SPEAKER_24]: What time are they starting over there?
[SPEAKER_24]: Nine, ten o'clock?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, check ddrfreak.com Go to ddrfreak, yeah Yeah, I mean, like you don't go there anyway But, you know, I just wanted to get that plug out there Don't forget Alright, let's see Moving on Oh, my dish at my table I don't eat turkey, I hate turkey So Thanksgiving's a really shitty holiday for me But my mom says she will be cooking ham And I like ham And she actually says she might just be ready to say fuck it And order a pizza, which I've been telling her to do for years So we might do that That would rock Deep fried turkey
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, it doesn't take too long to clean because they're really yummy.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't like turkey.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkTetsuya said, have any of you picked up Metal Gear Solid 3 yet?
[SPEAKER_24]: If so, what do you think so far?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, DarkTetsuya, if you were listening on Thursday, you would know that we got Metal Gear Solid 3, but haven't really played it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got it, and we haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got it, and we haven't played it yet because they've been playing Halo.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sadly enough, I've been playing more Rumble Roses than Metal Gear Solid 3.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rumble Roses is every cheesy thing you would want it to be.
[SPEAKER_24]: It is so horrifically bad in a great way.
[SPEAKER_24]: Last question.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, not really a question, but a comment from DDArchaholic says, Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll make calls and stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Good, good deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe we'll open up the Skype line for like one quick call if anybody wants to get in there.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll open it up and see if anybody wants to call.
[SPEAKER_24]: A lot of good questions.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next week on the show, don't forget that MidiHead is going to be interviewed.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's something we're really looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's going to be good to talk to him.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to know if he's remixed anything else.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because that In My Eyes remix is damn good.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I want to know if there's anything else there.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can visit his site over at midihead.com, of course.
[SPEAKER_24]: And hopefully we get more people in the future as well.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, Siggy's calling back.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think he has a question or comment.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, Siggy, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've forgotten one more thing you mentioned about 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's an option called Random Plus.
[SPEAKER_24]: Random Plus, and what does that do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's the same thing as Random, only you do it... Scratch is included in it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and the way you access Random Plus is hold the key wherever the random is for at least a few seconds, and the random will turn red.
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's how you access Random Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, supposedly you have to do something before that, but they'll do that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: So maybe it's an unlock, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I'm going to go and take another call real fast, Siggy, but thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's take another... Oh, damn it, just missed it.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was you that just called... Oh, maybe I hung up on him.
[SPEAKER_24]: Call back, person that just tried to call, because I think I hung up on him.
[SPEAKER_24]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, it's MPQ.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hello, MPQ, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_18]: I was just wondering if I have any right to complain about 2DX when I have...
[SPEAKER_18]: A poppin' music machine within driving distance.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, I don't know, what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_24]: Does he have a right to complain about two things?
[SPEAKER_24]: What mix of poppin' music is it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Five.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, see, now five's kinda old.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, it's good, but it's old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you can complain.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd say you still have a right to complain, but not as much as the rest of us, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bye.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, we gotta wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry to keep these calls quick, but we do need to wrap things up, and that means we gotta go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_24]: Arcadian, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, yay, Horde weekend coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Uh, Explicit, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_23]: Good turkey.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know there's codes out there.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've seen them before for Grand Theft Auto San Andreas where you can modify the damage that each gun does.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I can't find them for the life of me, and that pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_25]: That and, um... Yeah, I need to buy some more games for the DST.
[SPEAKER_24]: My final thought is... I don't want to get up and fly tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_24]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_24]: And you know, I left my email with all my travel information at work.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I know what flight I'm on and everything.
[SPEAKER_24]: So hopefully I don't have a problem.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or else I'm screwed.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is... God damn you people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sign up for stuff and give me my iPod.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh God, you didn't get suckered into that too, did you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no, it's just because it's an experiment, so I want help.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll help me, won't you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't buy into that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to get my mom to sign up.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no, it's more of an, I don't really care, it's just more of an experiment just to see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I found that if you do the blockbuster thing, you can cancel it before they charge you with anything.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, yeah, you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, uh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I decided it's fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a distraction.
[SPEAKER_07]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_24]: I just don't want spam.
[SPEAKER_07]: So looking forward to going to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one doesn't give you any spam mail.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm looking forward to going to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_07]: Getting the hell out of this state.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, gee, thank you.
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll miss you too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not meaning the people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm meaning the other people that don't exist in my universe.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tune in next week for more fun on the show.
[SPEAKER_24]: And hopefully, what I'm kind of hoping is that maybe we can get Karaoke Revolution 3 next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because you know when Jamie leaves, Matt has to sing.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's tradition.
[SPEAKER_24]: PICTOCHAT
[SPEAKER_21]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_21]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_16]: Lacey Pings, the wife is missing Didn't ask for her permission I'm wearing her clothes, her silk pantyhose Walking round in women's underwear In the store, there's a teddy With little straps, like spaghetti
[SPEAKER_01]: It holds me so tight, like handcuffs at night Walkin' round in women's underwear In the office there's a guy named Melvin He pretends that I am Murphy Brown He'll say, are you ready?
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll say, whoa man Let's wait until the wife is out of town Later on
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jamie, why the Christmas songs already?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I figured if our major department stores can do it and Walgreens can, so can I. Oh my god, are they playing Christmas songs at Walgreens already?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got the Christmas stuff up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went to Walmart the other day because we went to buy a silly headgear and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: A headgear?
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: We bought Care Bears party hats this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they already had a whole Christmas section open.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_24]: And to answer the question in the chatroom, yes, that was from the Bob and Tom show, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ryachan says, it's funny to go into Walmart and walk around in the women's section looking for stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: My mom and my dad just start singing, walk around in women's underwear.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because you're in the department.
[SPEAKER_24]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: So when do you go on your great adventure, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm flying out Wednesday at 2.45.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who wants to drive me to the airport?
[SPEAKER_24]: I would, but I'm working.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still trying to find a way to the airport.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, you could always do a shuttle?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm working it out, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that's good.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I guess we'll just kind of keep it a short afterbirth tonight then, since a lot of you guys don't have anything else to say.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, I know we didn't get to a lot of those Ultramix 2 MP3s, so I'm going to put in the rest right now so you guys can hear it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because I bet you guys, some of you guys were waiting to hear some of the rest of those songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we will get to those right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to start it with Jam On It.
[SPEAKER_24]: and La Cucaracha, Life is a Game, Looking for You, Mellow, Monkey Punk, Play My Game, and Red Room.
[SPEAKER_24]: All those songs you're going to hear right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a block of Ultramix 2 music.
[SPEAKER_24]: Enjoy, you guys.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have to set it up here.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now we can do it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Can't hear me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I jam on it, I jam on it, jam on and on and on and on it And if you're feeling like you wanna dance on that then go on ahead and float it Cause jamming on is what we do best, it's what separates us from the rest And if you don't think who's there for real, let me tell you what happened to the man at sea Say Superman had come to town to see who he could rock He blew away every crew he faced until he reached our block
[SPEAKER_16]: It's because we're three stories high, but one was made of steel.
[SPEAKER_16]: And when we brought our dead outside, he said, I'm so real.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, Superman looked up at me.
[SPEAKER_19]: He said, you rock so naturally.
[SPEAKER_19]: I said, now that you've learned a deal, let me tell you why I'm so real.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm Cosmo D from outer space.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can do rock for human race.
[SPEAKER_19]: I do it right because I can't do it wrong.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's why the whole world is singing this song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Outro Music
Thanks for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Life is a game, jump on the ride, turn on your flame, let's play tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you try to run, don't you try to hide, life is a game, let's play tonight.
[SPEAKER_16]: Life is a game, turn on your light Turn on your pain, let's play tonight Don't you try to run, don't you try to hide Life is a game, let's play tonight
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: In the city, looking for you Tonight, tonight, looking for you In the city, looking for you Alright, and when I find you I'll give you love, no It's all behind you, I'm gonna make it count No, no, no, no, no
Innocent Day, looking for you
All of a sudden, a commercial comes on and says, Hey, come to the zoo!
So me and my friends, we plowed in the car, didn't have much gas, good thing we didn't have to go to
I turned my head, he stole my ice cream That little monkey stole my ice cream And everybody
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't fuck it, with a monkey Don't fuck it, with a monkey That little monkey made a monkey out of me
[SPEAKER_19]: Turn the page and rock your body
[SPEAKER_09]: Say my name, I feel I'm burning up inside Play my game, I'm losing my mind
[SPEAKER_08]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, that was all the new DDR Ultramix 2 songs that we didn't get to during the live show tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jam on it, La Cucaracha, Life is a Game, Look at, excuse me, where's my cough button?
[SPEAKER_24]: Looking for you, Mellow, Monkey Punk, Play My Game, and lastly there, Jesper Kidd with Red Room.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, now we're going to go to some commercial free Bomani music and more.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you guys very much for tuning in and listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Excuse me, where's my cough button?
[SPEAKER_22]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Have a great night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: And now we'll be right back.