All the time we'll be together cause it's yours and mine Forever we're in this one thing
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
All the time we'll be together cause it's yours and mine Forever we're in this one day Don't you take my hand for I won't be your man So tonight we're gonna dance the night away One and one is two, don't you be so cruel Synchronize this love, it's what we got to do All the time we'll be together cause it's yours and mine
[SPEAKER_33]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_14]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_31]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_31]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_31]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_31]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_32]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is episode number 117.
[SPEAKER_10]: And for this, 117...
[SPEAKER_05]: 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to the B-Money scene's most crowded radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_10]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_10]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_10]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Her name is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know her better as DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_24]: When?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Angry Bunny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Grrrr!
[SPEAKER_10]: Also joining us as always, your other co-host, our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, also with us tonight, we have a whole crapload of special guests.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's so many.
[SPEAKER_10]: Joining us tonight, say hello to Floatwalk.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's happening?
[SPEAKER_05]: And whenever Floatwalk's here, you know Shark Skrull's here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just sneezed.
[SPEAKER_21]: I sound all weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's stuffed up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also here tonight, I don't know if he's been to the show in quite some time, if ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to Islander.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Doing just great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also here tonight, say hello to someone else who hasn't been here in an awfully long time, that has never been to this studio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Never.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, and also with us tonight, the town's resident poppin' music whore, and now 2DX 8-style consumer whore, as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to Navi!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: And with us tonight, as he is just about every other week, our Orange Ones Radio mascot, say hello to Arcadium42.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, so as you can see, we have a whole hell of a lot of people in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to talk to everybody in studio, we do have the chat up on our TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just visit our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: We weren't here last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you guys all had a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we've got a lot of stuff to catch up on tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ultramix 2, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to talk about 2DX Red's hit.
[SPEAKER_10]: News is coming out about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Consumer Style for 8Style as well as Pop It Music 10 just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_10]: We might actually talk about Bomani tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know this is weird for some of you guys.
[SPEAKER_22]: The what?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Manny.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to talk about that The Manny stuff tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Manny.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Manny.
[SPEAKER_10]: But first, you guys know we have to take a little break here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We will have the Skype line open at some point tonight, so if you don't know what that's all about, you should educate yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_10]: In this break, we're going to play some songs from the Ultramix 2 V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know some of you guys may not have heard this stuff yet, so this should be really interesting to you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: And even if you have heard it, it's really good, so listen to it again.
[SPEAKER_10]: In this break, we're going to hear some remixes from the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to hear I Feel by Toy starting it off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Check this out.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be right back with more Orange Lounge Radio Live.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_33]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_14]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_27]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_27]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode 117 on this 11-7.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sure glad I took that lozenge, you know, took care of my voice problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going on with everybody being sick lately?
[SPEAKER_10]: Quick poll in the room, because we have a lot of people here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who has been sick in the past week, or feeling it a little bit?
[SPEAKER_10]: One, two, three, I thought, didn't you just say you were sick, Navi?
[SPEAKER_10]: As of today.
[SPEAKER_10]: As of this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Four.
[SPEAKER_10]: About half.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm a sick club.
[SPEAKER_10]: Half the folks in here are in the sick club right now, so I'm a little worried.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope we don't catch it, but I think everybody's past contagious stage.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I exhale hard enough, I can make the raspy voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've got the rockin' pneumonia and the boogie-woogie flu.
[SPEAKER_24]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_10]: The boogie-woogie flu?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a song.
[SPEAKER_24]: You ever heard?
[SPEAKER_24]: I cannot believe you've never heard that song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe I have heard it and I just forgot it because it sucked.
[SPEAKER_24]: It doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, if you're just joining us, welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We do have a whole lot of special guests here in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Flo walks here, Sharks Girl, Islander, Iguana Girl, Navi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcadian 42, and then of course myself, DarkSakura, and Loki, all here.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a crowded house.
[SPEAKER_10]: A good way to come back from episode, or I should say a non-episode, not having a show for a week, so it's a good way to come back.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we're going to start off tonight's show as we start off every week, this week being no different, and I want to know, how was your week and how was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: And also tonight, a bonus question, how was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, start us off as you always do.
[SPEAKER_24]: My Halloween, well we did the thing at work and I was wearing these fuzzy leg warmers and fuzzy arm warmers and had cat ears and a tail and went around playing with yarn and blah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_24]: We had Rocky though on Saturday night, well technically Sunday morning, Saturday night, and I got to play with lights.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow, it's
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I just, I didn't, I don't think I had enough time to get used to it, but it was cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Halloween, I was just sort of like, dress up, what's that?
[SPEAKER_24]: And the rest of the week was all busy, busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_24]: And had fun yesterday, hanging out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, that was it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I kept this one short because we have a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm shocked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Usually you have like a 15 minute monologue.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, FloWalk, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, Halloween, gosh, I really can't remember much of it because there just really wasn't a bunch of Halloween type stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't get a chance to break out my Lucas from the Wizard costume.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aww, I bet it was so bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Indeed it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, uh, let's see, as far as the week goes, gosh, man, I think... I just have to interject, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: You went to Classic Gaming Expo, of course, you were there, and I think most, well, a few people in this room went to Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how many of you guys saw the power glove that was in the room, where they were showing all the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every time, people would walk by it, like, every other person would go, it's so bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Myself included.
[SPEAKER_10]: Myself included.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, as far as the week goes, gosh, I think I probably speak like just everyone else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably been sucked up in way too many video games to count.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Katamari's just been giving me eye strain like a mother.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although, for those who have played, I don't know if anyone else has gone a perfect 10 meters on the North Star, but... Alright, nice!
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool, yeah, it took me like about seven tries or so, but once I figured out the pattern, it's like, yeah, cake, and then all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, let's see, I actually am not working at Konami for the time being, but I did get hired over at the Princeton Review over just this week, so if anyone needs some hookups on SAT cheat sheets, hey, then again, I didn't need that because I got 1440 on mine, so, hey.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then today is just, of course, you know, always making the track up from the South Bay up here and jamming to Sirius Radio, which is like the greatest invention next to the iPod.
[SPEAKER_01]: And here we are now, and it only gets better from here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is Sirius the one that's getting Howard Stern?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was checking out because I need to get my car stereo replaced, and I was kind of thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sirius went from 600,000 customers to over...
[SPEAKER_21]: just under a million in less than a month on that one announcement alone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Figures.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm one of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: No surprises.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be my dream one day to get this shit on satellite radio, but yeah, I'm not holding my breath on that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I did see one of those things at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like a stereo where you can listen to internet radio like anywhere in your house.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was $180.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And hopefully, you know, in about a year, technology comes down.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shark Skrill, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't even remember what I did for Halloween, really.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this thing working or no?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's working.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go back and make sure the audio levels are up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, yeah, I just kind of hung out for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was boring.
[SPEAKER_21]: You went shopping today, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: I bought shoes.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was a good girl.
[SPEAKER_21]: I only came back with one pair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you one of those girls that has like 100 pairs of shoes in their closet?
20.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's probably average for a lot of girls I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the scary thing is I haven't bought any shoes in like two years.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then in like the past probably nine months, I've bought like 10 pair.
[SPEAKER_21]: I get them like all the time.
[SPEAKER_21]: People are threatening to call me Imelda.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I'm not even going to joke with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of my best friends in high school, who I used to do my public access show with back in the day, she had 100 pairs of shoes in her closet.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, there's not enough days in the year to wear all those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you worn every one of those pairs each one day at least?
[SPEAKER_10]: She's like, I think so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, I went through my shoe stash the other day, and I was like, I don't even remember buying these things.
[SPEAKER_21]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_21]: These are cute.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now I'm wearing them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's talk to Islander.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_02]: Week's going by just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only one who's, like, not sick, thanks to this, like, freakishly good immune system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, like, no, seriously, like, Jessica, like, just kind of shakes her head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, as you can see on camera, she's giving me the finger, because I hardly ever get sick, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's the RTF genes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it definitely is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It must be the RTF genes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, uh, no, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Halloween was basically my day to recover from Rocky.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what was really funny was that after dinner, we went and got some food.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not some food, but some candy for the kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no kids showed up at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was kind of surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: None.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No kids at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other than that, I've been trying...
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying to get ready for... I wanted to go to the Madden Challenge for Madden 2005, but that's not happening because I suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've just lately been playing a lot of SmackDown.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did I tell you one day I saw the Madden 2005 bus broke down on the side of the road?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, on the 680... On the 680, I was driving down... I think it was one time I was coming to see you one day, SharkScrawlers, driving down 680, and there was the bus broke down on the side of the road.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, that is hilarious!
[SPEAKER_10]: I talked about that like weeks ago on Outside Talks, but yeah, it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Iguana Girl, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a little while.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's been quite a while since you and I have been on a show together.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of like a reunion.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_19]: 2001 all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad we can be candid about it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, for those that don't know, Iguana Girl and I...
[SPEAKER_10]: Weren't the best of friends the last couple years.
[SPEAKER_19]: To put it lightly, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, you know, but, you know, time heals things.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we've got a bunch of big balls and we sucked them up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you know, we just, you know, kissed and made up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, without the kissing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, but it's worked out good, and, you know, everybody always thought there was this big, like, oh, Orange Lounge versus DDR Freak, because you are the goddess behind DDR Freak Radio, and everybody's always been like, oh, you know, it's, oh, Orange Lounge versus DDR Freak, and not really.
[SPEAKER_24]: We know, I've been sitting here going, uh, don't I do both?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, it's good to have you on, and certainly, if you want to make a plug for DDR Freak Radio, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listen to DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, I think there's...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there's like... I think there's 90,000 some odd stations on Life 365.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't checked.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are many more stations that we could pick on besides DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: For those who don't know, Guanagirl and I used to do a show way back in the day under Sedation Live, which is still on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just doesn't have us on it anymore, but it's got the very lovely... Kind of moved to Texas.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, the show went and moved to Texas.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it does have the very lovely Jenna, I can't remember her name.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jenna Saunders and Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they still are on the air, so check them out, understationalive.org.
[SPEAKER_10]: And sometimes you can even hear the old episodes have a Gwana Girl and I on them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're reunited on the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: In our other names, mind you.
[SPEAKER_10]: The real deal names.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, okay, so enough of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_19]: My Halloween was, as most other people in this room, or a good portion of other people in this room, would be spent at Rocky Horror.
[SPEAKER_19]: I played Columbia and got to get all dressed up in all the sequins and do my hair and all that fun jazz and bounce around and hope that my top didn't fall off.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then after that, Halloween, I got Cheat Night.
[SPEAKER_19]: I actually got to have...
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay, cheat night!
[SPEAKER_19]: Got to go to Old Spaghetti Factory and eat those nasty carbs and all that fun schnazz.
[SPEAKER_19]: This week, unfortunately, has been spent being sick.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sick...
[SPEAKER_19]: Work, school.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sick work, school.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like my mantra this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I ended up having to take a couple days off of work, which sucked.
[SPEAKER_19]: And today has been pretty neato mosquito.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yesterday was pretty neato mosquito because I got to spend a lot of time with Miss DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: And today has been all spiffy because I get to spend it with everybody else.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I'm in a relatively good mood and hopefully I won't be like coughing too hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, Halloween, I was at work, I did nothing, there was no reason to dress up, I work in a deli, I have a costume that smelt like bleach and meat when I come home.
[SPEAKER_07]: My week, well actually the past couple weeks have just been way too busy for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, shit's been falling apart at work and I've been working like 46, 48 hours a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually kind of looking forward to being sick right now, hoping it lands on a day that I don't have off.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, overtime pay rocks though when you've got, and I know you being the import bar, you've got what, eights coming out?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's crap coming out, but on my paychecks right now, they're almost double what I normally get, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: All I've been really buying are all my little collectible stuff, but I don't have any more room.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even have room for the stuff that's coming in the mail this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually have over $100 left out of my paycheck this week, so I don't know what's going on with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm just going to take some time off.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to tell that cold to hold off about a week so you can get sick on 15 November.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, three days after.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or maybe 20 November, around that time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Assuming my package gets in the States by... No, it can't, because the 18th is Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remembering back to how things process when they ship from Japan, actually it's going to kind of suck, because I'll have to wait more days.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have the science down to a T. My shit will ship on any given damn day.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as the package gets into the States by Friday, it will ship on a weekend or a holiday.
[SPEAKER_07]: If not, it flies around in circles over Hawaii or something for the weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then it gets on San Francisco on Monday, and then it gets processed and whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, okay, so that was my week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then today, today was alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I slept in forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tried playing some 2DX again today.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was having timing problems when going back to old styles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Got pissed off.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I'm proud of myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those are good scores.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just jealous because I haven't touched my 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't worry, I'm not going to be bragging on here or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was what I did today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I sucked at everything else today.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, I'm 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to ask something.
[SPEAKER_24]: I actually played 7th style last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_24]: So I did do something with the money related.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_24]: And my copy of Papa 9 arrived.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_24]: I haven't played it yet, but I have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have enough time to unlock everything before 10 comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That gambler's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't even know that I'm going to get 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll take a very, very, very, very long time.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's quite alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't have a lot of time to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe if we find what, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you have to be in the game to let it sit in its place so the timer will run and count.
[SPEAKER_07]: Find that and let it sit on for, like, you know, a day.
[SPEAKER_24]: I like to play the little RPG mode.
[SPEAKER_24]: You open the chest, you have X song unlocked.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But seriously, it probably took, like, it took... I don't know, whatever, never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well then we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go on to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_03]: For Halloween, I didn't do jack shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I watched Dark City the night before, but didn't do anything on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next morning I got some candy, but unlike last year, they didn't do the big sale, because it was like Monday instead of like a weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either that or Safeway learned their lesson about people coming in the next day and buying things for like 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead they just did it for half price, so I bought some stuff and shared it with work, and then worked all week and didn't do much this weekend other than straighten up a little bit and then catch up on message boards and
[SPEAKER_03]: Then today went to store and then went to the arcade for a little bit and played one game of Drum Mania and the cymbal was broken and one game of Guitar Freaks and that was working alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's good to know there's still some people in town that actually play Bomani.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's good to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I wanted to say, because you mentioned the day before Halloween, I just wanted to say a happy late birthday to Navi and Mel B, who both have the same birthday, if you can believe that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Day before Halloween.
[SPEAKER_16]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to figure out who's older.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I'll talk about my weekend, my day, and my Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, my Halloween was kind of stupid because I was having relationship issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I didn't really have much of a Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a talking to on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were no treats on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: And really not even a trick either.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you had good food.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: But there was good food.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, there was good food.
[SPEAKER_10]: And because we had gone to Spaghetti Factory, I went and celebrated Cheat Day, even though every day is Cheat Day for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: We got to make fun of the guys in Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: We made fun of the guys in Walgreens who were like, I don't know what they were doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were hitting on you or something?
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe they were drunk.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were drunk.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were very drunk.
[SPEAKER_10]: But so, as you may have picked up, a lot of folks in the room here, when we're not doing DDR, we're doing Rocky Horror, so I was involved with all that too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quite involved with all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope you don't see the pictures.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of girls making threats over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I got pictures of you too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't push me.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was Halloween the day before.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this last week was pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got back into playing Final Fantasy XI, which, you know, addict, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I play that quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, yeah, that was my cue.
[SPEAKER_10]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, gosh, not a whole lot else going on, really.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was watching Loki play Grand Theft Auto most of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw The Incredibles last night, which was a cute movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of people are saying it's going to be Oscar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Kill Bill Vol.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2 a little better, but, you know, I just like violence.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I decided on Saturday, this will be yesterday, that I want to be just like Tanya, and I'm going to start the DDR diet.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I have to modify my diet a little bit because part of my diet is that I want abs.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm now doing the DDRS diet, which is DDR and sit-ups.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see how that works out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll keep you posted on my progress.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I found that I'm actually playing Max 2 a lot for DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because nobody's on Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a couple months ago I was playing Ultramix and there would be some nice people on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I've been kind of pissed off lately because whenever I sign on to Ultramix, all the games on there are like 8 and 9 footer songs, which is cool and all.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I can play those once in a while, but I don't like playing them back to back to back for a half hour.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it really stinks when you're playing against people on a controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I'll have to wait for Ultramix 2 to come out so that Xbox Live kind of gets a swift kick in the ass and, you know, that gets jump-started again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll have people playing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for the meantime, it's all about the mega dance hits non-stop in Max 2, which has, you know, my Kylie and Ghost and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it's been a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, sit-ups.
[SPEAKER_10]: I threw my back out yesterday doing it though because a hard lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_10]: Always stretch before you exercise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Always stretch.
[SPEAKER_10]: How could I be so stupid?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess we should hear from Loki as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your Halloween?
[SPEAKER_10]: My week was alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't do much.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did I do this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's something between Final Fantasy XI and Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um, let's see what else I'll say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we went on our first quote-unquote ghost hunt yesterday.
[SPEAKER_10]: We went to Coloma for what seemed like hours, but actually it was only about an hour.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um... It was stupid, actually, because...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it was just walking around a stupid cemetery and taking pictures of gravestones and that was just like, eh, whatever, but it kind of...
[SPEAKER_10]: We kind of got a dry run for the whole ghost hunting thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyways, related to that, I finished the so-called Gate to Hell device thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was hoping to bring it along with me yesterday, but we didn't have a recorder anyway, so that would have not worked.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, how the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's done, so that's one project out of the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: And other than that, I also saw The Incredibles, and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And... What else did I do?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Halloween...
[SPEAKER_10]: Since I was kind of forced to dress up, or I should say persuaded to dress up by my girlfriend, I ended up dressing up like Loki that day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I ironically left from Dogma, so I had a nice coat and wings, and that was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, I don't know, we just had a party and watched the new Dawn of the Dead and then Shaun of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's all I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, have you seen that preview for the brand new Mask sequel?
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember the Mask with Jim Carrey?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, it looks so lame.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Alan Cumming, who is my god, he's so awesome, he plays Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ha ha ha, Cumming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess we'll do now.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go to another break, and then when we come back, I want to make some big announcements.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a big announcement to make tonight regarding a giveaway, a really, really big giveaway that we're doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've heard us talking about it for a while, and we even promised it would happen a couple months ago, but it didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's all right, because it really, really is happening soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: We actually have a date.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have the prizes in our possession, and if you don't know what we're talking about...
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to talk about it when we come back from this break, featuring more of the Ultramix 2 VRare.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also tonight, we're going to hear some stuff from 2DX Red at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: So in this break, a lot of you guys in the chat room were requesting to hear the Max 300 remix, so we're going to make that happen for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: And as well as some Gyrus, the new Gyrus mix is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I know there's some fans of Day Behavior too, so we'll throw them in there as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
I was picked up for a TV show It's called P24 I am the girl that you all know To love, hate or adore I've been waiting all my life Just to be seen Seen by everyone I wanted to be someone
[SPEAKER_23]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_16]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live here on this lovely Sunday evening, as we are every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a big week for those of you guys that are Xbox fans.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know a lot of you guys have Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huge game coming out Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Biggest release.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you've been waiting for it all year long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Karaoke Revolution is coming out for Xbox on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you can't wait for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I hear that folks are going to be lining up around the corner at midnight to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But just, you know, don't riot please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's say orderly.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's enough Karaoke Revolution for everyone.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hear that they expect that there could be extra copies on the shelves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a couple.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but seriously, Karaoke Revolution, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: It came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I know we were talking about Karaoke Revolution, Xbox, a couple weeks ago on the show, and then suddenly, I remember Iguana Girl made a post in her live journal.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was actually talking about Karaoke Revolution Volume 3.
[SPEAKER_19]: Volume 3, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, Iguana Girl and I have been known to do some karaoke in the past.
[SPEAKER_19]: and one of the songs that's being featured happens to be something that both Sky and I used to do on a semi-regular basis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Back when we actually spoke.
[SPEAKER_19]: And for those that are really interested, there is a file.
[SPEAKER_23]: Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_19]: on the internet that you can find somewhere at a particular convention that a particular Sky and I went to.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, that was when we first played DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the same weekend that we first played DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you want to see what I look like the first time I played DDR with this hideous zit right on my nose.
[SPEAKER_19]: The hideous face!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my God, the face!
[SPEAKER_19]: But yeah, if you're...
[SPEAKER_19]: If you're coos enough to be able to find it, then, you know, that file is still out there on the internet so far as I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just think about what... Now, pop quiz, you guys, think about what Iguana Girl and I talked about during the last little banter session, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you might be able to find it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so anyway, Iguana Girl posted KREF3...
[SPEAKER_10]: And I knew, I had heard the Karaoke Revolution 3 had duets, and I even remember looking at an early song list, but I just kind of skimmed it because there were so many songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even remember connecting that, oh my god, Love Shack was in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because maybe at the time I didn't care either.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: That Love Shack crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I don't want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameFacts.com GameFacts.com
[SPEAKER_19]: and the Karaoke Revolution 2 booth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because, you know, they had a nice little seat and it was air-conditioned and I liked to sing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they had the little Logitech microphones.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Little handhelds, which, thankfully, we're getting.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was assumed that, okay, well, we'll get to try this out next May.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I was kind of going...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it just seems like, you know, to put out the song, six months to wait for that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I decided to look for a street date, and sure enough, GameFacts.com, I bring it up, says 11-9 is the street date.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, is Xbox coming out the same day?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure enough, Karaoke Revolution Xbox, 11-9.
[SPEAKER_10]: A date you guys might have heard of for certain releases of certain games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I have no idea where the hell this comes from.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have any idea, Mel?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you have some of the inside scoop at Konami, but do you have any idea how the hell this just blindsided us all?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think what all boils down to is it just makes marketing sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, KR1 did really well, KR2, you know, followed up pretty nicely, and hey, it's holiday season, why not milk the product for what it's worth, really?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't think it's any surprise that we're getting a karaoke revolution 3 and duets, Logical's next step in the right direction, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: That was fast!
[SPEAKER_01]: It really wasn't that hard to, you know, I mean, 1 and 2 were pretty much not that different, you know, aside from just one extra in the mode.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's pretty safe to say after they did, like, KR1, they had already been working on KR3 because it's really just kind of like drop this in and, you know, you just kind of add on top as opposed to redoing a whole new engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mean, it pretty much looks the same, but now you've got duets, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now you guys all out there in Radioland will have to find a friend to play this game with.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please go out and find a friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, please, in fact, just for the sake of having a life.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this is good, because now Iwana Girl and I can practice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you know, someday, at our favorite bar, they have to do a duets contest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someday, it's got to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we need to talk to our favorite KJ about making that happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we've got to win that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we can spend the money on games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I'm going to be fucking broke after November.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quick poll, going around the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Games you're looking forward to by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't have to be Babani, just any games you're looking forward to by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh man, there's still more stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, it's kind of hard to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, obviously, yeah, you know, the 8th style is definitely the one I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still looking forward to Rumble Roses, that's going to be pretty dope.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that does come out Tuesday, awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: It seems like most of the games I'm looking forward to have already come out, and it's like, you know what, I need to look forward to more, man, I'm still catching up on like three or four more games, you know, it's like, maybe by March, you know, I'll be caught up, and then by that time E3 rolls around, and it's like, great, more anticipation, you know, in May, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I figured they're just kind of blowing everything out now because once next-gen systems come out, you know, obviously those first launch titles usually kind of blow ass and, you know, but yeah, I think Romo Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: right now is definitely high on my list.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shark Skrull, anything you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_21]: Right now it's mostly like Ultramix 2 and 8th Style because I've got all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just got Donkey Kongo a month or two ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, how was that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: We didn't get a chance to pick it up for the show here.
[SPEAKER_10]: That and Tycho, we completely missed.
[SPEAKER_21]: I am so freaking addicted to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just sit there and just bop away.
[SPEAKER_21]: My mom's like, what the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm playing Kongo, leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_21]: And my friend from Nashville, Cincinnati, everywhere just came back and he's got it too.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I found someone I can play with.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might have to buy this too before the next time I visit.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will drive your mom crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, yeah, you know, I got that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just got Burnout 3.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got Star Wars Battlefront.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just catching up to everything I've just bought recently.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_21]: The freaking crack game from way back.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just catching up to what I already bought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_21]: For the most part.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander, what are you looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Mel, I'm looking forward to Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much everything that I'm looking forward to has already been released.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of things I still need to pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably, for example, MK Deception.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still want to pick up just for MK1.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to get the Collector's Edition for MK1, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought Deception, but it doesn't have MK1 on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, there's...
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a few others, but I mean recently we just picked up, you know, of course we have Extreme, Katamari Damacy, Madden 2005 for me, and SmackDown vs. Raw for myself, and between those four games, I mean, there's still stuff on Extreme that I haven't unlocked yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because I've got so much stuff to play, so most of the stuff I've been looking for has already been released, so I just need to, you know, just kind of save up for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Iguana Girl, what are you looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I would officially like to start the Iguana Girl Really Needs New Games Fund because I am too damn broke to be able to afford anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: I would really, really love to be able to get A-Style, but first I'd love to get 7-Style, a new controller.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's kind of helpful to have a controller that functions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have a PayPal you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_19]: If I could remember the name, I would.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm incredibly broke and trying to make ends meet, but almost out of debt type of deal.
[SPEAKER_19]: I would love to get 8th style, I'd love to get 7th style still.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I would love to get an Xbox to be able to play the Xbox versions of games.
[SPEAKER_19]: And also, of course, because I'm a karaoke whore, Karaoke Revolution 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Navi.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I bet you not a single one of his games are going to be domestic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, as far as ones that have yet to be released.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still want to play Deception and San Andreas, but just haven't really gotten around to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so looking forward to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Any interest in the US version at all?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't checked out any song listings for that yet, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: But... God, what else was there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Supposedly, the sequel to Karate Mani Damashii is still supposed to be out before the year's over, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, the Japanese one came out in February.
[SPEAKER_07]: They haven't given a release date on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're being all super secretive on it, but I think it still says it's supposed to be out before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I think I'm going to go get one of those Dragon Warrior slime controllers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those are so cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: What site can they go to to check those out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, they're now up for pre-order.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just checked last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're up for pre-orders at NCSX and Japan Video Games, and they're $45.00.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_29]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the only thing I'd be anticipating would be 8th style, because there's so many things, even, there's so many songs I like in that mix, in that style.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I haven't played, like, 7th style in months.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mainly because I, since I do typing and stuff all day, it's kind of hard to do more stuff with my hands.
[SPEAKER_03]: And nothing really else, because I hardly follow games anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't touched my Japanese PS2 in months.
[SPEAKER_10]: It feels so neglected.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's crying in my room under the pile of laundry it's under.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to cuddle with it tonight and let it know I still love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just, you know, have no use for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some rejection.
[SPEAKER_24]: Poor thing's going to go crying off to the Xbox now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, my JPS2 is going to elope with my GameCube.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ever since Josh and I stopped playing Four Swords, I haven't touched the GameCube either.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to elope.
[SPEAKER_24]: You'll get the GS2.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, what are you looking forward to this holiday?
[SPEAKER_24]: Definitely ApeStyle, which I actually have to go and play Asia and make my pre-order.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, I know for sure I'm getting the Taiko no Tatsujin US one, because Dan basically slipped and told me he was getting it for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Although he made an interesting slip something about an arcade-style controller, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: for GDX.
[SPEAKER_24]: We were talking about expensive presents.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie's favorite kind, for those listening, by the way.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't really think I'm going to get it, but I was talking about a $400 set of Copic markers that I wanted.
[SPEAKER_24]: They had it at A1 Comics, and I was like,
[SPEAKER_24]: I really want this, but I would rather have a tablet, because I want a nice big art tablet.
[SPEAKER_24]: He was like, well, you could get that, or you could get an arcade-style controller.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then he didn't say anything else.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_30]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Very.
[SPEAKER_24]: Although, honestly, I want to try actually building one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I haven't seen any place now that has 2DX arcade style controllers for anything less than $500 now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't there a third party that was making one though?
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't there a third party that was getting one to make one?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's tons of third parties for pop and music arcade style controllers and they're only like $250.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, they've gone up like $150 since I got mine.
[SPEAKER_24]: See, I can just make one.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: I found all the schematics to make one myself so I could do it if I had time.
[SPEAKER_24]: But...
[SPEAKER_24]: As far as any other game, I definitely want Katamari Damacy 2.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sort of in about DDR right now just because I'm so busy with everything else I don't really have time to play.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was actually thinking about getting the DDR aerobics game though.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_24]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember it was Aerobic Revolution or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was sort of happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: We heard it was coming out and then we didn't hear anything else.
[SPEAKER_24]: The game I want that already came out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_24]: but it's really crappy.
[SPEAKER_24]: I decided to import Bujingai.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's the game with Gakuta as the main character.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now somebody had sent me a link about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gakuta was doing a voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Dark Knight was telling me about this.
[SPEAKER_24]: He's the whole character model.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: The game, it was, in fact, I put pictures in my live journal way back when, you know, when they were actually in production of the game.
[SPEAKER_24]: But it just looked really, really awesome, and I heard that they really, really butchered it for the U.S., but now the import's going to be cheap since the U.S.
[SPEAKER_24]: version is out.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: The live importers should have it really cheap, but I have to go around jumping around from, you know, building to building as Gak.
[SPEAKER_24]: Gak didn't have to... And all of this fabulousness.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't have to speak in English for the English one, did he?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, they probably got somebody else.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_24]: I can't hear another voice with that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have to have his, you know, voice.
[SPEAKER_24]: It just doesn't, I wouldn't be right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_24]: Hopefully a game where I can shoot things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, as far as my, uh, top three games for this holiday season, I would say number three is a tie, um, 2DX8Style, I gotta get, I know it's gonna get me back into 2DX, which I'm sure makes Navi, yeah, he's grinning over there, cause, he missed, I guess, I suck now, and it used to be like, Navi and I would have little friendly competitions about, you know, who can beat this song first, and then at one point I just said, ah, fuck it, you beat him, and I just kinda quit 2DX, but I think 8Style might get me back into it a little bit, but it's kind of a tie, because Rumble Roses,
[SPEAKER_10]: I really want it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is strange because, and this is no secret to those of you who listen to the show, I'm a gay guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since when did you turn straight?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the thought of women kicking the shit out of each other in mud wrestling to Bomani music type stuff because the artists are doing it, it's hilarious to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I mean, jeez, I'm a straight chick, and I love playing DOA, Extreme Beach Volleyball, and putting them in the tiniest little freaking bikinis I can find.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do it all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's something about being able to kick the shit out of, you know, become a woman that can kick the shit out of everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, and I'm not one of those, like, transsexual whatever's, okay, I just...
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then after they've slowly beat each other to submission in the mud, they slowly strip off the clothes and go at it in a very aggressive sexual, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob is all about empowerment.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to tell.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, um, before we get too far away from it, the third party controllers I was thinking about for 2DX would be Controlica, which is a new site that's actually come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to be selling, supposedly in the winter, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: 2DX arcade style controllers that are supposed to be on par, or if not better, for $3.75 plus shipping.
[SPEAKER_10]: And based on their popping music controller, which looks just like an arcade style controller, all metal, really nice, it should be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I want Halo 2 really bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, me too!
[SPEAKER_22]: And we can play online and I can run over you with the Warthog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, you guys have to understand that back when I was in college, my buddies at Sonoma State, I had a bunch of friends that went to Sonoma State over in the Bay, and they all had a really fast internet connection, so they would set up Quake servers, and I used to get on there and school them at Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't listen to them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was the best at Quake, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: And so now the Halo 2's out and it's on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like everybody that was in college, that little circle of friends in college, they have an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're all getting Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like we're going to relive the old days through Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's so precious.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I really, really want Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: So shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't hate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you suck now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_19]: Because he's gay, duh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I remember why we haven't had you on the show in a year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then my number one, absolutely DDR Ultimix 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe it's going to live up to the hype.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no doubt it's going to be a Bomani fan's wet dream this winter.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm looking forward to it, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm also looking forward to being able to play, and Sigurd has already accepted this challenge.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to play Sigurd on this show, live, and beat him at his own steps.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the challenge that's on the table right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you listening?
[SPEAKER_10]: You listening?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's already been broughten!
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, was that everybody?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, I didn't get your top three.
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you looking forward to this holiday season?
[SPEAKER_10]: Give me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if this is coming out within this time frame, but Alien Hominid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't pay attention to this shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: God.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that one looked really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did I tell you about that last time I was here, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, you mentioned it, but then wasn't it like your friend or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, my friend James, his friend is the one who designed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that one would be cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gosh, really, as far as video games, I'm not looking forward to anything, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really, E3, I was just kind of, eh, you know, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: No, there's not really anything I'm looking forward to at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um... No, I can't think of anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless, um... Well... Well... You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: You got Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, and you can beat Cop Senseless with your pimp cane.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if there's anything else that really you need.
[SPEAKER_10]: They could always have a Driver 4 so that I could see even worse AI.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: My god, that game sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just, the only reason I play it is just to see how bad it sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, it's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's funny, though, because Grand Theft Auto San Andreas...
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a point in the game where you have to go into this rapper's house and steal his rhyme book.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he's playing Driver 3 and seeing how bad it sucks when you walk by him.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing I'm really looking forward to, and hopefully they'll get it out by winter 2004, it's In The Groove, the home version.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, actually, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I would like to see Pump It Up exceed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though I don't play Pump It Up and I despise the arcade, I'd still like to see it because it'd be something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All the good games have already come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of the Konami ones are already out, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, I don't know, I can't think of any good ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess Metal Gear Solid 3, but I don't like even playing Metal Gear Solid 3, or Solid, or Solid 2, so, I don't know, the, uh, the DS, I guess?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, that might be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they can start re-releasing, oh, a new Animal Crossing game, if that ever comes out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Animal Crossing DS would be cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, these are those times when I'm very grateful my man works where he does, so I can get my free DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, have you gotten a copy of the Ultramix 2 VR?
[SPEAKER_24]: He's got it, he just hasn't brought it home for me yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know those are hitting the shelves, so if you haven't found yours yet, go bug your local GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a great CD.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, even if it wasn't even DDR related, it's still a great CD.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think it is just awesome that for the first time we have full length versions of songs that weren't done by Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, not that Konami songs are bad, don't get me wrong, but it's just neat to have other stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So check it out if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you guys noticed this, and this is out in the Ultramix 2 thread over on the Freak right now, so there's no secret, but that AlienC16, whatever the guy's name is, his website...
[SPEAKER_10]: T.O.Y.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, I want to talk about some things that are going to be coming up on the station.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, I teased this.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got a contest that's going to be coming up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Floatwalk, you were a big part of helping hook us up with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm actually going to, if you don't mind, DarkSakura, I'm going to bring up the cam for a minute because I want to put these on the cam real fast.
[SPEAKER_10]: But let us know about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've talked about it on the station a little bit before, but remind us again, Floatwalk, what are we doing with our buddies at DDR Spot right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, DDR Spot, for those who actually come visit us once in a while, we'll reward you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because roughly around next week or so, we're going to relaunch basically another version.
[SPEAKER_01]: And obviously it's going to be more or less coinciding with Ultramix 2 coming out and such.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge is doing a giveaway, as are we.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're doing the same gifts, actually, which I have brought up finally.
[SPEAKER_01]: As you know, of course, me being the man and all that kind of stuff, I got my hookups here and there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And those in Orange Lounge, I know a bunch of y'all are Kira Yamaoka fans.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we got four of his promotional CDs, which are actually like little mini CDs, which have, I believe one of them is the...
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that song?
[SPEAKER_01]: Room of Angel, I guess it is?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it has that, and then it has a spoken track on it afterwards.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was some kind of promotional giveaway in Japan, and he has autographed all four CDs.
[SPEAKER_01]: So those who want to get a piece of the man, they are more than welcome to try.
[SPEAKER_01]: But let's see what else is going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's our big giveaway for the time being.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's probably more we might have in the future, but be grateful for what you have.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this is the way the contest is going to work, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to start this contest on... I've got to bring up the calendar because I forgot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not tomorrow, but a week from tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: November 15th is when this contest is going to start.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to run for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Monday nights, Tuesday nights, and Thursday nights, Orange Launch Radio has certain spin-off programs.
[SPEAKER_10]: You might have heard of these.
[SPEAKER_10]: Diversion on Mondays, Pump Up the Volume on Tuesday, and Outside the Box moving to Thursday nights this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So starting on the 15th, on each one of these shows, we're going to ask a trivia question.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something about Akira Yamaoka, something about Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_10]: It won't be too difficult, but you know, my challenge, you might have to do a little research.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to ask you a question on each one of these shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then, for each week, because we have two CDs, we're going to be doing this for two weeks, at the end of each week, we'll take all the emails with the correct answers, and we'll be drawing one randomly, and whoever gets all the answers correct, and we pull them randomly out of the hat, they win a signed Kiriyama Oka Silent Hill 4 Limited Edition CD.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's imported from Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: You're considered a regular and you're not eligible.
[SPEAKER_10]: But a lot of you guys would be eligible to win DDR spots.
[SPEAKER_10]: And vice versa, DDR spot staff could be eligible for ours.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so you got some competition out there that we all want the CDs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to keep them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we'll just close the station down tomorrow and I'll just keep them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, no, we're going to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it's any consolation, even I'm not keeping an autographed CD.
[SPEAKER_01]: These are all, you know, sharing to the people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, you know, I have my own autographs of his, but that's neither here nor there.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I got a big announcement.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of people in the room don't even know this one yet because we just got the okay on it just a couple hours before you guys all got here.
[SPEAKER_10]: But next week, we're going to have an interview.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our very first Bomani artist is going to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Conception from DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: He did the song Altitude.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's going to be on the show next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's not going to be here live.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to talk to him over our brand new Skype out thing that we've got where we can call him and we're going to be talking to him.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we might have another one in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you want to say anything on it or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: We might also have the guy behind the most kick-ass remix in Bomani, in my eyes, the MidiHead remix, MidiHead.
[SPEAKER_10]: We might have MidiHead, so we're working on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're working it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This could be the beginning of something beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I'm looking forward to asking Concepcion a lot of questions.
[SPEAKER_24]: I feel like real radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, it's so weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty soon, you know, we'll outgrow this little apartment studio thing we got going.
[SPEAKER_24]: That means we can have a compound.
[SPEAKER_10]: We might have to sell ads on the site because people might actually want to get known out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's definitely interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to ask Conception a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: of questions about how he became hooked up with Ultramix 2 and what his music's like.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's actually going to send us a song, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't think a lot of you guys have heard it yet, so we're going to play that for you guys next week on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: What should we do now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are we going to go to break?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's do a break.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys want a break?
[SPEAKER_10]: We can break things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, let's do a break.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think... How much longer are you guys going to be here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Another segment, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another segment?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe another hour?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see if we can't do some good old-fashioned Bomani match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's how it's going to work, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to get a caller on Skype.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, what we do when we get somebody on Skype, they will get to challenge either Float Walk, Shark's Girl, Islander, or Iguana Girl, or Navi, or Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can pick somebody to challenge on tonight's Bomani match game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that should be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys up for it?
Yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi, what's up with 2DX Red?
[SPEAKER_10]: The game's out?
[SPEAKER_10]: It came out the day after the site went up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the official, it was like the 27th or 28th of October.
[SPEAKER_07]: It went up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's out.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else do you want?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've had a brain fart.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bring the microphone to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I stalk you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, brain fart.
[SPEAKER_07]: English, do you speak it?
[SPEAKER_07]: English.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's red.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very red.
[SPEAKER_07]: Things about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's, God, it's another 2DX mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know what all there is to be said.
[SPEAKER_16]: You just need to listen to that music.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm annoyed at the site right now, though, because there's no artwork for me to download to make my desktop wallpaper.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have you give me inspiration, Loki, then I'll do something intelligent for once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, it's the 11th game in the series.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got brand new additions.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, you've got on the side, while you're playing the game, it's actually showing you progress, basically, kind of like the combo meter in...
[SPEAKER_10]: Keyboard Mania, so you can see how you're doing versus the max combo in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing that's being added to this game is also High Speed 4, which I don't know if that's more of a challenge or helpful, but that's also being added.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then we've got the addition of, was it 8 plus stars?
[SPEAKER_07]: They've broken down the ratings into 1 through 8 and Flashing 8s.
[SPEAKER_07]: Flashing 8s now are just songs like
[SPEAKER_07]: A and Kakumei, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been plenty of songs that have been upgraded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some that I thought were kind of weird to upgrade, like Zero One's now an 8, and Linus is an 8, and a bunch of other crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most of the... A lot of old artists, the regular artists, are not in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are off doing other projects right now, so they have revived... A lot of old artists...
[SPEAKER_07]: like fourth style kind of stuff like... Nobunood or... No, no, no, that was a fake.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a fake?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a fake.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no Superhighway?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there's no Superhighway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there was no Voter of Stellum either.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they revived Wall 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love their new song.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you see the new video for it, it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a bunch of twitching animals to the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Baby Weapon, DJ Swan from 5th Style.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually a handful of artists that, you know, like, when the 2DX, when the remix album for 10th Style came out, we're all, who the fuck are they?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now they have their own songs in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ 19, DJ Tomo, I think DJ Yoshitaka was one of the ones that was on the 10th Style remix album also.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad to see Ryu doing something other than happy hardcore.
[SPEAKER_07]: His new song isn't as great as they were in 10th Style.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_34]: I forget what his song was though, but it wasn't... Be Quiet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be Quiet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that song, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that, um... God, um, I can't understand what the fuck Paul Terry is saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, she sucks, again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, she's only good with, um, um, um, um... What's her name?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the guy's name?
[SPEAKER_24]: Is she out of key, as usual?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what's really weird?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, like, anything...
[SPEAKER_24]: Red Zone
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you heard it?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Tatch and Naoki, and it sounds like some really old DDR song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Naoki, I mean, he needs to just go under another alias and just stay under that alias and never, ever, ever, ever go back to Naoki again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, honestly, I mean, I like Euro... No, I don't like Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not going to try to lie there.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, stuff like B4U, Brilliant to You and stuff, that was good back then.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what Red Zone sounds like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop making the same damn song over and over and calling it something different.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's really funny that Red Zone sounds like that, but he's in collaboration with a new sound producer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slake is no longer a sound producer on this, but apparently he's got three songs in the mix already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, uh...
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, as like old artists that are no longer with the mix, this current mix right now, we will not be seeing Mr. T, Tak, Shoichiro Hirata, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: God, I'm forgetting.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a ton of them that just, that aren't in there, or at least aren't in there yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, was any of the artists that, what was it, from like, I think it was from like 9th style,
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: One of them is Tayo, and the other one is D-A-N-C-E.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell is up with a guy being in B4U?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you gotta either feel sorry for him, or he's the luckiest bastard in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a guy in the group B4U.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is not a guy in B4U.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a guy!
[SPEAKER_10]: I swear to God it's a guy!
[SPEAKER_07]: You want me to point it out?
[SPEAKER_34]: Show me the guy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Show me the guy!
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to see this!
[SPEAKER_07]: There were five people that won the Bimani Vocal Audition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three of them are now members of B4U, and one of them was the chick that has the two songs in 2DX right now, and another one is a guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has not had any songs that I know of yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And where are you going?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is your high quality radio right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, go to Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: You talk, I'll get there.
[SPEAKER_24]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a key, key, essay, key, I believe is the name of the song, by B4U, and the new Orange Lounge song, and I'm going to try and say this with my French accent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Les fillets, bon accs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me read it, I'll say it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Shark Skrulls are going to be going, I know French, let me read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll try to get her over here after the break.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we're going to go to this break, we will be right back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: From StepSquad to Orange Lab, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_16]: Holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yay, Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have several little DDR factions in house.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have representation from RTF.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have representation from Step Squad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we have representation from the Nobodies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, DarkSkull.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big fat Nobodies.
[SPEAKER_09]: BFN for life.
[SPEAKER_09]: For real.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm representing Heaven's Gate.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just forgot to drink the Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think a new DDR squad has just been born.
[SPEAKER_10]: BFN, Big Fat Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this our gang sign?
[SPEAKER_10]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do we keep doing this?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Navi, want to be in BFN?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, BFN should be that, Big Fat Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be taking applications a little later.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's BFL.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a little different.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, a few people said I was in the GFR squad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, so speaking of GFR, did you get this guy in B4U situation sorted out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, yes, yes, it's not B4U, but he's just some ugly guy that's in a picture with B4U people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, it's this guy named Reija Sakurai, and looks like, I don't know, he's going to be singing something for some Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Poor bastard.
[SPEAKER_10]: He could very well be in the... And he'll be giving head at Vellfire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I wouldn't be surprised if he's in one of the CS songs for Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to segue for about 30 seconds here to give you your In The Groove update.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because everybody's got to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: This Halloween, to celebrate Halloween, they have an Unlocked song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anubis, the god of death, and Florida, as if you need another reason not to go to Florida, just got In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_22]: What part of Florida?
[SPEAKER_22]: What city?
[SPEAKER_22]: The back part, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, it's just because I'm going to be, you know, not an hour away from Pensacola.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, at the end of the month, I'm going to be an hour away from Pensacola.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that, ladies and gentlemen, was your In the Groove update.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're so mean to them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, seriously, there's a point where... I feel bad because I did give a review and there are some good things about the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very few, but some.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, yeah, it's not DDR King.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: We actually have a special guest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody actually messaged me on Skype and said that they wanted to come in and talk to us for just a second.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a very special guest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know at least one person in this room is going to get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm actually going to give him a buzz right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see if we can get him on the line here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, is this Travis?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, Travis...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you guys?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought maybe you'd want to say hello because this is the first time Iguana Girl and I have been on the air together since Under Station Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: And with everything that's happened in the last couple weeks, this is proof Armageddon is here.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's Travis.
[SPEAKER_19]: Travis, I miss you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you're looking good, baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, he's stalking you on our webcam right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, hey, 40 pounds lost, baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looking good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put your pants back on, Travis, please.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think Jenna would like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like doing it in my pants.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Travis, do you have anything you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh geez, is this, is this, okay, let's talk, I'm gonna get him off the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just, I'm just asking the logical follow-up question, is there anything else?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, the logical follow-up question would be, what does he want to plug?
[SPEAKER_06]: Your butt?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really have nothing to plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing to plug?
[SPEAKER_22]: We already plugged you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not the first time that happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on with Understation Live?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's why I wanted to give you a chance to plug it so folks can go listen to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't even listen to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't even do the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't do the show anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if that's what you call wasting a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I thought that's what you... That's what we always used to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's changed since Jessica and I were on there?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called a baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kira.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is the baby doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: She's a little shit.
[SPEAKER_19]: I bet she makes a lot of little shits, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, she makes big shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big, stinky, chunky shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to get her to play DDR?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, in your wildest dreams, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still love that Too Unlimited video you did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually just watched it just the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had been working on others, but my job unfortunately takes so much time away from me, I don't even have time to sit down and update my live journal.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we noticed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how are things on the left coast?
[SPEAKER_10]: Left as always.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sunny?
[SPEAKER_19]: Rainy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Angry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cracking up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, let me ask Rob this.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you feel about yourself, you, Rob, running for public office?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've contemplated it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I seriously have.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I just don't think, because kids don't vote, the youth doesn't vote, I think if I were to run, I would have to get the youth vote connection.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in this area, which has a bunch of retired citizens, that ain't going to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've given it serious thought in the past, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, have I got news for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, is everybody sitting down?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody got their towel?
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't forget your towel.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an announcement.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: As I talk really close to the mic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well we can hear you just fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so everybody shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seeing what has happened in the last two weeks...
[SPEAKER_06]: With the election, a country divided, one side against another, people burning down houses, cars, accosting people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Half the country likes one person, half the country likes the other person.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've decided to take a stand.
[SPEAKER_06]: I, Travis Donovan, officially announce my candidacy for President of the United States in 2008.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, Travis, wait, wait, wait, wait, Travis, Travis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hang on, just make me stop the music.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not going to be 35 by then.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to be 35 at the time of the inauguration.
[SPEAKER_06]: Birth certificates can be altered by a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have decided I am running for president, and if that doesn't work, I'm running for governor of Texas in 06.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hang on, hang on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my crowd here too.
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you do realize what this means.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I have to run.
[SPEAKER_10]: Far, far away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_10]: And I just put that whole rant in my live journal about how I wasn't going to move to Canada, but now I'm reconsidering.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I have two propositions for you on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to legalize gay marriage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's not go there yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because after all, I'm the working man for the working people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, here's my propositions for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm running for president.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna need a vice presidential candidate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: I am so there.
[SPEAKER_09]: But wait a minute, you're a Republican and I'm a Democrat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could that ever possibly work?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and your point?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a perfect opportunity.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, I've been ranting about it in my live journal to throw away the stupid bipartisan bullshit.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Travis and I can come together.
[SPEAKER_24]: Abandon the party mindset.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we can come on each other, we can come together.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, you're making a Guana girl sad because she doesn't know what she's going to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: She doesn't get to be vice president.
[SPEAKER_10]: What can she do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's fire Condoleezza Rice and put Jess in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_10]: What does she get to do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I don't want to... I get to stand around and have big boobs?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I...
[SPEAKER_06]: Secretary of Big Boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's an idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I actually gave that some thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jess can be Secretary of Agriculture.
[SPEAKER_00]: So long as I get to play with the cows.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to be the Secretary of Agriculture.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I figure you want a woman who PMSs as far down on the chain of succession as possible.
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't calmed down at all.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just zoning you, Travis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now great, you just lost us a vote.
[SPEAKER_10]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to go, Trav.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't say everybody was gonna like us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm honest and upfront about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna be plain spoken for the plain spoken people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will have no problem telling candidates to shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will have no problems pointing out that my running mate is gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't need the other candidates to tell me this, I've known this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm here!
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the point of John Kerry pointing out to Dick Cheney that his daughter was gay?
[SPEAKER_06]: No shit, I think he knows!
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, that was Edwards that did that, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you expecting him to have a revelation and a heart attack right then and there going, Jesus, she's gay!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm seriously considering this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a grassroots campaign.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a third party kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have to come up with a name for the third party.
[SPEAKER_06]: The People's Party!
[SPEAKER_06]: The People Party!
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: and if anybody can access the social... It could be the house party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Travis and Rob's house party!
[SPEAKER_06]: All the best!
[SPEAKER_10]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Totally live!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we're going to have to get my people in touch with your people and people things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think I'm all crazy because I live out here in Texas because, oh, I'm sorry, as people have pointed out in this last week, I'm a redneck because I live in Texas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't think you're a redneck.
[SPEAKER_06]: As people pointed out, now it's time for the South to secede.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, the rest of us are going to form the United States of Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha ha ha, you're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is my second condition.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're serious about going to Canada, along with all these other people who want to leave the country... Of which I am not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never leave to Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: if you were to sign a legal binding document that you will get your ass out and never come back I will personally start donating to the U-Haul truck to get you the fuck out and I will use big bills as I've said before just because the guy I did not vote for and did not want to win won that does not mean I hide my tail behind my legs and go to Canada that just means I have to yell a little louder
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you just sit there and bitch and whine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly, that's what we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the American way!
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn straight!
[SPEAKER_06]: America, fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but my question was, did you... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you expect, Rob, on the next day, Wednesday, to see a big, gloating thing in my live journal?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I think everybody knows that kind of stuff's in poor taste.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, not a lot of people in LiveJournal did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't really see a whole lot of gloating.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if anybody... I'm not talking about gloating.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of the people I knew, if they gloated, I could have said, well, California went blue, so... But, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it happens, so... Only half of California went blue.
[SPEAKER_10]: 55% went blue.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get it right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's half of California.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only 44% went red.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just FYI.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: We don't need to discount the over 4 million popular votes.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can't we all just forget about bipartisan shit?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's just have a bipartisan orgy and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get rid of the electoral college and parties.
[SPEAKER_24]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the electoral college is not stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had this debate with you guys back in 2000, and I'm going to have it over and over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It gives the small counties with the less population... Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not having that debate on this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have stupid 12-year-old games to be talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of stupid 12-year-old games... Yes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to be on Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get to frag a fag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, most people in Texas would be, you know, happy about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been four years since we lynched a queer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I accept your challenge, Mr. Donovan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you better, Mr. Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then when I kill you, I'm going to say, Ha ha, you got your ass kicked by a fag.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just like I do to the little hecklers that try to challenge me on ADR.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we put Jenna's 10-year-old nephew on, and he kicks both our asses, which he does on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is scary.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we've got to cut it short, because we've got to get to the bit that we stole from USL, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: What bit?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, the match game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You copyright stealin' motherfuckin'.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, wouldn't it have been copywritten before?
[SPEAKER_19]: You stole it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Copywritten and trademarked.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I stole it, like, one hundredth time down the line.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's homage!
[SPEAKER_10]: Imitation is the finest form of flattery.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love you, Travis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bye, Travis.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was nice to have him on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, Travis.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've never been asked to be a vice presidential candidate before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been asked to be somebody's maid of honor, but never the vice presidential candidate.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are going to open it up for match game in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, we had one other person that wanted to talk to us in the studio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we're going to make another call, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's go ahead and make that call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_19]: One ringy-tingy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, is this Shane?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can barely hear you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you talk louder or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this loud?
[SPEAKER_10]: Somewhat.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can, like, barely, barely hear you.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can't yell.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well, what's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: You wanted to say hello to some folks here, or what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, hi everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_10]: How's it going for you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're sick?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, another sick person, great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you sick with?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm puking.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, unfortunately the volume is so low that it's hard for us to hear you right now, but do you have anything you wanted to say since we called you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to say that everybody needs to buy Karaoke Revolution for Xbox this week so Halo 2 doesn't take all the sales because I don't want to keep selling Halo 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And watch Drawn Together on Comedy Central because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And is there any Ultramix 2 songs you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but I can't say them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I thought he was going to say Baile La Samba.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, I already said that last time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Baile La Samba.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll play Baile La Samba just for you a little later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, I'm sorry, we're going to have to let you go because it's too quiet, but you have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, you too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone say bye, Shane.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye, Shane.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come back to California, you bum.
Play Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I hope he heard that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They said, come back to California, you bum, and play Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think he already hung up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully he hears that when it comes through a little later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: What we're going to do now... Should we get into Match Game?
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys want to take a quick break?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's get into Match Game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to find the Match Game music though.
[SPEAKER_24]: How about a one song break?
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to do just a quick little break while we set up?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_10]: A quick one song break.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, everybody's been wanting to hear...
[SPEAKER_09]: What was the song that I wanted to play for people?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Set People On Fire I don't remember, what was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it's Baile La Samba, since we just talked to Shane, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to play this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back right after this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Baile La Samba from DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back.
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to get into the Monty Match Game pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're just trying to get the files copied over that we need.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the way this works, we're going to open up the Skype line in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: And just as a reminder, there's a little bit of a buffer.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're going to want to watch for the little icon to turn green because that's really the moment when we're starting to take calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the first person through will get to play Match Game tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you get to challenge somebody in the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: but not one of the hosts.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to challenge a guest because that's the rule that I just made up.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was very Izzard of you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cake or death.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you get to challenge one of the guests and all the other guests will be answering questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the way Match Game works, we have a little statement that we read and the statement has a blank in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then you have to fill in the blank.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to try and match as many other people in the room on the blank as you can.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to make it a quick game tonight because Shark Skrull and Floatwalk, unfortunately, they have to get out of here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we have to kind of make it a quick game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be a three question game tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's like Mad Libs, only not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it's like Mad Libs, only not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's find ourselves some match game music here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not the same match game theme, but it's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Price is Right car music.
[SPEAKER_10]: A new car!
[SPEAKER_09]: You've won the Geo Metro.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see what happens when we open it up and get a caller.
[SPEAKER_10]: And remember, if we can't hear you very well, we are going to have to boot you and get somebody else.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the skyline is open and let's see who we get.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: John Fields.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, John.
[SPEAKER_10]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: You there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're dropping out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_34]: Sorry, hang on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, you gotta cancel the porn torrents to get it working.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I think he disconnected.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, here you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, he's here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we got our contestant.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm gonna put us back in do not disturb mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so John, the first question is, who do you want to challenge tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me go down the candidates one more time, John.
[SPEAKER_10]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: Floatwalk, Shark's Girl, Islander, Iguana Girl, Navi, Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's it gonna be?
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's try Navi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi!
[SPEAKER_10]: You know I suck at these games, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: John knows that you suck at these little games, so he's going for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's have ourselves a little match here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me bring the music back.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right everybody, it's time to play the Money Match Game!
[SPEAKER_24]: You've won a gremlin!
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight's contestants, on the Skype line, John Fields!
[SPEAKER_05]: And in studio, he'll be playing against Navi, the poppin' music whore!
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's meet tonight's celebrities!
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, she's fabulous, she's beautiful, she's very angry, it's DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_05]: Next stop, down the line, he's fresh, he's cool, he's silent, he's low walk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who else are you expecting?
[SPEAKER_05]: Next stop, she's lovely, she loves her sharks and she speaks French.
[SPEAKER_05]: And has a nice tongue that speaks French, no I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well you know what they say about French, it's shark's girl.
[SPEAKER_20]: What the hell happened to my hockey season?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's over there and he likes boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an islander.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, our next celebrity.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's the future state of agriculture head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Official candidate 2008 and part-time DDR forum goddess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Florida girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, he's there, but you may not be able to hear him.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you'll hear me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The angry, the racist, the Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fool me once, shame on you.
[SPEAKER_34]: Fool me twice, a fool can't be fooled twice.
[SPEAKER_34]: And me, Skype.
[SPEAKER_24]: We need Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_30]: You want me to play as Mr. Spanky tonight?
[SPEAKER_30]: Hello everybody!
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_30]: This is Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_30]: Everybody's favorite DDRPC character.
[SPEAKER_30]: Now I know...
[SPEAKER_30]: that you guys want to see me in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_30]: So this is what you gotta do.
[SPEAKER_30]: You gotta send a private message to Order of Chaos on DDR Freak and say, Spanky in 2004.
[SPEAKER_30]: And also vote for my cousin Sal Piro, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so we have Mr. Spanky playing tonight as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds like some tough celebrities you gotta win over tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: John, you up for it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm up for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: You ready for question number one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob was so excited to be going to GameStop to get his copy of Karaoke Revolution Volume 3 on this lovely Monday night at the Halo 2 pre-sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when he took the game to the counter, the clerk looked at the game he was buying and said, You're buying Karaoke Revolution instead of Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_10]: Karaoke Revolution must be really blank.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: You gotta let the celebrities think about it, John.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: He looked at the game he was buying and said, You're buying Karaoke Revolution instead of Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Karaoke Revolution must be really blank.
[SPEAKER_05]: The celebrities are writing their answers.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have all the celebrities dinged in?
[SPEAKER_16]: Raise your hand if you're dinged.
Still thinking, DarkSakura?
Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got it, Sharks Girl?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, she's got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to have Navi go first, your competition tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, Navi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob was so excited to be going to GameStop to get his copy of Karaoke Revolution Vol.
[SPEAKER_10]: 3 on this lovely Monday night at the Halo 2 presale, but when he took the game to the counter, the clerk looked at the game he was buying and said, You're buying Karaoke Revolution instead of Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Karaoke Revolution must be really hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, John, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Karaoke Revolution must be really... A huge sleeper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huge what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sleeper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huge sleeper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a sleeper hit.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know those games that are really underground?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, neither answer perverted in the slightest.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see if that pays off or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got Hot and Big Sleeper.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, Karaoke Revolution must be really... Super!
[SPEAKER_10]: Super!
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a match, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Floatwalk, Karaoke Revolution must be very...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, since it's Microsoft, it must be Green with Envy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, Green with Envy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting, all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shark Skrull, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shark Skrull, Karaoke Revolution must be very... I've been playing way too much Katamari Damacy and playing the Pisces one, so it must be really fresh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fresh!
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander, Karaoke Revolution must be really... Neato.
[SPEAKER_09]: Neato!
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Iguana Girl, Karaoke Revolution must be really...
[SPEAKER_10]: Hetero.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, going for a little bit of that reverse psychology there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like it, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I particularly heard full of before that, so I say porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Full of porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Full of porn!
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we'll see on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, not a match.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's close to hot, but not close enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki must be very... Gay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you went for the obvious one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to put gay people, but I'm like, no wait, that's what the question was the other way around.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said, karaoke must be very much for people into water sports because the box is yellow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all tied up with a big nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to the next question, shall we?
[SPEAKER_10]: You ready, John?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura was all excited to be getting a really expensive present for Christmas this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was really excited to see a big package come from an Orange Lounge radio fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when she tore off the wrapping paper, she started burninating the Christmas decorations in a fit of rage when she saw that they had bought her a blank.
[SPEAKER_05]: The celebrities are currently thinking of their answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: When they saw that they had bought her a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, everybody, uh, everybody, ding-ding?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, ding-ding-ding?
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, John's gonna start us off this time.
[SPEAKER_10]: You ready, John?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, uh, DarkSakura was all excited to be getting a really expensive present for Christmas this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was really excited to see a big package come from an Orange Lounge Radio fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when she tore off the wrapping paper, she started burninating the Christmas decorations in a fit of rage when she saw that they had bought her...
[SPEAKER_10]: A flamethrower.
[SPEAKER_10]: A flamethrower!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, because that's why somebody would burninate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very logical.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will logic pay off?
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably not, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi started burninating when they saw they had bought her... A Foreman Grill.
[SPEAKER_10]: A Foreman Grill!
[SPEAKER_24]: I got one of those for Christmas once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Started burninating the steak.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, DarkSakura, what did you start... You started burninating when they bought you a... King of All Cosmos package.
[SPEAKER_10]: King of all Cosmos package.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a large package.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: FloWalk, Bot Hurray, Apolitary Poster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apolitary Poster!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, not a match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Excuse me, I'm going to go be violently ill.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shark Skrull.
[SPEAKER_21]: A box of ferret poison.
[SPEAKER_10]: A box of ferret poison.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awe, I made her cry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander, a blank.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bag of boogers.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bag of boogers!
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear DarkSakura, I'm your number one fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I picked these just for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly enough, I could see that happening with some of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm your number one pick every time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ironically, mine's actually along the same vein.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Huge piles of feces.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huge piles of feces.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shade marks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcadian, we're looking for... I forgot the answers now already.
[SPEAKER_10]: A big fact is...
[SPEAKER_10]: with a karaoke machine of Politary's greatest hits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, a karaoke machine of Politary's greatest hits.
[SPEAKER_22]: Chirp chirp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it's sad that no one got Jamie's because mine was the king of the cosmos, Severed Cock.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a big package.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine's somewhat similar.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said that she burninated everything when she saw that the present was a dildo modeled after Naoki.
[SPEAKER_24]: How would I find it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all tied up 0-0.
[SPEAKER_10]: John, are you going to break this tie?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi, are you going to break this tie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Question number three.
[SPEAKER_10]: We here at Orange Lounge Radio have become very concerned about Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: When haven't we?
[SPEAKER_10]: But here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've been very concerned about Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's been playing a lot of Grand Theft Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he started to blur the line between San Andreas and real life.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other co-hosts got very concerned of this when Loki went around in blank.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other co-hosts got very concerned that...
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki was taking Grand Theft Auto a little too seriously when Loki went around and blanked.
[SPEAKER_05]: The celebrities are currently thinking, please wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are we going to get a winner?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll find out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anybody still working?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: It all comes down to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: We here at Orange Lounge Radio have become very concerned about Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's been playing a lot of Grand Theft Auto this week, and he's starting to blur the line between San Andreas and real life.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other co-hosts got very concerned of this when Loki went around and Navi...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_24]: and the outfit of some stereotypical thug and tried to jack a plane, crash into the ocean, steal a semi and listen to the light FM while shooting at people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very descriptive.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_24]: Shooting at people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, but now, it's a little too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: That doesn't necessarily mean I hit them, therefore not hurting them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: FloWalk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chase them with the purple dildo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_10]: StarScroll.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jumped out of a plane screaming, it's a mile drop, I'll live!
[SPEAKER_10]: This is true, this is true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_10]: When he said, bitch, I'm gonna kill you!
[SPEAKER_10]: Bitch, I'm gonna kill you!
[SPEAKER_10]: Very close to capping your ass, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_10]: Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hijacked a helicopter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hijacked a helicopter.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, that would have been exciting if Loki really did that, but I don't think I would have been concerned.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know how to fly a helicopter?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ran over pedestrians.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ran over pedestrians.
[SPEAKER_10]: He does that anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a match, he does that anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have figured that would have been a match, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shooting the po-po and pimping crack hoes to make some fat scratch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lovely, lovely.
[SPEAKER_10]: And my answer was, the other co-host got very concerned with this one, Loki went around and killed DarkSakura with his pimp cane.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got a ferret thrown at me for that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's review the scores, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's look at how our contestants did tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's look at the final scores!
[SPEAKER_05]: And in second place is Navi with zero points!
[SPEAKER_05]: And a tie for second place is John Fields with zero points!
[SPEAKER_10]: Congratulations John and Navi, you are our big losers tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Navi, you get a frown, a collective frown from those of us in studio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, and John, do you know what you get for your score tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: A frown from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you get hung up on.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a good sport.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, he tried.
[SPEAKER_10]: They always fall for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hang up on them every time.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, no, thanks seriously for playing, John Fields.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too bad about the, you know, no answers or anything, but, you know, it happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I guess Shark Skrull and Floatwalk are going to have to be leaving us soon because they've got a long drive home.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, I quickly wanted to ask Floatwalk and, you know, Shark Skrull just some, you know, general questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Floatwalk, anything, I guess I should ask you about
[SPEAKER_10]: Ultramix 2 Ultramix 2 Ultramix 2
[SPEAKER_01]: I was hanging out with Jason Enos last night, so he gave us a kind of a scoop on why there were delays and all that kind of stuff, and it's actually pretty funny, but only people who are in the test group would appreciate such bumblings, I guess, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, I'm starting to get a little nervous there, that we're going to have to wait for Christmas to see Ultramix 2, but it's good to know that it looks like it's still on target anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's looking to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, right now, things are pretty happy in the DDR camp.
[SPEAKER_01]: Extreme sales have actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, what Jason did was he was comparing Max 2 sales along with Xtreme, how they've been doing week by week, and Xtreme's been doing a good, like, up to around 33% better than what Max 2 has been doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice!
[SPEAKER_01]: So they're looking, even projecting around holiday season, they're probably going to be jumping Max 2 figures by about 40%.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, things are going well for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Max 2 has almost hit 500,000 units.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice!
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, I mean, who knows, it could be a greatest hit someday, but
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting, interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, what do you think, and I know you're not there anymore, so you can't really say one way or the other because you don't know, but what do you think the chances are we're going to see some kind of Extreme 2 next year?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's pretty safe to say, I mean, if it's a profitable franchise, you just keep milking it for what it's worth, and it's, I mean, the good thing about DDR is even though the gameplay is pretty basic, it's always progressive with its music, so the music will always drive sales and people to try new titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, uh, oh, yeah, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully if there is an extreme too, they'll have the sense of humor to make it purple.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be very funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got to let Jason know that from Orange Launch Radio, that we want to make Extreme 2 purple.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it happens, if it is Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, some interesting news that's been going around about Ultramix 2 is the song packs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did say on The Freak that there's going to be, what, 7 through 12, I think they said?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe every month, every other month, we don't really know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll just say I wouldn't be surprised if they space them out a little longer than once a month.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: From what I've seen, there's definitely some very interesting choices, like things that the hardcore B-Money people would be very... Oh, so you know about some of the stuff that's coming up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, I know everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Watch out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anything else you want to share we should be looking forward to from the world of Konami?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of hard to say because, I mean, for all intents and purposes, everything's been...
[SPEAKER_01]: Released out for this fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably the last game that's going to be pretty big for those who are into the RPGs and 4 will be coming out early January.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to play a demo with that actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the only cool thing is, you know, I'll get to see my writing in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because me and another guy had actually helped do some translation or like rewriting for that project itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's main stuff from Konami for now, I mean... Now, are you going to come back after Ultramix 2 is released?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to come back to the show and kind of, you know, fill us in on how this happened?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because now, you know, all the information will be out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: You get to tell us a little bit more about how it all happened?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I'd be more than willing to, you know, come up here and talk about stories of, you know, like songs and like who got to do this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you'll probably find out who did what steps and then like what caused us to think, you know, why we did that pattern and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: There are definitely some interesting stories and
[SPEAKER_01]: You'd be surprised at some of the songs that people like on the V-Rays and stuff, but there were actually some testers who did not want to touch certain songs whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, we're going to have to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's plenty of interesting gossip that will go down afterwards.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, if I'm not mistaken, though, there's still about half the song list we don't even know yet still.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah, there's some things that people don't know about, and there's a lot of funny things to...
[SPEAKER_01]: Although it kind of sucked in a way that the VRare had more or less spoiled some of the things we wanted to keep really top secret.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what though, when you stopped giving clues, we had nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know, GameStop employees can't be quiet to save their lives.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they ever going to tell us, give us more clues, give us a song list here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably not, because we're only about 10 days out.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just ain't happening.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're no fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I mean, it's... Upper management has been really stressed out from Ultramix 2, just trying to basically get it in before... I mean, our target date was actually probably the second week, basically around the same time Halo 2 was supposed to come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, 11th we were looking at, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it got pushed back, but I mean, just kind of stuff happens in the business.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, and it's also interesting because we've heard that some things changed with Ultimix 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some song list changes happened, some things behind the scenes, so, you know, maybe they had to go back and do something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I mean, it's not uncommon to have one song one minute, and then, like, a couple versions later, yeah, we decided not to have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, people, you know, I think I mentioned one time about Dancing Stage Unleashed, you know, there was supposed to be
[SPEAKER_01]: A certain song, which was actually slated for the USMAX 2, I think it was Grooves in the Heart.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was supposed to be on USMAX 2, but just never made it for one reason or another.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, of course, you're probably never going to hear from me about what songs didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_01]: and it would actually, sad part is I do have one to tell, but it just breaks my heart to even think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was really good, folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, you got me all, you're going to have to, now, see you in a year, nobody will care, so you'll have to tell us in a year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless someone shoots me up with some, like, sodium pentothal or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we can arrange that.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, thanks for coming by, Mel.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're welcome back anytime, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: SILENTHILL4
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, get your pens ready.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we'll have like some kind of certain theme plotted out and then see what people can do with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And kind of off topic, my own personal plug, I'm going to be selling a Silent Hill 4 stand-up display.
[SPEAKER_01]: If anyone wants it, I'll be putting it somewhere on some place and I'll sell it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll probably post it on the LiveJournal Silent Hill forum.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shark Skrull, I didn't want to neglect you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're sitting there and you look kind of bored.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just feel kind of hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is kind of hot in here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any exciting plans for the next few weeks for you?
[SPEAKER_21]: Try not to murder my fellow co-workers that I can't stand.
[SPEAKER_21]: Try not to walk out on my job because I really need money.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's about it.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I want to come down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, we're going to have Dave and Buster's Play Day pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we can harass a new friend of mine who works there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, harassment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Harassment is fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what else am I going to ask you?
[SPEAKER_10]: How's hockey going?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does it look like it might get better?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're being stupid morons.
[SPEAKER_21]: The players are being idiots.
[SPEAKER_21]: From what I hear from friends who actually have contacts in the upper level of Sharks management, the owners are willing to negotiate and work on it, and the players aren't.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're saying, we want what we want, too damn bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, from what I hear, the Sharks are planning that there won't be a season this year.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which pisses me off, but it saves my wallet.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you know, hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess there's a bright side.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, yeah, it could be all bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if there is a season, like a partial season, like they ended up doing with baseball or something, hope your Sharks can win it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, we're undefeated.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_21]: Nothing, nothing, we rule.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like our match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you guys sticking around?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you guys going to be taking off too?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to talk to Iguana Girl when we get back about a promotion she got recently.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to talk to her about what's going on with the Freak.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll talk about that when we get back.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are going to take another break.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about some more 2DX Red stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi, as our resident whore who knows a little bit more about this stuff, why don't you pick some songs for us that you want our chat room to hear?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, which one?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we're going to hear Horizon, and what else do you want to hear?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to hear Death Disco, Texture, I'm sorry, It's Lake with Texture.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do do do do do do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wonder Bullfighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we're going to hear this 2DX Red music.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when we come back, we're going to talk to Iguana Girl and Islander a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we've got to get the cage match and the FUs in.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've only got less than an hour of show left.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to squeeze this all in.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: My FU of the week is a two-hour drive to the Bay Area because, damn it, I want to stay here longer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, I'm sorry, hon.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just have to take Monday off work sometime.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm seriously thinking about calling in tomorrow, but, you know, hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then, you know, someday, someday we're going to bring the show over there to your neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to someday.
[SPEAKER_10]: So someday when we have a three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Floatwalk, any preemptive FUs you've got to get out for you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, man, well, I guess just FU2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just FU2, like, game companies putting out too many damn games and just, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: basically for not giving me enough time to play everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and FU2, my new job, I was supposed to start Monday, but they said they couldn't start me until Wednesday, and whatever hurts my bank account really just makes you go FU.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, guys, thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you later, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, most definitely, the sooner the better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go to break.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Show's not over yet, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm losing a couple people because I've got a long drive, but we've got plenty of show left.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you!
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We gotta get to the cage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye, Sharks Girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye, Foot Walk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: They got a long drive back, guys, so they're good sports for coming all the way down here to come on our show and eat Mongolian.
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: But that doesn't mean you replaced J-Dog.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, King of All Cosmos, aka Spike, has not been able to put the amount of time into the site that he would want to.
[SPEAKER_19]: So he decided to step down and I was put into his place.
[SPEAKER_19]: So now basically I'm helping out with the forums and keeping things hunky-dory on the forums and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a hell of an undertaking, I bet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we've got a lot of projects that we're working on right now and trying to get squared away.
[SPEAKER_19]: So yeah, it's a lot of stuff to do, but I've got such a wonderful crew that I'm working with.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, everybody's just fabulous to work with.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which includes our very own DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: As well as Islanders, next to you over there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, he's our staff member.
[SPEAKER_10]: And several folks listening tonight, in fact, but judging from our chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, hi you guys, thanks for listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: VX, JasonXV, and Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, of course, Jason.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw Sherlock blue in there earlier, so that's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys for listening.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you probably can't say a whole lot, but anything exciting coming to The Freak in the near future you might look forward to?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: Can't really say anything about it right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a lot of stuff that's really up in the air, but don't be surprised if you start seeing some changes around the site.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, that's always a good one to leave people with.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: How did you get involved with that anyway?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, I remember that you and I, we had our first DDR experience together at that regular convention.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, October 2000, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then about a year after that, we weren't talking to each other, and then suddenly...
[SPEAKER_10]: Suddenly you were running up the corporate ladder, a DDR freak.
[SPEAKER_10]: How did that happen?
[SPEAKER_19]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I, you know, just through the site, I mean, back in the old boards, you know, the green boards, as we, you know, affectionately call them, I started to get to know some people, and Jamie and I were becoming really, really close friends, and what ended up happening was she introduced me to some other people, which introduced me to some other people, which ended up basically with...
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember seeing the nomination thread and being so proud.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't even remember any of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was surprised because it was out of the blue for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, good job.
[SPEAKER_10]: Congratulations to you.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was August 2001.
[SPEAKER_10]: Out of curiosity, there have been several mods on DDR Freak that don't mod anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: How many of the mods that were there when you started are still there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Jamie's one.
[SPEAKER_10]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't think of too many people.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_16]: J-Dog?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, J-Dog, he owns the site, so that doesn't really count.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: What else do I want to ask you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, now, just between you and me, because nobody listens to this show, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which forum is the biggest bitch to handle?
[SPEAKER_19]: See, that's the funny thing, is everybody else... Yeah, see...
[SPEAKER_19]: Mr. Islander is, you know, Coffee Gunner is Breath Random Chat, but I don't mind random chat.
[SPEAKER_19]: Random chat's fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like random chat.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, it's like the evolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do too, but I refuse to get involved in political discussions.
[SPEAKER_19]: See, here's my problem.
[SPEAKER_19]: My most hated forum would be DDR Chit Chat.
[SPEAKER_19]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_19]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: How much do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Unless you count Thumb Thumb Revolution, I have not played DDR in 2004.
[SPEAKER_09]: How many of those mods actually play DDR?
[SPEAKER_19]: Quite a few.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_19]: Surprisingly enough, actually it's about a three-quarters split, I would imagine.
[SPEAKER_09]: So here's the logical follow-up question.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't play DDR anymore...
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the community.
[SPEAKER_19]: All of you dumb fucks out there, I love you to death.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_30]: You pissed me off, but I love you.
[SPEAKER_30]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_30]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what drew me to it to begin with.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was just like Rocky for me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I started out with Rocky because it seemed like it was fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: I get to go dance.
[SPEAKER_19]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_19]: But what kept me there despite everything else was the community, the family that you grow from it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's honestly been the best experience about DDR for me was the camaraderie that I've felt, you know, this big huge happy
[SPEAKER_19]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_19]: and oh my god, maybe Orange Lounge and DDR Freak Radio crossovers?
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't say it, but I'm neither going to confirm nor deny those reports.
[SPEAKER_10]: We shall soon see.
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be some interesting things happening this November.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_20]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Islander, I don't want to leave you out of the fun because we're talking to a Gwana girl, but you were one of the first people on DDR Freak, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: How did this whole damn phenomenon get started?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, story goes, there was a group of guys that I saw playing
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR, you know, way back in the day at Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: First time I ever saw this machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I started noticing, I started seeing the same people over and over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, i.e.
[SPEAKER_02]: Floatwalk, who was just here earlier, just left actually, J-Dog, Pokai Kenobi.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we started talking to one another.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we started seeing each other more and more and more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next thing I know, Jason comes up with a website
[SPEAKER_02]: with a huge long URL.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was something at Berkeley, EDU, and da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sad thing is, I remember that site.
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was horrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, when I first used it, NS3, it was the NS3 site that we came on board with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the N3.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: N3.net was next.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it just kind of progressed from there, how quickly people caught on and how much people loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's really amazing how much the site has really grown.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, my God.
[SPEAKER_19]: 45,000 members.
[SPEAKER_10]: How many hits a day?
[SPEAKER_19]: I wouldn't even know what the stats are, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_19]: But let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_19]: The reason why we can't keep the video section up is the sheer amount of bandwidth that is used would cost us probably a good $500 a month in hosting fees alone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I got a good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys should do one of those Winamp TV things with streaming videos.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just remember, I suggested it, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want my credit.
[SPEAKER_19]: And a lot of people have suggested BitTorrent for it, but part of the problem with that is, A, we're talking about the common user here.
[SPEAKER_19]: and a lot of common users aren't going to be able to figure out BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, at least right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, at least for right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, obviously, you know, things like IRC were foreign to people back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you haven't guessed, DDR Freak has to cater to the lowest common denominator sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_24]: As in, no, I'm going to be high school.
[SPEAKER_10]: No naming names, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_24]: I wasn't going to name names.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was just going to say complete idiots.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, as she said, the newbies, which I actually love.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some newbies are cute!
[SPEAKER_02]: If you go to the site, I am still listed as the DDR Amstabor.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, one of the things I loved to do way back when was I loved to go to various arcades, talk to people, get them interested, and I just loved going around meeting people
[SPEAKER_02]: who played the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, when the Sacramento crew came down to the Bay Area and everybody hated us.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to point this out.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were the bastard children of the DDR community for the longest time and now she's the queen of the goddamn forum.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to point that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is hilarious to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meanwhile, the people that chastised us are banned!
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember Prestige!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes, he was there too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, a lot of names.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you were there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: He said I had big tits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate to kind of cut this short, but you guys are welcome back anytime.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're actually welcome in this house again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love this, that we can just be candid about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Life's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, things change.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, don't you go anywhere, Navi, because I want to talk to you still, too, after we get the cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to get to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've only got like 30 minutes left in the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did Jamie just say we skip FUs?
[SPEAKER_24]: We should skip FUs so that next week I can do double FUs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about that, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe we'll have to do a mini FU segment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody will have to think of one really good FU.
[SPEAKER_24]: One really good FU.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that goes for chat room, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: You only get one really good FU tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: But in the meanwhile, we've got to, got to, got to get to tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm going to queue it up here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you want to participate in tonight's cage match...
[SPEAKER_10]: All you got to do is head on over to our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's bring on the cage match music, Jamie's favorite song.
[SPEAKER_24]: I vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_10]: You cannot vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm still voting for Holic.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, your FU suggestion got FU'd, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, well, F you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see how fast we can get through this cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last week in the Orange Lounge cage match, it didn't happen because we weren't here, because we had Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, for two weeks running, you have had my pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: My pick was the winner of the Orange Lounge radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a song by Ian Van Dow, which you know from Castle's Nurse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: The whole guest here, we get to do our best Simon Cowell on all the songs that play, except for last week's, because we already did it last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, alright, I'll shut up and play a clip of song number one.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Reason by Ian Vandal.
Music, Music, Music
[SPEAKER_15]: Are there things that I should know?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will you stay or will you go?
[SPEAKER_16]: Where is the love?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that was song number one, last week's winner, or two weeks ago's winner, I should say.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Ian Van Dow from the album Ace with Reason, some happy poppy trance music.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie's favorite!
[SPEAKER_10]: You gave that song an 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to remind you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go on and we're going to go to Loki's pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, what did you pick out tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I figured I'd get something really sweet for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Earlier in the show, you heard me mention MidiHead, basically the guy that did the really kick-ass remix of In Your Eyes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, well, I got another track from him.
[SPEAKER_10]: You won't even find this on his website, because I asked him for it, and he was laying it up to send to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And your internet penis is humongous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, this song is featured in one of the trailers, or not, I should say TV spots for Matrix Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the song is called, um, I don't know what it is, Speed Demon.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's by a group, or a guy called Monolithic, and guess who Monolithic is?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Middy Head, and he's the singer, and enjoy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here it is, song number two tonight, Monolithic, Speed Demon, enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Monolithic with Speed Demon.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go around and see what everybody thought of that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind, we're all a little pooped right now, so I don't know how that may affect the scores, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll give it a seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_29]: Let's see, Guana Girl.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sounds like the type of stuff I actually used to listen to, so I'm probably going to give it about seven and a half also.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, seven and a half from Guana Girl.
[SPEAKER_29]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, not my style, but I still enjoyed it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd probably still give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, good deal.
[SPEAKER_29]: Navi.
[SPEAKER_07]: The music was pretty good, but then the vocals kind of ruined it for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounded like Bad Underworld with the cowboy twang, so I give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the background was good, but the guy's saying leave something to be desired.
6.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I've always, I think MidiHead's a really talented guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I prefer the In My Eyes remix over that, but it's got a good beat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think cut down a little bit, that would be like a fun little 2DX song or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2DX is going to come out here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, so I give it like a 7.5 as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be trending.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's better with the Matrix reloaded visuals with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I still gave it a 9.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, remember, it doesn't matter what we think, it's all up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can choose between Ian Vandal, that song, and DarkSakura's song, which we're going to hear next.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, what is it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, it's by someone named Vlad.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's Supersonic Electronics.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: If anyone happens to be checking random chat on GDR Freaks, they'll know what I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm a little concerned, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, this is Vlad with Electronic Supersonic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey baby, wake up from your sleep.
[SPEAKER_26]: We have arrived onto the future and the whole world is become... Electronic Supersonic Supersonic
[SPEAKER_26]: Electronic Hey baby, ride with me away, we doesn't have much time My blue jeans is tight, so on to my love rocket climb Inside tank of fuel is not fuel, but love Above us, there is nothing above, but the stars above All systems gone, prepare for down count 5, 4, 3, 1
[SPEAKER_26]: Fly away in my space rocket.
[SPEAKER_26]: You no need put money in my pocket.
[SPEAKER_26]: The door is closed, I just lock it.
[SPEAKER_26]: I put my code plug in your socket.
[SPEAKER_16]: The sun and sky is bright like fire.
[SPEAKER_25]: You and me gets higher and higher.
[SPEAKER_26]: The only thing can stop us is flat iron.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, love crusader, I want to be your space invader.
[SPEAKER_26]: For you I would descend the deepest moon crater.
[SPEAKER_26]: I is more stronger than dark vapor.
[SPEAKER_26]: Obey me, I is your new dictator.
[SPEAKER_26]: For you is Venus, I am Mars.
[SPEAKER_26]: With you I is more richer than all the stars.
[SPEAKER_26]: Make a wishes on a shooting stars.
[SPEAKER_26]: Then for you I will play on my cosmic power.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ladies and gentlemen, fasten your belt seats.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have commenced our descent.
[SPEAKER_27]: I trust you enjoy this flight as much as you enjoy this accent.
[SPEAKER_26]: Now, back on Earth, it's time for a down splash.
[SPEAKER_26]: Into sea of eternal glory, my spaceship crash.
[SPEAKER_26]: People have arrived to cheer me from near and far.
[SPEAKER_26]: And as I float, I open door and shout, I am world's biggest warship.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_26]: Long live Space Race.
[SPEAKER_26]: Long live Movania.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just cracked up when I first heard that, so I give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_29]: Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's got a nice rhythm and you can dance to it.
9.
[SPEAKER_34]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_34]: I thoroughly enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_34]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_34]: It's a 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: Navi.
[SPEAKER_07]: It makes me giggle like when I heard heterosexuality by Army of Lovers.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gets a 10 because it has to win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, Arcadia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, this is something I would expect from Loki, not from you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, based on the butt plug in my socket line, 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people wonder why Push got elected.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess a 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, it would be a better fortune cookie song than it would be a cage match song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, somebody jealous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone jealous?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's recap and then you guys can place your votes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Song number one you can vote for tonight is Ian Van Dow with Reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Song number two you can vote for tonight is Monolithic with Speed Demon.
[SPEAKER_10]: and song number three you can vote for tonight is Zlod with Electronic Supersonic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't have a lot of time tonight, guys, because we want to get into the FU segment pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_10]: So get those votes in now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got like a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: So do it, do it, do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it now!
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: While we go ahead and open up the Skype line, maybe some folks out there have some questions, want to speak to some of our guests that are left here in studio.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if anyone's going to actually call, but we'll see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to take a... What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to do a sim update.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, Loki, what's going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, there's been updates to both the in-the-group skin, no one cares, and the DDR red skin, which is meh.
[SPEAKER_10]: and also Step Mania, Release Candidate 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing important.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing to see here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Move along.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that was quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: What can I say about that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I guess what we can do right now while I'm tallying cage match votes, Jamie, why don't you go ahead and plug some of those other shows that you can hear on our lovely station.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sure there's people who would like to give it the plug.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tuesday night is my show, Pump Up the Volume, starts at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yo!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to cut you off real fast because we just got a call on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_24]: Too bad!
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll finish your plug, then we'll go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_24]: Never mind, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Silence Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pat!
[SPEAKER_10]: How's it going tonight?
[SPEAKER_22]: Pat!
[SPEAKER_10]: We are good.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're pressed for time, but we're doing pretty well, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, Shark?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't like the other two songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Ian Vandal is probably the winner here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, see, I have a feeling that they're going to go for the funny one.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, I just don't like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it not funny to you, or what was up with it?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm annoyed by German techno.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just that amusing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't we all?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't the world be a better place?
[SPEAKER_09]: The only German songs we should be listening to should be by Rammstein!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's in Germany, alright?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let it stay there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't erotic from Germany?
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, that's probably the only song that we should have heard from... No, because Rammstein is considered Eurodance.
[SPEAKER_13]: The last time I checked, Germany wasn't in Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Germany's not in Europe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you have a question for any of our guests that are here tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got a guana girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you're a mod over on The Freak, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is it working for a guana girl?
[SPEAKER_10]: Does she carry an iron fist or what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, she keeps an iron fist pretty well.
[SPEAKER_13]: She keeps a check on me all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know she's got an iron bra.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hopefully you haven't had to deal with that yet, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was it made in Taiwan?
[SPEAKER_10]: Here comes Iguana Girl on the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think she's going to post a link to the Iron Bra.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you haven't seen this, Sherlock, you've got to check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if I want to see this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, I think we've got in all the votes for Cage Match, so if you don't mind, Sherlock, I'm going to sidetrack for a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to announce the winner of tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: First of all, what do you guys think won out of all those songs?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're fucking ruining America, goddamn you people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight's winner is... Vlad!
[SPEAKER_10]: With electronic supersonic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: The tribe has spoken.
[SPEAKER_10]: With almost, get this, get this, Sherlock, twice as many votes as songs one and two combined.
[SPEAKER_13]: You people smoke crack, I swear.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well...
[SPEAKER_10]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_10]: I already told you we were the bastardous, cancerous sub-community here, and that vote speaks for itself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah, it seems like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you get a link to the picture there?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd rather not look at it again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me look.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see if it actually works or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me put it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're in our chat room there, over at OrangeLawrenceRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, there it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Iguana Girl with the lovely white face in the iron bra.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to state on your 15 seconds of fame here, Sherlock?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd say something, but then Iguana Girl will probably hate me for it, so I'm just going to... Oh, now we definitely want to hear it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me guess, the internet is serious business, guys?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, the internet is very serious business.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what I tell everyone.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why does that taste rough, Iguana Girl?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I'm going to do a nice little shot on the camera right for you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, Chris?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, she just banked her bottom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's only when Sherlock calls in do we get the bondage coming out on this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess we'll have to call in more often then, alright?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, are you coming to E3 next year, Sherlock?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I'm hoping so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, Iguana Girl says something about attacking you at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah, she's gonna attack me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and dyeing your hair.
[SPEAKER_13]: I talk about Mod of the Month when I'm not supposed to.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then she hates me for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, you came in second place this month, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, Iguana Girl did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, she did.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now that Jason's out of the picture, it's on for next month, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, PMG came out of nowhere last time.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's anyone's game.
[SPEAKER_10]: All I have to say is Orange Lawns Radio, we're plotting something.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're getting involved this next time, so you guys look out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You look out.
[SPEAKER_10]: or we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, thanks for calling, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have a great night.
[SPEAKER_10]: We gotta finish up the show here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like hearing from new people once in a while, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we've got to, got to, got to, got to get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you already sent me your FU of the week, I had to close it on accident because of the cage match voting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you want to get those back into me right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the meantime, we're gonna limit it
[SPEAKER_10]: Anger.
[SPEAKER_24]: A big, massive, humongous FU to the cost of plane tickets into Gulfport, Mississippi and Mobile.
[SPEAKER_24]: I couldn't find one into Mobile for less than $800.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I couldn't find one into Gulfport for less than $500 at the time I needed to leave.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I was on Travelocity trying to pick my time.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I found one into New Orleans, but that means that my family's going to have to drive an extra hour and a half to come get me.
[SPEAKER_24]: But at least I get to leave New Orleans at 5 in the afternoon, which means that I get to enjoy the French Quarter during the day.
[SPEAKER_24]: but it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ridiculous!
[SPEAKER_10]: Totally ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you to my car, and mainly Ford, because they make shoddy cars, and my car is falling apart, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just bought it, like, what, six months ago?
[SPEAKER_10]: Used, granted, but it only has, like, only, like, a thirty-some odd, you know, thousand miles on it, and already the brake system, I think, is going out, or the front part is going out, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they have a class action lawsuit for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shoddy breaks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: But lucky for me, I was smart and bought the extended warranty, so it will only cost me $50 to fix.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever the fuck's wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, ha!
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's my guess right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whether or not they fucking try to screw me out of that, that's another story.
[SPEAKER_10]: For next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: My FU this week goes out to Sprint, PTS, because I went over there today to get a brand new cell phone and found out they have shit for deals right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I figured, you know, I'd be able to get a good deal because I'm not under contract with them right now, but all their deals are pretty shitty.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, the salesman, excellent salesman, told me to come back later because they'll probably be getting better deals around Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you guys, I swear to God, I'm going over to T-Mobile where I can have a cell phone that Catherine Zeta-Jones endorses.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to be generic on this one because it kind of encompasses a couple of different sections, but a giant F you to people who can't seem to understand that when you're banned, you're fucking banned!
[SPEAKER_19]: You're not supposed to come back, and if you do come back, don't whine and bitch and moan about the fact that you've been banned.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to give you some advice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I realize that I don't have to do any banning or anything like that, so I don't want to deal with the same bullshit you do, but this is how I deal with it here on Orange Lounge, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: You just got to look them right in the eye.
FIRED!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what you got to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there are those people out there that are banned from the show like years ago, and they still keep... Yes, we have banned some people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, yeah, really, really tired of people who think that they're being cute and make threats on certain other websites that they're going to attack certain websites.
[SPEAKER_19]: And don't think that we're not going to catch wind of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Giant F muted those dumb shits.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to close watching you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have none.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to that, Islander!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, Islander's just a nice guy, honestly.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you have a chance to meet him in real life, he's honestly the nicest guy.
[SPEAKER_20]: A wonderful contrast to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi!
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually have an FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to people who stop talking to you for like three months, call you back because they miss you, make plans and then flake out on you, and disappear again!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, wonderful world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, and then in reference to her band thing, I got banned.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a link to some sim files or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I checked back on it periodically.
[SPEAKER_07]: It kept showing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, can't load the page.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then the other day, it says, You are banned!
[SPEAKER_07]: From what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Freak?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or where?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was some guy who posted his keysounded 2DX BMS files.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was in his signature.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got some of those a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he only has two people on there at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remembered that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I checked again like the other night.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, I'm banned.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm all,
[SPEAKER_07]: That's odd.
[SPEAKER_16]: F that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcadian!
[SPEAKER_10]: Lucky to lies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's check out what the chatroom has to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Start off with Zaku.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you, oh boy, here we go, it's political, brace yourselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to the Jesus-lovin' gun-lovin' red state voters for electing that no-good excuse of a chimp of President George W. Bush to a second term in the words of a great pump-it-up song, Lazenka Save Us.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was awfully punny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Raichan, fuck to you to being one of the many that's sick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I think she's saying fuck you to herself for being sick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: I missed that somehow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jazz says, F you to procrastination.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_10]: Poto says, F you to laggy towns in MMOs.
[SPEAKER_10]: MPQ says, F you to the arcade for being close the day I went there.
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackDevilerX says, F you to those Asian files on the DDR Freak forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those guys piss me off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any comment on that?
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry I cannot control the content of the idiot post.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I figured while you're here I would let you say that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Elmullet says, F you to Halo 2 and a type the game will never live up to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blue using Halo 2, that's all that matters.
[SPEAKER_10]: And lastly, DDR Angel says, F you to my video card for suddenly not liking Final Fantasy XI again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wondered why I hadn't seen her on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Grr, no Final Fantasy XI for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm, birthday present maybe?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'll keep wishing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, done, bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jamie has some advice from the laundry room.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's yelling back to the laundry room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Play a real game.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, play a real game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_07]: V-Rares, and all that stuff to find out how great they actually are.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: November's just a busy month, and we'll have to carry over some stuff to next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know you're welcome back here anytime, all you guys are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, as long as I'm willing to drive here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, in a little ways.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But thank you, of course, for coming, as always.
[SPEAKER_10]: And thank you guys, Iguana Girl and Islander.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come back sometime.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, good luck with that radio station.
[SPEAKER_10]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be interesting to see what happens in the next couple months or so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck to you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: And good luck with the moderation of those forums, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Arcadian... Damn the man.
[SPEAKER_19]: Save the empire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcadian, big thanks to you as well for being here, as always.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: And try not to get pulled over tonight, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's a bad boy outside of this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: You would never guess it, but boy oh boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now it's the part of the show where we go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just like Jerry Springer, we go around and get all the final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Navi, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've run out of walls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Iguana Girl, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_20]: Butt plugs in socket.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander, your final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eat, drink, and be merry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcadian, your final thought for tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: You see, I'm bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't know the half of it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe not.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, can't have that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have the device done, now to haunt the house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, quick!
[SPEAKER_10]: Your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go, I'll go with mine.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is, Outside the Box moves to Thursday this week, so please don't forget to listen and fuck... Fuck Survivor and fuck The Apprentice!
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have clean clothes.
[SPEAKER_10]: They smell like gain.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_10]: One last thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: The final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: One word that sums it all up.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll give it to Iguana Girl tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight's final word.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you very much, everybody, for listening.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you next week where we're going to interview Conception and talk all much more about all these Bomani stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final word.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boobies.
[SPEAKER_33]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_33]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_33]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_33]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thanks for watching!
Back to him that night
[SPEAKER_18]: Christmas trees, decorate the house with lights at night Snow's on the ground, snow white so bright In the fireplace is the Yule log Beneath the mistletoe, F.E.J.
eggnog
Merry Christmas and Happy New Year
[SPEAKER_33]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio Afterbirth, the part after we fade to black.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully you guys know to stick around because there's always something fun after the credits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight, my God, we are so pooped though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's just been a hell of a show.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a way to come back after not being here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do, I need to talk about ratings though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to talk about ratings for the station.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rating, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Ratings for the station have fallen 20% in the past two weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am quite disappointed in you guys, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's your chance, go in your little player window right now, vote us a 5 that you love this station, you want to listen to it every day, and then do so.
[SPEAKER_10]: And help our ratings get back up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now we realize, okay, we were off for a week, we had some repeats in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you know, we had some shows, switch days and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: No more excuses, we're done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so you gotta whore us up so that we can be the number one internet radio station of all time.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is the ultimate goal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we do love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping that with the Akira contest, we'll be able to get back up in there and some other things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, you guys know I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I can't expect you guys to listen all the time, but it would make me a happy boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I also want to talk quickly about The Incredibles, that movie, because I'm surprised you didn't say much about it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of the movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is what all superhero movies should aspire to.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is actually...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very misleading, like anyone that's seen the previous, because they think, oh, it's a kids movie, oh, this and that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But actually, it has a story that I would say is on par, if not better, than a lot of the animated Superman and
[SPEAKER_10]: Batman series and we know that those are awesome writers on those series and of course the guy that wrote the whole damn thing the guy behind the Iron Giant that movie was incredible this movie is literally the set design the character development everything is just excellent you need to see this movie I cannot stress that enough it is awesome, I cannot wait for a sequel
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see his movie yet, Navi?
[SPEAKER_10]: At all?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have not.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last movie I saw was The Grudge.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked it a lot, and a lot of people that have seen it either said they liked it and thought it was really scary and then other people said that movie had absolutely no substance whatsoever, it was crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked it, I thought it, I mean, it was more something like, wow, it was actually a scary movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't see very many scary movies very often anymore, at least that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, for the record, I did not get to see the Star Wars 3 trailer when I saw The Incredibles, just for whoever asked.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really care, I'm not like the hugest Star Wars fan in the world, I mean, you know, hooray, the movie's coming out, but, you know, I'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I like the grudge as well, except for the audience I saw it with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you should have been the mom.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should, like, compare audiences later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, that's going to do it for the afterbirth, you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to take off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie's got to get home, and I got tests to grade and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So thank you guys for listening, though, so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really do appreciate the fact that you guys support this station.
[SPEAKER_10]: Through our high points and our low points, we are working on so many exciting things for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're teaming up with Spot.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're teaming up with Freak.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's amazing, the stuff that's in the future for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really thank you guys who have supported us, especially those from day one, but we definitely welcome all you guys that hop on board as the show goes on.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it's on, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: Remember, do it for the ferrets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: They love you too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's hear a little ferret love there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get a little ferret love.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, we don't get enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't get enough love out of Loki on this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, will you please let the listeners know how much you love them?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, enjoy the post show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys can probably figure this one out.
[SPEAKER_10]: We definitely have to load you down with some 2DX Red music.
[SPEAKER_10]: So enjoy, have a great night, and we'll see you tomorrow night for Diversion at 7 o'clock for Monty Remixes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great night, guys!
When I got the older baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're live here with this post show going on of 2DX11 style, also known as 2DX Red Music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it's taboo to call it 2DX11 style.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not supposed to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might get bitch slapped by some rabid fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But actually what I'm going to do right now is I'm actually going to do something technical on this end that has to do with the archive of the broadcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: The past few weeks we've been having trouble with it, though, and it stopped the station.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you guys get booted from the stream, it's going to go back to the Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_10]: So just restart the stream in like 15 seconds if we disconnect, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to try it now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to hope we don't, though, so I can keep going with the 2DX Red stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I lose you guys, then good night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.