[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, June 3rd, 2012, rumored new Wii U functionality is revealed, details emerge on the next Skyrim expansion, and Apple answers rumors about an Apple console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet, and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts, and I'll be joining you over the next couple hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, the one, the only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, dog, what up?
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm full of curry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurry, hurry, hurry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get your rice and curry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Thai, not Indian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerds out there will know that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're actually taping here on Thursday, May the 31st So a little disclaimer before we get into the news too much tonight Especially with all the E3 stuff starting to come out Things may have changed between the night we taped this and the night you guys hear it Why did we do that this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, as I mentioned on last week's show, I'm going to be out of town Therefore the OLR studio will be closed that night And Loki really wants a night to sit at home and play Minecraft all night uninterrupted
[SPEAKER_03]: IDDQD IDDQD
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't die.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's really for the poor programming of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, the future updates and stuff, when you're digging underground, you know if there's lava one brick away from where you're digging.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're digging and all of a sudden, oh crap, lava, killing me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the first tip I got about playing Minecraft is never dig straight down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I wasn't digging straight down.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was digging straight forward.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then all of a sudden I hit a block in Lava Flow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anyhow, we'll talk more about our gaming weeks in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you still took the time off from work so you can kind of watch it, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't take any time off work, but I'll still be watching it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But technically it's related to your job so you can kind of get away with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because I'm awesome like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of think that my work is more interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this year especially, you know, I'm feeling a little eh about E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, maybe I'll be pleasantly surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to go into it with low expectations is probably a good place to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I think Bobby put it best.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf, of course, the man who you hear before us on Sunday nights at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said, you know, if I had to miss my first E3 in, I think he said it was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you think the bar is so low this year?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is the Wii U. Is excitement really that low about Wii U or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think the Wii U is doing enough different to make it like, ooh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like the graphics are like, whoa, that much better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, whoa, this is a totally new technology way of controlling things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically...
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, look, we made a big DS minus a D. But isn't this a good place for Nintendo to be, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I know that sounds really weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody likes the negative buzz, and obviously E3 kind of left them with a very meh feeling, a lot of people walking out of the Wii U. But, I mean, when the bar is low, they really have the potential to...
[SPEAKER_05]: For a whole year, they'll be on the cutting edge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even still, you know, even those new systems, you remember the very first, you know, games that were coming out on the, you know, Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 just kind of looked like up-res PlayStation 2 and Xbox games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's not always, you know, the biggest, best looking, well, definitely never the best looking games at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, you know, ways after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so quickly, I know we kind of talked about this a little more in depth a couple weeks ago, so I don't want to dwell on this topic too long, but since this is our last chance before E3 officially hits and the press conferences start, what are your final predictions out of E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: One prediction each for the big three.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are your final big predictions out of E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be asleep when they're made.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let me ask you, DarkSakura, do you have any interest in Wii U at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: because when you say you're apathetic and you don't care it makes me think that Nintendo's just not doing anything to excite you that there's nothing that's happening there that you go oh this is new and fascinating
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to be excited until I actually sit down and see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And granted, I feel somewhat similar, but I'm hoping to be pleasantly surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really hoping there's that one game that I gotta have.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, predictions for the big three?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really know what Nintendo's... Just based on what they've rumored to be coming out in the new Mario game, New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me, which I think is what it's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, that does not appeal to me at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: didn't ever appeal to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I understand... Well, the one with the DS was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the Wii one came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then number two's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they all look the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish it would do something innovative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take one of those franchises like Mario or Zelda and do a little Big Planet thing with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have this fucking amazing level editor with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can even make it like an old 16-bit Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Re-release that and have this fucking amazing level editor where you can share it online and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to bring you back because this isn't a prediction.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is wank.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what you want to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't what you're going to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm prepared to be completely underwhelmed by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my prediction.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll talk about all this wonderful stuff that the Wii U can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it'll be just these stupid games that... Hey, look, it's WWE 13, but with this extra feature.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hey, look, it's Darksiders 2, but this extra feature.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hey, look, it's Batman Arkham City that came out last year, but it has this extra feature.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't fucking care.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not gonna make me... I'm not buying another console because it has a cool gimmick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want something that's going to be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii was very different than what was out there on the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I was interested in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was completely boring later on because there was nothing really good for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing I really needed to have.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Microsoft and Sony?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hoping we'll see... They'll probably announce their TV thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole initiative where they're going to have some sort of IPTV.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because all these little apps that they have that are tied to your cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you can have the Xfinity app.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but you have to have Xfinity in order to actually view any of the content on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can do that on my PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do I need your stupid...
[SPEAKER_03]: It says very useless for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's something like, hey, you pay for Xbox Live and you get TV content with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I don't have to pay for cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, cable doesn't want you to do that, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then for PlayStation, Sony, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really, it kind of, it's going back to what we were saying before.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing I'm really expecting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's nothing like, oh, I can't wait to hear from,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Gravity Rush I hear is kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a demo out for Gravity Rush.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a demo out for both, but I haven't gotten a chance to try them yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I hear it's okay, but it's not like, woo, gotta have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Resistance was one of those things I was like, ooh, first-person shooter, that might be really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hear it's just kind of meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm like, well, crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I have to wait until the fall for some good games to come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're back to the 3DS again, where it's just like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I gotta wait until the fall for some good games to come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, am I gonna have to sell this system too?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I'll go real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Nintendo obviously is gonna be very heavy on the Wii U and the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I...
[SPEAKER_05]: This may just be the fanboy wanking me, but I kind of think they're going to drop F-Zero on us and I'm going to have to get one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's what's going to ultimately happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think there'll be something kind of cool where that little tablet's going to have the map and kind of like the racer's cockpit or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe something like being able to use power-ups and stuff will be all on the little touch screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the HD screen will be nothing but gorgeousness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, possible fan wank, but there are rumors that that could be the big one that's being dropped.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm just going to remain hopeful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope this is Nintendo's chance to finally prove that they get online and I think they are going to show that they get online finally but no more so than say Sony you know it's not going to be like oh my god Nintendo's the must have online so I think they'll do about as well as Sony
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't know what they can do to impress me at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if they are going to be hedging their bets on two big first person shooters which usually aren't my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what to think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see new franchises.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really do too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want something to be on Kinect that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was that whole Gladiator game they showed last year that we never really heard anything about again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine they're going to show more of that this year but I'm not
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Fable of Journey.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be their big Kinect game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not on rails!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, a great example of where the bar is really effing low.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's a chance to blow me away.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I liked Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think there's ever going to be another good Fable.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd be willing to bet Rise isn't going to come out for this console.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing I want to say about Microsoft, though, is I still think Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Windows 8 gets dropped at some point during the conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Microsoft's big push at the end of the year as a company.
[SPEAKER_05]: That whole synergy.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be something with your Xbox and Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was watching a video of that interface today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, there are things that they've made improvements to, but that fucking Metro desktop is... That is all optional, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have to use that, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Question mark?
[SPEAKER_05]: It replaces the start menu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Sony is so unpredictable, and yet I think is really predictable.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, obviously, you're going to have the God of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to have probably more hints of The Last Guardian and the PlayStation fighting game, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and I think there will still be, of course, more Vita and I'm hoping for more Vita, PlayStation 3 kind of, you know, togetherness.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's that, what was that dungeon crawler game that never ended up coming out with the Vita's launch?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vaporware the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, something, it's like Diablo but not
[SPEAKER_05]: They showed that off last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine more of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the one that was at launch, the Ubisoft title that ties in.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I know what you're talking about, the Sony one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what the hell it's called.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not Sorcery either.
[SPEAKER_03]: That came out and that's the Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not Sorcery.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they just were talking about like, oh, hey, where's that game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's some pretty cool ideas that they have for new franchises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember Cameo?
[SPEAKER_03]: The launch title for the 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was really cool looking when they showed it off at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay when it came out, but it could have been a good sequel, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: It could have been a good title.
[SPEAKER_03]: That type of game was pretty cool and not something that really the Xbox has from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have that type of platforming like a Ratchet and Clank or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to move on here and start to get into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to kind of wrap things up, though, again, hopefully we're all pleasantly surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know we're feeling kind of eh about this year's E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope it gets people buzzed because this Christmas could be quite a disaster for video games in general if there's not anything to get excited about.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's one thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the video game market could live through a recession, I don't know that it's going to have a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, but if this year is bad, that could have a real impact on the Sony Microsoft consoles next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, please, Grand Theft Auto for October.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please, Grand Theft Auto for October.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually, what is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Lego City stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still want to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That actually might sell me a Wii U. Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, by the time you guys hear this, the full VOGnetwork.com website should have launched.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to think what tense to use here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, since you guys are hearing this Sunday, we had a special on Friday talking about the future of the network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to repeat it here because it's like 95% a go right now, but there is a chance it could be delayed to the 8th.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will has had.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you will has had by this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: My hope is, though, by the time you guys are hearing this, the full VOGnetwork.com website did, in fact, launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check it out and just... It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were unicorns and rainbows and... I don't know about unicorns, but there may be rainbows.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was definitely a unicorn on the test site, but I think that's being removed for the full... There were sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were sheep.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: All the E3 talk got me sidetracked.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: We've only had half a week, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played... Actually, Dan got the new Arkham City expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Harley Quinn's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that looked really neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched about half of it and then I had to go to bed because I had taken NyQuil and I was like...
[SPEAKER_02]: You play a lot of it as Robin.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I liked Harley Quinn's voice actor, she gets really annoying after a while, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, for fans of certain little Easter eggs that were found in the game before, you're going to get pissed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I already know exactly what it's gotta be, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, I played, I had this really good streak in Fractal, which I love that fucking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fractal is so fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had a really good streak and then I got pissed off at the game again and stopped playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, then I played like some WoW and played some Star Trek Online only to find out that they completely redid your skills and it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm like, I don't have my kick-ass bomb skills anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you hate that when you leave an MMO and then you come back and they change everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently, like, some of the stuff I have, my legacy items are pretty good, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still the, the, I'm still an Admiral piloting a Defiant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you still playing with all the Scottish people?
[SPEAKER_02]: I weren't on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only a couple people were on and they weren't the Scotsmen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're apparently all still there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just there at weird times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course you did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played lots of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I built a giant pig.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, I saw the pictures on your Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you say you built a giant pig, you must have found the pixel layout somewhere online.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a guide online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love, it was like a hollow pig.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could climb up the ladder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can climb up the ladder into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a house.
[SPEAKER_05]: You live in its butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can live inside.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess, actually, here's the best part.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the dinosaurs in Pee Wee's Big Adventure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when they go to watch the sunrise?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can live in a pig's ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just thought that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, what do I want to build next?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll build a giant pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: That thing is scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'll be running through and then I'll look at when I'll see this pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just like, it's always there staring at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey, I have a question for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you make a slide?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you could totally make a tongue slide for your pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make a water slide.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can make, you should make a drooling pig water slide.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to make a water slide out of its bum?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's kind of gross.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do it in its mouth so it can be the drooling pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not making, I thought about making, see, I was going to have that pig and I was going to have, like, another pig that I reskin, like, you know, to make it all evil looking, like with glowing eyes and fire and, like, spikes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Darth Pig.
[SPEAKER_02]: Darth Pig.
[SPEAKER_02]: Da, da, da, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was funny, though, because all the pigs keep wandering around the giant pig.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like they're worshipping the idol.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: All hail our bacon-y god!
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, and another thing, too, Rob, since we're on the same map.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know I started a new map, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm on seed OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not on seed VOG anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got sick of VOG.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sick of OLR, too, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to go back to VOG, because you know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if you go to the bottom, was it the bottom, the southwestern portion of the map, there's this giant hole that goes straight into the ground with a waterfall in it and stuff, and it's pretty awesome inside there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what you need to do?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to put a video on YouTube of your giant pig.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm going to have... I've already... I'm planning on making a giant roller coaster ride thing or possibly... Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: They even have water slides that you can make.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make a water slide thing with jumps and all this cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: What has happened just three months ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: I should go find a clip from this show just three months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do people play Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or just ask DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, DarkSakura, what do you think of Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and then Loki in the meantime, I'm gonna make a fucking Minecraft theme park!
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: As soon as somebody either pays for me to have an account or gets it to me for free somehow... Just play the demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't like demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll pay for you to quit complaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember back when I had the volume and the little thing said give me a dollar?
[SPEAKER_02]: People did send me dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone sent me a $2 bill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kickstarter to buy Jamie Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was before Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should be paying me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else for your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a little bit of Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually played a Kill Confirmed game with just the three of us, so that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just don't play a lot of Call of Duty anymore because everyone's really busy and my co-worker's out for a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I get more Minecraft time then.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, I started getting bored, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, because I'm like, well, I don't know really what else to do in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I may actually go start a new seed at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's the old R seed?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that great, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, I haven't explored the entire map.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can tell you, the underground really annoys the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's some weird... There's like... Okay, if you want, like, just this gigantic mountain...
[SPEAKER_05]: I would almost play it just to see how different it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some seeds I've seen that are really crazy, like just valleys inside of a mountain with lava and water and all sorts of...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, whenever we get those VOG forums that may or may not be there I have no idea what the crap you guys are talking about You should share some of your awesome seeds for Minecraft Alright, look, let's move on What seed?
[SPEAKER_05]: You tell it what word you give it You can give it random numbers and letters You give it a word and you can make a world that uses that as the seed But the good thing about that is that if I use capital V, capital O, capital G and he uses the same thing, we have the same world essentially
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it's kind of randomized, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just thinking of Final Fantasy VIII now, where there were seed members in their gardens.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I've been working on the website, not as much as Bobby has, but I still have been working on that quite a bit this week, so I haven't had a whole lot of time to game.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I have gamed, I've played a little bit of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane and I have been running some dungeons to get heirlooms for the monks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will inevitably roll in the expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: and otherwise I checked out the Mass Effect 3 multiplayer expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it the Rebellion Pack or was that the last one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Recruit Pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something war related.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another freaking multiplayer pack came out this week and it adds the two male Quarians, the two Cerberus defectors and the two Vorcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dang, people are already unlocking shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went into a random and I already was playing with a male Corian, which was kind of neat to just kind of see one running around.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got to play on one of the new maps.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there are two new maps.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of them is, I think it's Thessia was the one I was playing on because it's based off that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't want to spoil it because it's staged near the end of the game, but something big happens there.
[SPEAKER_05]: so I was yeah I was having a good time on that map and apparently there's a new type of credit game too on the third sixth and tenth wave you have to do something different than just killing everybody it's either like hit the four beacons or upload all the data now there's a new one that's kind of like fetch it and bring it back
[SPEAKER_05]: so and it's kind of like Murderball where the person who's carrying it walks really slow and is more vulnerable to attack so I kind of like that they're doing different things with it you know Mass Effect good times after finally having played the entire fucking trilogy up to this point it's kind of nice to be current and get to experience a lot of this Mass Effect hubble when it's current so that part's cool all right now we can do gaming news right yes all right let's do it
[SPEAKER_03]: Or The Phantom
[SPEAKER_03]: SnakeOil
[SPEAKER_03]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: to coexist with regular stuff like renting titles or stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's never going to be you just play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until it's the holodeck, there will always be a need for another console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or until it will suck your dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: The console either has to be the holodeck or if they build the console that sucks your dick, then they don't need anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I lose out.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm losing out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now, now, now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be the holodeck.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can demand whores in the holodeck.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be an inverter for women.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm just saying, though, there's never... In terms of the vacuum attachment.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's never... Well, even when those, you know, even the blowjob machine and the holodeck come out, they're going to need to make improvements to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always going to be improvements done to everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be too bad if you get a glitchy hoe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let it go, let it go, let it go.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, female attachment, not the male attachment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we'll have to wait and see what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure that announcement next week will be in the works if they are going to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they could do a lot of different... I mean, I don't think it's going to be only that because another thing that they considered, at least Sony did, was making it online only.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: yeah think about this though real quick if they do adopt like a cloud gaming thing then they can have all the fucking control you know what I mean think about it because when it's in there they get all of the fucking control like they could release like a beta game or something that you could play for like an hour and then it's like pulled you know it's like and then the advertisements right in the middle of it and there's nothing you can do about it like that part of it's kind of
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they could do that, and then everybody else doesn't do that, and then no one plays it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, basically they ultimately rejected the idea of a download-only console because they remembered, hey, we released something called the PlayStation Portable Go, and that sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they decided not to do that instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Or even better, it's like Sony puts out online-only consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Servers for online console are being throttled.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one can play anything on their console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you buy the special Xfinity version, then it won't count against your cap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comcast subsidized two-year agreement.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, if it goes online-only, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what, console makers?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's a little fact for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's funny you bring up PC games because Diablo 3 is one of the big PC games, of course, in the world right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as you know, they've been having quite a few issues, especially launch day was really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got a little better for a little bit, but just within the past couple days before we're taping this show, apparently there's been more error 37s.
[SPEAKER_05]: The auction house has been delayed and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, one country is taking this shit seriously and it's Korea.
[SPEAKER_05]: They take their Diablo series, they take all their Blizzard games seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, I knew that those WoW subscriptions were expensive, but man, that they're collecting souls now, that's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blizzard apparently refused to refund Diablo 3 to Korean players who should have been eligible after consumer complaints.
[SPEAKER_05]: The FTC thinks that Blizzard is violating Korean law on electronic commerce and commercial contracts.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to gather evidence and so forth related to this raid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Korean players are frustrated with the server issues happening in Diablo 3 and asking for refunds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blizzard denied it saying contract terms.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that whole little...
[SPEAKER_05]: The FTC is considering these terms to not be good to the player base, as you can imagine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, we have received many complaints from Diablo 3 users.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, just like people here complain to the government, it's happening in Korea too, and they raided the office.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I always have a problem with those contracts, if you will, anyways, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not presenting that contract before I purchase the item.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like I get this sprung upon me once I open the box and try and install and play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: At that point, it's like, too fucking late.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_03]: You either agree to this or you get nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, one very interesting note I want to share is according to the Korea Times, the FTC is investigating if Blizzard should be liable for its ill preparation in regards to player traffic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I've ever heard anything like that before that's interesting basically that Blizzard could be responsible for not being prepared for how big their game was going to be I don't know why but I find that fucking fascinating and I think that they should be liable because they had a beta they knew how much traffic was going to be in there and they need to have enough servers and they didn't I mean come on
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to expect the worst case scenario.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to have those extra servers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop trying to cut costs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: He didn't have to make this an online only fucking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's your fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, you know, looking ahead here, if something were to happen, and let's say the game gets pulled in Korea or something, it's not actually the worst case scenario for Blizzard because the real money auction house already doesn't exist in Asia.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I believe that was also because of Korea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't let them do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's still one to watch though.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is kind of unprecedented.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm very curious to see what comes of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anything, this could also just be, you know, for headlines and, you know, to let everybody know we are not messing around, people.
[SPEAKER_05]: This could just end up being a big slap on the wrist and negative press.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no such thing as negative press.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's only press.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about press with a negative slant?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about Lee press on nails?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tacky in more ways than one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, speaking of tacky, Konami, bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, how many of us were led to believe that the Silent Hill HD collection was a port?
[SPEAKER_02]: That they were porting and then reskinning and redoing voices and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Up to the part with the fog?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I kind of thought that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was actually not ported from the final version of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was ported from incomplete source code.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually lost the source codes for the Silent Hill games.
[SPEAKER_05]: The missing source code parts were replaced with frog DNA.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's how they got Jurassic Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here is what the producer, Tom Hewlett, had to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it looks like they just were working with what was left over.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was sort of like what you do when you've got leftover spaghetti, but you don't have enough to make a full meal out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you make a sandwich or something out of your spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_05]: A spaghetti sandwich.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've done it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in college.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, ladies and gentlemen?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think any other gaming podcast in the history of ever would compare Silent Hill HD to a spaghetti sandwich, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're both terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, spaghetti sandwiches.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cold spaghetti sandwich on sourdough bread is actually okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying, just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like a sloppy joe with noodles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Subway sells meatball sandwiches.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not very good either.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, though, that's why we had all the issues because they used frog DNA instead of fog DNA.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no fog in there because they didn't use the right DNA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-uh-uh, you didn't say the magic word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the other thing, the other quote in here was saying, and this is actually pretty funny, I'm going to read this, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of issues such as textures and sound had to be taken out of the compiled game, and that brings with it a host of unique issues, especially when taken on top of the tricky coding workarounds at play in the original games.
[SPEAKER_02]: We certainly had our hands full, I think at one point Heather was blue.
[SPEAKER_03]: La la la la la la la la la la la la.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you can't cut it, then don't make the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's deadlines and investors and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angry internets.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if people have decompiled the release versions of the games, why couldn't they just do the same thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I look at shit like that Sonic HD that outdid Sonic 4 Episode 1, and I kind of go, they did it without the original source code.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: or wasn't the Streets of Rage HD collection done with completely original programming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there was that fan one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are all both 2D stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And once again, this wasn't necessarily something that they needed to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had put these games out before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did they feel compelled?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I know, money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they wanted a quick buck.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad I didn't buy it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where did they put the source code?
[SPEAKER_05]: You would think that kind of stuff goes in a vault somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Akira Yamaoka smuggled it out in his butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clearly.
[SPEAKER_05]: He left Konami and took it with him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess a drive could get demagnetized or something, but how do you lose source code?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why you make backups.
Backups.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet someone could find it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you check behind the couch?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to look online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill Source Code.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates for games coming to a store near you that are hopefully finished.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, Madagascar 3, tying in the new movie that's on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, 3DS, and DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: The new play control stuff is being re-released.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got the Mario Power Tennis on the Wii, which is a port of the GameCube game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Pikmin 2, because Pikmin 2 never came out over here for some reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those, oh hey, we localized this game, but oh, we forgot to release it in the other territory.
[SPEAKER_05]: That whole new play control thing, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, it came out in 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should put out a game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know that the Wii is just like a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could take GameCube games and we'll add the Wii controls to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you kind of have to add the Wii controls to it because there are no GameCube controls.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, that's actually a guarantee on some of the new consoles because there's no GameCube controller ports.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or backwards compatibility anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or backwards compatibility, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you're a Sims 3 fan, Jamie... I lost count.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sims 3 Katy Perry Sweet Treats Pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: More Katy Perry!
[SPEAKER_05]: Just in time for the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have actually officially stopped playing Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they never, every time they would release it, they would never work out how to get it to not have the crappy slowdown issue with your add-ons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what this calls for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Katy Perry Simlish music!
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a good video.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually is a cute little video.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's not in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to stop shading.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and that's, I kid you not, that's literally it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you count Max Payne 3, which technically for us is coming out tomorrow, but it would have been out on Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, on PC Let's travel to Japan and check out the release dates over there Not a whole lot to get excited about but there's a couple games here and there On the PlayStation 3, Tokyo Jungle comes out this week and I'm not sure exactly what this game is Sounds like a zombie game Fucking amazing is what it is
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see the description here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Humans disappeared from Tokyo all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, so it's like 28 days later.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leaving the animals to fend for themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play the game as various animals in this apocalyptic scene.
[SPEAKER_05]: Learn to hunt, gather, and mark territory.
[SPEAKER_05]: P. Game of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to watch this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You play by P?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will watch this right now if it will look good.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Africa good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm rubbing up on buildings.
[SPEAKER_05]: Africa good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, where is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just type the game's title on the YouTube, you'll find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where did you hear about this?
[SPEAKER_03]: From them talking about Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this coming out here?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but at least I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It very well could.
[SPEAKER_03]: I posted actually a thing on Twitter about it because they were talking about dogs and stuff like that, palmerians.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get to be a Pomeranian?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you can be a Pomeranian.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a stinking ad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's wait for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buy me 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Pomeranians.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have wolves.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play as horses, cows.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have different rabbits.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you be a fox?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you could be a fox.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might be able to.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, the best part about it is you unlock costumes for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can get an elephant in roller skates and you can dress them up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a ridiculous looking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just... I need this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so now... Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's by Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or published by Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's Japan Studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Krispies!
[SPEAKER_05]: How many freaking publishers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so we just see like an abandoned city.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dog.
[SPEAKER_05]: That wasn't a dog.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was like a panther person.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is really terrible radio, y'all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was Akotaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was today.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a video on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tokyo Jungle Come on, kick into gear, show me the peeing I want to see some dogs peeing
[SPEAKER_02]: Lions, Bulldogs, Gazelles, and Beagles
[SPEAKER_02]: Giraffes.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hell game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I want to fight between panda bears killing each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a brown bear and a panda bear.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pandemonium.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chickies and piggies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did we see those two dogs were about to mount each other?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the fuck is this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I will import this shit if I have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: This looks astounding.
[SPEAKER_05]: This looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they going to show this at E3 next week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, let's get this game since there's no region coding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Animal Dance, Animal Dance, Animal Dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like they could set the trailer to that music.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you know what they should set it to?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Gilda Radner, Let's Talk Geordie to the Animals.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the new President Cat as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's face it, y'all.
[SPEAKER_05]: President Cat ain't happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I want Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I posted a link on my Twitter.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was today.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: The story is like in Tokyo, little dogs are the king of the jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's basically talking about it's the commercial, I guess, I think, for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's seriously awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, that is now one to kind of keep your eye on is Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch, that'll be like... Bring that to the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be in the corner of the Sony booth somewhere, like some poor intern doesn't even know anything about the game and has to show it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Africa.
Africa.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what Africa should have been.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Africa with killing.
Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_05]: on the PlayStation Vita, Mobile Suit Gundam Seed Battle Destiny, and a Hello Kitty game, Hello Kitty Toeiso Block Crash 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're all waiting for June 14th when Persona 4 comes out on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's just be real right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, lastly, to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, nothing until Lollipop Chainsaw on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does look pretty awesome, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on to the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: On June 5th, Madagascar 3 is a video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was having to do my... I should do my riff-raff voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Master... No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Master...
[SPEAKER_02]: on June 6th we have Virtua Fighter 5 Final Showdown and June 8th Dungeon Bowl which I have no idea what it's about but hey it's got a neat name Chair of Swords for PC, Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 I'm sorry Game of Boring I mean Thrones Chair of Swords and Rayman Origins Chair of Swords alright just a few more stories for you guys I did see one cool thing having to do with that show what?
[SPEAKER_02]: the doctor sitting on the throne what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a few more stories for you guys in the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, there are a couple of court cases resolved themselves this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Epic has one lawsuit against Silicon Knights.
[SPEAKER_03]: As you may remember, Silicon Knights was complaining that...
[SPEAKER_03]: Unreal Engine is too hard to program and that's why two humans sucked it wasn't because we can't make a good game um and they lost so um they owe now 4.45 million dollars to Epic and um
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, of course, they are disappointed with the outcome, Silicon Knights, and they're going to appeal because it can never end.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, Activision is also expected back in court again because Judge has okayed, no doubt, to continue their lawsuit for their appearance in Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may remember that they claimed the agreement...
[SPEAKER_03]: was that they would sing their songs as their characters because they have themselves in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, you can sing anybody's songs with anybody's characters and so some people took offense to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so now they apparently can file their lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I keep feeling like every few months we hear that that lawsuit has slowly progressed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slowly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was originally filed in 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our justice system at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of this sounds plausible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the latest features in the latest dev kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video chat available, but it must be from the main menu of the system, not while playing a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems plausible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Voice commands available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Facial recognition similar to the Xbox Kinect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ability to share achievements with friends by sending videos or screenshots with drawings on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could make the internet a lot more fun, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The TTP possibilities with that are quite quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so that could... Achievement, penis!
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine that the game, like, you know, right up to you getting the achievement actually takes a video, not just of, like, your feet in game, but also, like, video of your face, like Burnout.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember that Burnout game that would, like, show video of you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's Pikura.
[SPEAKER_05]: This could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other interesting one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to know if you think this is plausible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch a friend play online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they kind of have that with spectating, but not all games support that like on Xbox 360, so maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would definitely see the technologies there and people are doing it with, you know, Ustream and Twitch TV and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are just sitting there watching other people play games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Multitasking Keep a text or video walkthrough open from the site while playing the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Swap back and forth as needed.
[SPEAKER_05]: um you can't like have the internet and your game going because those are two different applications but you can have your game going and then you can like I don't there's not a lot you can do with the game suspended I don't think because you really like if you launch anything else it says you can go look at your friends list on the 3ds notifications that's about anything the Vita I know you can because you can like open stuff and as long as you're not trying to run two games at the same time
[SPEAKER_03]: I can see that it's possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, with the other screen, maybe have a walkthrough on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hey, if this is all true, especially kind of like the video screenshot drawing stuff, that's the kind of stuff that I would like Nintendo to surprise us with that would make me go, oh, okay, maybe they do get online.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, this could just all be fan wank and come visit my website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and the other thing, too, is I don't know how much of this they would actually be talking about at E3, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a lot of bullet points for stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, I think all that would come to light in the press announcements or the behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, it's not going to be at the keynote, but you'd see it behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of that stuff tends to come out of interviews and stuff and sites going in asking the questions, is this true, is this true?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, and some of the stuff they read on the internet, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, enough of all this newfangled Wii U drawing penises on your achievement stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go back to a time when games were a little bit simpler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take a trip down memory lane with a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's gonna step into the vault and pull out one game that she thinks, hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: Play this or GTFO.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't have GTFO when I was little.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was get off my lawn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a music game by Konami where you use a guitar.
[SPEAKER_02]: That should just be all that you need to know, but let's go a bit further than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's mostly rock and J-pop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, even every source that you look at is going to say, oh, that's what led to Guitar Hero, even though they tried to deny it in my living room that it was because of guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it's on its 19th version, Guitar Freaks V8, which came out March 28th, 2011.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is said to be the final release of Guitar Freaks V. There will be a spin-off Guitar Freaks XG, actually, well there was one, that came out in Japanese arcades on March 10th, 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had two more buttons added to the fret bar instead of the three.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there is a sequel called Guitar Freaks XG2 that came out on March 9th, 2011.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the controller looks kind of like a Fender Jazzmaster or a Fender Mustang.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has three buttons, red, green, and blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has a pick lever so that you also have a knob that you can use as an effector.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it'll add chorus and delay effects to your guitar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so it really plays a lot like...
[SPEAKER_02]: A reverse poppin' music, or reverse Beatmania 2DX, where everything scrolls very DDR style, you know, from bottom to top, except it uses the bars, and you have to use your strum lever while you hold the appropriate colored button.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can pull your bar back when you see a little guitar flashing on the screen, and you get a wailing bonus.
[SPEAKER_02]: and in some cases you even have hidden things that you can play that will populate this new, I'm glad you picked that song because that's like one of the best songs ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll populate a, what's the word I'm thinking of?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, a new series of items to play on the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually very distracted because Rob picked fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should play a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband and I would pull the crap out of this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, basically your life is powered by your- Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is somebody who edited Fire to be the Mega Man song.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not the song.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I meant- That's not the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: That actually is kind of rad, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I knew it sounded wrong, but I like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let me find the real fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Find the real fire, because real fire is good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although it sounds very MIDI-like.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's the right one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the full version.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me get to where the guitar is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the...
[SPEAKER_05]: I can totally hear where somebody heard the Mega Man song in that though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, your scoring depends on how accurate you are with hitting the key.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have perfect, great, good, poor, and miss.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ratings of poor and miss will deplete your groove gauge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perfect and great will replenish it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If your groove gauge is empty completely, you fail and the game is over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Depending on how the cabinet is set up, you have one to five songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Session Link Super Session
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss this so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could not tell you this far after.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one that had the really cool drum beat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right on Time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right on Time, that was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would always play Right on Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing that you remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is right on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The drum, when you play this in the medium mode, was just like constant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could do it for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: And remember those calluses I had on my hands from playing the damn drum?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we would buy our own drumsticks and use our own drumsticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as the different versions of them, I don't even know if I have time to list them all because there's so many.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, let's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck tons.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had regular mixes up to 11th, and then there was an 8th mix power-up version.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had V2, V3, V4, Rock X Rock, or Rock Cross Rock, V5 Rock to Infinity, V6 Blazing, XG, V7, XG2 Groove to Live,
[SPEAKER_02]: V8, XG3 that came out February 2012 Guitar Freaks V4 and V2 Infinity that were looks like European releases so there's just been all kinds of different versions and also for the Drum Mania ones over in other countries they were called Percussion Freaks just saying so that's it I still was waiting for Sax Maniacs
[SPEAKER_05]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't give up hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Freaks, originally in the arcade, but eventually on the PlayStation in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's in the collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clearly part of the inspiration for Guitar Hero, because again, Red Octane, who funded the original Guitar Hero, used to make... Denied it in my kitchen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Used to make...
[SPEAKER_05]: and those controllers for Guitar Freaks, which had five buttons on them at one point, which Guitar Freaks never had five buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everybody was like, why are they putting out five button controllers?
[SPEAKER_05]: XG has it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, we were going to go right into rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think in light of the power outage a couple weeks ago, I think I should save what we've done so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's do a quick in studio break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back with more Orange Launch Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not live on this June the 3rd of 2012, but it's a radio trick.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're taping on May 31st, a few days beforehand.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thanks to those of you that showed up to chat along with the show anyway at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we will be back live next week, June the 10th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: And podcast folks, hey, you got another show this week, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it'll be a little bit shorter tonight because we're missing the live interaction and just since it's earlier in the week there's not as much to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, we do still have plenty of news including tonight's rapid fire news which Loki's going to start us off with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, there was a new Ratchet & Clank game announced that will also be, well actually it's only going to be released on the PlayStation Network, kind of like what they did with the second Ratchet & Clank game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or no, there's like a middle Ratchet & Clank game, like the second and the third one was out on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's Ratchet & Clank Full Frontal Assault and it's coming this fall.
[SPEAKER_05]: All those Ratchet & Clank games have kind of suggestive names, don't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ratchet and Clank Future Quest for Booty Did they find the booty?
[SPEAKER_03]: They probably did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, it's been rumored for a while that Battlefield 3 is going to try to pull Call of Duty Elite and come out with their own service.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually leaked out and then they finally announced it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe it leaked out and they... I don't know if they've confirmed it or whatever, but what ended up happening is there's this Battlefield 3 Premium...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to cost you $50 and includes five themed expansion packs, some of which have already been announced, and actually one that's already out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to Karkland, which was a pre-order bonus if you bought the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, of course, the Close Quarters DLC, which I think is out, or it's coming out next week on June 4th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then they have Armored Kill, Aftermath, and Endgame are the next three as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently you're going to get exclusive weapons and also two weeks access early to said packs as well of other unique endgame items if you pay $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it seems like they're trying to copy what they're doing with Call of Duty Elite and of course they weren't going to want to do that because if it works, if the shoe fits they made quite a bit of money but originally it came out on the European PlayStation Network store and then got pulled but once it's on the internet that's right, screenshots alright
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, moving on, if you want to get some good games and do some good, there's always the Humble Indie Bundle available at HumbleBundle.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, every time one of these bundles comes out, the internet blows up with, best one yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the fifth one, Humble Indie Bundle 5, was just announced today, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Best one yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I already bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, for real.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, okay, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Psychonauts, Limbo, Super Brothers, Sword & Sorcery, EP, and Amnesia are all available.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you pay above the average price, you get Bastion, which, you know, there's tons of great games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every single one of those games is something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got it for $5.60 to get Bastion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure that the average price is way higher.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've already got most of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, I have amnesia, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not just about being able to get the games cheap, but that you are doing some good because the money doesn't just go to the developers, but it goes to, if you want, again, you get to choose how you divvy up the money, it goes to the Humble Indie Bundle or Child's Play Charity EFF.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want, you can plunk down 15 bucks, give it all to Child's Play Charity and say to everybody else, none for you, bye, and that's how you divvy up the money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, as of the taping of the show, the minimum is $7.51.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine that's going to climb closer to $10 by the time... It's still worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit, these games together, easily worth $60.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, the price of a regular retail game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, if you're feeling charitable or shit, you just want some good games, head over to HumbleBundle.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, it's been out for one day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Already up to 187,100.
[SPEAKER_05]: This number's just climbing.
[SPEAKER_05]: 46, 8, 50, just keeps climbing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine by the time Sunday rolls around, they'll easily be at a half million.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: so Humble Indie Bundle 5 we kind of mentioned this already earlier in the show but if you missed it Game Informer magazine is teasing in the shadows a new Gears of War apparently to be on the July issue of their magazine obviously if this is you know what it is it could be Gears of War 4 it could be a Gears of War spin-off game it's a prequel
[SPEAKER_05]: So just like pre-Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a prequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of Battle.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a prequel because of spoilers regarding the main characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: There cannot be a sequel with the main character.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever said it had to be the main character?
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, in one of the Mass Effect games, they kill Shepard and bring him back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's not a spoiler because that's in the very beginning of the game, Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anything is possible, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I always love when people say, oh, no, they can't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a prequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Time travel and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: They can do whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look what they did with Star Trek, for fuck's sake.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another Gears of War game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They found a way to maybe bring Khan back, although they swear up and down it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another Gears of War game.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, whatever it is, it's coming soon, as in E3 soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some more stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Spy Hunter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do Well, I was playing that on my iPad, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Spy Hunter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which the control sucks, because it's no steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to tilt your iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, basically it's a reboot on the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically super spy racing type game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically you are the spy and you have to go catch bad guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you do that in a fast vehicle and you destroy enemy vehicles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your car is called the G6155 Interceptor, which is supposed to transform from a supercar to offer an assault vehicle to a speedboat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can go hunt and capture those nasty, nasty spies.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the real question is, did they license the theme from Peter Gunn?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if not, forget it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the theme in a remix dubstep of the... Dubstep is evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wubba, wubba, wubba, wubba, wubba, wubba, wubba.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's being done by Warner Brothers Interactive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be on 3DS and PS Vita in the fall.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do Dubstep and Downtown Julie Brown have in common?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wubba Wubba.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wubba Wubba Wubba!
[SPEAKER_02]: So Capcom has registered a trademark for a potential game called Remember Me.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't really know anything else about that except that it was filed on May 22nd this year in both the US and Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe this will be something at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be the subtitle to another game too, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It may not necessarily be a standalone game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember me, the sensible Capcom that put out regular games that were fun and people liked buying them and we didn't have download content that was on disc?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember me, sensible Capcom?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm gone forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now it's time for a joke that nobody but maybe two of our listeners will get.
Remember!
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, you know what I was distracted by, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: A story about this guy eating his roommate's brain and heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ew, that's like that grody old... Have you read about all that crap coming out of Canada?
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't happen in Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy eating faces in Florida, but if I lived in Florida, I'd probably go crazy too.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: People, stop being ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that guy in Canada got caught finally?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: This guy named Alexander Kinyua ate his roommate's heart and brain and his dad found him with the head and hands in a bucket in his basement.
[SPEAKER_02]: His dad turned him in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not Google that guy who they want in Canada because you'll read all these stories about he didn't just do fucked up things to humans and you will get mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will get mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Allegedly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say allegedly.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's a guy in Japan who killed a couple of women and ate them and now he's a celebrity and does tours.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Serious?
[SPEAKER_05]: In no evidence.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: He wrote... That sounds like the plot of Natural Born Killers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you ever see that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Robert Downey Jr.
[SPEAKER_05]: back when he was on drugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll find the guy's name.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he did it like 30 years ago, and now he goes around doing tours about what it's like to eat people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That totally sounds like the plot to Natural Born Killers.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anyhow...
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need some happiness and cheerfulness.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's look at video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got his name.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: His name is Issei Sagawa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's nothing more happier and cheerful than Doom 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doom 3 is getting the HD treatment for PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not only are you getting Doom 3 with HD graphics, extra levels, 3D support, they even have head-mounted display support, which...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not really sure there's that many head-mounted displays out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that apparently John Carmack made one, and it had duct tape on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: John Carmack has one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's why it's in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he's supporting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, Doom 1 and 2 are also included, and it's supposed to be out this fall.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's another awesome question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why Doom 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because... Just because maybe it was kind of over... I don't want to say it was overlooked, but it certainly didn't have that same cultural grab that the first two did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Doom 3 because they are a new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rage Bombed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not Quake 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Quake 3 was Quake... It's basically Quake Live now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Quake Live, which I think they... Don't they have Quake 3 on Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_05]: They do, you're right, they do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And technically they were releasing Quake... Well, they actually are releasing Quake 4 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Quake 4 wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: On Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was one of the launch titles for 360, remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and here's the thing I want to kind of know about it, though, is remember, the launch title, and hopefully you can find Dirt Cheap now, it...
[SPEAKER_03]: The game wasn't very good, but it came with Quake 2 on another disc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The even-numbered Quakes, it's like the opposite of Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_05]: The even-numbered Quakes are not very good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Quake 2 was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quake 3 was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Compared to 1 and 3, 3 was the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: Asky Quake, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's only going to be $20.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to be coming out in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you can buy one of the original copies for $5 and get it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you're not into first-person shooters, maybe you're into first-person role-playing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of the biggest ones out there right now is Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_05]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally, an expansion coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't know exactly when yet, but we do finally have a title.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one of those pre-E3 leaks where the companies try to get a jump on all that press coverage.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be, you know, because everybody's fighting for time during E3 week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, what is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, you can turn into a bunch of bats, so there's a vampire theme going on, which was already in the game, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can already be a vampire, but this actually shows, like, you can transform into, like, a giant bat thing and, like, fly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, kind of a really weird... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, bat thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, bat thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: 30 days later is when the rest of us can play it because Microsoft basically sold their soul to get this and so can you in the expansion to Skyrim because Microsoft gives it up better I like the little castle on fire the little dark castle looking thing it's like the little obsidian portal in Minecraft but prettier
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you played way more Skyrim than I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's your interest level in this?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm interested in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not as excited as before, you know, because I was like, oh, I'm going to get whatever expansion they put out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, like, it has to do with vampires.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't really done anything with vampires.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been just trying to make sure I don't turn into a vampire because it's lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not because of Twilight, but I just don't want to be a vampire or a werewolf in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that horse that was on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that map.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's glowing like Tron?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I think that was the Elder Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: When you said that you were interested in that, it totally made me think of Alucard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm interested in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is kind of, it does look like you can play as Alucard in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would play Skyrim if I could be Alucard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wish.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can name your character Alucard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it would be really impossible for them to add it later on because it's such a rewrite of code.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just want, you know, I know they have Skyrim, or not Skyrim, Elder Scrolls Online, which is really weird because it gets lamer and lamer each update that they put out on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like every update that there is for it, I get less and less interested in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I really wish there was just like co-op.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like four-player co-op in Skyrim would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is the part of the show where we'd move into the mailbag segment, except there's no emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So instead, we're going to plug and say, email us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to email us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll read your email next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surely, with E3 going on, there's going to be something that makes you want to email us and have your voice heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: So mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't call them Shirley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lack of email makes us angsty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, my FU goes to this continuously not having a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, boo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the fact that I can't go to E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of miss going to E3 each year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a couple years now that I haven't been able to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if it is a lame E3, I still like going and playing the stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my boss and his boss get to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: They go to meetings.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, so where did you go check out at E3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we didn't even go on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, what was it, last year?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to think what they saw last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was something very lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It may have been Bethesda.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's just, they waste time there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would like to display our new game, Cat Butthole.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do take that back.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is their fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they only go down for like one or two days.
[SPEAKER_03]: They miss a day or two of the time there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: You could be hitting the show for... But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't fucking care and his boss...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to just too much to do and not enough time to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to the fact that I kind of bring that on myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, F you to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what you get for procrastinating.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not even procrastinating.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just maybe I don't know how to say no.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe I need to learn.
[SPEAKER_05]: That has nothing to do with this program or VOG or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just other things in life that maybe I need to just say
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's time to stop because I'm just too damn busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, look at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is possible to say no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say it to you all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that's it for the FU of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into a few more stories for you guys before we say goodnight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always a rumor that there's going to be an announcement of a redesign of the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's actually looking like it may actually happen this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason behind that is Amazon has stopped carrying the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily that they've stopped selling it, but they themselves have stopped selling it on the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's only available through third-party providers, because you know anybody can go on Amazon and sell stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's actually stuff that's sold directly by Amazon.
[SPEAKER_03]: that's in the US region not only that but in Japan they also have stopped having the 3DS available so why do you think they've stopped selling the 3DS maybe because there's another 3DS coming out did somebody report the original 3DS is flawed to Amazon and they stopped selling it that could have happened too maybe
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: so it's interesting the other thing is the thoughts are that there's a rumor that they're going to announce Monster Hunter for the 3DS coming this E3 as well for the North American region alright I mean there's going to be a redesign it's just when I think it could be this holiday
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, this is pretty shitty, is, uh, rumors and fakeness all over the interwebs, and, uh, I, I, I did want to bring it up, though, because there was a part of me that went, well, what if?
[SPEAKER_05]: Square Enix announced what's gonna be at their booth, that part's not a lie, and what I thought was interesting, was completely missing from that list, was Final Fantasy Versus XIII, because it's like, shouldn't that fucking game be out by now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, how long has that been in development, and we've, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the thought out there is, well, maybe it's like a secret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe something's happening with it, and they're going to show it at one of the conferences or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this crazy-ass rumor came out, complete with fake footage, that Final Fantasy Versus XIII was renamed to Final Fantasy XV.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be fair, that part I'd actually believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people poo-pooing that idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd actually believe that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still don't understand how they tie with each other anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I'd believe more?
[SPEAKER_05]: That they renamed Final Fantasy Versus XIII to Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you mean there was already a... Just shh, shh.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's already a Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, apparently the game was going to be coming to the Wii U. Now, I guess it's because of the footage.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even watch the footage, but I'm looking at it here, this one-minute clip here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can just tell that that's an overlaid thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently people are watching this footage or whatever, and then you see the logo for Final Fantasy XV, and yeah, it doesn't look too convincing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it did kind of make me stop and go, well, why couldn't it be on the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the Wii U is supposed to be getting all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's why.
[SPEAKER_05]: They wouldn't put it only on the Wii U. It's because... Well, to be fair, it was PlayStation 3 and Wii U. Like, somebody took out the Xbox logo and put the Wii U logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: They know that they need to make money on this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to cut out the Xbox just because of the Wii U. I mean, they sold plenty of copies of Final Fantasy XIII and XIII-2 on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to ignore that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And XIV was cut for totally different reasons that had to do with the Xbox Live infrastructure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rules that were bent for Final Fantasy XI, Microsoft would not bend on again because XI didn't do that well on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, they're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's anything going to be for the Wii U, or even like, it's always been their own game that's been kind of lame on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think if there's anything on the Wii U, it's going to be another lame Crystal Chronicles game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: If that whole Wii U being similar to the Game Boy Advance linking to the GameCube, there was that Final Fantasy game that was specifically for that setup, so it would be very easy to make a sequel to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't see them doing... I don't see them coming out with... Because I've seen rumors... Of course, everybody's making up fucking rumors.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a rumor I read, and I didn't even open the page because it just looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're talking about...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Kingdom Hearts Remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to have all these different characters and stuff from all these games and it's only going to be on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could Square be withholding Kingdom Hearts 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I wish?
[SPEAKER_05]: If wishes were fishes.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got plenty of stuff that they're working on right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: If wishes and musts were buckets of... Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If wishes and musts were clusters of nuts, we'd all have a bowl of granola.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is official.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to Tim Cook with Apple, they don't really care about doing consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not interested in doing it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe someday, but not now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they're cool with the little iOS games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, he says customers love games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just makes me think of bitches love games, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: but he goes on record saying I'm not interested in being in the console business and what is thought of as traditional gaming but Apple is a big player today and things in the future will only make that bigger
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if the rumor's true that they're building their own TVs and shit, then they can just take the iPad, iPhone stuff over to the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: It prints money.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not console in the traditional sense, that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can't deny it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apple's a player in gaming right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're probably thinking that they're beyond consoles anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're bigger than consoles, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Smurfs Village just puts that Gears of War to shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really don't need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be honest, they don't need it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to see Apple do a console.
[SPEAKER_05]: What they're doing right now is challenging the industry enough, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially Nintendo, the handheld market.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't deny that the iPhones and iPads are breathing a lot of heat on not just the Vita, but the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: To the point where shareholders are calling on Nintendo to put Mario on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually agree it would be terrible because the touch controls just wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the record, on a whim, I got Mega Man 2 on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the stuff that comes from the stuff that comes out of an ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what they could do, though, on the iPhone that would work is like a Zelda game like they have on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was all stylus control.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might work.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it still sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a guitar pee urinal that basically has like little strum bars in it and a big fret bar coming out of the top that you can pee in it and then you can actually get a code to download your pee song later.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's sad is that is the second time we've talked about pee-based games in a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I brought it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I weep for our society.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's apparently a video up of what guitar pee sounds like.
[SPEAKER_05]: No thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I do have a few things I was just going to cover real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: So someone supported Super Road Blaster to the SNES.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Super Road Blaster, or I should say Road Blaster, which was a 1985 Laserdisc arcade game with animations, like a full motion video thing, like Dragon's Lair or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's actually created a ROM file that's 6,320 megabits, although when you compare that with the largest SNES cartridge, which is only 48 megabits, it's a little impossible to run without special software.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can actually get a SD2 SNES SD card adapter that will allow you to run the game on a physical SNES, and it actually works.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can download the ROM, which is 118 megs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for a Super Nintendo ROM, that's huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it plays a full motion video and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that cartridge back in the day probably would have cost about $900.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have cost about as much as the... And it would have had to be in like a super gigantic box.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neo Geo CD Projekt Red Cyberpunk
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have a late tweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a tweet just now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or I should say an hour ago, but that was while we were in the middle of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here's a question from Osfer who sent a legit question for the show tonight, so we need to entertain it here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Osfer tweets us at twitter.com slash OLR asking, tweet for the show, what is a game that frustrated you like no other?
[SPEAKER_05]: A game that frustrated you like no other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle and Desu was one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because some of the puzzles get really hard and fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just a pain.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, um... Shoot, it's something that actually... Well, Fractal, actually, for a little while was getting me super frustrated because I'm on the part now where you have splits in weird places and it'll, like, completely mess up your trying to get your blooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's pretty fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a few games with puzzles in them.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few puzzles...
[SPEAKER_05]: For me, Super Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan used to ask me to play Super Meat Boy because he used to giggle when I would get really frustrated with the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was some type of satisfaction for him.
[SPEAKER_05]: So definitely Super Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's the whole point of that game is to get frustrated and want to throw the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: V, V, V, V.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing is I played that game without downloading it on Steam, and then I just now downloaded it on Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't import my save.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Womp, womp.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually copy it directly out of the save folder.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so, because I am not fucking doing that again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did that with my games.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 3DS, I'm just stuck in one level that I'm never going to get past.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's when that little asshole is following you and you can't get him killed either.
[SPEAKER_03]: I finished all that, but I have one more little shiny object thing to get, and it's just like, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I quit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's the tweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Retro City Rampage, speaking of Super Meat Boy, has this cool little trailer that they put out for a game within the game called Virtual Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's done like Virtual Boy, but you're playing as Meat Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you also get to play as Meat Boy in the game, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it has 3D with like the red blue glasses if you want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's funny because Super Meat Boy kind of had those throwback stages like there was the NES stages and there was a Game Boy stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: A Virtual Boy stage makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of funny actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the last thing I was going to mention real quick, well, actually two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo's patented a new kind of input device for the 3DS it's a vibrating stylus it's going to allow you to have some sort of haptic feedback for stuff based on the position I guess of where the stylus is compared to the camera
[SPEAKER_05]: TTP V
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the last one was kind of in the line of why the fuck did they make this?
[SPEAKER_03]: CTA, a company that makes accessories, and I think they made that thing for, was it Connected Ventures?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember the raft?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was completely pointless.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it was just a raft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That shit was amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have done themselves one more.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have made an inflatable go-kart that you can sit in and play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard of this already, I thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: The 3DS Mario Kart 7 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, for the 3DS now.
[SPEAKER_05]: A giant inflatable kart for your portable console.
[SPEAKER_03]: You put your 3DS within this little steering wheel thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you spend $40?
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need to pretend that you're in a cart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just so stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's going to bring us to the close of another episode of Orange Lounge Radio, but not until we go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought tonight my final thought is hey, there's pictures of the E3 show floor I'm sad, I can't go I'm sad that you're sad no leaks
[SPEAKER_05]: my final thought is I really want to just thank everybody who's worked really hard on VOGnetwork.com especially Bobby's been doing a heck of a lot of the coding and all that fun stuff but you know and again I can't say too much because I don't know if the Friday thing happened for sure or not yet at this point but just some of the people that are doing some other work behind the scenes who I'll congratulate more specifically later on I just really want to thank you all for your work I'd like to thank the Academy and yay VOG
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Launch Radio, remember, we don't ask for you guys to send us tons of money or we don't ask for much.
[SPEAKER_05]: We always ask for you is to help spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Word of mouth is what gives us advertising and just tell a friend or two about the show or leave us a nice review on iTunes always helps and what have you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It all goes a long way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help promote the show and of course the new Voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a wonderful week everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back live on June 10th at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until then have a safe week and have a fun E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!
... ...