[SPEAKER_00]: Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, June 10th, 2012, E3 2012 has come to a close and we discussed the highlights, the lowlights, and everything in between with our live audience.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, Loki in the mid lights too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio live as we always are every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at VOG Network, the Voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_12]: VOGnetwork.com is where you can go and if you click on live chat, you can chat live with us, the hosts of
[SPEAKER_12]: of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about gaming and, of course, this week, the Big E3 Expo with my co-host.
[SPEAKER_12]: First up, Jamie Summers, or DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like you were giving my salad the sting eye.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was trying to figure out what was in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, is that avocado?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's avocado.
[SPEAKER_02]: I made, basically, avocado mango salsa.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And put it over fresh greens.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just, you know, green things are always kind of the, hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: with goat cheese on top.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all raw.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And delicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I am back to eating raw food.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not vegan, mind you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not vegan.
[SPEAKER_12]: How do you do raw food without being vegan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sashimi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fish.
[SPEAKER_02]: And beef tataki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And raw milk cheese and raw milk.
[SPEAKER_02]: That works.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yogurt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can have fermented things, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's also go over to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who will probably talk about his very non-raw food diet of McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had pop chips, I think that falls somewhere in between the two of you
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually had dinner before I came to this show, and then I picked that up on the way, because I was still kind of hungry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to stop at Burger King, but there was a bunch of car crashes right in front of the turn to turn into the shopping center with the Burger King.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, ah, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Party at Burger King.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's probably stupid people in the light rail.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever happened to parties at Burger King?
[SPEAKER_12]: When I was young, and this might be dating myself a bit here, but people used to have their birthday parties at McDonald's and Burger King.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that still a thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's all Chuck E. Cheese now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Chuck E. Cheese was... That's not food either.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, sometimes they have good games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It really is the shittiest pizza anywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, it's still okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know who started Pizza Time Theater, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And crap, now I forgot his name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Atari dude.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, Nolan Bushnell.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Didn't he start a place in Woodland Hills not that long ago?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if it's still open.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was about a year or two ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to the original Chuck E. Cheese way back.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the coolest one, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like two stories?
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a two-story slide.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had the full animatronic band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Mobile, where I'm from, we had a massive Chuck E. Cheese slash Showtime pizza that had the party room with the hippo girl in it who played a piano.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Alan said he remembered that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we had the big party room with the full band and the room that you go into to go to the bathroom that's all LED lights on the wall that would give me a seizure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the hands and feet on the wall that would clap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chuck E. Cheese in a way is almost responsible, I mean for real, for me being like so into video games because I remember, I distinctly remember going when I was three or four years old, it was my sister's wedding reception and
[SPEAKER_12]: for some reason was at Chuck E. Cheese that's awesome no no no wait no no I think it was like the after reception reception like it was like the real reception was at the Elk Lodge but then like the wedding party and the families was more for the kids so they I think my sister was like let's do something for Rob and the kids and so because my sister was is 16 years older than I am so that's why like I'm I'm four and she's like 20 getting married right
[SPEAKER_12]: We all went to Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_12]: People ask, what is one of your earliest memories?
[SPEAKER_12]: I distinctly remember Crystal Castles and the trackball and the little box that they used to have to bring over that you could stand on so I could be a four-year-old playing Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had to sit down pole position.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when they closed the big Chuck E. Cheese, they actually moved the same pole position cabinet to the newer Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did, as an adult, go back and play the exact same one I played as a small kid.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let's go to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks to Travis last night, we have thevognetwork.com as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can also access at thevognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I believe, I don't know, I might get a hand slap from Bobby for making this public, but I know you registered it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Voiceofgeeks.com also works.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Several ways you can get to our website.
[SPEAKER_12]: We prefer vognetwork.com, but you can also do thevognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Going to our chat room, Vince Raven is in our chat room saying, is this a pre-recorded show or live?
[SPEAKER_12]: It must be live because I just read your name.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are live tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know it was taped last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no such thing as pre-recording.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just recording.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they say.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the buzzword.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's voiceofgeeks.com, not voiceofgeeksnetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right, it's voiceofgeeks.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: And some folks in the chat room are hand slapping there for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, some folks reminiscing about Showbiz Pizza, which I believe was the Chuck E. Cheese of the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of the same thing and they merge.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like Black Wolf is in there saying, Showbiz Pizza where a kid can be a kid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, now it's where a kid can get shot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if you read some of the crazy things that happened at Chuck E. Cheese on Yahoo and news and all that stuff, but they got an image problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: We have folks, I see Rob from Girls Gone Wow from the UK is listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw Clover Nikon, who I believe is from Australia, is listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got like an international group here tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now here I am talking about our little hometown of Sacramento, but there used to be this place called the Mindshaft.
[SPEAKER_12]: That place was the shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it's like an abandoned RV.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, now it's like a scary place.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you used to go underground to start the miniature golf.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had a two-story arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then right before it closed, it had a dance club in the basement.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was commonly known as the Mormon Dance Club because I guess the mineshaft was owned by Mormons.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so the Mormon Dance Club...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't even know how that works, but I just know that's what everybody calls it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We did go there one summer, like, you know, just, ah, we'll go play miniature golf there, because I've never really been there before, like, and man, it was run down.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Morpheus is reminding me about Samstown, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Samstown was awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn, we had some great entertainment.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm sure wherever you're from, in your hometown, you used to have these great entertainment places that have probably all shut down.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alan, were there any awesome ones in the Bay Area that I'm not thinking of?
[SPEAKER_12]: He's ignoring me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, he's shaking his head.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what we had in Mobile?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still there and it's changed names, but it used to be called Mount Asia.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a huge, like, multi-level mini-golf, but it had a great arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I played Trog for the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hooked on that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: the only thing notable I can remember in the East Bay was in Concord there was a big Malibu Grand Prix which had the RC cars and then a huge arcade but it closed when I was like 7 so I barely remember it they still have some in Scandia I love, not necessarily our Scandia our Scandia went, I don't know what happened to our Scandia it's just weird but like the other Scandias they still have the old arcades and stuff they're kind of cool, they still have that vibe they have the go-karts and miniature golf and that kind of stuff
[SPEAKER_12]: I miss retro arcades I wish that's why I loved Flynn's Arcade at Disneyland and we weren't here last week because I made another trip to Disneyland and so I got to see Electronica's replacement which is the Mad Tea Party now I didn't see the actual party because we were there on weekdays but I saw the decorations and it pained me to see Flynn's Arcade just gone just totally gone the front had been replaced with something else that wasn't even really themed for Alice in Wonderland just made me sad
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Vognetwork.com, our official site has launched.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you visited it back in May when we first established the network with Bobby and Understation Live, we had kind of a temporary site there that was just one page with the chat room taking up the whole page.
[SPEAKER_12]: The full site is now available and if you haven't been able to take a look at it, I really encourage you to go because...
[SPEAKER_12]: In one week, and I'm not just saying this because it's part of my idea, the whole site.
[SPEAKER_12]: But in one week, we've accomplished so much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really proud.
[SPEAKER_12]: And a lot of that is the very hard work that Bobby's been putting in on the programming side of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But there's been a lot of hard work on the content side too.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have some great authors for editorials that we picked up thanks to Twitter shoutouts.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jeff, I know, is one of them, and Elliot.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've been writing some great stuff for the site.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's not just video game stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember, it's the Voice of Geeks Network, so we have articles on Indiana Jones.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have articles on, of course, Minecraft, and there's some other things, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's a wide variety of things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, right before the show, I was asking Ramal, who are these people that are writing stuff for our site?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't recognize these people.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Twitter's a powerful thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know Elliot's been following me on Twitter for a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's based out of the UK and he sent me a direct message that took me like three weeks to respond to because my Twitter app was acting up but he already did some writing I think for either a high school or a college paper and I was like, alright, you want to write for us?
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool, let's see it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And he did that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jeff came in from, this is really cool, Video Game Outsiders retweeted us when I put, or retweeted me I should say when I put the call out for...
[SPEAKER_12]: uh authors which by the way let me just really quick really quickly say the fact that we're all like supportive of each other I love video game outsiders and you know I know they they sent the retweet for me and everything I hope this dispels the whole there's an all games and VOG network war
[SPEAKER_12]: and they're a fightin' and it's civil frickin' war.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let it go and stop it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stop spreading those rumors.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let them do their thing and be great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let us do our thing and also be great because if we're both great, everybody wins.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, Jeff came in through that retweet and his stuff's been great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, Loki, you say you've been reading that stuff and it's really funny and it's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, going to our chat room again at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: A little more reminiscing there and some talk about E3 as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft is teasing that some of the content from Orange Launch Radio, I love this song, is coming this week to VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right, it's going to be growing.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you haven't checked out vognetwork.com, please do.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not just the station.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the articles.
[SPEAKER_12]: And most importantly, the big thing that was announced the Friday before was that it's all a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can actually sign up.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can find loot places on the site.
[SPEAKER_12]: So EJ from Girls Gone Wow, continuing our conversation from a couple weeks ago, there's your loot.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can check it out over there on the site and you can get loot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't tell you how you get loot, but I'll tell you one of them is really easy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like sign up for the website easy and you get loot.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can comment on articles, thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can actually, if you notice, Bobby posted a review of, I'm going to mess up the name of this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Jam Music Band or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: This just came out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: He wrote a review of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you can actually write a review that agrees or disagrees.
[SPEAKER_12]: And your review, if approved by the original author, which they're not going to disapprove it just because you disagree with them, will show up right underneath the original review.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you can kind of have your own say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, I disagree because X, Y, Z. So pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll have more stuff like that come to the site in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_12]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: VOG Network.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Again, Orange House Radio listeners, if you haven't checked out the website since the placeholder that was there last month, so much has changed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go back into games and talking about E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: And before we get into our own gaming week and the stuff we've been playing as we usually start the show off with, I know we're going to do a lot of recapping about E3 tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I want to talk about this topic that's been brought up that's kind of hovering over the air.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that is the question of, is E3 still relevant?
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, the ESA was very quick to defend that question, basically, that was asked by saying, of course it's still relevant.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't have the quote in front of me, so I'm paraphrasing, of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: But all the attention is on Los Angeles this week, and it's still the place to have games shown and be covered and be exposed to the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is the place to be.
[SPEAKER_12]: But there's a lot of people that are saying, well, you know, in this day and age of the Internet...
[SPEAKER_12]: and where everything kind of goes to Spike TV the first day or G4 hits the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it really that important to be there live and in person?
[SPEAKER_12]: So I want to ask those in studio, especially considering this year E3 was a bit different for us personally.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is the first year at Orange Lounge Radio in quite some time.
[SPEAKER_12]: We didn't really cover it.
[SPEAKER_12]: None of us went.
[SPEAKER_12]: And let me ask that question.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is E3 still relevant?
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's still relevant because they have a lot of great games being shown there, but they've kind of made it really difficult for... Well, they've always made it kind of difficult for independent coverage of E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's more of having to cover the... You don't get invited to the press events, so you cover the feed from Spike TV or something like that, and you make your comments off of that, which works just fine because it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: you get to see the same stuff pretty much except you don't get to actually play any of it
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think for the gaming industry, I think it's not necessarily the greatest thing for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, just because a lot of companies are being hit financially pretty hard and they can't afford to have these really huge booths and spend millions of dollars on the stuff like THQ, for example, not at E3 because they can't afford to spend money on that kind of stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have jobs at stake and...
[SPEAKER_10]: and their own companies, so they can't do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think that as far as saying, oh, E3 is the place to go for game news and to see the games and stuff, I don't think that's necessarily the case.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, yeah, it is a place to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's definitely something that people look forward to, but there's also other conventions out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's PAX, which is definitely getting a lot of coverage for games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And honestly, I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: You can scale down your booth size a bit and show the same type of stuff there, and I think still get the same kind of press coverage that they're getting with E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Granted, they're not doing these huge keynote events and stuff like that, but I still think it's a good way to get your game covered.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plus, in the day and age of the internet, there's also companies just launching their own games on Kickstarter or through other means, and they can get press coverage that way or...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I don't think press is necessarily a problem, because people were probably talking about Madden and Assassin's Creed and stuff like that beforehand, but now it's just, hey, look, we've got a bunch of people showing off Assassin's Creed at the Sony press conference, at the Ubisoft press conference, and at the Xbox press conference, and at the Nintendo press conference, because they only showed Ubisoft games...
[SPEAKER_10]: because a lot of them just thought they were so awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I could see how they could come to that conclusion.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just... I'm just jealous I didn't get to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like to play some more games, but honestly, digesting it through just reading other sites' covering and stuff, I feel that I kind of took in more information than if I were to be stumbling around because it seems like every time I'd go to E3, it would be like, oh, hey...
[SPEAKER_10]: There's this really cool game and I didn't get to see it because I completely was unaware that they had talked about it or it was announced or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I just never made it over to that booth because I wanted to go see something I was aware of beforehand.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it is important to be there in person if you can.
[SPEAKER_12]: I always enjoy the experience.
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Morpheus from Saturday's Under Station Live I'm reading like comments from other shows tonight but that's alright it's a network DJ Morpheus from Saturday's Under Station Live says I said it during Bobby's show but I see South by Southwest becoming the dominant game showcase in a couple of years that's a very interesting prediction because South by Southwest is the place where things like Foursquare really took off and I don't know if you view Foursquare as a game but if you look at VOG Network as a game South by Southwest would probably be our show right?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's an interesting perspective, especially with the technology and everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Except Foursquare kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: But think of all the clones that exist.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, think of it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Facebook basically jacked Foursquare.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, then again, one could argue, okay, Grant, I better get this out or I'll get corrected.
[SPEAKER_12]: Google Latitude was kind of also before all of that, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: I believe that was, if I got my tech history right, that was Dodgeball, and the Dodgeball guy started Foursquare.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've gone cross-eyed.
[SPEAKER_02]: At this point, these big conventions just kind of seem pointless to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if they really wanted to get reviews and get the press information out there, they would go to like a virtual format, you know, VE3 or something, and send out demos directly to the press.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're just wasting time and money.
[SPEAKER_12]: WhatUpG in our chat says, the only thing you don't get from not being at E3 is any hands-on time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I remember a couple years ago when they did a lot of demos, not all of them, obviously, but quite a handful of demos were available on Xbox Live as they were there at the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2006 was the year that they did that, and they had MotoGP and Lost Planet, and there was one other one, but I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: E3 at home is basically, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: We know that you can't go to E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's some of the E3 demos that are available right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why don't they do that anymore?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a good way to get information out about your game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I understand people are like, oh, it's not finished.
[SPEAKER_10]: But who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: You just put that up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, unfinished game, but you get to check out the demo for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shadownext, JenJuz bring up an interesting point in our chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sending out demos to the press wouldn't necessarily work.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not everyone has debug units that can play the early code.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe that's a part of it that the code isn't ready for that live environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: They usually prepare demos that have taken care of hiding any errors and are programmed for certain time limits.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some companies are sick of doing that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember reading an article on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some companies are thinking that E3 demos are actually not a waste of their time, but it's taking away time from developing for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, why have E3 at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't see it being relevant anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Going to other comments in our chatroom, Dartetsuya says, we totally need VOG Con.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dream big, maybe someday, dream big.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see, and Tigerclaw notices that I am on PlayStation Home right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is correct.
[SPEAKER_12]: Over there on the TV, look, I'm sitting next to Tigerclaw on the couch.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am in PlayStation Home, and I wanna pimp the new VOG Network Clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you have your PlayStation nearby, fire it up,
[SPEAKER_12]: Search in the clubhouses for VOG and you'll get VOG Network in all caps.
[SPEAKER_12]: And hopefully, oh, it looks like Blender left, but hopefully he'll be back and he can accept more apps into the clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I gotta say, Blender did a great job with the clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't even know they had new ones now.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's got this whole desert, I think it's called the Desert Penthouse or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like a little pool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look at all those arcade games he's got in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the couch totally looks like it's floating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, notice Tigerclaw and I are sitting on the couch, but not too close together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not too close.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a nice doodly distance apart.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do not believe that that's actually home.
[SPEAKER_10]: No one is doing The Running Man.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hey, DDR Machine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that a DDR Machine?
[SPEAKER_12]: Get out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's like a little DDR Machine over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe that is a DDR Machine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, speaking of home, they have the whole virtual, you know, not to, you know, I mentioned Xbox a minute ago, but they do their whole virtual Sony booth.
[SPEAKER_12]: Granted, it's not the same as being there, but it's kind of a neat little tie-in.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, it kind of, again, there's always that question of what the hell's the point of home?
[SPEAKER_12]: But when you see something like that, you kind of go, oh, that is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you ever look at the virtual booth in home?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't been to home for a long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually haven't ever used home.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you gotta check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of neat there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing on my PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe Tigerclaw is fulfilling the running man quota here.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I gotta say, this may be the reason to bring a live webcam back to the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't have the cam on us, but put the cam in Sony Home.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you guys can look at that while we broadcast.
[SPEAKER_12]: I seriously might do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brainstorming live on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mister, I'm gonna keep the webcam.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can have the webcam.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look, here's the webcam.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: All yours.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a blast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I thought you had your video camera hooked up.
[SPEAKER_12]: That died, sadly.
[SPEAKER_12]: That $400 camera died.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's part of the reason we haven't had video in a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: That webcam isn't the best resolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually think that my camera still works.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I've never tried it as a webcam.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have to convert all of those Disneyland movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think my Panasonic still works.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an HD camcorder that I'm not using at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's move on and talk about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll come back to E3 in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki's going to wrap up the whole thing for us and we're going to give our witty insight and commentary.
[SPEAKER_12]: First off though, let's talk about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I am so proud of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a bunch of Mass Effect until I decided that I really would rather play it on the PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I hate the targeting system so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it hurts my hand to try to retarget.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I kept dying when I found Counselor Troi.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: The matriarch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I swear, she must have been on some pretty nasty PMS.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, so yeah, all of the Asari commandos whooped my ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I decided to play on PC instead, and I've remade my FemShep and totally going after Garrus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't judge me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Another one indoctrinated, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played some WoW.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_12]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dealer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dealer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you are the game pimp, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to kind of blame Shane for that, really, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was just like, that's like the whole, like, this is like, Mass Effect is now this Tupperware pyramid scheme.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Shane is kind of like the regional director, and he got me hooked.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now, in an attempt to, you know, get my free toaster, I got DarkSakura hooked.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a pyramid scheme.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, and I want to point out, Tigerclaw totally moved closer to me on that couch.
[SPEAKER_12]: You see that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's still a doodly distance.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is a doodly distance.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I think that's the... That's the appropriate distance for dudes to be apart.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is the programmed distance away.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where your hitbox is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I also played... I did play WoW.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll put a picture of this on OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I started another MMO just because of Iguana Girl, of Jessica Harper, who has said, it's gorgeous, it's gorgeous, it's gorgeous, so finally I'm like, okay, I'll give it a try, you know, because I'm a little bored with WoW because other people are playing Diablo all the damn time, shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, the Pyramid Head scheme, pfft.
[SPEAKER_02]: um so I started playing Lord of the Rings online and it's actually not bad um it's very pretty I actually prefer it graphically to well um lots of lots of fun in-depth stuff I really like how it more mirrors the books and you know without Tolkien's horrible horrible writing I'm sorry you spend we spend five pages describing the landscape and like half a paragraph describing the people you're talking about that's not good writing
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm probably going to hell in the minds of lots of Tolkien fans, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play a little Diablo, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I actually, you know, I've only played, I'm only a level 8 character right now in Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_02]: it's enough that I've gotten kind of a grasp that number one I like the camera in WoW better but I like the scenery and the graphics in Lord of the Rings better I do have to say that WoW has better water effects just saying um
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually, when I had it optimized, it basically lets me run the game at full settings.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had some lag today, but for the most part, it actually runs pretty smoothly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've basically had some problems with some kill stealing, so I don't like that my targets aren't locked, but you know, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the free part.
[SPEAKER_02]: The free's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played some STO this week, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to play Dabo at Deep Space Nine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been MMOing it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have been.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like a little whore here.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not a whore because I'm paying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody clip that little phrase and send it to Travis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a Momo slut.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing the field.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, if guys can do it and are lauded for it, then a woman should be able to be lauded for spreading herself out a little bit too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Double standard here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Double standard.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was writing his show for him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... And I have also decided... I played the Minecraft demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: The freebie version that's on the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hated it!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: because I'm playing it in windowed mode and it gives me a little bit more to focus on other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turned off the motion blur, turned off the fill grain.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of that, it still made me sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hate to say it, but I do get motion sickness with Lord of the Rings because of the camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's like, you know how in WoW the camera auto-adjusts when you're running?
[SPEAKER_02]: In Lord of the Rings, you can actually turn your camera around, you can watch yourself sideways, but you're still moving forward with W. Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: if that makes sense so I'll try to hit sideways because that's the direction on my screen is trying to run and my camera is oriented the other way so it's more or less I guess a little bit of user error but I still would prefer that auto orienting and I don't know if I have a way to turn that on
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it's got this full cosmetic thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like, not necessarily like transmogging.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because honestly, I really like the transmogging system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you really have to think about what you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do like the cosmetic system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can get clothes dye and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And crafting is better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, crafting is so much easier.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I'm about even.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, WoW is still, thanks, sorry, you know, I still like WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: I signed the blood pact, I'm not quitting.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Pandaria may kind of, you know, WoW is really a lull for a lot of people now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a goat monk so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know the one thing that really, and I decided this today, the really big thing that Lord of the Rings does not have going for it, no true caster DPS class.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a hunter, that's your only real dedicated DPS class.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know me, I like the pew-pew.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have what?
[SPEAKER_02]: A mage, a druid, a shadow priest, you know, on WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play Caster Pew Pew.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, if that popped up on Lord of the Rings, I'll know that might, that might pull me over permanently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I like free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I say I like free?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like free.
[SPEAKER_12]: The MMO queen has spoken.
[SPEAKER_12]: Meanwhile, Loki, how was your gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_12]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I played mostly Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I started by building an artificial volcano.
[SPEAKER_10]: I took the largest mountain in this one area and then I built on top of it all the way up to the top of the skybox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I covered the whole thing with obsidian because I had duped a bunch of obsidian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I poured some lava over the top of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: and got too much lava.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a ton of lava on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: You put that in the wrong spot and it'll just spread like crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I finally took care of that and got it a little bit more situated to how I like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then started to hollow the whole inside off.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually it's kind of cool because the whole thing is actually the Shrine of Fire because there is fire all over the place.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's lava fountains on the inside.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: So you had the shrine to fire in your basement in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You had the shrine to fire in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_12]: What game do I make the shrine to fire in?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what I need to figure out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that just reminds me of something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can have a house in Lord of the Rings and I might build a shrine to fire there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just don't burn down your house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss MOG houses.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Rob, I miss MOG houses.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow needs houses.
[SPEAKER_12]: They do.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rather than me just pretending that my goat lives in the back room of the tavern.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let the man finish his game in a week so we can get to E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's going to get the rest of the damn show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyways, so other than, yeah, I've just been playing Minecraft for the most of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of cool, though, because unbeknownst to me, there was a dungeon in the middle of that mountain that I built the volcano on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now I have this dungeon that's going to be in the bottom of this giant fortress to fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you'll be able to fight mobs down there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'll be playing a little bit more of that this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: I do find it funny that sometimes I'll be inside the volcano thing like hollowing it out and I'll hear a cow catching fire because it was stupid and walked into the lava.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the other game I played, ironically, was an Atari 2600 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's an Atari 2600 game that's exclusive to the contest I'm playing, which is for Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if everyone heard, but Ready Player One, the wonderful book they keep talking about, they have an Easter egg hidden in the book.
[SPEAKER_10]: and they have a contest now that goes along with that easter egg you find the easter egg, takes you to a website you play this Atari 2600 game you find the easter egg in that, takes you to the next website which the game unlocks there July 1st and then you play through that game, then you get increasingly harder and the next game unlocks August 1st, kind of like the real hunt except there is a real prize the real prize is a DeLorean a DeLorean with a replica flux capacitor inside it that is being given away
[SPEAKER_12]: Which sounds all kinds of amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes me want to get into this book series.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I found the Easter egg after a little bit of a hint from online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone mentioned that you have to look for a certain... Because I was looking through the book.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't really get a chance to look at it the first day and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm like, I'm looking for a URL, but I didn't quite catch it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then they mentioned, oh, well, you have to look for this type of thing that's with the letters.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I'm like,
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay, there it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I went and played the game, beat the game after Josh went to bed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I didn't even make the top 100, though, on leaderboard.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again, it doesn't matter because each game is time unlocked.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the next game is not going to start until July 1st.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then the final game is August 1st.
[SPEAKER_10]: And really the contest is whoever has all three games completed first is the winner.
[SPEAKER_10]: So how fast you are at the first game and second game doesn't really matter as long as you get the third game after completing the first two.
[SPEAKER_10]: As long as you're first in that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Stax was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like a throwback to Pitfall.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: You're supposed to find six puzzle pieces, and then once you find the six puzzle pieces, you have to find the Easter egg in the game, which is very reminiscent to Adventure.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then once you find that, you go back to a certain room, and you find a QR code that unlocks the third place.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's eventually where the game's going to unlock next.
[SPEAKER_10]: And apparently people were aware of the website.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been talking to Tetsuya about the whole thing since he's into the whole...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, Gamma kind of tried to help him out with the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But he's like, oh, hey, I knew about that website way a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it wasn't necessarily because of the Easter egg in the book.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just it's kind of obvious what the website is.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was kind of fun to get to play an old game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's also fun to kind of participate in this real-life hunt thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, if I win a DeLorean, I don't really know what I'm going to do with it since I don't know how to drive stick.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there's all the other stuff you don't think about, like paying taxes, registration, and all that stuff, and shipping the car to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's expensive.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's a fucking DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have a fucking DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some things are worth it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Roll that window down, fucking pop in the CD because it does have a CD player that the guy put in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all Back to the Future soundtrack right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just blast that shit up the radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I won't, you know, spend too much time talking about all of that since there wasn't a whole lot of gaming involved.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I will say that mummy ride at Universal Studios is fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Xtfer and I were screaming like girls.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wish somebody got a YouTube of it because you guys would have got a kick out of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, on to games.
[SPEAKER_12]: When I got home, I did play some games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played multiplayer Mass Effect a little bit this weekend because Osfer from our chat room and Acidic Vampire from our chat room and Shane from Horde House is also in chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: We all are playing now and there's an event going on this weekend.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were having fun last night trying to survive a gold map.
[SPEAKER_12]: It didn't go very well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, we got to wave five, maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also did some multiplayer over on PlayStation 3 with another listener, Stan.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had kind of a crappy connection in Soul Calibur, so we were trying to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a dude with a lightsaber doing the Running Man.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that's Black Wolf.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got more dancing now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, two Running Men.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now it's home!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, Blender signed into the clubhouse and I guess accepted all these new people, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got VX, Jason, XV.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, back to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there was multiplayer Soul Calibur, which sadly was too laggy, but Stan makes some hilarious characters.
[SPEAKER_12]: I loved his Mr. Slave.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, people can get away with that in Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was pretty risque, we'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then played some Marvel vs. Capcom 3 Ultimate, which I, that's really Alan's game, not my game, so I was pretty much button mashing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But hey, I was having some fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks to the whole PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, Sony, for all those free freaking games this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: I realized... Are you borrowing my copy of LittleBigPlanet 2?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't have it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe I didn't loan that to you yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think you did.
[SPEAKER_12]: So... What the hell is that shirt?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like... Sorry, I'm distracted by... It's a DDR shirt.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is terrible radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: What...
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like he's not wearing pants or is that like a Minecraft bottom?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blender, what the hell are you wearing?
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like he's not wearing pants and it's like a censored butt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, PlayStation games.
[SPEAKER_12]: LittleBigPlanet 2 was one of the free games.
[SPEAKER_12]: So finally, what, about two years late, I'm finally getting into LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's great, obviously.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love the mini games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just a great platformer.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've barely scratched the surface of the game to be honest but it's everything I loved about the first one now with you know grappling hooks from the very start and more cutscene stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will say the only thing I kind of didn't like is that the story is really weird in the beginning I like the more ambiguous nature of the first game which relied a lot heavier on the narrator and so forth now in this one they're trying to like build a different story and I'm not really into it but that's my one tiny tiny little bitch about it otherwise it's a little big planet and it's great and I really don't know why it took me so long to get into part two I really don't I don't have an excuse
[SPEAKER_12]: I was too busy playing Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still haven't really gotten into Part 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I played maybe one level of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was just like, other game.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that was pretty much my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, the free LittleBigPlanet 2, Mass Effect, wow, Diablo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played a little Diablo with Shane, started a Witch Doctor, got it up to level like 6 or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Enough to beat the beta.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got up to the Skeleton King and then I was like, I gotta go eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I killed the crap out of the Skeleton King.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually was hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little.
[SPEAKER_12]: A little.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Housekeeping real quick and then we'll get into E3 news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Join us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_12]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Twitter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, again, we're not attached to a big magazine.
[SPEAKER_12]: We hope VOG Network.com will become all the rage someday and geeks everywhere will visit it and then we can say we have a big website behind us supporting us.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is one of the aliens.
[SPEAKER_12]: and Plenty more to come soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let's get into E3 news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki is going to be taking this over since I was away at Disneyland and not paying attention to my TV.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was trying to follow the news best I could, but Loki, you were on top of everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: So let's run down the various press conferences.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first people up were Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so Microsoft had their press conference, and it was kind of weird because they started off really strong because they showed Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how you start off a fucking press conference.
Boom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo 4!
[SPEAKER_10]: Here it is!
[SPEAKER_10]: Get excited!
[SPEAKER_10]: Some other cool stuff that they showed off besides Halo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, there was the unveiling of Splinter Cell Blacklist, which was an Ubisoft game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That looked pretty awesome, so they had a little clip of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, talking a little bit more about arcade games.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had the summer of arcade stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were talking about some of the games we can expect for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, some interesting things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some that we already knew about and some that were kind of on the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, they were talking Deadlight, which is going to be a new side-scroller game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked kind of like a zombie survival horror type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tony Hawk Pro Skater HD, which is supposed to be out, I think, in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dust and Elysian Tale was something that was actually supposed to be an indie game a while back but they ended up getting it published because it looks fucking amazing and
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Other things that they were talking about, of course, you know, entertainment was a big focus for Xbox since, you know, they were talking, you know, about making this like the center of entertainment for your household and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, of course, more app announcements, including, you know, partnerships with Nickelodeon, Paramount, Machima, or Machinima, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Univision, Televiso, yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell yeah, until somebody on Twitter told me they were ending Sabado Gigante this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: NHL and ESPN, of course, is getting some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other game announcements.
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo 4, Forza Horizon, Fable, Gears of War Judgment, Dance Central 3, Usher,
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, a new Nike fitness game is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Partnership with them.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, Xbox Music was another big thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were talking about the entertainment thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to have 30 million tracks with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, it's going to support some of the new features like Smart Glass, which was another big unveiling.
[SPEAKER_10]: SmartGlass is basically this technology where they can use any iOS, Android, I'm assuming Windows Phone, tablet, device, anything that you may have already.
[SPEAKER_10]: You download an app for it and it becomes a second screen just like the Wii U or the Vita and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was floored, personally, hearing that that's not exclusive to a Windows device.
[SPEAKER_12]: That they are going to open that up to iPads and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's smart.
[SPEAKER_12]: More people will adopt it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I think, finally, Microsoft had to admit, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Apple's got a big bite here.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we've seen Microsoft take little... Like, they dipped their foot in the pool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because there's a fully functional Xbox Live app for iPhone and iPad.
[SPEAKER_12]: it's a universal app that's actually quite good it's very similar to the xbox.com website you can manage your friends list from it you see your avatars like it's a full-fledged app so Microsoft doing stuff with Apple products is not unheard of but I did not think they were gonna just jump in the pool full in so this was a pleasant surprise
[SPEAKER_10]: Game of Thrones Game of Thrones Game of Thrones
[SPEAKER_10]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plus, you'll be able to control your console using this as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, long-awaited, finally announced, Internet Explorer is coming to the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we will now have an Internet browser.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will support the smart glass stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will also be Kinect-enabled, and you'll be able to use voice commands to do searches and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not a huge fan of Internet Explorer, but hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least it's an option to browse the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'll get porn on my 360, so yay for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xbox porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: What about emulators?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we know if it's going to support Flash or Java or any of that?
[SPEAKER_12]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it isn't complete until you get Super Mario Brothers running on your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they already technically have that reset glitched Xboxes and they have now the dual NAND reset glitch chips you can get where you have one mode that you can boot in that's, you know, hacked and one that's stock, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Go into some comments from our chatroom at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Osfer says, I can't wait for Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Metroid atmosphere and look to it really pulled me in, and Cortana looks better and more emotionally charged than ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've heard a lot of good things about it from people who were on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I gotta admit, I feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_12]: As much as I wasn't super-duper into the first-person Metroid gameswell, that's not true, I did love Metroid Prime 3
[SPEAKER_12]: but I mean like just seeing that gameplay footage of Halo 4 for me sorry I'm going backwards but that's fine blame the chat room um I I was really into it I mean I and I haven't really cared about Halo since Halo 3 which you know once I played Halo 3 wasn't you know it didn't throw me the same way Halo 2 did but watching the Halo 4 I was like you know maybe the change in developers wasn't necessarily a bad thing because it forces them to kind of
[SPEAKER_12]: Start over with some new ideas.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you do see some of this other influence.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's no disrespect towards Bungie.
[SPEAKER_12]: They made a great game.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm sure whatever they've got, this Destiny thing is going to kick ass too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, look, you had people making Need for Speed games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And granted, the Need for Speed games are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now you have another company, Criterion, making these Need for Speed games or making sequels to these Need for Speed games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not saying that the old ones weren't good, but now they have a fresh take on them, and so it's a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_10]: One other thing, kind of a rumor, but now those $99 contract Xboxes or whatever are coming to more retailers other than Microsoft stores because Microsoft, they kind of figured, hey, we don't have a lot of stores out there, so
[SPEAKER_10]: best buys and also select GameStop locations and from what I hear also from my boss meeting with Microsoft there's actually anybody's going to be able to do it as long as you're willing as long as you fit the criteria that they are looking for and there's like specific things that they need so
[SPEAKER_12]: By the way, this was on the OLR Twitter last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sometimes you get the secrets.
[SPEAKER_12]: Little secrets.
[SPEAKER_12]: What we can.
[SPEAKER_12]: What little secrets we get.
[SPEAKER_10]: We will let you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there is all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Overall, I think they had a decent press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I know a lot of the people that were kind of... Oh, some other announcements that they made, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: and some of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, they showed Black Ops 2, a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They announced that they're getting DLC first for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same with South Park.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Stick of Truth is getting DLC for it first.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's coming out March 5th now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to have Kinect support as well on the 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tomb Raider is getting the DLC first on Xbox and also Resident Evil 6 is getting DLC first on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to say though, South Park, The Stick of Truth, fucking amazing looking.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is just, I cannot wait for that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game looks perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really hope I'm not let down because sometimes trailers look good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks great.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, a lot of the complaints about the press conference were, hey, the whole entertainment stuff, hey, I'm here to see the games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to see all this garbage about Nickelodeon and Paramount and Xbox music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't fucking care about Xbox music, but an okay press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: So next up, how do you think overall Microsoft did?
[SPEAKER_12]: There were a lot of people online kind of razzing Microsoft, not fans of the press conference.
[SPEAKER_12]: But in a way, I was kind of like, well, what the hell did you expect this year?
[SPEAKER_12]: You knew you weren't going to be seeing the new Xbox.
[SPEAKER_12]: They said that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know people were saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, because Destiny isn't being shown anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're going to have to give us hints about the new... No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: They'll just show more Halo, which is probably what they did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they did show a Halo, and they showed some third-party stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the things I'm kind of surprised they didn't show anything for was Fable the Journey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much other than announcing that it's going to be coming out fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't really show anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was, you know, I was hardcore thinking there was going to be something with Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I guess I was wrong there.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the smart glass thing, kind of.
[SPEAKER_10]: Smart glass is going to be... I get like a half point.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think smart glass... Well, smart glass also supports... Not only does it support tablet... Because not... Let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not everybody has a tablet or a smartphone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It also does support computers, like PCs and laptops.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you have a laptop, you can also control your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although...
[SPEAKER_10]: I asked then, why the fuck do I need to view my content on the Xbox if I have my laptop in front of me?
[SPEAKER_10]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's another option.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sometimes you have that party environment.
[SPEAKER_12]: You want to show multiple people at once.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember that one New Year's Eve party where we were looking up on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had to see the dinosaur porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or what was that?
[SPEAKER_12]: The pterodactyl porno.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Wii Browser.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of those websites, yes, it was a chick and some dude in a pterodactyl suit and it was the most hilarious thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, from Microsoft to pterodactyl porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to the chatters.
[SPEAKER_12]: Live.VogNetwork.com A lot of props for South Park.
[SPEAKER_12]: Acidic Vampire says, South Park looks great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stan says, I think it will be good.
[SPEAKER_12]: The South Park creators are really involved in this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tiger Claw says, I liked how Trey Parker and Matt Stone trolled the Microsoft press conference when they showed up for their game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Degenerate Johnny says, I'm calling it.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of the South Park's DLC will be Cartman's Ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Could be Ass of Fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they have, you know, it's very cool the way they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Lemmy Winks or whatever that was.
[SPEAKER_10]: They do have a Lemmy Winks tie and one of the summons you get is Mr. Slave and Mr. Slave sucks the enemy into his ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Literally.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that was that whole Paris Hilton episode or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it's basically that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing is off limits or sacred.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's kind of cool, though, because you get to play as your own character in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you design your own character.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't like Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's a reboot, you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't like Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm still looking forward to that, although the delay, you know, having to see it two years in a row is a little bit like... But I suppose it's not the first game, it won't be the last, that gets shown across multiple years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless I can lock the butler in the fridge and break her neck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not interested.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's technically a prequel, so I don't think there's a butler.
[SPEAKER_10]: You crash on an island.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Uncharted, Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it looks good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad they showed it again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you kind of forget about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so next was Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't understand how they're able to pull something like this off.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had three press conferences because one was not enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had a conference that was a pre-E3 conference that talked a little bit about the Wii U. Then they had the regular conference which talked mostly about the Wii U. Then they had a 3DS conference the following day.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Interface, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be the Miiverse.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what Miiverse is, it's kind of an upgrade of the Mi Plaza.
[SPEAKER_10]: You basically see all your Mi's congregating Mi's from friends, Mi's of people playing different games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you see them playing the different games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And plus, you can talk to each other, not only in text chat, but you can picto chat with them as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's Facebook for me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You basically can interact with people in a really elaborate way.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got, you know,
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess spoiler stuff that you can do in there where you can make it so that people don't see your post.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to get spoiled on the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they have this whole like kind of like you can post in different spots in games and stuff like for example oh I'm having trouble in this area in the game can anybody help me and then like you know hey I got through this part of the game like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's great and all but
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's kind of like what GameFAQs is for or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it's neat that they have this feature and that they showed all this stuff, but I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the other things they are showing off also is a brand new controller for the Wii U, the Wii U Pro Controller, which looks like an Xbox 360 controller with the analog stick and the face buttons flip-flopped.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that'll be used also in conjunction with the Wii Pad and stuff if you want to play regular games instead of using the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although it will support a Wii Remote and all the Wii accessories as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, they have a TV button on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the TV button is for is for actually using the tablet as a remote for your TV, like a universal remote.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually launch the system and everything from the pad before you even turn the system on, or you can just switch the channel on your TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could do that with my Xbox controller.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good question from SheHulk in our chat room, and I didn't catch this either.
[SPEAKER_12]: No Blu-ray or DVD for the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't say what they're using.
[SPEAKER_12]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't say what kind of discs they're using.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe they feel it's not needed because I noticed Reggie did emphasize, and the way he said it too was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: He said, you know, Netflix, Amazon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hulu it's there you know he's like it's all there yes of course it's there but we want you to experience me you know it's kind of interesting yeah so let's talk about stuff that people aren't gonna care about and let's talk more in great detail about something else but to his credit what else are you gonna say about Netflix and Amazon and Hulu everybody knows that stuff already you know they're there yay that's that's really all there is to say
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You rhymed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ranma in our chatroom says Wii U will support Blu-ray storage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I haven't seen anything yet, but I would assume it's Blu-ray, unless they're going to come out with their own proprietary format, which, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: One, of course, the big game, the first game that they unveiled was Pikmin 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, something that has been rumored to be coming to the Wii or the Wii U at some point, and it is a launch title.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they showed off Pikmin 3, and it looks pretty...
[SPEAKER_10]: Scribblenauts Unlimited was another game that they showed off that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does use the tablet and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting a Wii U.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did not hear these rumors.
[SPEAKER_10]: We would have never heard them on our show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We would never have known about that a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then of course, surprise, they're trying to director's cut coming to the Wii U, which is neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I might have missed this because I was playing in a home over there for a second, checking out the awesome backyard that Blender built for the clubhouse, but Mass Effect 3, Wii U, which has a lot of us kind of wondering, how is that going to work?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, I mean, you can't...
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you target on your little monitor.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: That part, I figure maybe the biotics and the gun stuff is on the monitor or whatever, but I'm kind of like, how can you just skip Mass Effect 2?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, Mass Effect 1, I can see people skipping, although I don't recommend it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I could see you skipping that, but you can't skip Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: So Mass Effect 3 is going to have to really have something special to separate it from the other versions to get me to want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although Mass Effect 3 does have a pretty awesome multiplayer, so it'll be interesting to see if that's pulled off as well on the Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_12]: Plus, microtransaction hell.
[SPEAKER_12]: Again, I wonder if that's going to be pulled off as seamlessly on the Wii U. They must think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I think that tells us a lot right there about Nintendo's online structure if EA is willing to put Mass Effect 3 on.
[SPEAKER_10]: another title that they announced was Sing which is being developed by the DJ Hero developers and Sing is your generic karaoke game with the words on the Wii pad whoopty shit that's what I have to say about that and admit it Call Me Maybe was stuck in your head all week long after that and it's the number one song on iTunes it was not I've never heard of that before
[SPEAKER_10]: I would play it for you, but you'd slap me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it that bad?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: 3DS stuff, they talked a little bit about Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's supposed to be coming out this season.
[SPEAKER_10]: Holiday season.
[SPEAKER_10]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2, which is headed to 3DS August 19th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, Luigi's Mansion, Dark Moon for the 3DS this holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: They, of course, announced... I thought it was going to be New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, but they had to trump me, and it's now called New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: You, which is announced, and it will have multiplayer... Gotcha!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo!
[SPEAKER_10]: And so they have that coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Batman Arkham City Armored Edition is headed to the Wii U, and basically the Game of the Year edition with some extra bells and whistles in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just want to say real quick, because some of the folks in the chat room are commenting, you know, we're about a minute lagged from when we say things to when they get encoded and people hear them.
[SPEAKER_12]: So people in chat right now are talking about Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Acidic Vampire says no Mass Effect 1 and 2 on the Wii U equals fail.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Actdeft reminds us PlayStation 3 skipped Mass Effect 1.
[SPEAKER_12]: But again, I'm saying Mass Effect 1 is okay to skip.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't recommend it, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had, though, to be fair, they had a motion comic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, and WhatUpG reminds us that they did have that bridge.
[SPEAKER_12]: So Technus says BioWare will just do another interactive graphic comic, and that's certainly kind of the likely thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, DarkTetsuya linked us in chat to the story on MyNintendoNews that mentions that Mass Effect 3 Take Earth Back, which I guess is what they're calling the Wii U version, will include an enhanced storyline from the original game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh no, this says PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think he got the stuff mixed up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I was going to say, Take Earth Back, I heard, was a DLC expansion that's possibly coming in the future.
[SPEAKER_12]: So never mind, I guess that's not about the Wii U. That's what I get for trying to do stories live.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, and I'm surprised that they did this because I didn't think it's that popular anymore, but I guess it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it said the original game.
[SPEAKER_12]: So this is about the Wii U version.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the original game on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I'm seeing this for the first time, so I'm trying to process this myself here.
[SPEAKER_12]: EA hasn't spoken about the enhanced content, and they're saying hopefully it's not just going to be the reworked ending.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: That is a lot of their launch lineup.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you'll be able to interact with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then also, some of these Wii U games, they showed that you can play them without actually having the system on the TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can exercise and stuff like that without looking at the TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it just looks stupid if you're working with the Wii Fit balance board and Wii tablet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, just come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then finally also the Wii U will support two different Wii gamepads however there will be a hit in frames per second they'll actually be halved so the upper limit will be 30 frames per second on both Wii U tablets which whatever honestly
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a different developer now because before it looked like Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_10]: It still has that kind of sandbox thing to it, but it definitely doesn't look like Grand Theft Auto anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it looks pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely one of the launch games to have on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, it doesn't sell me a system.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I still am worried that they didn't talk enough about what their online plan is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we know about Miiverse and I can talk with people, leave them little notes about shit in-game, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: which are going to have already been out for a few months by the time the system launches.
[SPEAKER_10]: Assassin's Creed 3 looks pretty cool, but why should I buy another system to play a game that I can already play on my system right now and look pretty much the same, but it's going to have a few extra gimmicks with it with this new controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the problem that doesn't sell me on this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the Wii...
[SPEAKER_10]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: U
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, how am I forgetting about Nintendo Land?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to say, I haven't heard of Nintendo Land yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo Land, basically the Wii Sports, Wii Play, whatever, Tech Demo Land.
[SPEAKER_12]: The giant cocktease land, because there's my F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is basically Tech Demo Land.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: which is great maybe they'll have two they might have two SKUs where one is the kind of like remember the old old school NES how they actually had three versions of that when that first came out there was the robot pack that came with Rob the Robot and like Gyromite and then there was the action pack that came with the Zapper and Super Mario Brothers Duck Hunt and then there was the vanilla ass pack I don't remember what it was called the core the core did they call things core back then I think it was called the core system well whatever it was just the NES and Super Mario Brothers basically
[SPEAKER_12]: so I wonder if the Wii U won't launch with a similar type of thing where you could have just the plain Jane system or you get the extra maybe the extra Wii U controller since we hear that they will support two players yeah here's the thing though they're going to support two players but not any of the launch titles are going to support two players on those pads don't so it's something that's coming way down the line um
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you've got New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: for the 3DS, New Super Mario Bros.
2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now you have New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: U. The problem is, that game looks last gen.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game looks like a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, I know it's a great game and you're launching it on the system, but I think you need...
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to show off this game system, you need to come out with something big, like a Super Mario Galaxy type of game, or a Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something like, holy shit, I did not expect to see Mario like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead of, hey look, it's slightly prettier New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just doesn't look...
[SPEAKER_12]: Good.
[SPEAKER_12]: As much as I do want that Mario Brothers Wii U game, but I'm not sure I'm totally sold on this system yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: But just to be devil's advocate for a minute, doesn't Pikmin 3 kind of show off some of those capabilities a little better?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but Pikmin 3 is not a game I think that's going to appeal to everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it... Pikmin doesn't have... It has a following, but it doesn't have a huge following.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a niche game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't sell that great.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ranma's reminding me of a couple other Nintendo packs that I forgot earlier.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was the Power Pack when the Power Pad came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was later.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, the Mario Brothers Duck Hunt World Class Track Meet.
[SPEAKER_12]: And he says that there was one that was Hogan's Alley in Duck Hunt.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember Hogan's Alley ever being a pack-in game, but maybe it was like... Maybe it wasn't very well distributed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hogan's Alley
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lawn Trader reporting the news from 25 years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, that's just my problem, though, is they don't have... There's still a lot of information that we need from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: A price and a date, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, but they did that with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: They came out later around Tokyo Game Show time, because they don't do Tokyo Game Show, but they'll do their own little thing, and that's when they'll announce it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, cool, but I need to know more about the system, and right now, as it stands, I'm not buying one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not even buying one near launch.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just... I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't... I'm kind of with you, but the price will... I mean, A, the price, and B, my disposable income, which I may or may not have at that end of the year, will really factor into my decision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and here's the other thing, too, is just...
[SPEAKER_10]: I learned my lesson with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Wii was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: But see, the Wii, compared to what was already currently available, was very, very different.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is just, hey, look, I have a traditional controller with a goddamn screen on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's my problem with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know all these cool things that you're talking about with that controller?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: You've had two screens for fucking years now with the DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how many really, truly unique games have you seen come out of it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably a handful.
[SPEAKER_10]: You probably can count them on one hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: of games that are really using both screens just in an amazing way.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't think we're going to get a lot of these really big games because you've had time to do something unique with this and you're just not going to use these two screens.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be a gimmick.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will say this, though, to Nintendo's credit, is that even though the Wii U lineup left me feeling, and I think a lot of us feeling a little, eh, especially when they ended with Nintendo Land, I think that was a big, eh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, that was just kind of, that's it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zelda or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: But the 3DS lineup looked great.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gotta say, that new, you know, the Golden Coins Mario game looked great.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Castlevania game especially looked great.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I feel like the 3DS, I kind of wish they'd show, I mean, I realize they did that whole second press conference where they showed more, but I was kind of hoping for a little more at the big show because there's a lot of good stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you know something that was missing?
[SPEAKER_10]: The redesign of the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that too, but Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_10]: No Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was missing, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Delayed Delayed Delayed Delayed Delayed
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a very... I gotta say, I mean, you're gonna have a hard time selling somebody on... Let's just, you know, an average parent or whatever, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can buy the system now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, who knows what the Wii's gonna be, you know, dropping down to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, let's say it goes down to, you know, 99 bucks or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, man, $99 Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: and you know you've got the Wii system right now and I can buy new Super Mario Brothers and it's pretty awesome I mean the people aren't gonna know oh hey oh that's the Wii U version you know and honestly the Wii U stuff aside from oh cool I you know I can play on my Wii pad or whatever when um you know someone's on the TV or
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck, that's not how you're supposed to be selling your system.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not supposed to be selling your system, hey, when someone wants to watch TV, you can play your game system on this pad.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you're supposed to say, hey, when someone's playing something on the TV, you bop out your fucking 3DS and you play New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2 on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how you fucking solve that situation.
[SPEAKER_10]: You sell them on the portable system and the regular system.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't say, hey, you don't fucking need the portable system because, hey, you got the stupid tablet now.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're at an hour 18, so before we move on to this, let me read some comments from chat on this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Clover Nikon in our chatroom says, at vognetwork.com, live chat, says, I would like a new platformer of Black Tiger for the Wii U and that would help convince me to buy one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have the Playstation 2 compilation pack with Black Tiger and Dungeon Buster chimes in saying I'd snatch one up day one if it had something like that everybody's got their dream game you know I've been sitting here saying F-Zero F-Zero F-Zero god damn it F-Zero you know everybody's got their game that they want to have let's see Acidic Vampire says screw a 3DS Castlevania give me a next gen Castlevania a la Symphony of the Night amen to that Shadow Next Gen who is at the show chimes in most of the Wii U titles shown at E3 are launch titles so
[SPEAKER_10]: Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
[SPEAKER_10]: True and not true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Launch window titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not launch day titles.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're launch window, and that's... And although what he's saying is mostly true, Nintendo doesn't... I mean, Nintendo certainly doesn't project, let's say, quite as badly as Sony, last Guardian, or Microsoft, Halo 4 last year and Tomb Raider,
[SPEAKER_12]: do, but Nintendo did troll us what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't project?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not as bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not saying, but I am saying, Nintendo did do that whole Smash Brothers thing last year, and we know that that's a good three years away, but they didn't show anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they said, we're announcing it, it'll come out eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, Rob, Bagenator's calling on you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: F-Zero is overrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get out!
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone smack him with a fish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is he in the home?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is he in the home?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I'm going to go bop him in the head in Sony Home right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm on the hunt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where's Ragenator?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to go smack him.
[SPEAKER_12]: Meanwhile, speaking of Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk a little bit about Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony had some pretty interesting things.
[SPEAKER_10]: They came out talking about their Sony mascot Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony All-Stars Battle Royale game.
[SPEAKER_10]: did announce two new characters for it and kind of confirming that there are going to be some third-party characters in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: They announced Big Daddy's going to be one of the playable characters and also Nathan Drake, which is kind of a duh.
[SPEAKER_10]: But those are going to be available as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure they've got a lot more to unveil there.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did talk a little bit about...
[SPEAKER_10]: Some interesting ideas, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of them was this, I don't even know why, a wonder book.
[SPEAKER_10]: J.K.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rowling's Book of Spells
[SPEAKER_10]: and you know they're kind of sending it on oh hey she she wrote it and it's all this all new stuff and hey check it out it's pretty sweet it was pretty fucking boring it was probably the worst thing that they had of their whole here's the thing though now keep in mind we weren't watching the press conference we were only reading the tweets because we were in line for Indiana Jones or something at the time and
[SPEAKER_12]: so while you guys were kind of like seeing that and I guess bored with the presentation those of us were kind of reading about it and we actually sat there going that is a brilliant move by Sony because the part there that you glossed over that I think is crucial they have fucking JK Rowling in their back pocket now don't underestimate the power of that woman
[SPEAKER_12]: Pottermore ain't that great either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pottermore's actually pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I suck at mixing spells.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a lot of people going crazy over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pottermore is also very age-broad.
[SPEAKER_12]: True.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just think...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think there's a lot more to this, especially with the whole, you know, Sony does have a family friendly thing that they need to try to get a little bit of that Nintendo audience.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think the Wonder Book is a way to kind of push that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't underestimate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand where you're coming from there, but it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: you're asking someone to purchase if they don't own a Playstation 3 you're asking them to purchase a Playstation 3 a Playstation Move set up and then this Wonder Book on top of it like a $400 investment for a fucking lame ass looking game I keep saying Wonder Book and I think of Superbook right?
[SPEAKER_12]: I might...
[SPEAKER_12]: buy that one instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it could be worse, I guess, but to buy that for that specific thing, it looks terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you think about it, Rob, they also have Harry Potter for Kinect, so if you want to go that bullshit route of, well, they have J.K.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rowling's in this book of things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I could read a fucking book and pretend to do magic or I could become fucking Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think becoming Harry Potter wins.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fine, you made your point.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm in fucking Hogwarts.
[SPEAKER_10]: My creepy face is on that stupid avatar.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you made your point.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and, of course, you know, full free games if you're a subscriber of PlayStation Plus and they're going to be adding more as time goes on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, PlayStation 1 Classics are coming back to the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: No duh there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of, you know, been leaked out already.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're going to slowly roll those out starting with, I think, Final Fantasy VII and maybe Tomb Raider, some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, some Vita titles...
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a whole lot of first-party Vita titles that are going to be coming out for the... I was also shocked at the lack of Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was basically... I mean, all the stuff that was coming out this fall is pretty much stuff we already knew about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, LittleBigPlanet carding and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_12]: To be fair, some of that may show up at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_12]: After all, Sony is a Japanese company.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of that may be in their back pocket for Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least I hope to hell that's what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, also there's the PlayStation All-Stars Battle Royale, which is going to be on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Another pretty cool thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got to say this.
[SPEAKER_12]: ShadowNextGen in our chatroom says, where is the Vita price drop?
[SPEAKER_12]: That was made up by the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think people assumed just because the 3DS had a price drop, the Vita was going to get one too.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's too soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're not going to announce a price drop yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think the tech in the Vita, it would be a bigger loss to Sony to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not going to announce a price drop three months after it's come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be like, oh yeah, we failed.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not going to announce, hey, we're going to drop the price in October.
[SPEAKER_12]: That being said, however, now that they've kind of ignored it at this show, now they might have painted themselves in a corner to have to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tokyo Game Show is going to be critical to the future of the Vita believe it they did talk about you know some games that are kind of big does Call of Duty Black Ops Declassified not necessarily going to be the same Black Ops 2 games so it's a little disappointing to me but we'll see what it is and then Assassin's Creed 3 Liberation which is going to be its own kind of unique game with its own character which is kind of cool that launches October 30th as well
[SPEAKER_10]: and then of course the big big reveal that they had was the brand new Quadric Dream game which is Beyond Two Souls and just such an amazing looking game basically kind of taking everything that you liked from Heavy Rain and just amping it up just the motion capture in it now is just ridiculous how well that looks um
[SPEAKER_10]: and big name stars behind it as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely got to check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have now... God, who's the fucking actress?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ellen Page.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ellen Page, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ellen Page is now doing the mocap and... Kitty Pryde.
[SPEAKER_10]: That too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kitty Pryde.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw the screens from it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't like the quick time event stuff, then maybe not for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you probably didn't like Heavy Rain either.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need to go watch that trailer.
[SPEAKER_12]: I heard a lot of excitement about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Granted, I kind of missed the boat on Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely watch the demo footage.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have 20 minutes for the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to check it out for sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: So overall, Sony's conference?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: How'd you feel?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and one more thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: A little Big Planet 2 is getting some DLC that's going to turn the Vita into a controller for the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of cross-play stuff there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think...
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, out of the three, I think they have the strongest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they showed off this really amazing game, a new property for them, a new IP.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, they were showing off some of the stuff that they had.
[SPEAKER_10]: Third Party was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't seem like there was a lot that bored me too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wonder Book was pretty eh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, but it wasn't like, it wasn't like Nintendo's press conference was just like, okay, when we get into the good stuff, when we get into the good stuff, it's over?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's over?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's like, when are we getting to these like, holy crap, holy crap, I need to buy the system for this game, but, I don't know, it's pretty cool, and I mean...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think next year's Nintendo's press conference it better be anyway it's gonna be a lot like that one a couple years ago remember that year I think this was two years ago where Reggie came out on stage and was basically like you want games fine here's some games bam bam bam bam he showed like eight of them off in a row and he's like there's all your fucking games good night
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Zappy in our chatroom says Nintendo needs to learn the magic of one more thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Harness the Steve Jobs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did that with fucking Metroid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_12]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fucking Metroid game!
[SPEAKER_12]: Metroid game by Team Ninja that sounds awesome and will be okay when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was that, I think that might have been the same year.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that was the year before, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was the year that that Metroid game was actually coming out that I think was the year where Reggie was like, we got this, and we got this, and we got this.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if any of you fuckers write that no games are coming out for the Wii, I will personally come to your house and beat your ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least that's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: My body is ready to kick some ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, quickly the third-party crest conferences because we're already an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't have them any this year, but Ubisoft did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry off of them, of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Konami had the online one that showed lots and lots of Metal Gear Rising, which, granted, if you like violence, looks great.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't watch that one, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ubisoft, they had Just Dance 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is going to have some Wii U specific features including a puppet master mode where you can change up the dance moves on the fly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's kind of fun if you're in a party environment, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Marvel Avengers Battle for Earth, which is coming to the Wii U and Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: and it also supposed to be like kind of they said drawing from the secret invasion universe that has like scrolls posing as superheroes and stuff but it looks terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: The secret invasion thing was crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was even worse than Civil War.
[SPEAKER_10]: The gameplay looks bad, just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have like the X-Men in there, so I don't understand how that's Avengers, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were involved in Wolverines and every team in the Marvel Universe ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, he's got to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: He even hung out with Power Pack.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, time for a total tangent where I derail the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I finally saw the Avengers this weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it good?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you save for the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we thought once we saw the dude, we thought it was over.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we realized in the car on the way home, wasn't Jamie talking about a scene with blah, blah, blah?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_12]: There must have been more after the...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why you always, always, always, always, always stay through the entire credits of a Marvel movie because they will fuck with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: One does not simply leave a movie before the end of the credits.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: That means we're going to go back and see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rayman Legends was another game that they showed off and that was a sequel to Rayman Origins.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to have 5 player co-op with the Wii U and also the Pro Controller and Wiimote are supported and the gameplay looks just
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just really, really cool stuff that they've got going there with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the games that I thought was a joke when they were showing it originally on the Wii U pre-E3 conference, which was a zombie game that this really dorky guy was just kind of being all cliche about and like,
[SPEAKER_09]: I need help!
[SPEAKER_09]: Help me, internet!
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to know how to beat this boss!
[SPEAKER_02]: That commercial is the dumbest thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's a real game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zombie U is the name of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a fucking stupid name.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was originally Killer Freaks from Outer Space, which was going to be a neat looking game that had almost like evil rabbits looking characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now it's a generic zombie shooter game.
[SPEAKER_10]: but they're going to have some interesting uses of the Wii controller and honestly to me this game looks like it's going to be another Red Steel which some people may like Red Steel but Red Steel ended up being one of those games hey it looked pretty cool at E3 and then when it came out it was not very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just kind of ehhh.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, um, zombie game, neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, um, of course, they talked a little bit about, um, Far Cry 3, which...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that trailer they showed was a bit graphic.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just, boobies!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, boobies!
[SPEAKER_10]: And apparently, you know, I know Bobby was talking a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I even asked him, like, hey, were you watching this online or were you watching this on, like, Spike or G4 or something like that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did they censor those fucking tits on TV?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope, they did not.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's a little... Boobie soft.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a little problem, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And boobie soft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sad I missed it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boobysoft hashtag was launched from there.
[SPEAKER_12]: By the way, I love Aisha Tyler.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think it's great that she got to emcee.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's funny because what do her and Joel McHale have in common?
[SPEAKER_12]: They've both hosted The Soup on E!
[SPEAKER_12]: Aisha Tyler was the host before.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think she's great.
[SPEAKER_12]: She's got a podcast too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Girl...
[SPEAKER_12]: I almost said Girls Gone Wow, but that's not her show.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not her show.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Girl on Guy, I think is the name of the show, and it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan's a really big fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But she's actually a gamer, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: She is, and she has a big lady boner for Halo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like her a lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: She's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've met her.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would love to have her on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that will never happen because she does the talk on CBS.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I would just love to chat with Aisha Tyler.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I met her in person once.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's...
[SPEAKER_10]: She was not that annoying, but the other guy, oh my fucking god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why was he there?
[SPEAKER_10]: He was so fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the banter was just annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then finally, they were talking a little bit about their service that they've got.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have some free games that you can play, including they've added Trials Evolution and Beyond Good and Evil HD, I Am Alive, and some more stuff to their free play service.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty awesome that they've got that as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Watch Dogs Watch Dogs
[SPEAKER_10]: That game looked rad.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it looks fantastic.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did watch that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That looked rad.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Most people were going around saying Ubisoft won E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, whatever the hell that means.
[SPEAKER_12]: Congratulations, you win an E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they did pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Based on that, almost single-handedly, that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That had more people talking than anything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically this kind of futuristic game where you play this guy who has hijacked control of, it's in the future, Chicago, and basically this computer runs the whole city.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every telephone network, street lights, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: He has this almost like a magic phone that he can dial in and hack anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: You find out information about people and it's just this whole espionage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stealth kind of action game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's a shooter element in there as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: And just the integration with your phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to kind of use the smart glass stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really cool looking thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I don't mean to sound anti-Nintendo, but A, was that game announced for Wii U?
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I don't think it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: And B, I think that's a real problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a real problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: When more people are talking about somebody else's game that's not coming to your system more so than your brand new system.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is very...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki,
[SPEAKER_12]: However, to be fair, yet, we never know what might ultimately pan out before the launch.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may not be a launch window.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember, Reggie was focusing on launch window games.
[SPEAKER_12]: This may not be until 2013.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, this definitely isn't a launch window.
[SPEAKER_12]: That could be the problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shadow Next Gen says it wasn't announced for any system.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't announced for 360 or PS3 either.
[SPEAKER_10]: The press site they have listed for PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone thinks it's for Next Gen, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I...
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks very next-gen, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another game that was not at Ubisoft at all, which is kind of surprising, was Rainbow Six Patriots.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was just missing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So who knows where that's been, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty exciting lineup.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's quickly do EA.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're running long for Part A, but we knew we would.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's E3 week.
[SPEAKER_10]: EA, real quick, they had lots of sports games to show off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, brand new Madden now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a brand new engine that's going to be running.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new Infinity Engine has really awesome physics and stuff, so that looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: They talked a little bit about some new games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dead Space 3, which is kind of a duh that's coming out in February.
[SPEAKER_10]: Need for Speed Most Wanted being rebooted by Criterion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looks like Burnout with cops.
[SPEAKER_10]: Burnout Paradise with cops, great.
[SPEAKER_10]: SimCity that's going to be now online online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only, which is kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_12]: That decision is going to tank that franchise.
[SPEAKER_12]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because what they're saying, and Bobby went into this a little bit on his show tonight, and I totally am agreeing with his sentiment, is that it's getting away from that whole sandbox thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember how you could unleash Godzilla and a nuclear strike and all that on your city?
[SPEAKER_12]: And then, okay, just go back and load your save file.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: When it's online only, there's no save files now.
[SPEAKER_12]: People like doing that in The Sims.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why would you do that to your franchise?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that is a really bad decision.
[SPEAKER_12]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_12]: It worked for Diablo.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not going to work for UEA.
[SPEAKER_12]: Diablo being online only, not that everybody's okay with that anyway, but so many people were already playing that game online that it wasn't a deal-breaker.
[SPEAKER_02]: But SimCity, you don't play that online, ever And it's sad too because that's a game that I would like to play offline And it looks like an amazing game, it's just Unless you do have a local file Because for some online franchises they do pull your data off a local file So that could work But, not likely
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that they're going to because Diablo 3, if you think about it, could have done that as well but they didn't go that route.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they just shot the franchise in the foot with that decision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can always change it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think they're going to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the whole thing is they're trying to combat piracy and they think that online only is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Once again, you're hurting the legitimate users of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Medal of Honor Warfighter looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very realistic-looking game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crysis 3 is just kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't understand why I need to use a bow and arrow in this game, but neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's a beautiful-looking game, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: SimCity Social for Facebook they announced, which...
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Battlefield 3, of course, the Battlefield 3 Premium service, they announced that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's out on PS3 first, and then PC and Xbox, kind of opposite of Call of Duty Elite.
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Wars Old Republic is sort of going free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going free-to-play up to level 15, and they're going to also be adding new content as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also Madden NFL kind of jumping on the social bandwagon that they have with FIFA.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they actually have some interesting stuff now.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new game has like a fake Twitter feed that's on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It comments on your performance and stuff like you're having real fans comment on your game, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got that going.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plus a lot of other presentation perks that they added with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: and last but not least the big one EA has secured the UFC franchise so that's going to be coming to EA now and they bought it from THQ for an unsaid amount of money and basically the reasoning behind that was UFC 3 which was the last UFC game to come out from THQ didn't make their money so they have to cut it and that's what they did they cut the franchise and sold it to EA
[SPEAKER_10]: Although I'm worried now that if it's going to be like EA Sports MMA, which is kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a lot of news from E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I think we kind of covered it all there and gave our feedback as well as you guys there in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we do have some more to talk about.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're not done with the show yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to get into some of the little stuff in the next half.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's kind of sad that we didn't see was No Dead Rising 3 announcement.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: That didn't end up happening.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it's one of those things, you know, like I've been hearing from a lot of different developers and publishers.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not ready to show.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not ready to show it yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or they're not ready to talk about that yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which is the whole excuse behind Last Guardian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Last Guardian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Capcom had a few things that they were showing off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, Street Fighter...
[SPEAKER_10]: you know I don't really well Street Fighter X Tekken for the Vita and then they also had Lost Planet 3 which was a big thing Devil May Cry they're kind of focusing on those franchises if you think about it those are coming out quarter one so this might be a fourth quarter game might be something for next E3 or maybe something that they announced at Tokyo Game Show who knows so it may just not be ready yet hmm interesting
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, we're running a bit long, but we do have a few more segments we want to get in here before we get to Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some people prefer it long.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and what is coming out a little sooner than any of the games we just talked about.
[SPEAKER_10]: This week, we don't have a whole ton, but we've got Lollipop Chainsaw on PS3 and 360, and that's sometimes all you need.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dirt Showdown is supposed to be coming out this week, although I'm not sure if it's actually going to be coming out on Tuesday because they're having production problems, but sometime hopefully this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's on PS3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then not a whole lot else.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're a fan of the Nickelodeon series iCarly, there's a Groovy Foodie game coming out on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: on the Vita, getting a couple games, Metal Gear Solid HD Collection, and Gravity Rush.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gravity Rush looks pretty awesome, so hopefully that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, I believe that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Persona 4 The Golden comes out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a whole little accessory set as well that you can get for the Vita.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's also a Super Monkey Ball game called Tokumori Asobita comes out this week as well on the PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a feeling more people will be crazy about the Persona 4.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know there's a lot of fans of that here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_12]: Going to the PlayStation 3, Lollipop Chainsaw in Japan as well, and also a game called Lord of Sorcery, as well as some new joystick adapters coming from Hori.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that Lord of Sorcery from Sony?
[SPEAKER_12]: I believe that is just Sorcery here.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is from Sony.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's a Move integrated game.
[SPEAKER_12]: FIFA 12 gets a price reduction as well on the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quickly taking a look at the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: Akai Katana Shin gets a price reduction this Friday as well as Shatos gets a price reduction as well and Lollipop Chainsaw on the 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's Japan.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have a few things in the UK and I would tell everybody if my thing would pull up.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have coming up on the 13th, Doctor Who, The Eternity Clock and Gravity Rush.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on the 15th, we have Combat Wings, The Great Battles of World War II, Heroes of Ruin, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Future Soldier and Lollipop Chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_12]: and that would do it for the UK alright well let's go way back back past E3 and past what's coming out this week and go way back in time to when things were a little bit simpler
[SPEAKER_12]: Back when you had to read about E3 and Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, maybe not that long ago, but still pretty far back.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week, where DarkSakura's gonna go into the gaming vault and pull out an old-ass video game.
[SPEAKER_12]: She thinks, hey, while you guys are waiting for all this stuff to come out, respect a classic.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one literally from the vault, which is how I decided.
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked a box of PS games, and this was the second one on them.
[SPEAKER_12]: and what is this week's classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Policenauts Policenauts is one of the cinematic adventure games that was done by Hideo Kojima it has yeah it was a Konami game the old Konami logo
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, I miss that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was initially released for the PC-9821 in 1994, and then they remade versions for the 3DO, PlayStation, and the Sega Saturn in 96.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has never officially been released outside of Japan, although they were going to localize it on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on August 24th, in honor of the 46th birthday of Hideo Kojima,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very interesting game because it really refers back to different references like to Lethal Weapon and Urashima Taro, which is an old Japanese tale.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is about a detective who travels to a space colony to investigate his ex-wife's murder and her new husband's disappearance.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it is first person point and click interface and you play as the protagonist Jonathan Ingram who is a police not basically former police officer trained to be a police officer in space.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the console you use the mouse but on the Saturn version you can use the light gun for shooting parts of the game so it's actually a little bit more rich in terms of play.
[SPEAKER_02]: but on the other consoles it's basically point and click first person shooter type stuff and you know with random saves and everything and it actually has an easter egg that if you've got a save file of Tokimeki Memorial it refers back to it so pretty funny
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course that came up in Metal Gear Solid where it read your save files on your PlayStation card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you are a careful man who saves often.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, again, like I said, Jonathan Ingram is a police knot who is assigned to Beyond Coast, which is the first functional space colony in 2013.
[SPEAKER_02]: So next year, we're apparently colonizing space.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he goes to see what happened to Lorraine, who was his ex-wife, and her husband's vanished, so he has to find out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he works with his buddy from the LAPD, Ed Brown, who is helping him with the investigation.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so it really is just that point-and-click now for different versions that came out I did mention it originally was on the NEC PC 9821 and it was one CD-ROM that had an installation floppy disk and the cutscenes were rendered were rendered in hand-drawn pixel art instead of full-motion video
[SPEAKER_02]: It also is considered to be some of the best pixel art in the history of video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it came out on the 3DO on September 29th, 1995.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was two CD-ROMs and had animated cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was CG animation.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the graphics were completely redrawn for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS version came out in January 1996 on two discs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the version I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I have the Best Hits version of that, just to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it came out on the Sega Saturn on September 13th, 1996.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it used, like I said, the light gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other versions that have been out is that there was the Policenauts Pilot Disc for 3DO that had a playable demo of the backstory of the game, featurettes, and information on the voice actors and developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then there was the Policenauts Private Collection that came out on the PlayStation February 9th, 1996.
[SPEAKER_02]: that a lot of the same content and an earlier version of the game script the PlayStation 1 has been reissued twice there is the Konami the best version which is the one that I have and then it came out for the PlayStation store making it downloadable for PlayStation Portable and for PS3
[SPEAKER_02]: there was a plan to localize it on the Saturn there actually is cover art that exists for this and there's a fan translation that was done for the PlayStation which you can actually use through what's the word I'm thinking of?
[SPEAKER_02]: Emulator and I've seen a bunch of it through that I've played through half of it in Japanese with a copy of that script so
[SPEAKER_02]: There was also a soundtrack that was released, and then Policenauts FN, which is arranged versions of the music from the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was the MIDI Power Pro 3, so there was a MIDI arrangement of Policenauts music, and the Snatcher Policenauts music disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called Music Collection of Hideo Kojima Black Disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there you go, Policenauts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, if I may say so.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also references to Policenauts and Snatcher in the Metal Gear games.
[SPEAKER_11]: When it detects your save files and all that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, here's an obvious one.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a scene where Otacon is flashbacked to being a big nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's scenes from Policenauts and Snatcher in his flashbacks.
[SPEAKER_12]: BaconBits in our chatroom asks, is there an official release on the US PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: But maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bug them enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you can find Policenauts, I think, relatively inexpensive if you're getting the re-release.
[SPEAKER_02]: And again, you can play it on an emulator with an English patch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to go to the trouble.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or if you happen to be able to read and understand Japanese, you can play it on a PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's the way I played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sat down with a freaking script that gave me my options.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We beat the freaking Rurouni Kenshin game, the RPG, with a copy of the script.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we beat Grandia.
[SPEAKER_02]: We played through half of Grandia with my friend Krista there because she could read everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will tell you this right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Japanese reading is like a literate five-year-old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, I know maybe 30 kanji.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Keep trying.
[SPEAKER_12]: You might get up to a six-year-old soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe when I move.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're almost two hours with no break here.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I need to go check into the show tonight at vognetwork.com and get my VOG points so I can get more loot.
[SPEAKER_12]: And hopefully you guys will do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or you might join us in the VOG Network Clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_12]: Again, just search for VOG in the PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_12]: And there's VOG Network all in caps.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think we're going to fill this place tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blender's already like, do we need a second clubhouse?
[SPEAKER_12]: We might.
[SPEAKER_12]: So anyhow, we're going to take a quick break and we'll be back in a minute with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 460 for this June the 10th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are live at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Be sure to check into the show, get your points, and maybe some hidden loot there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, we're live in the PlayStation Network Clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is where most people have left, honestly.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to convince Sony somehow to give us more than 30 people.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: to get in that clubhouse but I was checking out Blender put in all these little like arcade games you can play and I was playing Electro Kid which I didn't realize I mean I knew there were some mini games like I remember there was like a Arkanoid clone breakout type thing that was kind of basic and some other little things that were in there when home first launched like that Electro Kid I was just playing was kind of like a old school 8-bit platformer
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of behind the times on home.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they have the Namco games or something that you could do?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they tied into the... All it would do is a launcher for the Namco collection game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that's lame.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's not quite the same thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But still kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it looks like they are building more and more games into home.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I was checking that out a little bit during the break.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: I got my start on college radio too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I used to DJ for KCSE 95.5 in Chico, California even though that wasn't a real radio frequency.
[SPEAKER_12]: You had to have this little thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was cable radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: You had to hook up the cable to your radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: also at vognetwork.com be sure to participate in the forums we are running forums again they look very generic right now but I know that's on the plate for Bobby to expand this week Bobby has been working non-stop on the site you have to remember VOG Network has only been up in its full form for a week and for a while about a month before that he was coding the version that you saw on Friday when it launched and he's been still coding non-stop that week and I'm always like Bobby you should like take a break Bobby you should go to Disneyland like I did Bobby you should like get away from your computer he's like
[SPEAKER_12]: We gotta do a mobile site.
[SPEAKER_12]: We gotta do this other thing, you know, things I can't talk about.
[SPEAKER_12]: We gotta do this other thing, this other thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm just like, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_12]: So he's working very, very hard behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, DarkSakura, you did some of the graphic stuffs.
[SPEAKER_12]: So some of the pretty colors.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's other things coming up.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Content-wise.
[SPEAKER_02]: That directly involves our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: But should I?
[SPEAKER_02]: I should.
[SPEAKER_12]: Drop a hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: VOG10 and VOGBLOG.
[SPEAKER_12]: E3 Rapid Fire News
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: and so there is currently a beta right now which they have not accepted me very disappointed there but that will be hopefully very soon we'll get to play the full thing and I will definitely be picking it up and I may actually get into a game that's not you know
[SPEAKER_10]: Minecraft for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a sequel announced to Dead Rising, Dead Rising Riptide.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is coming out soon, probably this fall, I imagine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Consoles and PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doesn't really say when, but there's supposed to be an extensive reveal this summer, so probably fall.
[SPEAKER_10]: and last but not least was a game that wasn't shown during the press conferences but Project P100, a Wii U launch title which is going to be coming to us from Platinum Games and it kind of looks like a cross between Beautiful Joe and Pikmin
[SPEAKER_10]: and you basically play like these superheroes that get other superheroes and other citizens to kind of form together to attack monsters that are attacking Earth.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw somebody in chat, and I'm sorry I forget who, said that that was their game of the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: So some people are already excited about this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: WarioWare WarioWare
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, the description says Wario and his Diamond City friends are back in action Game in Wario features a collection of games that use only the Wii U gamepad controller The games retain the original flair and character of the micro games from the WarioWare series So it sounds like it's maybe a more fleshed out version of WarioWare which could be very interesting
[SPEAKER_12]: some games called Arrow and Ski and Shudder sound a lot like, you know, one word WarioWare games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, unfortunately it's not WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, if it was WarioWare... It's not, but it sounds like it kind of might be.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like it might be the spiritual successor, you know that term?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want a spiritual successor.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want an actual successor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Screw the spiritual successor stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need a spiritual successor.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's if your franchise didn't do very well.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is WarioWare that we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is kind of cool, you know, and I realize especially she's a good role model for women because she's in there doing a boy sport that has a lot of, you know, and she's, well, you're kind of giving me stank face a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, well, I hate the term men's sport when...
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's driving a car.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't like it either, but let's say male dominated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that works.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: And she kind of kicks a lot of ass and has done very well for herself being a spokesperson for various sites and so forth.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now she's going to be playable in a video game.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Clover Nikon in our chatroom says, I want Alex Kidd to be playable.
[SPEAKER_12]: How about the return of Alex Kidd?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where the hell has he been?
[SPEAKER_13]: We need Alex Kidd in Shinobi World 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dream on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember the first game had a lot of old Sega characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't be surprised if that happened.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are some Danica haters.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cue the Danica haters in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you want to talk about a franchise that could, you know, or a company that could use one of those, like, oh, hey, our mascots are fighting in a battle royale type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sega would be pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would.
[SPEAKER_12]: Didn't they do something like that?
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought they tried.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they had a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me read the haters.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's always going to be haters.
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Morpheus says, great, another avenue that shows Danica can't drive.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blender says, Danica sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm ho.
[SPEAKER_12]: So every fandom has their haters.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_12]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe they can get hired at EA.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the tiny little silver lining in this.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moving on to some more rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see what we've got.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, first of all, the Humble Indie Bundle 5 has three new additions to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you pay above the minimum, which is right now at $8.14, you get Braid, Super Meat Boy, and Lone Survivor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I think this is pretty cool, you know, for the Minecraft fan in the room, that Marcus Pearson actually paid $9,999.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And next up, Portal 2 in motion.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually is going to use the PlayStation Move.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't give a crap about that because I play it on the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's basically the stuff that they had.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember that was, I think it was like Sixth Sense or N-Sense or some weird like...
[SPEAKER_12]: it uses the same from the Razer Hydra yeah Razer Hydra I was just gonna keep naming random names yeah you know the motion controller sucks or well not suck but no one's buying it for the you know right so why not recycle the content here I just it pissed me off because Sony showed that in one of their little compilations of footage and we were like holy shit a new portal game holy shit yay yay yay and then it's oh it's move DLC whatever right DLC is DLC I guess I don't give a shit I guess
[SPEAKER_02]: and well, how about Sony stuff anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have to import it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can be a gazelle.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is the game we lost our shit on last week and said it should be the new President Cat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that didn't take long.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are bringing it to North America.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in fact, this actually was... I'm trying to find the guy's name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scott Road, who was the Sony VP of Product Development and Worldwide.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, it'll ship here, it'll ship everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to him, I'm going to read this directly from the article.
[SPEAKER_02]: To him, Tokyo Jungle's worldwide release is emblematic of Sony's crazy innovative approach.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says the game is just wacky but in a good way because we like to show that there's still an art form and you can still experiment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want the hell out of this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of want it too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm lusting in my heart after it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lusting in your heart is lusting for real.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, now we're to the part of the show where we're going to get to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Radio Quote Room.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the hell is a foogle you might be asking?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's Facebook and Google Plus combined.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get a foogle.
[SPEAKER_12]: We ask a question on Facebook and Google Plus and you guys answer it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we read some of the answers.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a lot of answers tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't read them all.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: We read some of the answers here live on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: But if you want to see all the answers, check us out on Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_12]: The link is on our website.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is because you can't get a short URL on Google Plus yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just go to OrangeLawnTrader.com and in the upper right hand corner is a box that says Extended Play.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just click on that Google Plus logo and you can add us there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yes, there are people using Google Plus because we got a couple responses over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tonight we have Michael D. answering our question of the week which was What, in your opinion, was the highlight of E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_12]: What is the thing you are looking forward to most of all?
[SPEAKER_12]: And Michael D. says from the press conferences Oh, excuse me, he did sign it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Techness, my bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Technus says, from the press conferences, I'd say what Ubisoft announced pretty much blew the big three away.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had a great combination of going in strong with their existing IPs and finishing with Watch Dogs, a game that sounds as amazing as it looks.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would also like to mention that the tech demos for the new next-gen engines, i.e.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unreal Engine 4, CryEngine 3, Final Fantasy tech demo, look extremely impressive.
[SPEAKER_12]: Overall, I was pleased with this E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except for Microsoft, in which I ask, please stick to the game, save the multimedia info for CES.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good point there about the tech demos for the next-gen stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of that stuff was really impressive.
[SPEAKER_12]: And finally, you know, just when you think the graphics can't get any better...
[SPEAKER_12]: There they go.
[SPEAKER_12]: They get better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lastly, going to a comment from Robaba on Google Plus says, I think the understated highlight was Smart Glass.
[SPEAKER_12]: If they use its potential, it will pretty much derail the Wii U tablet controller.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't get me wrong, I want the Wii U to succeed, but it will have to be truly awesome to be successful.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm still waiting for the delay in release to 2013 because their marketing should be almost full swing by now to release in the fall.
[SPEAKER_12]: Predicting that Wii U may just delay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think Nintendo can afford it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their stock
[SPEAKER_12]: I just don't like too many shooters.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to Facebook at facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Picaruno answered and said, probably going to get some shit from someone for this, but apart from Assassin's Creed 3, none of the games on offer wowed me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wonder Book is a great idea, but its implementation on the PlayStation 3 is stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would sell a lot better on iOS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's what I'm going to say about Wonderbook.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to bomb as bad as I have judgment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, where the fuck were the Vita games, Sony?
[SPEAKER_12]: Flaco Jones says... Again, the thing that most excited you about E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Redertainment says...
[SPEAKER_12]: Quantic Dreams Beyond Two Souls stood out for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I loved Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bought a PlayStation Move just to play again.
[SPEAKER_12]: When I saw Beyond Two Souls, I made a mental note to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then I made a note on my Droid that reads, buy Beyond Two Souls the day that it comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's two people in a row excited about Beyond Two Souls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Metal Gear Solid game, or it's not Metal Gear Solid, Metal Gear Rising game actually is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shane from Horde House commented and said, I'd have an addition to my previous statement, which was about Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd say Mass Effect 3, Wii U, Beyond Two Souls, here it is again, Watch Dogs, and Last of Us were the only things I cared about at E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm super hyped for those games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, completely forgot about Last of Us, one of the big games that they showed, and that was one of their two IPs that they introduced.
[SPEAKER_12]: But granted, we knew about that one already.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Last Ofus.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sad it's no longer the Last Ofus.
[SPEAKER_12]: TigerCaw says, I think the highlights for this year's E3 was Ubisoft with their accidental nip slips up courtesy of Far Cry 3 and the unveiling of the new game Watch Dogs.
[SPEAKER_12]: The new game from the creators of Heavy Rain called Beyond Two Souls during the Sony press conference.
[SPEAKER_12]: As for Nintendo, Zombie Reggie.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you happen to watch the video of the pre-E3 conference?
[SPEAKER_10]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the fuck is up with Miyamoto holding a banana?
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of bananas for no reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wanted to be a gif.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ronnie B says, I agree with Picaruno.
[SPEAKER_12]: Assassin's Creed 3 and the concept for Beyond were the only games that stood out for me, really.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hate what they've done with Dead Space.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stan says, hate on me all you want, but Pikmin 3 looks so fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I almost went out and bought Pikmin 1 and 2 just from watching 3's trailer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, now would be a great time to rebuy 2, because didn't the new control version come out, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that out here in the States?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pikmin 2, yeah, just came out today.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Acidic Vampire says I'm stoked for South Park RPG, Tomb Raider, Beyond Two Souls, The Last of Us, Pikmin 3 and Dead Space 3 Oh and the upcoming PlayStation 3 Xbox 360 with a gimmicky controller aka the Wii U Actually I'm not enthralled by it
[SPEAKER_12]: RedTheHaze says Devil May Cry and Metal Gear Rising.
[SPEAKER_12]: Screw the haters saying that they're similar.
[SPEAKER_12]: They should shut up about games that aren't out and that they haven't played before.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, and the Ellen Page waifu simulators, which is the new emerging video game genre.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's because Ellen Page is heavily inspired in The Last of Us, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: In one of the characters based off her?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sort of?
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the characters looks like her.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, let me do one more comment here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, two more.
[SPEAKER_12]: Critical Myth said, Highlight was the Square Enix next-gen demo, but for right now, I'm most looking forward to The Last of Us.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least we have a good idea when it's hitting the shelves.
[SPEAKER_12]: And lastly, from DarkCharger,
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing particularly stood out.
[SPEAKER_12]: E3 this year is about the whole show being greater than the sum of its parts.
[SPEAKER_12]: Despite the lack of a single bombshell, the many games, mostly third parties, were enough to keep it not only my attention, but have me checking the calendar for several important releases.
[SPEAKER_12]: Perhaps entering E3 with tempered expectations ensures that I, or the gamer in general, always wins.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting final note, but a good one I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: I think a lot of pressure would be off.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: and it's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really curious to see what happens because, you know, when the Wii first came out, there was a lot of us going, what the hell is that name?
[SPEAKER_12]: But it worked, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: At the very least, we still have the Kung Pao jokes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And any attention given back to Kung Pao is more attention and possibility for a sequel to that movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shadow Next Gen brings up a good point.
[SPEAKER_12]: The DVD format on the 360 is becoming a serious issue.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe it can't afford to be DVD only much longer.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I guess there is always digital, but it's not really going to help.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that there's always a possibility that they'll have game installs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have it on the PlayStation 3, so just have it now where it comes with chips on three disks, but you only need one.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can install the other two.
[SPEAKER_12]: But technically, you can buy an Xbox 360 without a hard drive, so that shit shouldn't be required.
[SPEAKER_10]: Technically, it still has four gigs.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not enough for some games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's move on with some more stories.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to get to the mailbag of the FU's of the week, and of course, your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: But let's try to get through these stories kind of quick here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently Vivendi is looking to sell part or all of their stock in Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course Vivendi owns 61% of the controlling stake in Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: and apparently they're holding a meeting on the 22nd of this month to discuss the potential for the sale of part or all of its holdings and basically I think they're trying to drum up some more money and basically they're saying some people believe that Vividi is worth more if it's split up into various parts and the potential split doesn't really mean anything for Activision other than a lot of shares on the market all at once.
[SPEAKER_10]: so yeah I don't really think it means a whole lot other than you know one company is not really going to own anything although it is kind of sad when you think about Vivendi did purchase all these other companies when they bought Activision and
[SPEAKER_12]: It seems like a weird time to sell it off.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe they're a little worried about some of this Diablo 3 fallout, and maybe they're worried about the next WoW expansion, and maybe this new Blizzard product.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm focusing on Blizzard, but I can't help myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that's... I think they just want money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sell off some shares.
[SPEAKER_10]: And who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_12]: Retire.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Sega doesn't want money, clearly, because they took Hatsune Miku Project Diva F for the Vita to E3 to show it off, and then said, oh, it's not coming out in North America.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which is very weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's very weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: Usually games don't show up at E3 that aren't coming out in North America.
[SPEAKER_12]: But according to a Sega rep, it was a sneak peek of a game coming to Japan.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are many Project D.Va fans out there, like DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it is disappointing to hear that this will not be coming out.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, Vita is region free, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you could always just import it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe this is all hint, hint, hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not coming to America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hint, wink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Import.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we read your emails here on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura is going to dive into the email bag.
[SPEAKER_12]: Head first again at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and pick out some of our favorite emails to read right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm going to read all the ones that are in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not very long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey OLR, quick question for all three hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of all the games you saw presented at this year's E3, which ones are you planning to buy on day one, if any?
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, I'm interested in Beyond Two Souls, and I want to play Tank, Tank, Tank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm sorry, that game is freaking addictive as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, I'm not super interested in hardly anything, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm a little behind still I feel but I definitely want that new Tomb Raider game I'll probably end up getting the Wii U I don't know to be determined that Ubisoft game Watch Dogs looks really good too I might check that out Mass Effect 3 on the Wii U
[SPEAKER_10]: Borderlands 2 for sure, South Park, The Sick of Truth, and... Oh yeah, I totally want that South Park game too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really know, those are the only two that jumped out right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Grand Theft Auto V, whenever the hell that fucking comes out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, where was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Eh, it's not ready yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_10]: They probably think, hey, well, Take-Two's not really at, you know, they aren't really at E3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their booth always has an electric fence.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so they probably, you know, maybe it's just not ready to show off yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, I mean, if you think about it, it's probably about a year away from being released, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Sincerely, Osfer P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: All my love goes to the Krogan, but I guess I can spare some for my fellow Mass Effect gamers
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, actually, speaking of titties, Far Cry 3 actually looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually may pick that up day one.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what game looked ridiculous?
[SPEAKER_12]: Alan made me watch the trailer last night, that Hitman Absolution.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, well, the trailer was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: The trailer was totally ridiculous with the stripper nuns and guns.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're trying to think, like, this is all the things that boys like.
[SPEAKER_10]: don't forget exploding toilets well even like a lot of people in the industry are just like what the fuck was that trailer that just makes no sense the game looks pretty good anyhow
[SPEAKER_02]: Robert M here you guys mentioned Retro City Rampage's Meat Boy minigame on last week's pre-taped hate that word taped show last month's Nintendo Power had a feature on the game for WiiWare including Explosion Man minigame as well not sure how that works license wise I get the impression that this will join Meat Boy and Spelunky as unreleased especially this late in the Wii's life cycle for what other consoles is it scheduled?
[SPEAKER_02]: As for the voice of Geeks Network, how practical do you expect it will be for shows doing video content, under Sedation Live in particular, to have a video podcast feed?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know when he was doing Friday Night Gaming, Bobby said such a feed would be three gigabytes an episode.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, the problem is you have to compress the video and then it's tricky.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's tricky to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, yeah, video podcasts are hard and there haven't been a lot of successful ones that are over.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, most of them are like five minutes long.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how they deliver the video podcast because five minutes worth of HD video is like our three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're about the same size.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty of them that you just post them to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think Travis has been putting clips on YouTube and so forth, and I'd certainly encourage him to continue doing that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But for now, I think him particularly is very about getting people in for the live experience.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I don't think he's going to take a whole lot of effort to try and get the video up when he is putting the audio out there at least.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I will say this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give mad props to Travis.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's got that shit on same day turnaround now Like forever we were like Travis get season 5 up Travis get season 5 up He's worked out a system where he's on same day turnaround now So props to him I think that is important too I finally saw the disco thing Disco disco Good lord It made me glad I didn't have a webcam at the time
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, God, did he put that on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't look.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are looking at doing more type of like vlog content because like Travis did that studio tour that went up during the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm going to do one that's a little more talking head, but I've got one coming up in the next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Should I spoil it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Spoil!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll say this much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll drop a hint.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to explain why I am not doing a particular podcast.
[SPEAKER_12]: People have been asking me to do a podcast on a certain topic and I'm going to explain in depth why that's not going to happen and sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: So to continue with the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for the Voice of Geeks Network, how... Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already read that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, you're sexist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just finished watching the E3 press conferences.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I was really looking forward to what Microsoft and Nintendo had to offer and didn't really expect much from Sony, I ended up liking the fact that Sony focused on games for the most part.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was really considering the Wii U since I thought it would be next-gen system that would get all the new games that other systems shared.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus Mario and Zelda.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, after their press conference, it seemed like they were focusing too much on the gimmicks and the multi-console games were all out of date.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess I'll have to pass on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did think the new Kinect features and the smart glass that Microsoft presented were cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, when it comes to games, I just don't care about getting into Halo or Gears of War after all this time, and they didn't offer anything new game-wise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony still won me over with their exclusives.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved Heavy Rain, so I will be buying Beyond right away.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Last of Us looked like a great way to tell a different kind of story with the already proven Uncharted game engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And while I don't care much about God of War or PlayStation All-Source It's All-Stars, not All-Source All-Source?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the amazing game where you fight STDs
[SPEAKER_05]: That is important.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh God, it's Herpes Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Power up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bed sores.
[SPEAKER_12]: Herpes Man versus Mrs. Gonorrhea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ringworm gun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ringworm gym.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, ringworm gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: All stars.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still nice that Sony is delivering for fans of those types of games as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wish Wii U wasn't trying to ram this new controller down our throats.
[SPEAKER_02]: More like up your ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, it's not just swallow it, it's take it as a suppository, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had high hopes when I saw the Pro Controller that there would be an alternative, but they aren't even getting the awesome-looking Watch Dogs game.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least not when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That means no Mario or Zelda for me, as long as they keep pushing gimmicky controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's from FlacoJones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Once again, it gets me thinking about the Wii U. Their biggest features that they were pimping out... This system can be played when someone wants to watch TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't understand that.
[SPEAKER_10]: This system is supposed to be so awesome that you want to play it on your TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I know a lot of people probably have multiple TVs they can play it on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't understand why that's necessarily a feature that we need to be pimping out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, once again...
[SPEAKER_10]: Just like the Wii was, they're pimping it as like this party environment.
[SPEAKER_10]: That all these party games, you know, like Just Dance has this, you know, Puppet Master mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hardly ever have people over to my house to play games nowadays because I have a kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't just be getting the party going and, you know, oh, hey, we gotta be quiet because we have the kid there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have that.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fact that New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: U or Rayman Legends has five-player co-op, I can't get two-player co-op in my household, let alone five people.
[SPEAKER_12]: BlackWolf says, you know, if they didn't spend all that time discussing the new controller, we would have been like, wait, why did you not give us more information on the controller?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we wouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, they would have.
[SPEAKER_12]: I agree with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you're just in the same boat that I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: What more information did we get about their controller?
[SPEAKER_12]: The quote-unquote final design and the whole fact that you can use two of them now, which was a big thing people were bitching about last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not important, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you think about it, that's not important because we didn't see any games that used two of them, so who knows how that's going to be utilized.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we already saw the final design.
[SPEAKER_10]: It got leaked out already.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what did we need to know about the controller that we didn't know already?
[SPEAKER_10]: Back to the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I read the last email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I'd say hi and keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your show helps make my Mondays bearable at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to hearing your opinions of E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: One last thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just bought my first smartphone and was wondering if there are any apps and or games do you think I'd be crazy not to get?
[SPEAKER_02]: Peace and chicken grease, Serious Turtle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to know what kind of phone you have too.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't know what kind of phone.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a big difference between Android and iOS.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's some games that are between both.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like Cut the Rope.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Temple Run.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm so addicted to Temple Run recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Bubble Bobble, not Bubble Bobble, Puzzle Bobble, best move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Played the crap out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And seriously, it is, you know, that, I actually really liked Espagobluta 2, and I really, you know, as far as, you know,
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm still playing Noby Noby Boy
[SPEAKER_12]: Both are worth getting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robot Unicorn Attack, Peggle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beat Hazard is on iOS now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plants vs. Zombies I don't really like so much on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would need a larger thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: R-Type actually, believe it or not, R-Type is one of the few shooters that works very well on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just seeing what else I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as regular apps, I've got Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Twitter I use Echo Phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I paid for Echo Phone and it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're on iOS, Flipboard.
[SPEAKER_12]: Flipboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I have the Tumblr app, Goodreads, because I like to share my books.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Steam app, AIM, Pinterest.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I've got all the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then... Xtube?
[SPEAKER_12]: What's that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_12]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've also got a program that when I go to eat out I use called Check Please that actually splits your meal, includes or disincludes tip and lets you go up to 30% tip.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, downloading that right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: QR Reader because of all the stuff using QR codes now and actually a really neat little clock program called Nuka.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nuka does all these interesting different digital watches and the Nuka app is actually pretty fun to play with and has neat timers and everything and
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Secret Garden that Ikuma JP did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I use Shazam all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not going to go through all seven pages of your phone, are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just picking the best ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the Kindle app.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Shazam because I go to Pinkberry and like the music, so I'll tag the music at Pinkberry and then I usually go and download albums.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're playing Mass Effect 3, get the data pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's just lots of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you go to Disneyland, use Mouse Wait so that you know how long you have to wait for
[SPEAKER_12]: Space Mountain but really those are just some good ones and that was the last email awesome just root your phone and download them all for free alright let's move on with the FUs of the week because some things at E3 might have made us angry or maybe stuff IRL we're going to find out right now
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really upset about anything except for my nail polish deciding that it all wouldn't come off tonight and my nails are kind of brittle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, fucking to my throat for being sore.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not really, I don't know, it's like a weird thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it's allergies or if it's cold or strep throat or what.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for, like, the last two weeks, my throat's just been, like, I'll get sharp pains every now and then.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you might, I feel really raspy right now because I talk a lot, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, but, like, I'll just all of a sudden I'll be, like, talking and I'm like...
[SPEAKER_10]: I like to keep all my body parts intact, even the unnecessary ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are necessary.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do serve a purpose until they get infected.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I still have everything I was born with except for my wisdom teeth.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm missing a gallbladder.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm missing wisdom teeth.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_12]: My FU of the week goes to, believe it or not, this is going to shock you, Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_12]: Disneyland on Wednesday was a fucking hot mess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess all those people were there for the Cars Land preview, the cast members, and that must have been all the veteran cast members because the noobs were running the place.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, yeah, just so crowded, especially for a Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I get that it's summer.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I've gone E3 week the last like three years and I've never had an experience as terrible as last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like every other year has been relatively good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know because I didn't get to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: How bad did the Mad Tea Party blow?
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't, it wasn't running weeknights, but I did see the decorations.
[SPEAKER_12]: The decorations look great.
[SPEAKER_12]: They spent a lot of money on them, which kind of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: My friends were there this past weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said it was the worst thing to ever happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically, what did he call it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The mad suck party or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: The mad flop party.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a mad flop party.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like to call it the mad flop party.
[SPEAKER_12]: But yeah, the one thing that bugged me most of all is that Disney don't give celebrities the royal treatment and shut down the entire fucking ride just because one celebrity wants to ride it.
[SPEAKER_12]: They need to... I'm not saying... Look, I get if you want to have the little ushers, bring them up the exit and give them a little bit of special treatment, but you don't stop the entire fucking ride because the celebrity's on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care if it's Barack Obama.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care who it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't stop for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who was the celebrity?
[SPEAKER_12]: David Beckham and his wife, Posh Spice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they could do it at least for like a real celebrity like Neil Patrick Harris.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, that just kind of ticked me off.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, meanwhile, let's get back into... I know, I know, I just did not have a good experience on Wednesday and that ticked me off because it was like Extifer and Matt's first experience at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they enjoyed themselves because we had a really good time on Monday.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't nearly as bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got to fit in a lot of the good stuff, but Wednesday was a mess.
[SPEAKER_12]: I could go on and on, but I won't.
[SPEAKER_12]: So meanwhile, Loki, let's get back into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Twitter topics, a few, and then Skype line most of all in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: So one of the rumors that we were supposed to get out of E3 was that one of these streaming companies is supposed to be partner of a console, but we didn't see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No on live or no Gaikai teaming up with consoles, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: OnLive did say that they are going to be teaming up with smart TV manufacturers including LG smart TVs with Google TV and internet browsers as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to be allowing the online servers to be used in browser which is kind of neat and of course if you have one of those smart TVs you can download an app that will allow you to stream stuff and then you just have to buy the controller as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't seen smart TVs, you know, take off yet, but I mean, I'm sure in the future we're going to see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, everything's fucking connected to the internet now, so pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, one of the games they're showing on there is Borderlands and it looks sexy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nintendo is working on the system to figure out how Wii owners are going to transfer their content to the Wii U
[SPEAKER_12]: designer Katsuya Iguchi said we are readying the system yes to transfer saves and everything you've bought so the good news is if you bought virtual console stuff and WiiWare stuff they're going to transfer over to the Wii U and it doesn't sound like they're going to charge you more for it or try to sell it to you again
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a cookie, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if it's being done with the friend code, because that would be tied to the console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, while there's good news, we have to, of course, follow that up with a little bit of WTF news.
[SPEAKER_12]: That whole Miiverse thing, it came out after the show that...
[SPEAKER_12]: Miiverse, which will allow you to kind of like post messages.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of like the Nintendo Social Network, I guess, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_12]: Satoru Iwata said there will be filtering on the Miiverse content.
[SPEAKER_12]: The first will be automatic content filtering.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you post something that's like, fuck you and your fucking dog, it's going to hit that filter because it says the F word and won't post.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, the second, there will be a moderator reading all posts before they're published.
[SPEAKER_12]: That seems crazy, but yes, live people will be screening all the messages and they say it may take about 30 minutes between the time you post something and the time it's actually visible because of that delay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lastly, users can also flag if something is missed, which we know will happen at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is extreme.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get that it's kind of like a forum so you can post stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: There should be moderators for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a problem with them going all 1984 and just let's monitor every single thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, being an adult owning a console, I don't give a fuck if the word fuck is in, you know, something.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they're like, fuck this boss, I hate it, I fucking died nine times.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's acceptable to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not a fucking little child, I don't need to be, oh, let's start.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Little children will be using it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand that, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: They have wonderful parental technology that you can block this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can put content filtering for those age groups if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll figure out how to override by themselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then you've got to be smart in your fucking kids.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, maybe this system will get overridden too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to be able to go post in Loki's Miiverse, fuck you, you fucking fuck.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what Xbox is for, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's for saying far worse words.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Frisbee, everyone learn Leet.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, probably moderators will know Leet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go on a little tangent here.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about FIFA?
[SPEAKER_10]: FIFA and the whole Kinect thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you fucking swear, you get flagged.
[SPEAKER_10]: That shit is funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, that is funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, to me, the whole fact that the Kinect will pick it up if you're saying like, fuck you, flag.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you don't like it, unplug the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if they have that technology, why don't we apply it to the goddamn Xbox Live service?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because that's a little too big brother.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if I want to say, like, if we're playing Mass Effect Online and I want to be like this fucking Banshee bitch, Kinesma D, you know, then I should be able to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I should be able to swear on my TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I were to ever play FIFA, which is not going to happen, I'm not going to fucking use Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that's my Wii U news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Esperanto?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, that's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: The average person actually can look at a page written in Esperanto and figure out what it says because that's the purpose of the language.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone who knows any little bit of Latin, which just about every English speaker does know a little bit of Latin and Greek is part of the basis of our language and the romance languages.
[SPEAKER_02]: No Esperanto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've read a page in Esperanto and I've never learned it.
[SPEAKER_12]: How do I say fuck you?
[SPEAKER_12]: You fucking fucking Esperanto.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to look it up, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, read a story first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA's being bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my official title of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to copy Steam's 75% off sales because they think it cheapens the IP and they don't want to copy that practice.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a quote from David DeMartini, the origin boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they think it's the right thing to do after a certain amount of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think it cheapens your intellectual property.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, Steam is successful.
[SPEAKER_02]: It clearly works.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people are still forking out the money to buy the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what about it is cheapening the IP if it's bringing it to a wider audience?
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's not like Steam's just going, okay, we're going to charge less for your game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're coordinating with these different developers and publishers and saying, okay, hey, we want to mark it down to...
[SPEAKER_10]: drive up some you know business and you drive up some sales for you guys as well as maybe bring a little bit of you know exposure to your product and then EA saying ah fuck it we don't care you know well you know what no one has to purchase stuff through Origin just saying you know there are other services out there so if you don't want to put your stuff on sale then fine someone else will
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and here's another thing that he's saying is what Steam does might be teaching the customer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might not want it in the first month, but if I look at it in four or five months, I'll get one of those weekend sales and I'll buy it at that time at 75% off.
[SPEAKER_02]: What he's not realizing is that people who are into the game will buy it when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't care about waiting for a sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll get it when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, when Portal 2 came out, now true, I didn't buy it for myself because I knew I was getting it for Christmas slash Hanukkah slash Kwanzaa slash Festivus, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was all hot and bothered to buy it when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, so I've bought, like I bought Fractal when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I've bought tons of games when they've come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I knew, like for example, okay, here's a good example of
[SPEAKER_02]: Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not Marvel vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I bought it right when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Dan bought it right when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: As soon as Ultimate Marvel, and we knew Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 would be out, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We bought that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: If someone wants it, they don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to go get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The sheer amount of games I've purchased on Steam, well, mostly through the Humble Indie Bundles, but I have not played most of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have a lot of people, you know, my co-workers and stuff that buy stuff on Steam that say, yeah, I'll see this game for like five bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, fuck, I'm going to pick that up because I may play it eventually.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's a lot of really quick, just spontaneous purchases because of these sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure, keep your game at $20 and someone may pick it up or drop it to $5 and you make a ton of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the check stand purchase.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know when you're in line at the grocery store and go, oh man, I love Twix!
[SPEAKER_02]: Two for a buck!
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's usually a lot of these independent games that most people aren't aware of.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, sure, I'll try it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's a buck, if it sucks, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've paid five bucks for a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played The Binding of Isaac for like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, which was another game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but you know, it's good, it's something I can go back, you know, if I'm feeling kinda, eh, I'm bored, I don't have anything to do, then I can go in and play Cave Story, which I, you know, bought on the Hundle Indie Bundle before too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's, he's not, he's using business, the business mentality and not real world common sense.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well,
[SPEAKER_12]: The end of story.
[SPEAKER_12]: Origin is not as big of a deal as Steam is at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_12]: What brought people into Steam?
[SPEAKER_12]: Those sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duh!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and here's another thing that he says.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't believe in the drop it down, spring it up 75% off approach, which is not necessarily what Steam is doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we've got something else that we do believe in that we'll be rolling out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, I don't care because I'm only going to ever play one game on Origin if I have to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Buy 10, get one free.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're stupid anyways because they're like, oh, we don't believe in marking stuff down and bringing it back up in price.
[SPEAKER_02]: You clearly don't believe in making money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, apparently you have no idea what your, you know, iOS team is doing because there's a lot of EA games that go down the 99 cents when those properties are like $7 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like, I mean, hey, you,
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, two more stories and then the Skype line, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: XBOX GOLD
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently you can enter different tournaments.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some are free, some are with a paid entry.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can compete in a variety of different games through their service.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they actually do this right now through their website, Virgin Gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess right now they're going to be partnering with EA Sports, 2K Sports, and Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're going to have different matchmaking stuff and also...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, some different services.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pay to Have Game is their tagline for Virgin Gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be interesting to see what it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm curious on how that's really going to work and how we can leverage it to have tournaments for OLR and VOG Network and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too bad they didn't do this shit back in the day when Grand Theft Auto wasn't modded the fucking hell because I kicked a lot of ass in vanilla Grand Theft Auto and episodes from Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, there's always Grand Theft Auto 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is, and I will fucking own that shit again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your body is ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to play Max Payne 3 because that's supposed to be pretty awesome, but Grand Theft Auto 5, I will dedicate my life to that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let's move on to one last story here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to end on a good note with the stories tonight, and this is a great note.
[SPEAKER_12]: We talked a little bit last week about Curt Schilling's studio and all the closures and all that, but Big Huge Games, one of the studios that was closed in that whole 38 studios debacle from a couple weeks ago, has basically been...
[SPEAKER_12]: Gobbled up by Epic Games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this is good news because Epic Games is going to open a brand new studio called Epic Baltimore.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's made up of the folks from Big Huge Games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that's quite awesome that basically they've helped them find jobs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, not everybody's going to go because some people might decide to do something else.
[SPEAKER_12]: But most of them sounds like are going over to this.
[SPEAKER_12]: The official quote on this from Epic Games President Michael Capps, quote,
[SPEAKER_12]: So there they go.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are going to be working on a big IP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who knows what it is?
[SPEAKER_12]: It won't be Reckoning 2, though, unless Epic ends up buying that IP, because I believe the state of Maryland owns that now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Rhode Island, excuse me, Rhode Island.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, their thing was, we make IP, we don't buy IP.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they're not going to buy the IP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blackwolf ventures a guess that Epic Baltimore could be making Infinity Blade for consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is a pretty big Epic IP that wouldn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what would fit right with Epic in that it's something that kind of got canceled a long time ago even though it looked really awesome?
[SPEAKER_10]: Project Offset would have been fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was that first person fantasy RPG game that was like a first person shooter almost, but with giant dragons and shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked really amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be cool, like a project offset game, but developed by Epic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like an RPG fantasy game, but like Gears of War, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is open 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Certainly you have something to say about the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: So give us a call and we will talk E3 or whatever it is that's on your mind tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the meantime, quickly, let's try to fit in a couple last minute stories here, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, so yes, let's, uh, I don't have anything pulled up again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you don't?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can go to Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to Twitter.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let me go to Twitter real quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me bring it up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I wasn't prepared for that either.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, we do have some tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, and how convenient.
[SPEAKER_12]: Skypline's already going off.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now you have some time to pull up the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange House Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Shane.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, Shane.
[SPEAKER_12]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't wait to talk to you when you're on drugs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, that will be why you should tune in to Horde House on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which, by the way, gets... Well, they don't hear it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_12]: They hear it on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I meant Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Premiered.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's new for us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Should I just hang up and we could start this over?
[SPEAKER_12]: premiered at VOGnetwork.com on Warcraft Wednesdays and then on the podcast feed Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, anyhow, they don't need to know it's taped Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, so Shane.
[SPEAKER_12]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not taped on Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's taped really quickly live.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shane's been playing guru for me in private messages.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, for Mass Effect?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that I actually will not go to Noveria first.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's what I do.
[SPEAKER_12]: To what did you want to call on the show about tonight, Shane?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want to hear what you have to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to talk about your corgi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, my corgi that I will have this weekend.
[SPEAKER_12]: So he's not your corgi yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's my corgi.
[SPEAKER_12]: You put a deposit down on the corgi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That specific one that I showed you a picture of.
[SPEAKER_12]: The corgi can't exactly help you recover from surgery.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, that might make things worse.
[SPEAKER_12]: Probably, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to share with everyone what I shared with Shane earlier.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what Corgi means?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sheepdog in Welsh.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you're getting a sheep.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait a minute, but you're afraid of sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then it will run it away, clearly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what sheepdogs are for.
[SPEAKER_02]: They herd sheep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Away from me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, okay, now I'll hear what you have to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you really want to call in about tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to gloat because clearly I won that list list from a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: What makes you say that?
[SPEAKER_08]: The segment on the show where we come up with a definitive list, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and we had to say what we wanted on Wii U. And of everything we all said, me talking about Mass Effect was the only thing that came true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, congratulations, Shane.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get a no prize.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you get a new version of Mass Effect on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shane can have a Raspberry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can someday give you a free piece of loot on vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I want something worth something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't devalue the loot at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't sell it or make money off of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can soon post it on your profile like you're supposed to be able to do at home.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do I have a profile?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you can have one night alone with Caden.
[SPEAKER_12]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're like, just one?
[SPEAKER_12]: What if they decide in Mass Effect 3 on the Wii U, they're just going to not have Kaden in it because they're just going to say, you know what, we're going to just go with this storyline from the first game.
[SPEAKER_10]: What if, because it's on a Nintendo console, they cut out all the sex scenes?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I don't know if I could get it then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still waiting for the Garrus nookie, so.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to wait till, well, I shouldn't spoil.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in the second one.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So in the first one, I've decided that I am going to bang the hell out of Kayden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just out of support for Shane.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the right way to play the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Ashley's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've taught you well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like her.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Tali, but she's kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: the other thing I was calling in about because I care so other people should care the new DJ Max game on Vita while it doesn't have a release date I guess PentaVision confirmed that there will be a collector's edition in America and they announced three of the licenses already which are just songs from the previous games but it's still something important because we actually get a real honest to goodness K-pop license
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what bands are we expecting to see under the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Right now we've only got a K-pop group called Kara with their song Step from Technica and then a guy named Mr. Funky who does a lot of music for the later DJ Maxx games with Rockstar and Signalize by Paul Bazooka who again does a lot of music for the later games.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what's interesting is that I don't know where Step is from.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it's from a Technica game but
[SPEAKER_08]: Rockstar and Signalize are both from the latest Technica game that came out, Technica 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we might see more transplants from current music instead of stuff from way back when.
[SPEAKER_08]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like it would be worthy, I believe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I just need to know how many hundreds of dollars I'm going to spend on this collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that will happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll probably only be like $10 or $20 more than retail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it won't come with anything that's worth anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, they haven't in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to get awesome puzzles and face masks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in the last one, I got a CD and a crappy book.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Might not actually be worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just download the game instead.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Shane.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Talk to you later in the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good luck with surgery.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry about that, guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just had Bugmageddon here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know why, like tons of bugs.
[SPEAKER_12]: They just love the light.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Alan's trying to do laundry outside and had to run in and all the bugs followed him.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's gross.
[SPEAKER_12]: Raid everywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: 1-877-KAMOLR 1-877-KAMOLR 1-877-KAMOLR
[SPEAKER_10]: They got Gabe Newell in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, he is quite handy with blacksmithing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so, of course, he was in there to poke fun at the fact that Half-Life 3 is not out and he was... Jerk.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was forging a new crowbar.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got another call on the line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Chugga-chugga-choo-choo, motherfuckers.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Drew Salley.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, and you can say that word on this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: You got that right, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so sick of being...
[SPEAKER_01]: held back on Bobby's show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, he's just taking the Nintendo approach.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love this.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guys, I love this new Nintendo approach with the moderating everyone's shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, I know most people are complaining about this bullshit that they're going to monitor everything before you post it up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm thinking cha-ching, cha-ching, motherfuckers.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just sent my resume off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I could probably weed through that shit at home all day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe there will actually be some type of Nintendo reality show where people audition to be one of the moderators and they'll call it The Moderator.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's a genius idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it'll be on the Nintendo Network.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like something a Japanese company would do for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you could compete.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fucking right I can.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, friggin' right I can.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so what are your thoughts on E3 this week, Jim Salley?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was all next to nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Every time I watch E3, I don't want to say I'm depressed afterwards, but I feel like I was let down the last couple of years.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't say you're depressed because you look for the cyanide?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I didn't make the Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did make Kool-Aid with Vodka in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I thought we were going to get some crazy shit to see, but nope.
[SPEAKER_01]: We didn't get nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That Wii U is pretty weird, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's strange.
[SPEAKER_12]: What about the stuff that everybody's going crazy about?
[SPEAKER_12]: What about the Watch Dogs and the Beyond Two Swords?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, that's all garbage to Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, if it's not Halo 4, it's everything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you're a Halo 4 fan?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who isn't a Halo game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who doesn't love Halo?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I have fallen out of love with Halo a bit since all the stuff after 3, but I will say Halo 4 looks pretty darn interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think about the different look?
[SPEAKER_12]: It has kind of a different look to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's about time we change it up a little bit anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was getting kind of drab before, almost redundant before.
[SPEAKER_01]: So why not change it up a little bit?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really concerned, though, with the...
[SPEAKER_01]: I wonder how well they'll do, because Bungie kind of babied us.
[SPEAKER_01]: They did it right for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So do you think the change in studio was a good thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because to be honest with you, I don't think Bungie could keep it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: They said it themselves that they were getting kind of sick of, I don't want to say sick, but they were getting kind of bored with doing Halo, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And if they're not going to have that same drive to build the great Halos like they did in the past, then it is time to pass the torch on to someone new.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can agree with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually has to do with anything that one is working on.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't have the enthusiasm, it's going to show in the end product.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is why we see a lot of Obsidian games when they know they're only getting the sequel, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: They just pump it out as quick as they can because they just need to get their money and they want to be done with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: They want to move on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was an error though, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what else does the Jim Sally train want to share with us tonight here on OLR?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is Loki there or is he eating pizza right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, I'm really ashamed of myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to admit this to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I've been at the very last mission of Grand Theft Auto 4 for about a year and I can't fly a fucking helicopter to save my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Their controls are kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is there like a cheat though or something I can do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like
[SPEAKER_10]: To control the helicopter better?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, like a helicopter doesn't die mode or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you can put in your god mode code and just bring up your phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then when you have the phone up, you can just keep hitting the health.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the...
[SPEAKER_10]: GTA 555-0100 is the number and then basically you just keep hitting that and you'll keep replenishing the health on the helicopter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really though, it's difficult to keep shooting down the bad guy in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So really my best bet is to go get a kid from the elementary school to come over and just do it for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have to type that in as I'm falling to my death?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, you just type it into your phone beforehand so you have that cheat up and then you bring it up on your cheats menu in the phone and then you can just keep hitting A over and over or X or whatever and just, you know, each time you hit it it'll recover the health in your helicopter or you can just wait until your helicopter starts smoking or whatever and just hit that and it'll replenish the health on the helicopter.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're my best friend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Friends are made.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now you have something to do right after the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right after the show, baby.
[SPEAKER_01]: GTA 5, 5, 5.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jim, Sally, I got to let you go so we can get into some more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: But thanks so much for stopping in tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just want to dedicate this call to my buddy Birdman.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, Bird, if you've been drinking too much and I got to call your brother to come over and take you home at the party, then maybe you've had too many beers, Birdie, or not enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: And don't drink and drive, ever Don't drink and drive, that's why I called your brother You drunk fuckbird Jesus Christ, man Don't drive your car to my house and drink a six pack of beers Get the fuck out of here, bird, go with your brother I love you, Sky Alright, love you too, take care Thanks, Loki No problem Oh, I see how it is
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say bye, Darky, but I guess not now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye, sweet Darky.
[SPEAKER_01]: Heart face.
[SPEAKER_01]: Little bum.
[SPEAKER_01]: I made the little bum thing for you with a three.
[SPEAKER_12]: With a number three.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm hanging up now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everybody look at my bum.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a great note to end on.
[SPEAKER_12]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you think you can follow that call, good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Meanwhile, I'm going to try to do Twitter topics here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every time I've done it, though, I've been derailed, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we'll go to a couple tweets here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tigerclaw305 sent us a tweet about Nexon pays $685 million for 14.7% of NCSoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: NCSoft, they've made games like Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know it's one of their big titles.
[SPEAKER_12]: ION, they've done a couple other MMOs as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are now the largest shareholder in NCSoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's part of a two-year agreement between these two South Korean gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we'll see what is born of that partnership later on.
[SPEAKER_12]: TigerClaw sent us another tweet about Kojima seeing social and core games converging together.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this is kind of some of what she saw in some of the Nintendo's presentation.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what Kojima said.
[SPEAKER_12]: In an interview with CVG, he said, quote,
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think social and core games are separate both will evolve together and at some point I feel the social side of things will converge with the core gamers I think in the future maybe Metal Gear will change in certain ways to integrate social aspects if you look at other games on the market now you can see it's already happening so Metal Gear may at some point get involved how do you guys feel about that do you think he's on to something there or do you think maybe too far casual Metal Gear game
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I thought what Xbox Live and PlayStation Network did was already kind of social.
[SPEAKER_12]: And not that it's always showing the best parts of society.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, I kind of thought that was the social gaming.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because what used to be social gaming, arcades.
[SPEAKER_12]: And look what Xbox Live and PlayStation Network has done to arcades.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think... I mean, when I hear this, I think Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And there's very few Facebook games I get excited about.
[SPEAKER_12]: Very, very few.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although I will say, you don't know Jack is pretty fucking awesome on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft
[SPEAKER_12]: The Noobuo Summer Bundle Kickstarter So it's a Kickstarter that he's linked us to It's music inspired by video games And it's a Kickstarter They're trying to raise $8,000 And why are they doing this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well they're trying to do video game music information in English and Japanese
[SPEAKER_12]: A two CD original and arranged soundtrack album for the browser game Roko-Chan And doing some different design work there Proceeds of the Kickstarter will benefit the bundle's eight participating musicians And will be the first source of funding for the Roko-Chan team So I guess it's kind of like a little bit of a startup company here Slash get a cool little soundtrack album I will say this though, some of the albums that are included in this Super Meat Boy Choice Piano Cuts
[SPEAKER_12]: Splatterhouse Volume 1, Volume 2 and Splatterhouse Butchered so if you're a Splatterhouse fan also in there in the arranged pack looks like our friend MegaRan who was on the show a few weeks ago is involved there with Black Materia the remixes as well as some stuff by Metroid Metal so those are some groups you should know of so go on to Kickstarter and search for N-U-B-U-W-O N-U-B-U-W-O N-U-B-U-W-O there it is that's it for tweets the phone ain't going off so I'm thinking the show's about over
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in tonight to our little program.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's an app in the App Store, and it's also, it's iOS and it's Android, called Stitcher Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you can give us thumbs up and likes and stuff, and there actually is like a chart that ranks shows.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think last I looked, we were number 40 or something in games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we can go a little higher, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Give us some thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stitcher's free, so go get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's on the web, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll have to get the link for the website or Tiger Claw will beat me to it in about five seconds here.
[SPEAKER_12]: We could definitely use your thumbs up and your likes over there on Stitcher Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'd really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or just tell a friend.
[SPEAKER_12]: Word of mouth is how we spread the good word of Orange Launch Radio and grow the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_12]: Before we conclude tonight, though, we've got to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark Sakura, we'll start you tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ladies first.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm changing the fortune cookie.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can change the fortune.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to get off Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_12]: Spending too much money?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been luckily not spending too much money, but I'll talk to you after about stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just seeing some of these ideas that people come up with.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like, really?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we're not doing a Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's definitely not what I'm getting at.
[SPEAKER_12]: My final thought tonight is I'm looking forward to eating what's in that crock pot right over there in the corner of the room.
[SPEAKER_12]: And all those bugs can go die of raid poisoning.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stupid bugs.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you everybody so much for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio and we'll see you again next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We didn't mention it all tonight surprisingly just because E3's kind of dominated everything but I will mention now we are two weeks away from the 10 year Orange Lounge Radio anniversary show if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two weeks away.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to be here?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I'll be here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was a week you weren't going to be here.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was supposed to be this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, but you made it anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hooray.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So are you really giving me the webcam?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I'm giving you the... Well, technically, that was from AkumaJP.
[SPEAKER_12]: So AkumaJP gave you, then gave me, then gave you back the webcam.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a great night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for staying up late with us or listening to us at work or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just can't thank you guys enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!