[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly to listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_14]: and just, you know, people who want to have fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's what we're doing here on Orange Lawn Trader tonight is having a whole lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'd love for you guys to join us sometime live Sunday nights at OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get back into the gaming news, though, so we have something to rant about.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of stuff to rant about, I hate to do this every week,
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, we play this game at work.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's what stupid thing is Sony going to do this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: They never disappoint.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there was news reports.
[SPEAKER_01]: This isn't exactly PlayStation 3 related, but there's reports that the first Blu-ray drives that are going to be available in the Sony Vios, yeah, they won't play Blu-ray movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's like a DVD player that does not play DVD movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what the hell is it going to do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, but you can, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Burn your own content and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's like a Blu-ray data drive or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: And because they said that the whole reason why that it can't is because there was actually some lagging software development and copy protection issues.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not good, because, you know what, I mean, these PlayStation 3s, they use PC drives, more or less, and, yeah, I hope they get this crap together when the PS3 comes out, or else, who knows, we may see some firmware updates now playing, you know, Blu-ray movies, because I don't know why else you would need a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there is actually some interesting news in regards to the Halo movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is information on Ain't It Cool News.
[SPEAKER_04]: The director was basically saying that, first of all, he prefers Halo 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: but that is talking about some of the material that's going to be in the movie, talking about how Master Chief is going to be a mix of the Man in the Suit and CG.
[SPEAKER_04]: To quote, the film has to have a feeling of reality so that it means I want to keep him as real as much as I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're talking about how it's hard to have someone who moves like an animation as opposed to someone who moves like a human.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're also working on having the Covenant be along the same lines, making them
[SPEAKER_04]: as real as they can possibly make the movements.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another quote from him, from an organic standpoint, they have to be believable.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also need to be terrifying and alien.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the best way to start doing that is to break the human silhouette.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although many of them are bipedal automatically, you can shift the overall body to something very alien.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I thought that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what do you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you think the Halo movie, hearing the director's perspective and all this, do you think the Halo movie is going to be winner or loser?
[SPEAKER_01]: Winner because he's actually a huge Halo fan and a huge gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's basically saying that he's been picking the things that are the most holy of holy things in Halo and keeping them as faithful as possible.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Chris, one of our in-house lesbians tonight seems to disagree.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't really have an idea about the Halo movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that I've heard other people who have done the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, oh, I was this huge fan of this, and I'm going to make sure everything's fine, and it just doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, do you think the guy who directed Street Fighter was a huge fan of Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_02]: If he was, I feel very bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, or at least a huge fan of Jean-Claude Van Damme or Kylie Minogue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_14]: PoohEater seems a little upset in our chatroom over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Aw, no Uwe Boll for this movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uwe Boll can die in burning hell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, don't hold back, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Zappy says, all hail Uwe Boll, maker of crappy game movies.
[SPEAKER_14]: I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, he may make crappy game movies, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I really think he's going to nail Postal.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't get that game wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Postal is a crappy game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That means he's going to do it justice.
[SPEAKER_01]: He needs to realize that his movies are never going to be taken seriously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just make it campy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe he should do the Dead Rising movie if there's ever one.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, he shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Romero should.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go, Dawn of the Dead Part 2!
[SPEAKER_14]: The Consumer Electronics Association, or CEA, might be checking into the fact maybe they want to do a massive trade show specifically about games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, they already do the Consumer Electronics Show, and this was the nation's largest gaming show until about 1994 when E3 started.
[SPEAKER_14]: Only 11% of the attendees at Consumer Electronics Show 2006 had interest in games and gaming products.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, quote,
[SPEAKER_14]: Since ESA decided to eliminate the E3 event in its known format, we have been deluged with inquiries on whether we could fill the trade show needs of smaller video entertainment companies.
[SPEAKER_14]: This coming from Gary Shapiro, President and CEO of the CEA.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quote, our executive board met yesterday and unanimously asked staff to explore ways that we could help the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Consumer Electronics Association believes that trade shows are the most viable means for reaching a market and
[SPEAKER_14]: as they serve smaller companies and entrepreneurs who need access to media, buyers, and investors.
[SPEAKER_14]: Our board, association, and events are committed to growing the industry.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, nearly 80% of our members are companies with annual sales under $10 million.
[SPEAKER_14]: So maybe here's where the smaller game companies can seek refuge is CES, whether it be in the form of next year's big show or a smaller separate show has been heard about.
[SPEAKER_01]: To be honest, in the past it was that way anyway, so why not?
[SPEAKER_14]: E3 CES
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of our chatroom folks seem to think this is a good idea, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: NintendoManiac64 says, Woot for CES.
[SPEAKER_14]: RavensDolphin says, Yes, CES is geek central.
[SPEAKER_14]: Firebomba thinks a different expo should step up, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: They'll go to the open arms of Penny Arcade Expo, which a lot of folks have been saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, this...
[SPEAKER_14]: Are the lesbians digging Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maisie says, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm just a huge Penny Arcade fan.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a huge Penny Arcade fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those guys know their stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm a huge Penny Arcade fan as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I met a dude in the line at E3 two years ago buying hamburgers.
[SPEAKER_14]: We randomly met them at E3 a couple years ago, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I was in line with, we were in line buying lunch and just talking about stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they write very good editorial pieces on the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would love to go to Penny Arcade Expo someday.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just a lack of fundage.
[SPEAKER_14]: But have you been, Megzi?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would kill to go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I heard they're giving away a new car this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: The big gaming cluster tournament they have there of all these old school games.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will you maybe make an appearance at a later Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_14]: Pardon?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe make an appearance at a later Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd love to.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe we could have an Orange Lounge Radio booth and staff it with lesbians.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: The new breed of booth babe.
[SPEAKER_14]: These booth babes don't want anything to do with you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And how's that different than any other year?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very, very true.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, anyways, another cool thing that's going to be happening pretty soon, and you've probably seen it with a lot of the games out there right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, Xbox 360 games are pretty much the same with any other next-gen games.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're pretty expensive right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: $59.99 retail seems to be the going price for most games out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Samurai Warriors 2, Just Cause, Blitz the League, Fusion Frenzy 2, Viva Pinata, Cars, and Rayman's Raving Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_01]: And those are all going to be coming out $49.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: If that's still too much for you, $39.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to be having Test Drive Unlimited coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox Live Arcade Unplugged Volume 1, if you happen to not be on live, which is weird, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be coming out early September as well as Kabbalah's Alaskan Adventure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just going to give you a hint, the game's probably going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's probably why it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_01]: World Series of Poker Tournament of Champions is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pimp My Ride in November, Kabbalah's African Safari.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also to remind you, as we mentioned last week, the first party games from Microsoft, the launch ones...
[SPEAKER_01]: Cameo, Project Gotham Racing 3, and Perfect Dark Zero, all $29.99 right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as we mentioned in Part A, Ridge Racer 6, a whopping $19.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should invent a game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, wait, what's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Unpimp My Ride.
[SPEAKER_04]: And have it sponsored by Volkswagen, where you get more points for, you know, like you get like 50,000 points for spinners and...
[SPEAKER_04]: and if they have like if they have vinyl applied to their paint you know when you destroy that car you get extra extra points and if it's actually painted on then you get a lot of points so yeah alright
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to say real quick, though, I heard Megzi give a little cheer over Viva Pinata, and I haven't heard a lot of people really excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what has you excited about Viva Pinata?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I just like those really obscure, quirky games like Katamari, stuff like that, Cube of War for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on the right show.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually heard about it from my manager at work.
[SPEAKER_15]: Animal Crossing Good Thing, Bad Thing
[SPEAKER_14]: Fire Resurrected in chat says, I got my Viva Pinata pre-ordered.
[SPEAKER_01]: And another game, of course, Rapala Trophies coming out on the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also going to be $35.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: But really, how many fishing fans are out there on the 360 anyways?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you never know.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it's easy achievement points, you'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will get it for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, speaking of online-related things, and Megzi should be interested in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Rising already has download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually going to be released in about a month in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've already put out, though, some quick downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have basically keys that are unlocking costumes that are hidden in the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're called Miami Knights, Casual, Weekender, Round Shades, Burgundy Grandpa, Pink Paparazzi,
[SPEAKER_04]: and Man in Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do you get, Johnny Cash?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, he's just got a black jacket, black pants.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, so you've seen these costumes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they're downloadable right now in live.
[SPEAKER_01]: They came out the same day as Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically in the very beginning of the game when you first get into the security room there's a bunch of lockers in there and you can walk up and change clothes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did that in Resident Evil 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get the keys and you get Jill's cowgirl outfit and...
[SPEAKER_14]: Dead Rising, Jill's Sandwich
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is there a smoothie shop in the mall?
[SPEAKER_01]: There is, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I see what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, go listen to Part A if you haven't yet, and you'll get that maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, smoothie.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dead Rising 2
[SPEAKER_14]: If not that, okay maybe that's a little ambitious, at least being the number two game, where Oblivion was a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, I'm looking at my list right now, right this minute, somebody is playing Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this person on my friends list already got the infinite mode it looks like, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lucky.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what's great though?
[SPEAKER_01]: If you happen to read somethingawful.com, they have a little page on there talking about Dead Rising and how to spend the 72 hours in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hilarious because they basically never left the security room for the 72 hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's funny, they kept taking pictures of the one chick's boobs in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dear everyone, I have heard your concerns and passed them to every source within Capcom Possible.
[SPEAKER_14]: I feel your pain as I myself have a large SDTV and am having trouble reading the mission objectives, item names, etc.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd like you all to know we have heard your concerns and take them seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been seeing campaigns on other forums to send hundreds of emails to our support email.
[SPEAKER_14]: unfortunately this doesn't expedite or increase the importance of the concern in any way but it does take time and resources from other fans equally deserving concerns all concerns are always important to us and do what we can we do what we can we would like you to know we appreciate your feedback blah blah blah so basically they're saying please stop emailing us we know
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a boo-boo in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: My bad, shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, my bad, shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you think they're going to do?
[SPEAKER_14]: You think they'll patch it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they'll patch it.
[SPEAKER_14]: You really think?
[SPEAKER_14]: That seems like an awfully big thing to patch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does he have font size?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mixi?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't really know much about it since I have yet to play Dead Rising, but it seems like, like you said, a big thing to patch and kind of a...
[SPEAKER_15]: Dead Rising MMO
[SPEAKER_14]: I think a lot of folks would have just liked to see Dead Rising be multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_14]: But my thought is, if they've done Dead Rising multiplayer, what's going to be the big catch for Dead Rising 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: Be the zombie?
[SPEAKER_14]: Didn't they already do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the perfect MMO would be you have your everyday life and then you release your serum.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if your character gets infected...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's get into the mailbag and find some other great thoughts.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to put the hazmat suit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Jamie's going to suit up in the hazmat at bestest suit right now and get her hands wet and get there in the mailbag at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com They better not get wet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your emails right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they get wet, that means my suit's broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: First email comes from Nailhead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll start by saying that I love the show, been listening to the podcast for a year, it makes traveling to work and back much faster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most games that I buy are from recommendations from Orange Lodge Radio, so thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a scary thought that we're influencing the general public like that, but no thank you, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a story that you may want to know about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm part of a small film company in Huntsville, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shout out to Jamie, I know she's from Alabama too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_04]: And we are in production of a World of Warcraft documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll link you to this article because I love the way it's written much better than me trying to describe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to read the URL, it's fairly long.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's at wowinsider.com slash 2006 slash 08 slash 08.
[SPEAKER_04]: slash bowling dash four dash GnomeReagan G-N-O-M-E GnomeReagan, actually, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I don't...
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dash wow, dash documentary, dash in, dash the, dash works.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it sounds like go to this wow insider and look for an August 8th post.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sounds like, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, the link to the film's webpage is at worldofwarcraftthemovie.com and the film company is deadworkers.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as cool as zombie flesh eaters, but still pretty damn cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd be curious to see what this documentary would turn out like.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be great if you mentioned it on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would surely help get us more interviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we would love to interview you all as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is, if we can make it out west.
[SPEAKER_04]: In closing, I'll list three things about your show I love.
[SPEAKER_04]: FUs of the Week, PC vs. Mac is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tend to side with Loki on this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are Bruce Campbell fans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's something funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of Penny Arcade earlier, they did a strip about Dead Rising and they had Mac fans drooling over the... That was great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The closing on this is thanks, I love you all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kisses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smoochie, smoochie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got one from Diginova.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey crew, a big hello from DigiNova on the other side of the pond.
[SPEAKER_04]: Been a while since I last called in, but I wanted to raise the subject of the OLR Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally find this part of the show one of the most interesting parts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, there are the regular callers, but to myself they are part of the OLR formula that makes it so addictive, that makes me so envious that I can't participate more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait to see the reaction of this week's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: At this point, I want to make my dedication to the OLR crew and have purchased the above domain, which isn't a total rip-off, but I hope this makes me an official trooper from Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be sure to listen to and pass the word of OLR to the masses.
[SPEAKER_14]: So somebody bought OrangeLounge.co.uk for us, in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, maybe we should have a UK Mirror.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm down with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Email us back if you want to help run a UK Mirror for us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_14]: A, I'm very glad someone's saying something positive about the call-in segment because I think, I want to say either the reviews in iTunes or somewhere was bashing on the callers and I, you know, they're just mad they don't listen Sunday nights and can call in themselves.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what their deal is.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm really glad something said, because we really want this to be everybody's show, not just, you know, DarkSakura, Loki, and Sky hog the airwaves for, you know, three hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: We like getting you guys involved, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although my ego does like hogging the airwaves for three hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are the stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the diva of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Rob's the diva of the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Second thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm loving the increase it seems like we've been having in UK presence lately because I've noticed on Myspace we've been getting a lot of ads from UK folks lately.
[SPEAKER_14]: So whoever's spreading our name out there in the UK, thanks.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we're really glad that you guys are noticing that we want to be representative of gamers everywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not just silly America, but UK, Australia, Canada, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: So worldwide gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I especially love our UK listeners though because I'm going to move into your country one day when I have money I'm in your country buying your stuff eating your food Oh Bobby Bobby Blackwolf wrote us
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, our good pal Bobby Blackwolf from AllGames.com, who also does a show Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: The subject is Dear LLR Heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: As in, you know, less than three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear LLR, all in caps, by the way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is how many kills he'll get in the Chromestowns tournament, by the way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Less than three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like your mom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stop talking trash.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Less than three is how many people we have signed up to participate in the Chrome House tournament right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: This whole thing reminds me of that South Park episode where they're trying to get Tweekin, I forget the other guy, to fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Craig.
[SPEAKER_01]: Craig.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Tweekin, Craig to fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're all talking trash for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love your show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also love destroying the crumhounds of your listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: XOXOXOXO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heart, heart, Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a jerk.
[SPEAKER_04]: That email was full of awesome and win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I personally don't give a shit because I don't play crumhounds.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, easy for you to say until we get trashed on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to read this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey guys, just wanted to let you guys know I enjoy the show and wanted to share my thoughts about video games causing violence in teen pregnancy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The knee-jerk reaction from many in our age group, like Junami, is to blame the parents.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, the vast majority of us are not parents or are not parents of adolescent age children, especially when you factor out the Pac-Man and Sudoku playing grandmothers that bump up the average age of the gamer statistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's easy for those of us who aren't parents to cast blame, but it's not so simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who among us growing up had parents who were successfully able to control all the influence that shaped our minds?
[SPEAKER_04]: There are many influences on a child, including the extended family, community, peers, and yes, media.
[SPEAKER_04]: Parents can only control so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Full-time parents in the 60s couldn't keep Playboy and Pod out of the hands of children.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can single parents and dual-wage parents today...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's obviously not video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: People always blame new technology, trends, and music.
[SPEAKER_04]: The parents of yesterday were convinced that Elvis singlehandedly deflowered a generation of virgins.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not fiction.
[SPEAKER_04]: but there are very few parents of today who grew up with that music agree there have been studies done linking video games to physical agitation like increased heart rate and aggression but also after playing a game of football doesn't feel that same agitation and aggression video games are new they will be scapegoated until we who have grown up with them become the parents of adolescents ourselves but then I'm sure we'll be blaming VR my god that role plays my god that role plays snuff films we never had that satan
[SPEAKER_04]: Defensively pointing to the First Amendment as a shield doesn't solve anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game industry in particular and the gaming community in general has to take a lead in tackling these problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Without casting blame, we need to improve our society's respect for life and human dignity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_04]: These ideas have to be proactively taught.
[SPEAKER_04]: Simply censoring or removing media to the contrary doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eliminating the video game where you can kill a prostitute does not by itself create respect for women.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to directly teach respect for women.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to directly teach respect for women, and a society that has respect for women will naturally not be entertained by a video game where you can kill a prostitute.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the message that we need to communicate to the mainstream and to our government.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of fighting over whose fault it is, let's work on fixing the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a side note, Canton, Ohio is a socially and religiously conservative city that teaches abstinence only.
[SPEAKER_04]: Conservative parents seem to generally believe that kids, if never told about sex, will never figure out how to perform sex or even that there are certain bodily parts that can be stimulated.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is even though one of these conservative parents themselves conceived their current crop of children in the back of a four pinto.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I digress.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why these parents think that it must be music or video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: After all, children are never exposed to sex in their God-fearing homes and communities, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It must be an outside influence, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fighting the conservatives will always be an exercise in frustration.
[SPEAKER_04]: They think they're angels, but an all-demonic influence must come from the outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the long-winded email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wanted you to know that I enjoy the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, Johnny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree with every damn thing that you've said there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd like to say I have plenty of respect for women, but I enjoy games where you can kill prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have little respect for themselves, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I had fun with Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually, I have to say, I do love having my random vows of fake, non-reality destruction.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a release, a regression.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on top of it, there's all those added studies too about how solving even the puzzles in some of these more violent games, how they raise your cognitive function.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll have you know, I'm actually going to be putting Grand Theft Auto San Andreas on my laptop so that during our segments or during our breaks between Part A and Part B, I can play the hot coffee mod at whim.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I give props to that listener for being well educated.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well-educated.
[SPEAKER_14]: Individual.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't agree with some... No, no, no, I'm... No.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I... Saying I... You know, not often you see well-educated internet rants, so I'm very pleased Well, honestly, I think that that type of attitude should be applied toward all sorts of things within, you know, society that's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I honestly think that... You know, I actually... I'm not going to go into detail about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recently had a conversation with my mother.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a discussion with my mother and she started to preach at me and try to bring Bible quotes into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, excuse me?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, do you believe in Jesus?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, what does me believing in Jesus have to do with you respecting who I am?
[SPEAKER_14]: There's nothing wrong with being religious.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're really trying to convince people to not act a certain way, or not to play these violent games, or to not do something, you need to actually have something substantial to support your claim with.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have, to defend, I'm not conservative or anything, but to defend the conservatives, there are a few people out there that are just that dumb that they will go out and do stupid things from games, but I would have more respect for them if they actually researched the subject they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should see some of those anti-Harry Potter, oh, Harry Potter Promotes Witchcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're Christians, hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: There actually is a book, though, that one of my friends who is, she's a very, she's a liberal Christian.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is called What Harry Potter Teaches Us About Jesus or something like that and how they're actually using it as a relation, how it teaches good values.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, again.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does teach some good values, but.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, if you want witchcraft, you watch Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want, you know, Jesus and all that stuff, you watch The Chronicles of Narnia.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, there's movies out there that are both parallel to different religions.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm waiting for my goddamn Pagan series, or better yet, Scientology.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'm sorry, Battlefield Earth was already out there, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Tom Cruise, Saving the World with Scientology Jeremy Todd 1
[SPEAKER_04]: First of all, RidRacer.
[SPEAKER_04]: R-I-D-R-A-Y-S-H-E-R.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I found this on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jack Thompson was interviewed, well, not really an interview, but more of a discussion about video game violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: The main discussion was about the game Bully and how it could affect children in schools.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a link to the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look on YouTube and look under Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, do a search if you really want.
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, there's a reason why we've relegated this sort of to the mailbag segment and didn't talk about it a whole lot in depth tonight, and that is, unlike G4, we don't feel like giving this guy more attention.
[SPEAKER_14]: With all due respect to the emailer, I realize it's in the blogs and everything, you know, and people are talking about it, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to finish reading his email.
[SPEAKER_04]: They bring up some interesting points and I thought that OLR and possibly some of the listeners would want to see this video.
[SPEAKER_04]: My opinion is also, by the way, on game politics.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kept bringing some of the stuff up.
[SPEAKER_04]: My opinion on this video is that Jack Thompson believes that when a kid starts playing a violent video game, that the kid will instantly turn into an angry, violent kid and that that's just not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing I found interesting is that when they asked Jack if he had seen the game being played by someone...
[SPEAKER_04]: and he replies by saying no.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically he is saying that the game Bully will make kids violent even though he hasn't actually seen the video being played and he doesn't know what the game runs.
[SPEAKER_01]: To be fair, none of them have seen the game yet and also to be fair, his whole assumption on the game was based off of the press release about the game, the pictures they've seen so far of the game and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he's in the wrong for assuming that this game is
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, a certain way because of just, you know, a press release and some pictures and he hasn't played the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they're also wrong in defending the game because they haven't played it yet either.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, the whole thing is, it's an argument over something completely retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's just like saying, you know, The Passion of the Christ and, you know, Mel Gibson is making a movie pretending the movie hasn't come out yet or something like that and debating, you know, that whole movie without having seen anything on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, the whole argument, the whole interview is retarded.
[SPEAKER_14]: The whole thing was an...
[SPEAKER_14]: Ego cock-stroking thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jack Thompson wanted to be on cable TV.
[SPEAKER_14]: G4 wanted to be able to interview the big bad guy behind video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was nothing redeeming about that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They covered nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I wish to not waste any more time talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris emails us saying, Hey OLR, I recently received a DS Lite for my birthday and I was wondering, this is my favorite game for PSP and PS2 is SOCOM, if there are any games that are similar to SOCOM for DS because please let me know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, love the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty Call of Duty
[SPEAKER_01]: DS, I don't know about that, but there might be something like that coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say probably right now, Metroid Prime Hunters is a first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's not a whole lot of first-person shooters on the Wii just because of the control setup on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DS, Wii, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say, though, if you have these games that you like, check the publisher's websites and see if they have any release dates listed for any games along those lines.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just going to throw out as the Nintendo fangirl that Metroid Prime for the DS is really very, very good.
[SPEAKER_14]: and I'm not a big fan of first person shooters in general but that was very very good I liked Metroid and the DS better than I did on the consoles to be honest I like the first Metroid on the Nintendo a little wireless multiplayer goes a long way Super Metroid yes that game was the shit that's all for the email though alright you should email us too you there sitting at your computer or sitting on the bus or in the car listening to our show right now I mean if you're driving don't email us right now but send us an email at some point mailbag at orange lounge radio
[SPEAKER_14]: I just wanna say this isn't news.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I understand why we're covering it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just want to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: This isn't news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best game of the year, Elder Scrolls 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best voiceover, Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best alternative sport game, Mario Baseball.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best action game, Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best graphics, Elder Scrolls 4 Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best handheld game, Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best multiplayer game, Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter on the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: This one I have trouble with right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most original game, Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Freaks, anyone?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best role-playing game, Elder Scrolls IV, Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best shooter, Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best soundtrack, Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best strategy game, Star Wars Empire at War.
[SPEAKER_01]: And best traditional sports game, Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I rant for a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that game was really good-looking.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, Finite is a beautiful looking game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I rant for a minute, though?
[SPEAKER_14]: I am sick of G4 farting and it turning up on all these game blogs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, seriously, what has G4 done for the gaming industry in the past year?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a goddamn thing, but letdowns and disappointment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why is the gaming community continuing to give a shit about anything G4 does?
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, don't look at it and maybe it'll go away.
[SPEAKER_14]: We should be focusing our attention on more promising gaming representations such as Independent Radio, GamePolitics.com, which is an impressive website, GameplayHD, that whole channel which is run by people who actually know things about video games, shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually seen good stuff come out of Eurogamer TV too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: And YouTube.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to know something funny though?
[SPEAKER_01]: This year's G4ia was X-Play presents G4ia.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: X-Play is the only gaming show on that network anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: So seriously, gaming community?
[SPEAKER_14]: I challenge you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop giving a shit about G4 for like six months.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying, you know, even ever since the first GeForia that I saw, which was retarded anyways, I was amazed that Spike and their award show was actually better than GeForia when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, and this is a network that doesn't even, you know, this isn't a gaming network and they're doing a better show?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, GeFor is not a gaming network anymore, and that is a fact.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've come out and said it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is a guy TV network like Spike.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just fucking sick of seeing all these, you know, G4 does this, and it ends up on Dig.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, G4 can suck my dick.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will that end up on Dig?
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably!
[SPEAKER_14]: G4 comes to Orange Lounge Radio Studio and proceeds to get down on their knees and serve a slob.
[SPEAKER_14]: And G4, remember everything negative I'm saying about G4 is in the past couple years, pretty much every decision they made since the tech TV merger, I think we can all agree.
[SPEAKER_14]: G4, when it first started, had a lot of promise.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And sure, even myself, maybe on this program in the past, I gave Scott and some of the other G4 personalities a hard time, but no more than some of the internet gives us a hard time being a podcaster or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: that he believed in and something that is so much more beneficial for the gaming community and it makes me so frustrated that all games does things.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio, Gamer Andy, Chatterbox, Bobby, everybody does things and nobody seems to care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, you know, if I report a street date or something of something, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if G4 just says, oh, by the way, this is coming out, it will get posted on every single... If all games did an award show like G4ia did that, nobody would care.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's sad because that award show would be brought to you by real gamers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Real gamers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not Game for Pay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, that was my little rant.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was my little rant.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to give Scott massive kudos, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I absolutely give Scott massive kudos because the whole reason why we're on board with all games is that we believe in his vision.
[SPEAKER_14]: Next story, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scott is full of awesome and win.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's a good guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lawrence, I couldn't say enough great things about him.
[SPEAKER_14]: If we could afford to pay him to be our producer, we would.
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course Bobby, even though we give him a hard time about the whole Chromehounds and everything thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby is full of awesome and win too.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're great.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I would rather kind of lump G4 in with the Jackie Poo thing and just basically treat it like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's just not talk about them anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm taking a stand right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: G4, those words are banned from this program from here on out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless they are mentioned in other words and not together.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, yeah, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, we could talk about a G4 map.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, that would be fine, but unless they talk about something really big, with the exception of one segment that's coming up tonight, because I just realized there's something coming up in a segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: After tonight's episode, seriously, no more G4 news stories.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Gee, I wish I had forearms.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, Pooeater, just linked to the chatroom, a dig story about G4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did it seriously get dug?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, God, you guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, in news... Yes, please, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a full-length feature made especially for Xbox Live that will be coming out on the Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically a recap of the so far Battlestar Galactica series.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if any of you missed it, go get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Battlestar Galactica is awesome sauce.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad we can talk about good cable TV now because Battlestar Galactica is pretty fracking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to watch the old Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_14]: The new one just takes the old one and makes it great.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what they need to do for me though?
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to freaking put the new Doctor Who episodes up there for me because the new Doctor is cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I made the mistake of watching Doctor Who on YouTube and I found out what happens to Rose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I love my British sci-fi, y'all.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's a really good idea to put this on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a marriage of geekdom.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear Microsoft, Doctor Who, please, for the win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okie dokie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Louisiana employees of GameStop are suing the retailer for unfair labor practices
[SPEAKER_14]: Six managers claimed they were forced to work 60 or more hours a week without being paid overtime and were told they were not eligible for overtime.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA, by the way, and other major developers lost a court case of something similar.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what do you guys think of this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It happened in California, actually, and they changed, because this affected my husband's salary.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually had to change part of, I think, something from salaried pay to, it was part of a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had to rework, because it was violating some California pay and labor law.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, the company I work for has actually had to redo that, because they were paying us by something that's legal in North Carolina and not what's legal in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, that happened out here too.
[SPEAKER_14]: That thing's already up to seven digs on dig.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it doesn't link to anything because the podcast isn't up yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: They should have waited until the podcast was up and then they could link it.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys are so great.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love Oil Army.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Megzy was going to have a comment.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, Megzy.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you want to say on the GameStop thing?
[SPEAKER_15]: I like GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, this is Eris from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_15]: She called me like five times.
[SPEAKER_15]: Since I'm not a manager, it doesn't really affect me.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I guess I don't really have anything to say about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I don't want you to endanger your job.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to say, from your perception, does it seem unfair?
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't have to answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, if you're working 60 more hours a week in any job, you should be paid fairly for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: In California, basically, and I honestly, this is why I will never move out of state because I've worked in the South and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: In California, you're required to have, for every six hours you work, you're required to have two 15-minute breaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you work over six hours, you get a 30-minute lunch that you're not paid for, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you work over eight hours in a day, unless there are other prior arrangements made, you get paid overtime.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you go over 10 hours, you get time and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not time and a half, you get double time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's law in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you work over 40 hours a week, you get overtime pay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, did they specify whether these were, this is probably just a small detail, if these were store managers or assistant managers?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just said six managers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, alright, then I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that there's actually something similar in regards, at least for the weekly overtime.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of the, as far as I was aware, I think that most of the GameStop managers are on salary.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they actually, they eliminated that in California because it was violating labor law.
[SPEAKER_15]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop managers in Wisconsin are on salary as far as I can tell but if they're working 60 hours a week there should be some sort of provision because I believe that standard salary pay is on a 45 hour a week well in California it's 40 but I think that their old way that they did it is that 45 hours of pay each paycheck and if you're working 60 hours then no that doesn't apply
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not sure how it is in Wisconsin, I'm just a part-time worker, so I'm just glad when I get hours.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yeah, I guess that if you are working 60 hours, you should get some sort of compensation, because that's just insane.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, speaking of disappointments, PlayStation 3, not going to be playable at Lipzig.
[SPEAKER_01]: So all you German fans of the PlayStation 3 out there, sorry, basically Sony wants to save all their surprises for the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: And no word if other developers are showing off any playable PlayStation 3 games.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if Sony decides that they are not going to show the unit, you can bet that a decent amount of the companies will follow suit.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what's this mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: This means that they're going to have to pull out some serious leprechaun magic to get this thing to be impressive by the time Tokyo Game Show comes around.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not too surprised that they're not having stuff playable because they don't need any more negative press.
[SPEAKER_04]: but I am surprised that they're not gonna well, who knows, maybe they will detail some more stuff about their online service and that kind of thing but no game sucks well, speaking of that particular little convention, there actually is an Ubisoft lineup that was posted if anybody cares about Ubisoft which I do, because I think Ubisoft is they do some happy
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Messiah of Might and Magic will be out fall 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell Double Agent.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has single player, multiplayer mode on Xbox 360, PC, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Xbox 360, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Juarez, Western shooter, playable on PC, September 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Settlers 2, The Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't heard of The Settlers 1, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a strategy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Settlers, construction-based strategy game, playable on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Horses with a Z, riding adventure, playable on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Open Season, action-adventure, playable on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also there were members of the international development team available there who were giving some of the background into how games are created, speaking out on new projects, showing playable games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also had a playable of Dark Messiah available there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: some interesting things coming from Sony again talking about their online service for the PS3 well there's also an online service that's supposed to be coming to the PSP in the form of an iTunes like service to download movies and video and of course some music and stuff so anyways it's kind of interesting though right now they've got a total of 120 games coming out by the end of the year so
[SPEAKER_01]: PSP, Gameplay Elements,
[SPEAKER_01]: So some games will support GPS.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think actually Hot Shots Golf, the new ones coming out, will support that.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're also talking about the camera add-on is going to have a microphone built in.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be able to take still pictures and video.
[SPEAKER_01]: And future iterations of the PSP are likely, but Sony is believing that the device will have a 10-year lifespan.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is all coming from Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually had an interview that they did with John Kohler, the senior marketing manager for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to know when their download service for the games is coming out because if they're having trouble with the movies and the music, games is going to be another thing too.
[SPEAKER_01]: And do you really think this is going to take off?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, Maisie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like I said, I've got a vendetta against Sony and the PSP is one of the things I hate most about Sony.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, let's see, looking at it from, if you just look at it hypothetically, it's a great system, you know, it does all this stuff, but it seems like it almost does too much and everything is kind of half done, and it seems like all this other stuff is just overkill, and it's going to all be half done, just kind of like the movies and the music and the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pick something and do it well?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, the business world has that saying that if you do one thing well, then you've succeeded, if you do three things halfway, then you've failed, and that's the PSP.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: There really, to be honest, isn't a game that you gotta have for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I play Grand Theft Auto religiously, and that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's my one game I buy each year.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty sad, because I don't even play the DS that much, and I've bought more than one game for it this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I plan on buying a lot more coming soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there just isn't any games out there that come out that are really great.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's just...
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would I waste my money on this stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: The games are more expensive than the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, great that, you know, it's a more powerful system, but it's just, I don't know, they're not making good software for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have to, though, give mad props to DJ Janai, the Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Swan Kicks All Your Portable Asses
[SPEAKER_15]: The analogy I use a lot with the PSP when trying to explain to someone is it's like when you go to Thanksgiving dinner and you load up your plate with all sorts of stuff, like everything, way too much of anything, and then you sit down and you try to eat it and you just can't finish it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get sick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that too.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's all just half done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whereas the DS, you got a bunch of turkey and you can finish all your turkey and it's really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you have a nice nap when you're done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, then you fall asleep.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure we'll get some emails on that, so we look forward to reading those.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the meantime, we're going to shift gears here a little bit on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to do something we have not done in a long time, at least six months.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you know what, kids?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_14]: and all things considered, it's a pretty slow news week and it's time for us here on Orange Lounge Radio to bring back an old segment that we used to do back in the day when we did like a three hour live show and a podcast and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quite.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, are we ready?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I think, Loki, are you filming this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Match Game
[SPEAKER_14]: Video game match game to be specific.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, we got a call already.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Drew Nami, our old friend.
[SPEAKER_14]: We can't escape you.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you cannot.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're not in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're still there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love GS68 in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did GS68 in our chat room say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nissan Skype line.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, okay, no more calls on Skype, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have our contestant.
[SPEAKER_14]: You want to play some match game tonight, Drew Nami?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, and you're going to be playing against somebody from our chatroom, and the person you're going to be playing against in our chatroom tonight is DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so DMN, we did a trivia contest in chat earlier, and DMN won, so it's you against DMN tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sound good, Magus?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, you know how the match game works, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, well let me explain it for those folks that don't know how Match Game works.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's going to happen is that we're going to read some sentences and they kind of have something to do with video games, but not really.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then our celebrities here in studio will fill in the blank and then you guys are going to try and guess what's in that blank.
[SPEAKER_14]: And for every one that you guess, you get a point.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the person with the most points will win a fabulous prize.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tonight's prize is a space on our MySpace Top 8.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so let's introduce tonight's celebrities.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, celebrity number one is from Wisconsin and enjoys all types of different video games, especially those by Nintendo and is a lesbian.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say hello to Megzi, celebrity number one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi Megzi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, celebrity number two comes to us from the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_14]: and she's Megzi's girlfriend and does a lot of really nice sketch art that she's drawing right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_14]: She does a lot of great art.
[SPEAKER_14]: So say hello to Chris.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, y'all.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, celebrity number three is over there in the corner taping, videotaping all this hot lesbian action going on.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's the one and only Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll be number three.
[SPEAKER_14]: Celebrity number four is hiding behind the laptop from the camera.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get that thing out of my face.
[SPEAKER_14]: And celebrity number five is me, Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, my adoring fans all there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're a celebrity.
[SPEAKER_11]: Internet celebrity, yo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nelly hates the fact that Loki plays so many video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a nightly occurrence to hear at their house.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nelly's screaming, Matt, put down the blank so we can have whoopee.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, our celebrities are thinking of their answers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Matt, put down the blank so we can have whoopee.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Our celebrities are thinking about their answers.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm waiting on our...
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm waiting on our chat room person to send me an answer there.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have our celebrity.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are our celebrities a ding-ding?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, you a ding?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Megs, he's a ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're just waiting on our chat room, our chat person.
[SPEAKER_12]: In chat room, I am not looking at your answers.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm doing this all by myself, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you're not looking at chat room answers?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're doing it all by yourself?
[SPEAKER_12]: He's a big boy now.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, there we go, we have an answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, so Magus, what is your answer?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me read the question one more time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nelly hates the fact that Loki plays so many video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a nightly occurrence to hear at their house Nelly screaming, Matt, put down the blank so we can have whoopee.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, what's your answer?
[SPEAKER_14]: Matt, put down the Rez Transvibrator.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rez Transvibrator, so we can have Whoopi.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, and let's see what contestant number two in chat, DMN, said.
[SPEAKER_14]: Said, Matt, put down the Wii, so we can have Whoopi.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: I said Transvibrator.
[SPEAKER_14]: Transvibrator, 1.4 Magus.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yes, we're writing it down in studio, and she does have that written down on her little piece of paper.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had that written down ten minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Xbox 360 Control.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a boring answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: My answer was put down the Wii so we can make Whoopi.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I matched with DMN so it's all tied up one to one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Megzy, what did you put?
[SPEAKER_14]: Put down the... Corn.
[SPEAKER_14]: Corn?
[SPEAKER_02]: The corn?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're only going to get that if you've seen Sensitive Pornograph.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in Book of the Sexual Harassment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nerds!
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chris, Matt, put down the... Third hand.
[SPEAKER_14]: Third hand.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're still hot, so we'll give it to you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, but it doesn't help out our chatroom DMN, or it doesn't help out Magus any.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's still 1-1, though, which is a higher score than usual for a match game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're ready for question number two.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ready, Magus?
[SPEAKER_14]: Bring it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Any choice words for DMN?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you're going down.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Question number two.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oops, no music yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura is planning a road trip with her girlfriends very soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: Luckily, they drive a magical car capable of playing any video game to entertain themselves on the trip there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Realizing this, DarkSakura says, Oh, I better make sure to bring a copy of blank.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, our folks are thinking about their answers there.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have our celebrities.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, no cheating, no conferring over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we're not, but we all think the same thing anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which video game are they going to bring?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, we have an answer from chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we got everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus.
[SPEAKER_14]: We better make sure to bring a copy of... Kingdom Hearts for those Bishonen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kingdom Hearts for the Bishonen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: DMN says bring a copy of... LocoRoco!
[SPEAKER_03]: LocoRoco is close.
[SPEAKER_14]: If I had to be in the car with those girls, I'd be going LocoRoco as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm in hell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see if there's a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Animal Crossing!
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, all these girls love their Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you guys laughing at?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess, I guess... What?
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll tell you later.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is the Animal Crossing a euphemism for now?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll tell you later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tom Nook something dirty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tom Nookie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, look, what...
[SPEAKER_01]: What's your answer, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, my answer... I'm one question too late.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said the Rez with the Rez Trans Vibrator.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where were you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where were you when I needed you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match, not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: My answer is, of course...
[SPEAKER_14]: Girls are going to get together.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to play Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good answer from myself, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sad to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: Megzi, what did you say?
[SPEAKER_15]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chris?
[SPEAKER_15]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a... It's a massive... There are too many giggling girls on tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_14]: Way too many.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not in on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember those emails we got back in the day about the giggling co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this is revenge.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Question number three, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ready for question number three?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's still tied up, one to one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Question numero tres.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob gets very scared when playing Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because of this, he has to remember when playing scary games to bring some blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my answer.
Dang it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob gets very scared when playing Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because of this, he has to remember when playing scary games to bring some blank.
[SPEAKER_14]: Still waiting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have an answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so let's go over to Magus.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob gets scared when playing games.
[SPEAKER_14]: He has to remember when playing scary games to bring some... Clean underwear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Clean underwear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, and DMN says... Has to remember to bring some... Depends.
[SPEAKER_14]: Depends.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, a little bit, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oops, I cracked my pants.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, oops, I cracked my pants.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's see if we get a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have clean underwear and Depends.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those are different things.
[SPEAKER_14]: They are distinctly different because you don't poop in clean underwear, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: But you can poop in Depends all you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said Depends adult diapers.
[SPEAKER_14]: You did?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, that's a point for DMN.
[SPEAKER_04]: I specifically said Depends.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, point for DMN.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, oops, I cracked my pants.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, what'd you say?
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually said...
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, a baby bottle and a blanket.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because only babies would be scared of Silent Hill yet, jackass.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_14]: Burn.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ouch, ouch.
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys are very cruel.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: My answer was Rob better bring some Guinness because if I'm drinking, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guinness.
[SPEAKER_14]: It calms me down.
[SPEAKER_15]: Guinness goes well with everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Meg Z, we're looking for Depends or Clean Underwear.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_15]: Pyramid Head Plushies.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody should make one.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the way you think, Megzi.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chris, do we have another match?
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_14]: Bring some... I said a blanket.
[SPEAKER_14]: A blanket.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get really, really scared by those things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a big pussy, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if I want the lesbian on the show to be talking about what a big...
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go back to the scoreboard where DMN has two points and 23rd Magus has one point.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Magus, you're lagging behind.
[SPEAKER_14]: You've got two more questions to catch up.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ready?
Sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here comes question number four.
[SPEAKER_14]: Question number four.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I apologize for this after the earlier rant, but these match game questions were written in advance.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jack Thompson was on Attack of the Show recently, yelling back and forth with Adam Sessler.
[SPEAKER_14]: What you didn't see, though, was after the interview, Jack's feathers were so ruffled, he said about Adam Sessler, Man, does that guy need blank!
[SPEAKER_14]: Jack Thompson said about Adam Sessler after that interview, Man, that guy needs blank!
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh, Chris already ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm ding as well if I didn't already say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: You got it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we're just waiting on DMN there in chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, do you have an answer?
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you ready to go?
[SPEAKER_14]: More cowbell.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't give your answer yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, it's not my answer.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, I'll get another one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll pull another one on my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need to know about your ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sure you do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, okay, here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got our answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jack Thompson was on Attack of the Show recently yelling back and forth with Adam Sessler.
[SPEAKER_14]: What you didn't see, though, was after the interview, Jack's feathers were so ruffled, he said about Adam Sessler, man, does that guy need what, Magus?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yowie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yowie!
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, Chris and Maisie gasped at that answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: That might be a bad sign, though, because that usually means they didn't think of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: DMN says, that guy needs to get laid, says DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see if there's any matches here in studio.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, what was your answer?
[SPEAKER_14]: A good ass hammering.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that a match with to get laid?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's a match with to get laid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Both.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we think it's... No, actually, honestly, it's a half point on the Yowie side because he would be the recipient instead of watching it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's give a half point to each.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll give a half point to each.
[SPEAKER_14]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_14]: Why don't you just not give a point to either one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, let's do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, that is actually getting laid.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is technically getting laid.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll have to give it to DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, Magus, but we'll give you a half point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they've got a mirror up or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I didn't specify.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the ruling of the judges.
[SPEAKER_14]: So be it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: He needs to get shot in the face because...
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, shot in the face.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't hold back, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's because, you know, Jack Thompson says all gamers need... Oh, okay, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_14]: That'd be irony right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good justification.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, not a match, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: My answer was, man, does Adam Sessler need personality, was my answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Personality.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unfortunately, not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, enough Pyramid Head plushie talk, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: Meg Z, Adam Sessler, man, does he need... To sit on a tack.
[SPEAKER_14]: To sit on a tack.
[SPEAKER_14]: Would that count with getting laid?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it does at this point.
[SPEAKER_14]: Would that count as yowie?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe it would count if it was sex with Kevin Pereira.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ba-dum-bum.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, Kevin.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't mean it.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're still cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, Chris.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually said butt sex, which is... Butt sex would count to get laid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Come on, come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be yaoi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking of yaoi.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll give 23rd Magus another half point.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Magus has two points.
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't involve a paddle, does it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus has two points and DMN has four.
[SPEAKER_14]: DMN is on it tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Surprise butt sex coming from DJ tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have one more chance, Magus.
[SPEAKER_14]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_14]: Bring it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here it is, the last question.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you hear about yet another new flap on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_14]: When asked for comment, our dear pal Reggie told us, Oh, that last compartment.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's where you can store the blank.
[SPEAKER_14]: Celebrities are thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jinx.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, was that a ding?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, you dinged.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm just waiting on our chatroom player there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, don't give us your answer, but do you have one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to get two points with it because that's what you need.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, can I?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, don't get smart with me, asshole, or you're going to lose this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, someone has to be smarter around here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, but I'm bummed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Funny, funny guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd rather be smart in my little head than in my ass.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have a... Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, that's... Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fifth question.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you hear about yet another new flap on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_14]: When asked for comment, our dear pal Reggie told us, oh, that last compartment, that's where you can store the...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, what did you say?
[SPEAKER_14]: Lube
[SPEAKER_14]: You need some lube for your Wii, apparently.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe with a special cock attachment.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what you got planned for your Wii, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where would a match game be without this answer?
[SPEAKER_01]: That last compartment is the store of the Iraqi suicide babies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was in on that joke when it started
[SPEAKER_14]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: My answer was, that's where you can store the weed.
[SPEAKER_14]: You put your weed in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, the SNL.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_09]: That actually was my first answer, and I changed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, wait, get it?
Weed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fired.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magazine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lesbian porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lesbian porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chris.
[SPEAKER_14]: Drugs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unfortunately, no points scored there, so let's look at the scoreboard and tally it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, you have two points, which is very good for Orange Lounge Radio Match Game to even get on the damn scoreboard.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you should be very proud of your effort.
[SPEAKER_14]: But unfortunately, DMN kicked your butt by scoring four points.
[SPEAKER_14]: He broke the record.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, he broke the record.
[SPEAKER_04]: The record was two and a half.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Congratulations, DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're a winner and you get a space in our top eight on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to bump Freeze Pop for you because they have like 11 billion friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: They don't need any more.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, you get a clump of dirt as a runner-up prize, and we'll give that to you at the next show, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll dust it in your backyard.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: No special gifts for you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magus, anything you want to say while we have you on the line?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, it's on, DMN.
[SPEAKER_12]: Another time, another place, it's on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you have fun on tonight's program?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah, even though I did get served.
[SPEAKER_14]: You did get served, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, have fun and enjoy the dirt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, dirt is good.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hear it's a growing investment.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's gay dirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gay dirt.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's gay dirt because we all touched it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he gets a good old-fashioned orange lounge hanging up on at the end there for playing there.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: DMN is going to earn a space in our top eight.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you guys think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I'm curious because we haven't done the game in a long time and our podcast audience hasn't really gotten to see the game, so I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_14]: What did you guys think of the game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was that fun?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it stupid?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it a waste of your time?
[SPEAKER_14]: Give us feedback in chat and in mailbag.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's old school OLR for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a fun, stupid waste of time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: but anyway, we do still have a little more gaming news before we finish up the show and of course we're going to open up the skype line very soon for your general calls Loki!
[SPEAKER_01]: yes, speaking of games anyways, we've got to talk about Sony again why?
[SPEAKER_01]: because we have to and we've got to talk about the PSP and we've got to talk about firmware updates because with PSP's firmware 2.8 there are some more problems not only is it Sony's latest attempt to stop homebrew
[SPEAKER_01]: On the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You may not be able to browse certain websites.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because now, the brand new web browser not only allows a developer to use the site to obtain specific information on how you got to their website, more importantly, they can check what firmware you have and deny you access based on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a suggestion for the homebrew websites then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put a keyword on your site that says porcupine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever anyone puts in Porcupine, it brings up Homebrew Games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And all the information on Porcupine she ever wanted to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put in Porcupine in video game, and there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, but, I mean, I assume that this is only for, like...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, manufacturer websites or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, stuff that's pertaining to games, you know, official sites and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably not going to be if you're running, you know, Flash games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably not going to run into a problem with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But still, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, what more do they really need to do to block stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the web browser sucks as it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: And do we really need, you know, to deny people more browsing on there?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: More than likely, anyways, we wouldn't be able to pull up the page you're trying to block anyway, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I have one more story there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you going to upgrade, Loki, or screw it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I've got two, so yeah, I can.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we've got one more story for you guys, and then we're going to open up the Skype line for general feedback, so you can start hammering away there.
[SPEAKER_14]: The username is OrangeLoungeRadio, or you can always call us on the landline,
[SPEAKER_14]: 916-226-9067 But please keep in mind, that's a toll call.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not an 800 call.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you're not paying the bill, Mom is going to get very angry with you, says Meg Z. Like last night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to do a story real quick here on Dead or Alive Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: There are some new details.
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course, our in-house lesbians would love to hear some more details on Dead or Alive Extreme 2, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It sounds like it will be playable at the Tokyo Game Show, and Japan's Famitsu Magazine got a quick look at the game, and of course, you know, the trailer's online.
[SPEAKER_14]: Excluding Beach Volleyball, the game engine is mostly complete.
[SPEAKER_14]: For Beach Volleyball, we had the previous title, so we left it until the end, but since we're at last finishing up the other areas, we're at the point where it's about time we start making the new Beach Volleyball, and that comes from...
[SPEAKER_14]: Itagaki Itagaki
[SPEAKER_14]: JetSkis, JetSkis, JetSkis, JetSkis, JetSkis
[SPEAKER_02]: See, now, you're also talking to two lesbians who happen to be in graphic arts and are taking art classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Artsy lesbians.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the colors and the skin tones, that's pretty... Yeah, I got a bone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, let's go to the Skype line and see what they have to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we love interacting with our listeners, and we're going to take some phone calls right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, who is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Haven't called in a while.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple things.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, Megzie seems to actually have a lot of similar interests to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: She likes Nintendo games, and her opinion on Sony is pretty much the same as mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony, die.
[SPEAKER_14]: So a Nintendo Maniac agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: It loves the Nintendo, and Sony can go die.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Sony can suck my dick.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you just trying to get points with the lesbians?
[SPEAKER_14]: What else is on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing I've been dying to ask you this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please don't hang up on me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, guy, what do you think about straight sex?
[SPEAKER_14]: Try a joke that's not like 30 years old on this program.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not gonna hang up on you, but seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have plenty of new jokes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go to tonight's match game.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot there.
[SPEAKER_14]: For those that have no idea what we're talking about, you've got to go back to, like, an old To Go episode back when we were doing the podcast separately.
[SPEAKER_14]: When Guitar Hero first came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Firebomba says, fail, get.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chat room is booing you, so you better say something thoughtful right now to make up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thoughtful, thoughtful.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who needs TV when you have YouTube?
[SPEAKER_14]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are there any gaming-related clips on YouTube that you want to point out?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I just thought of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to let you go, Nintendo Maniac 64, but thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good job failing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Boom, failed.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's a nice kid, but seriously, leave the inside jokes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, it's Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, hi, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hadn't even said hello yet, but hi, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_05]: More lesbians.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: The lesbian gamers can have their own podcast as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_05]: This reminds me of an episode of Raw.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry to bring up wrestling, but it just reminds me of hot lesbian action, just kissing and all kinds of craziness.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look, I want this on the record.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're making the lesbian thing kind of a joke tonight because if we did really have a hot lesbian podcast, people would be like, oh my god, I've got a boner, da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_14]: Make out!
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, seriously, do you have anything gaming related you want to share?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they were talking about the PSP being like a big paperweight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think different.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love my PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you love your PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't own an iPod, and the Apple Store didn't open up yet, so I'm still stuck with it for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, like Chris is all, where do you live?
[SPEAKER_05]: I live in New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just don't understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no Apple Store in New Jersey?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is, but it's like two hours away, and they're opening one on the boardwalk where I live, so it's like heaven, finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, but you're not using, it sounds like you don't really use your PSP as a gaming device, you use it as an MP3 player, primarily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I use it for everything, mostly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, interesting, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd like to kind of try to redeem myself about my comments about Sony.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't get me wrong, I hate them, but the PSP, it's
[SPEAKER_15]: it's a good system if you're looking for it to do all that stuff but you're straight up games if I'm going to drop $250 on a gaming system I want it to play games are you going to buy Star Fox Command for the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: maybe are you a Star Fox fan?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not so much.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait to get my hands on that thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you have a little love for DS and PSP then?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I own two DSs and I own two PSPs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you're just a hardcore nerd.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, TV's dead and YouTube is for porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: YouTube is for great stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good night, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: You too, bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blaze is coming up with a witty retort there about me bashing on nerds.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blaze, Sky, again, you are hosting a podcast about gaming.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good point, good point.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am pretty hardcore to my nerdom.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Zones Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is Black Boy, James.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, Black Boy, James.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_13]: I had a question about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, what do you want to know?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because with their firmware updates, they include something else, like something to enhance the functionality of the PSP, and I was just curious, was there anything like that with this update?
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you're my man for the PSP updates.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, 2.8 was video podcast, RSS.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, this is that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you can watch the one-up show on your PSP, yippity-yay, hooray.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or you can watch Hope is Emo, which is a great vodcast.
[SPEAKER_14]: Upgrade your PSP so you can watch Hope is Emo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, maybe I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or maybe me and Gregor will go find a pizza box to live in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so does that sound worth it to you, Black Boy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just use iTunes for your vodcasting needs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: I use my iPod for my podcasts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, you're fancy enough to own a color video iPod.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm too broke, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have the old school one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I have an old school iPod.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was my Christmas gift to myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have Kristen's.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: I do actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wanted to say to your guests tonight that they get major love and win for being lesbians and not frightening me.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't mind me saying you're a gay gamer, correct?
[SPEAKER_14]: I am.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know that because you're on All Games Interactive all the time and they pick on you so horribly for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every time I listen to frickin' Ron, I cringe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I love Ran, but seriously, he needs to stop the gay jokes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, we all do.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't wait to come back to Arena and have more Ran love.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not like that!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd pay money for that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you loving our friend Black Boy here?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, most of the extreme lesbian jokes that we've been doing have been just that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're fully clothed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that's disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we are cuddling.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like you too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's go to one more call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Good evening, this is DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: DMN, congratulations on your match game win earlier this evening.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, apparently 23rd Magus wants my neck now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, he'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you want to say tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: I am bitching about World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not a big fan of this new news?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've never been a fan of World of Warcraft, mainly more so because I've got a roommate who's very hardcore into it, and I don't understand why it takes them almost two years to release an update to the damn game when, you know, pretty much everybody and their mom's at the highest level.
[SPEAKER_08]: World of Warcraft, though, it patches all the frickin' time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but there's a difference between a patch and an expansion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, patches just adjust certain things and piss certain people off.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have an expansion, it's a whole new way of opening things up.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you just do a patch, it's the same map.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing new.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they're not changing anything with this, DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, they're adding new stuff that's going to have a slightly different spin to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: True, but I don't see anything about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying, oh, you can go up to level, what, 70 now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's 10 more levels.
[SPEAKER_14]: Drew Nami in our chatroom, your good pal after tonight's match game battle, says, WoW doesn't end at 60.
[SPEAKER_14]: Patches add content.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, like I said, I don't play it, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just know the basics.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know 60's the highest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is there any MMO you do enjoy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Gunbound, but that's not really an MMO anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, I'm not a huge fan of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm intrigued by the, I guess, the society within them, but not a fan of playing them, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was born in Wisconsin, so to hear somebody else from Wisconsin on the show tonight was pretty freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay, Wisconsin!
[SPEAKER_08]: Only not so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bring me some cheese next time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: DM out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I brought Chris and Jamie cheese.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm offering to give you something from the Nintendo store because I work there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's supposed to give me that info.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's when I told you earlier that we need your address to... Look at all the straight boys trying to get points of the lesbians tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not trying to hit points.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just being a nice guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are a nice guy, DMN.
[SPEAKER_14]: We appreciate you calling in as always, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good one, buddy.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, thank you guys so much for the calls tonight on Skype.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was fun, and that's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_14]: So even though a few guys listening on the Internet are about to write us, they hate me.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys don't talk about video games enough, and you let your callers call in and talk about lesbians and yaoi.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is wrong with you people at Orange Lands Radio?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate you, Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope you die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: You can get in line behind G4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to cut you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Promise?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, baby.
[SPEAKER_14]: With that pyramid head plushie of love.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, eight last minute stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then DarkSakura, you have one too?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, well, Loki then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okie dokie!
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other news, of course, Atari has finally picked up Bullet Witch to distribute it in the US.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's always good, because that game looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, of course, Shiny has announced that they're doing a free MMO called Two Moons, which is supposed to be the most violent MMO to date, which is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, finally, the best part about this, you're going to love this, is...
[SPEAKER_01]: According to Game Daily Biz, production company Project 51 has snatched up the rights to do an anime version of Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_14]: My god!
[SPEAKER_14]: I think three sets of panties just got wet.
[SPEAKER_07]: That boner just came back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gross!
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did that get picked up by the mics?
[SPEAKER_14]: Could you folks hear that at home?
[SPEAKER_14]: That just collective gasp of
[SPEAKER_14]: We also got one from Sauce.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, real quickly, I just want to cover this too.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is a... This was actually reported on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is a guy, a fanboy here, who's doing a short film adaptation of Zombies Ate My Neighbors.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_14]: That person just wins the internet.
[SPEAKER_14]: You win your own slice of the internet just for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the adoration of lesbians everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically part of this...
[SPEAKER_01]: Project TV Short Film Contest Project TV Short Film Contest Project TV Short Film Contest
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't heard a gamergasm like that since Snake being in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: A gamer chasm, I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snakes on the game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge needs its own Wikipedia for these terms that we're coining tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last one I had, I actually saw this last week, and I'm trying to find the exact link I had.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, what it was is they were also doing a live-action version, this was also fan-done, of Devil May Cry.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's being done by some Japanese guy, so.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of fan service out there, so.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, well, tonight has certainly been a... Oh, I'm sorry, Megzi!
[SPEAKER_14]: Megzi, yes!
[SPEAKER_14]: Reporter-in-training for Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_15]: This isn't really news, but a couple weeks ago, DarkSakura gave a shout-out to one of my good friends who was in a car accident.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember this, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I just wanted to give an update, is that she's perfectly fine, and she actually went home yesterday.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_15]: So Larissa is back home.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: And doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: She made a full recovery.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, nothing psychological or weird or anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's give a big shout out to the twins right now, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: The twins, Larissa and Corinne.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: Our chat room wants us to mention the Grand Theft Auto Coca-Cola ad.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you haven't seen this on YouTube, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: We were watching this just before the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's this CGI ad.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a Coke ad with the Grand Theft Auto characters.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Check it out on YouTube if you want to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to mention something about that Devil May Cry short film that's being done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, the director has a MySpace page if you want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: MySpace.com slash Shadow Motion Pictures.
[SPEAKER_01]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's going to do it for tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's time to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: Megzi, thank you so much for being here all the way from Wisconsin tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, all joking aside about the lesbian, you're a very cool gamer gal, gamer in general.
[SPEAKER_14]: And have fun with the Wii when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_14]: And let us know how dirgeous service is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I will.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, final thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: Any last message you want to give to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ken Kutaragi needs a helmet and some oven mitts and needs to ride the small bus.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very well put.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_15]: GameStop for the win.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chris, likewise, thank you so much for being here and representing the gamer girls very well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is full of awesome and win.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome sauce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All your listeners are actually really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do have some great listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were very, very patient with all of our really stupid lesbian jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fangirl lesbian.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you all.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys all deserve your own piece of the win internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: As always, reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: And number two
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see the shampoo I sent you?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's made for very fine hair.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if your friend says I love you, don't punch!
[SPEAKER_03]: Say thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: And my final thought is you put your weed in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought is I want to play more Dead Rising, but people want me to play more Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Decisions, decisions.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good luck in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll be cheering you on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much for nominating me for this tournament.
[SPEAKER_01]: For not even having a team.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I say, screw it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's figure out a way to get Chris and Megzy and two other lesbian gamers and we'll just have the giggling lesbian squad go up against you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, right.
We'll kick
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll kick so much ass with our giggles.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because all the straight guys from all games in Gamer Andy will have such big boners that they won't be able to play.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll bounce around.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will take them on one-on-one, but this four-on-four crap is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't agree to do any sort of... I said I wanted to play these guys, but I never said... Just take one for the team, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you're being a woman.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks everybody so much for listening and tuning in, supporting Internet Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Even on a crazy night like tonight, the fact that you guys are sticking with Orange Lounge Radio means you too are made of winning awesome, and we love you for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks so much.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see you next week for Orange Lounge 196.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dark Sakura's not going to be here next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be at Disneyland having a big massive Disneyland Mississippi orgy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means...
[SPEAKER_14]: Boys, take control of Orange Lounge Radio next week once again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means enjoy it while it lasts.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_10]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: See you next week.