[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_09]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 194 for this August the 6th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_10]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_10]: More gaming news now, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, this news is actually a little bit about the DS and how it might interact with the Wii and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the things that they're speculating is going to be announced on the 23rd as well in their Nintendo press conference there is going to be about motion sensing control coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're saying that...
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the first games that's actually going to use it is Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam, which you might remember is coming out on the DS and on the Wii, so that's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to basically be an accessory that slides into the Game Boy Advance slot, very similar to the Rumble Kart.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're going to also be using it with games like Excite Truck and Downhill Jam for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will allow you to connect your DS or DS Lite wirelessly to the Wii and use it as a controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says the size of the accessory is going to be about the same as...
[SPEAKER_08]: and the Game Boy Advance Rumble packs that they have right now for the DS and DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_08]: And like I said, they're going to be showing it off at the Leipzig Games Convention on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, speculation for now, but sounds feasible, something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could see that, especially with the whole, you know, DS is going to download stuff from the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, well, I mean, not...
[SPEAKER_10]: Game Boy Advance had the Kirby Rolling Game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's nothing new, in a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they're saying that I think this is going to be more than just one direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's more than just tilting it back and forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually going to be, you know, kind of like the PlayStation 3 controller is right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: How they're going to be doing it with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: More along that line.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not quite what the Wii is, but, you know, more than just the Game Boy Advance cards.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they're taking it to the next level.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is the next gen after all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still more excited about the new item coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, there's going to be a new Chocobo game coming out on the DS by Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Chocobo to Mahou no Eihon, which means Chocobo in the Magic Picture Book.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, it's about a Chocobo farm, and a Chocobo lives there, and a caretaker named Shiroma, which I love puns in games, because the bad guy in the game's name is Kuroma.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shiro means white, Kuro means black.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, and so, uh, they have to go into the magical picture book world, which sort of makes me think of Winnie the Pooh now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, but, um, it's going to, uh, be, uh, 3D and, uh, supposed to be, uh, from what I'm seeing, it actually looks like it's going to be a really cute game, just from the
[SPEAKER_10]: No big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is Fat Chocobo going to be the star?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Fat Chocobo is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fat Chocobo is not the star.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, I think that Fat Chocobo needs to be like a special character.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or maybe if you eat too many greens, you turn into Fat Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the DS can have a new special attachment that will actually make your DS smell like Chocobo so we can actually know what a Chocobo smells like.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like chicken butt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ninten Cats Ninten Cats
[SPEAKER_10]: Our chat room is totally getting into the Fat Chocobo thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have Blaze says, Fat Chocobo equals fan service.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eddie says, Fat Chocobo is to pwn.
[SPEAKER_10]: WonderDog Harold says, Smells like teen Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Bandit gets a little more morbid.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wants some Chocobo nuggets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, they're just like chicken, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Choco-nuggets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drew's giving the thumbs up over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry for the side note, but when you say Choco Nuggets, it makes me think of that concoction.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still think of VG Cats.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was Kentucky Faraga Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an old VG Cats.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, I also like the Mog Nuggets or whatever they call it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say on our MySpace, which gives me an excellent opportunity to plug the Orange Launch Radio MySpace over at MySpace.com slash Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's an old, we have show clips on there, and I think one of them has Kentucky Fried Chocobo in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kentucky Faraga Chocobo
[SPEAKER_10]: Man, we should make our show exclusive to one of the consoles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then maybe they'll send us some stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But actually, they scored an interview with arcade manager Aaron Greenberg, and it actually confirmed that some of the old Xbox Live arcade games are going to be updated to make them more compatible with the Vision Camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Spades, Bank Shop Billiards 2, and other classic titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, we all know Uno is ready to go with the camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate to say it, but I think it's a big duh
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it took a genius to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: to play the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to say real quick before we move on, our chat room is lighting up on the whole webcam story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, great, now we get to watch more dogs painting while we're panting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not painting.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Teenage girls, you cannot get pregnant over webcam, so keep that in mind when you're doing Xbox Live in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gorilla seems to think they should do Strip Halo, and DJ Kibbles and Bits wants them to add the camera to Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, if you want to know what's up with all the Strip gaming references, earlier in the show we've debated the uses for the Xbox Live camera, and we seem to believe here at Orange Lounge Radio that the use that it probably will get, more than anything, is turning your favorite Xbox Live arcade game into Strip.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope they have poker with that camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know they do have the camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they should do a drinking game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of the collector's edition of it, it's going to retail for $69.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to feature an official art book called Destroyed Beauty and a bonus DVD featuring an inside look of the making of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably some of that stuff that was on live as well as the stuff on MTV.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you remember back when they had the Road to Emergency or whatever they were calling that show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out, November 12th.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also something else to check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, we've all been pretty excited about Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Red Octane had a party in Australia, basically, showing that there were three more songs going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That puts our track count around 11 now.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's going to be Stone Temple Pilots, Trippin' on a Hole in a Paper Heart, Anthrax's Madhouse, Motley Crue's Shout at the Devil.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as the other eight that were previously announced, there's Revan Horton Heat's Psychobelly Freakout, Kiss Strutter, good song too, Black Sabbath War Pigs, But Whole Surfers, who was in my room last night, Van Halen's You Really Got Me, Rush's YYZ, which I've played and is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_01]: The bass is so awesome in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also Primus, John the Fisherman, and Arterial Black by Drist.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm waiting for GWAR.
[SPEAKER_01]: They need GWAR in that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't see my GWAR.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what I don't see, which is a damn crying shame, is there's no ACDC.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is a damn crying shame.
[SPEAKER_01]: And no Metallica.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to mention this.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're still talking about the cam thing, but this is great because this goes back to what they were talking about earlier in the program.
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember how...
[SPEAKER_10]: We got issued the challenge by Bobby Blackwolf for Chromehounds that's going to be taking place, I guess some inner podcast war thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bandit decided to step it up and says, good, then when the cam comes out, we can all see Blackwolf's sad face after we all beat him in whatever game he chooses.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it wrong?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well done, Bandit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, how about taking it a step further and challenging Bobby to strip Uno?
[SPEAKER_10]: We love Bobby.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, there's certain things podcasters don't do with each other and that's one of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look, when we talk about love the independent podcast, we don't mean love the independent podcast, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: You lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: You liar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take his mic away, Loki, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Use it for a better purpose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he doesn't need to have that mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of a better purpose, I think MTV's Music Awards needs a better purpose because they're now honoring game music and sort of honoring game music.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have two different categories now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Best Video Game Score and Best Video Game Soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: The nominees for Best Video Game Score include Hitman Blood Money with Jesper Kidd doing the music on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck to him because he was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter Tom Salta doing the music for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dreamfall The Longest Journey Leon Willett and Evan Magnet Johansson Love that little...
[SPEAKER_08]: Elder Scrolls 4 Oblivion, Jeremy Soule, Electroplankton You know how MTV in their weirdo award shows always throws in some kind of interesting candidate in a lot of categories?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the movie awards always have something weird in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, the best video... Ah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oblivion would be my favorite, but that's... Video game soundtrack goes to... They have Fight Night Round 3, Burnout Revenge, which I like some of the songs on there, NBA 2K6, Driver Parallel Lines, and Mark Echo's Getting Up, which, you know, I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't Dance Dance Revolution a couple years ago get nominated in one of those categories?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: No love for the VDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was extreme, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Best soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_10]: Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very surprising with all the mainstream press love for Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm very surprised that's not there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Conspiracy.
[SPEAKER_10]: MTV hates Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_10]: News at 11.
[SPEAKER_01]: MTV also hates a lot of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: MTV hates you, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, because we love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jamie loves you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jamie's going to surf the internet up and down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, she doesn't love you, but she loves you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she surfs the internet up and down every week to find a website that you ought to be looking at.
[SPEAKER_10]: Up and down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because she cares.
[SPEAKER_10]: She surfs up, up, down, down, left, right, left.
[SPEAKER_01]: Left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the website of the week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Castlemania Dungeon
[SPEAKER_01]: which is the place to go to for anything, you know, uh, Akuma Jo, uh, Dracula X, or, sorry, I should just say Dracula's Castle, um, or Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything having to do with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have sprite rips, characters, history, sound clips, artwork, emulation, even fanfiction.
[SPEAKER_01]: Castlevania fanfiction.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, this is a site I have been going to for at least, um, eight years.
[SPEAKER_01]: My husband actually introduced me to this site.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Castlevania Dungeons URL is castlevania.classicgaming.gamespy.com slash dungeon.html But you can also, if you Google search Castlevania Dungeon, it will be the first site that pulls up.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I mean, it's absolutely fabulous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the site itself has had over 200,000 hits since it started in 1997.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's pure awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_10]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_10]: At least on the forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have to believe us now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can send those apology letters to mailbag at orangelongtrader.com enclosed cookies.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a runner up.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not your side of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I may mention one more thing, though, about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to give public kudos to the folks who run Castlevania Dungeon for keeping it alive as long as you have.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm only giving the forum users a hard time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have been skeptical of us, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, this could also be the site of the week, like an actual site, go-to site.
[SPEAKER_08]: In Las Vegas, they have the Pinball Hall of Fame where you can go and visit it.
[SPEAKER_08]: and if you're interested in checking out this place you can go play all the games and they have you know games ranging from the 1950s and up to 1990s pinball pinballmuseum.org so if you're in Vegas go check it out seriously that was almost a consideration why have I not been to Vegas for like the past few years like there's all these things I have to go see I have to see this we need to do a road trip live in Vegas I have to see Celine Dion no I'm just kidding I don't have to see her I'm kidding I'm kidding the woman has only done one good song in English and it was a meatloaf song
[SPEAKER_01]: She sounds like crap in English.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dear Celine Dion, if you listen to our podcast, please stick to French.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: She did the Cyndi Lauper song, too, and that really upset me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, this isn't to talk about Celine Dion.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's to talk about gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, God no, never.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is her cell phone game out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Has anyone downloaded it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Does anyone care?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to look into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: For you guys, the listeners, I will be brave, and I will pay the $5 to download it so I can review it on the program for you folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just for you guys, because I love you.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look, we're here to talk about big gaming companies such as EA, and EA has announced in their quarter one report that revenues were up 13% from last year, but net loss also increased in the same period from $58 million to $81 million.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: They actually did this whole earnings report and did a conference call.
[SPEAKER_10]: They talked with Gamasutra, and Gamasutra ran this report here.
[SPEAKER_10]: EA revealed, That's a broken sentence, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you get what it's saying there.
[SPEAKER_10]: First Party Wii titles won't be more than $49.99, suggesting that Electronic Arts games may debut for Wii at $49.99 at launch, but they haven't really committed to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to read more details on the call, visit Gamasutra.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Want to hear something, Poopy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Activision titles, they just updated their prices in our system, and they all jumped $10.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now they're all $59.99 for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure they'll change once they see that everybody else is $49.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, speaking of losses, I feel so bad for them, sort of.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sega Sammy loses, their profit basically dropped down 93%, at least from their Pachinko machine sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, which is actually kind of surprising since Spachinko is like hardcore, you know, in Japan, but still.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they had a profit of 779 million yen, about 6.8 million dollars, which dropped from 10.7 billion yen.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's quite a bit of loss.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're blaming upfront development costs for game making.
[SPEAKER_01]: and had a loss of 4.06 billion yen in the games division which was twice as much as last year's losses they're still saying however that despite this setbacks they are going to the previous full year earnings their commitment was to stay on track so yeah let's see we'll see
[SPEAKER_10]: A very interesting story related to gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is also another story, actually, coming from Gamasu.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Full Spectrum Warrior is being used to treat PTSD in war veterans.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that would be short for post-traumatic... Thank you, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a quote from the article.
[SPEAKER_10]: The idea being to be in the high-stimulus environment for a long period of time, maintaining a low psycho-psychological arousal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dennis Wood, Doctor at the Naval Medical Center in San Diego, California
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see what's in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, as you might have heard in the first part of the show, I had my hair done at this really cool place in the Castro in San Francisco called the John Brody Salon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wanted to make a mention.
[SPEAKER_01]: On August 13th, they're doing a grand opening celebration with proceeds going to a Benefit AIDS Emergency Fund and the Breast Cancer Emergency Fund.
[SPEAKER_01]: It starts at...
[SPEAKER_01]: 6pm they're having a cocktail hour 7pm with a fashion show 8pm raffle drawing and the dress code is to be stylish so if anyone is interested in attending you can go to www.johnbrodysalon.com that's j-o-h-m-b-r-o-d-y salon.com and click on the RSVP tab you can't get in unless you're on the list donation suggested is $10 raffle tickets are $5 a piece
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be a fun time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And again, it goes to benefit the AIDS Emergency Fund and Breast Cancer Emergency Fund.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hooray for good cause.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now let's get into the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, sometimes I can't hear this music without thinking of the old version of our show with you singing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, our first email comes from JeremyTodd1, who's hanging out in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says, since the Dead Rising demo came out this past week, I found an Easter egg in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you look at the restaurant's banner, you will see that it says Jill's Sandwich.
[SPEAKER_01]: Could this be an Easter egg pointing to Resident Evil when Barry says to Jill, you were almost a Jill sandwich?
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially since they are both zombie-esque games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a cool Easter egg I thought I'd share.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Krispy Kreme actually asked a question that has nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do any of you guys watch Lost?
[SPEAKER_01]: That show totally rocks my boxers.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have friends who do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't watch TV at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's me too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have my two best friends watch it, but I don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that I dislike the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Between the show and work... It takes away from your Survivor time.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I didn't even really watch Survivor last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I have been watching, though, is Big Brother.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't get enough of that show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know it's crap reality, but I just, it's... I love it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I call them unreality shows.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go Danielle, go Danielle.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't watch TV, so no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, from our dear friend Rob, with two B's, Robway, linked me an article on GameSpy, and just to read his email, it says...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's amazing to look at now because Microsoft is single-handedly resurrecting the puzzle game, and the old games on live arcade are from some of these.
[SPEAKER_01]: The rest are being covered by Nintendo's Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: The one I think they got wrong was Maze, First Person Shooter still dominates.
[SPEAKER_01]: The one I think they were right about is Full Motion Video.
[SPEAKER_01]: Full Motion Video will forever be in games, but not as a primary gameplay element.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that inspiration for new games can come from these genres and feel fresh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, the top ten that were listed was Space Shooters, like Asteroids, Xevious, Space Invaders, R-Type, Radiant Silvergun, Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Icarugo, though, is trying, I think, to bring it back.
[SPEAKER_01]: Puzzle games, Tetris, Best Move, Puyo Puyo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Light gun games like Duck Hunt, House of the Dead, Lethal Enforcers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next up was Text Adventures.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, we still have Orange Lounge Radio, the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then maze games.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I love, though, they linked Mousetrap, which was like my favorite ColecoVision game ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mousetrap was a great game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Virtual Reality, which I think, you know, like the Virtual Boy Power Glove games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, although I actually have a, what was the one that was supposed to be for Eternal Champions?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have whatever that was that came with Eternal Champions.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Activator, thank you, I do own one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, educational games were listed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oregon Trail was the example.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody in our forums posted a link to where you can play Oregon Trail online.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd seen it before, but it's a good thing to check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: FullMotionVideo was number three with Night Trap, Mad Dog McCree, Dragon's Lair.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, Dragon's Lair.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's that HD one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will be putting out a review of Dragon's Lair HD coming up in the next week or so.
[SPEAKER_01]: because it's freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Two, the beat-em-up, like Streets of Rage, Double Dragon, River City Ransom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technically, there was one released, which was that really awful Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really awful Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I must have missed that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the last one listed is Graphic Adventure, which includes Space Quest, King's Quest, Maniac Mansion, Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_10]: Salmon Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, hell, I forgot to mention during housekeeping, so I'll mention it now.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Silver Lining folks, the King's Quest IX, but not really, the fan project that changed its name to the Silver Lining, they released a patch for their demo, and it's available on our site.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you downloaded the demo last week, please download the patch.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's available on our site in the download section.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, the beat-em-up is not completely dead, but yeah, it is dying.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the last notable beat-em-up I saw was Guilty Gear Isuka.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I did the, like, you know, they actually started putting those in as little side games in the Tekken series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if you want to talk about beat-em-ups on the PSP, Guilty Gear Judgment, which is, I think, Guilty Gear X2 Reload or something like that, but anyways, that is going to have a beat-em-up in it as well as a fighting game for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the next beat-em-up I can think of is Yakuza, which is coming out on the PS2, and that's actually done by Sega Sammy, so that's September, I think, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, should be good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, JeremyTodd1 sends us another one that I did think was notable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, OLR, JeremyTodd1 here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to say again for fear that Rob will freak out again.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's certainly getting a lot of FaceTime on the program, but hey, we let anybody email us or join the chat room, so... Well, to continue with the email.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Would it be possible to listen to OLR live on my 360?
[SPEAKER_01]: No?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, I expected that, but a company named TV... T-Versity, I guess?
[SPEAKER_01]: has made their program for the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's a quote from them.
[SPEAKER_01]: With T-Versity, the menus on the Xbox 360 are extended to include internet content, making it possible to access radio stations, podcasts, and photo feeds.
[SPEAKER_01]: So would this allow 360 owners to be able to listen to OLR live using their Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I can't test this out right now because my 360 isn't connected to the internet right now and it is too much of a hassle to move it.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said he tried it last week and he didn't get it to work.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Forward the email to my personal account so I can check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: To me, it sounds like it's something that you would use with the Windows Media Center type of thing, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be curious, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: If we could listen to it live over the 360, I'm all over that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You actually can, because Dan listens to MP3s off my computer all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's just streaming MP3s from a PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: All it would have to do is somehow trick the computer into thinking you're playing a regular MP3 when it's a streaming MP3.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the trick.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, there must be something.
[SPEAKER_01]: or just download the podcast on your computer and link it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you could do that too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wants to listen to the music and the live shows that we don't podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't think of how to get that to work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe this program will work at some point.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last one is from Rye.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just emailing to say this is the OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love you email.
[SPEAKER_01]: The one that made me go squee.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just emailing to say how great you guys and girl are.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've listened to Orange Lounge for almost a year but recently registered online.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, I listened to your podcast and several others but what ended up happening is all the other podcasters gave up on podcasting with no warning, just stopped and left me really annoyed because they all stopped in a short period.
[SPEAKER_01]: So thank you, OLR, for being a reliable source for video game news.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it's tough to do podcasts every week and I think a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_10]: They hear other podcasts and they want to do their own podcasts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm all for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: People want to have a voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: But sometimes I think people don't realize how difficult it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does take a lot of dedication and work that you don't necessarily see in the hours that we're doing the show and putting it all together.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's why I have a great respect for other independent podcasters that stick with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And nothing against the ones who don't end up sticking with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you don't have time for it, you don't have time for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, it's trickier than I think a lot of people sometimes give it credit for.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad that we make time for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_01]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_10]: All our love.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought of another TV show I have been watching.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's a reality show, but it's a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even you'd like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Who Wants to Be a Superhero.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been hearing about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I adore Stan Lee.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except I hate Major Victory on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate him.
[SPEAKER_10]: He can go die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got Tevo, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I have the first two episodes on there right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let me watch them later in the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, my favorite right now is Monkey Woman.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least Major Victory had some style to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but he's an ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Monkey Woman.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, yeah, I like Fat Mama.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lucky Woman is a very Marvel name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, like, right now... Fat Mama has a song on her MySpace.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, it's funny because I love their names because... I did check out some of the names because actually two of my favorite characters right now in the Marvel Universe are Big Bertha and Squirrel Girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Squirrel Girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: She beat Doctor Doom.
[SPEAKER_01]: and now I'm a real dork.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's just close the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get back to gaming and close the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: We look forward to getting your emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of really cool stuff, one of the things that was coming out of E3 was definitely Crysis and basically Crytek's brand new
[SPEAKER_08]: Game using their CryEngine 2.0.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those who don't know, that's the next-gen Far Cry type of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what's interesting, though, is they're actually looking for people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they had a job posting for people to work on a console version of something for the Far Cry series.
[SPEAKER_08]: One would speculate that, well, it's coming out on the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: probably coming out on the Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 so pretty interesting that game looks pretty sweet I mean the level of detail is amazing so should be cool speculate away boys and girls well speaking of as far as things being planned SNK is not actually planning on doing anything for the Playstation 3 until 2009 according to Kotaku
[SPEAKER_10]: The PlayStation 2 is good enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's small and cheap.
[SPEAKER_10]: For us, the manufacturers, we don't have to invest in your system.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the PlayStation 3 is a risk.
[SPEAKER_01]: There won't be enough consoles at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Few consoles mean few software sales.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to wait three or four years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe 2009, 2010 is a good time to release a game for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: That does bring up a very good point, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is the same reason why, what was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Splinter Cell Double Agent was delayed because they thought there's not enough 360 consoles out there and so they delayed the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to see a lot of this with the PlayStation 3 games being delayed until like fall of next year because of this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's much bigger news than I initially gave that credit for when we were prepping this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty big because that's SNK kind of taking a stand saying, you know, we're just not feeling it from Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: But again, you know, to play devil's advocate though,
[SPEAKER_10]: S&K doesn't exactly put out a lot of games that, you know, I think of S&K and I think about, you know, games that still look kind of 16-bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that that's a bad thing because, you know, playability is what's important so they could, you know, continue to exist on the PlayStation 2 and there's going to be your, you know, the guy who doesn't consider himself a gamer or herself a gamer
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: or even like, you know, I want to say they did Baseball Stars or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It makes me weep that Magical Drop I can only get on my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to, like, make that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I know that they like the port games and maybe do, like, slight graphical updates to them and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fine, because that's what's in right now is, you know, people updating some of the retro games and stuff, and they really need to pay attention to some of these older games that were on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, there was more on the Neo Geo than Metal Slug and King of Fighters, so come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do a new Fatal Fury game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, just put something out that's different.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, and I know they're not doing it for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fine, because there are types of games that they release right now, unless they're doing something brand new, don't really need the power of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did SNK do Adventure Island?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that was Hudson.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do I remember an Adventure Island on the TurboGrafx?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there was an Adventure Island on the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't Hudson work really closely?
[SPEAKER_01]: And Adventure Island 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't Hudson work really closely with NEC or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because Bomberman 93 and Bomberman 94 were also mainstay TurboGrafx-based.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never mind, Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't Konami buy them now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Konami's doing the Hudson stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then Konami needs to put out an Adventure Island game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what Konami needs to do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Another Super Konami World.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're still doing Bomberman X Zero, which is coming out in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also the Bomberman game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, there's some love for Magical Drop in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: That gives me warm fuzzies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma says, I heart Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_10]: And DMN professes his love for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I named Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying that they really do have a larger library of games than those two.
[SPEAKER_08]: Metal Slug was an awesome game and I did spend a lot of quarters on it but god damn stop really porting this game to every single console and to be honest Metal Slug 1 through 4 or whatever they're up to now they're all the same they all look exactly the same with slightly different artwork in there they haven't changed anything but hey whatever it's a fun game just need some new stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I think, number one, this is probably going to be a start of a slippery slope.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if SNK is taking a stand like this, what's to say that some more companies may decide to take similar stands and the PS3 may not be as powerful at launch as we thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's funny you mention that, Drew, because the next story I have is about Atari.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was an interview on GamesIndustry.biz with Bruno Bonell, who's the CEO at Atari.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Atari has said they have no plans to release any games for the PS3 until at least 2007.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they're citing a lack of information being the reason why they are not going to develop for the console.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then the weird thing is, he comes out and says that, quote, picking up the high end of the market, the hardcore, passionate fans, in describing the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, they're taking a little more of a soft approach to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, well, you know, the PS3 is definitely gunning for that audience, but since we don't know shit about it, we're not developing for it until next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as also interesting is concerned, well, honestly, it's not really too much of a surprise, but John Woo's Stranglehold is actually delayed until first quarter 2007.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the very well-received at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be one of the top ones to be released.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's in development by Midway.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's just delayed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, to be honest, I actually looked at the dates on this in my system at work.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's only delayed two weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just happens to fall from December to January.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it is first quarter.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now everybody's saying, oh, it's 2007.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like two weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, seriously, folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Games get delayed for stupid reasons.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: But that is, it is still big news because that means you missed Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: They missed Christmas anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was, I think, well, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were like a week away from Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: But still, though, I mean, it's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: By that time, though, I mean, you're not going to be picking up for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most people have their Christmas gifts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to go for Christmas, Mommy!
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, no, you're not going to have kids doing that, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I don't get John Woo's stranglehold, I'm gonna cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you, Lel, and I want a Rad Rider BB gun and John Woo's stranglehold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of things, though, that you might be able to pick up for Christmas, though, I know we mentioned that before, and I think I said, you know, the 360 bundle not happening in the United States.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a fact.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, one thing that we do know is going to be happening is it might be happening in other countries, in Canada and in Mexico.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example...
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn you Canada and damn you Mexico.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mexico.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyways, yeah, so it is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying, though, that it's supposed to retail, I think, about $3.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And being that the game's dropped in price down to $29.99, so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yeah, I've been to Mexico!
[SPEAKER_08]: So, should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you caught that reference, you're pretty smart.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know how we had that story.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Loki just kind of shouted it out at the end of the last episode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember how we had the top 20 gay characters from games or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: And who took the cake?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tingle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, isn't it strange that now Nintendo is sending out a survey all about Tingle.
[SPEAKER_10]: A new survey is up at Nintendo's website and it's trying to gauge what people really think about Tingle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's some of the questions from the survey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before reading about this game, how did you feel about Tingle when he showed up in a Zelda game?
[SPEAKER_10]: After reading the article on Nintendo Power, did your opinion of Tingle change?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which of these best describes your view of Tingle?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll read the answers to this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Funny, interesting, boring, annoying, none of the above, and flamey.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last one's not there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Rupeeland incorporates a unique gameplay system in which everything costs rupees.
[SPEAKER_10]: The trick is that you never know how you need to pay.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think of this system?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fun, crappy, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And do you feel that Tingle is an interesting enough character to deserve his own game?
[SPEAKER_10]: But I thought this question is very interesting as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Tingle made an appearance in the upcoming title The Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess for GameCube and Wii, how would you feel?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would be excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be annoyed, and I'd hit that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding about the third one.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: So sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But speaking about a game I would hit, that would be Spore.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Spore is going to be coming out on consoles now, according to Will Wright.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of the things that they were saying is...
[SPEAKER_08]: A console controller really makes you want the game avatar based so you don't move on the character.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why RTS games suck on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: With Spore, about half the game is Avatar-based already.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Creature game and the Space game, it would be pretty easy for us to make intermediate levels Avatar-based.
[SPEAKER_08]: So from the beginning, we thought about how we could move Spore onto platforms including consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, duh, it's coming to consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might not be right away, you know, like the PC game, but it's coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's just stupid if they don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's a really gay picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, somebody in chat just put a picture of the upcoming Tingle game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, uh, it's, uh, a little bit fruity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you call it, like, Tingle's flamboyant romp in, like, Rupeeland or something, I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn, Tingle visits the Castro.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fabulous romp of Tingle in Rupeeland!
[SPEAKER_10]: Tingle goes to the bathhouse.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, seriously, that's pretty gay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look, let me put it this way with Spore.
[SPEAKER_10]: All Spore would have to do is buy me a drink and I'd make sweet love to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's a beautiful game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to play it so bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was so mad that we couldn't play it at E3 that we just had the demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: You keep seeing on all these news sites and stuff that 3D model feature where you create a creature and you basically hit print and you pay like 10 bucks or whatever to get it shipped to you and they will ship you a model of your character, a little statue.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds like something you'd do.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'd get like five of them and have them declare war on each other.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like a little kid playing with G.I.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joe's.
[SPEAKER_08]: We could have contests and give them away to people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, I shake my head at this just because poor, poor Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: Poor Sony trying to be like Microsoft again.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are apparently now wanting to call their rewards system on their online service.
[SPEAKER_01]: They want to call it entitlements.
[SPEAKER_01]: Much like achievement points.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only problem though is that
[SPEAKER_01]: The two words are... They can't really use anything against it, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, by definition, they are irreconcilable.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean... I like what's pointed out here on this article.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's on Joystick, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: That...
[SPEAKER_01]: Achievement is the act of accomplishing or finishing, while entitlement is the state of being furnished with a right to claim something.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, by definition, they can get away with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, it's still really close.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you're entitled to it, why do you have to earn it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's a weird title.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think... It's not a big surprise that PlayStation is going this route, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it kind of works for the Xbox, so why not do a similar system?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, if it works, I'm not surprised they're going to pick it up and do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if you think about it, okay, didn't Xbox kind of incorporate rumbling into their controller because Sony did it and it worked there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mean, if it works one place, why not do it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think they need to pick the right word, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is a dumb name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Entitlements is not the right name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless they're doing something, unless they have their own unique spin on this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: A little latency.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why isn't anyone doing anything about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are they letting Microsoft get away with this kind of crap?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is really, really wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony, I feel sorry for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze in our chatroom says you're awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the only person in there that says you're awesome, just for the record.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't worry, I only have Ridge Racer on my mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, so, speaking of the PlayStation 3 and the 360, during one of the Game Informer interviews with the creators of The Darkness, they were asking, you know, what do you...
[SPEAKER_08]: like about working on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: And how is it different from the 360?
[SPEAKER_08]: Will there be any major differences between the two versions of the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: And the response was, so far the two versions look pretty much the same, quite unsurprisingly, since we both use the same shader source code and content for both platforms, they will be identically gameplay-wise.
[SPEAKER_08]: There will only be a few minor cosmetic differences, such as in the PlayStation 3, we'll have better quality video for in-game TVs, and the Xbox 360 will have a bit more room for textures and memory.
[SPEAKER_08]: In other words,
[SPEAKER_08]: Both of the games are going to be almost exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very much like how PlayStation 2 and Xbox games
[SPEAKER_08]: are almost exactly the same, with slight minor differences.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, why do I have to pay 200 extra dollars for a system that'll have games that are almost exactly the same as the 360?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they'll have exclusive games you can't get on the 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am still the tech and whore, and I have to... Final Fantasy XIII, Metal Gear Solid 4... Who gives a rat's ass about Final Fantasy XIII and its 20 million versions?
[SPEAKER_01]: Me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tekken, Tekken, Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll buy Tekken 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tekken 2 came out already.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken also.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is a joke that has not been patented in your toilet paper joke book.
[SPEAKER_10]: Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm taking.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Skype line is opening up.
[SPEAKER_10]: www.orangelontrader.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Click on Interact With Us to get all the information on the Skype line where you can call us right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or...
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Ranma Satome, and I am dead tired from coming back from Otakon.
[SPEAKER_05]: What went on at Otakon?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just came back from the biggest anime convention in the country.
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe it.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the coolest thing that happened at Otakon?
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the coolest things to me was a friend of mine got hit by a car going to the convention center...
[SPEAKER_05]: He went to the hospital.
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't sound cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, what's cool, Paul, is they let him go, and we were all at Hooters the night having dinner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you in cosplay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please say yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nerds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, because I have gone around Disneyland dressed as Shorty from Best of Move 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nerd.
Nerd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, you know what we're doing right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's only a degree of nerdiness, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nerds and damn proud of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to violate your childhoods right now with this link I'm posting in the chatroom right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, please explain this for the podcast listeners who won't know what the hell you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh no, what is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: That is so cool!
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that a Waldo?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My friend Mike is Waldo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, if they had a wedding, who could find it?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a Carmen Sandiego.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I like the Carmen Sandiego better than the Waldo, no offense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, how did he find those two?
[SPEAKER_01]: Where in the world was she?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wherever Waldo was, apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they fucking?
[SPEAKER_10]: What is Waldeck going to think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Wilmette.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was her name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Waldeck?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wilmette?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is scandal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Waldo and Carmen Sandiego are off doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But check this out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have what's called Anime Parliament where people can bring their grievances about anime to a panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Waldo pulled Carmen Sandiego out and accused her of using all the government's resources to find her while he was still missing for 15 years.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is quite possibly the lamest thing I've heard in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_01]: No way, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's lame in a funny way, but you know, I'm just like, my god, anime conventions really are the capital of nerd country, aren't they?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to go to Otacon next year because Anime Expo is a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to book my room now because right now half the hotels are already sold out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Waldo's friend was Wanda, by the way, according to DMN in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll talk about that, Ranchan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, here's what else I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: What types of video game content were there at the con and was OLR horde?
[SPEAKER_05]: All I know is there was a couple of Tekken and Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: tournaments.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to get pictures, but you know my grief from the last con.
[SPEAKER_05]: The funk almost killed me.
[SPEAKER_05]: They put the game room in the big place in the center, and still, as I'm coming down the escalator, 30 feet away, I can smell it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a suggestion for you for cosplay next year to avoid fanboy funk.
[SPEAKER_01]: Larva.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wear the mask.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze in our chat room is trying to get into the zing here by saying, you know, because I was talking about anime conventions being the capital of nerd country.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze says, Sky, remember that you are hosting a podcast about video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_07]: Burn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're supposed to make a point first, and then you say touche.
[SPEAKER_07]: You haven't made a point yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was two degrees of calm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, PodCulture wants me to go to DragonCon, which actually would be reasonable since that's actually near my family.
[SPEAKER_10]: DragonCon's in Bobby's neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_10]: He'd let us stay at his house, I bet.
[SPEAKER_10]: We could play Chromehounds all night long.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yuri Lover says we should go to YuriCon, but actually I'm going to YaliCon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course you are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, our costumes arrived.
[SPEAKER_01]: Me and Chris and Megzi are cosplaying Organization XIII characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: And our trenches arrived.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be scarred for life should I see pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drew, I could scar you even worse than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anime Next 2007, we're doing original Organization XIII cosplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Jesus Christ and the Twelve Disciples as Organization XIII, all with Keyblades.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just have dinner already.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lunchtime.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be online after the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to let you go, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to get other calls in, but thank you for calling, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, for those folks that say, hey, it's the same people that always call in, why don't you call in?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I hate reading that about the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same people that always call in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then you're obviously listening, so why don't you call in?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's go to, speaking of, so that being said, hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one and only Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, Zaku, what's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, basically the fact, you know, obviously the VMA is not having, you know, any music games for that, you know, lame, but yet somewhat important video game soundtrack nomination.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, could the record be starting right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, if we could put this on record, my next statement.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excuse me, one moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck MTV!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, same, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have to understand that MTV pretty much, you know, they suck the dick of hip-hop and rap just because it rates in more money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, this leads you to believe that MTV's that desperate for cash that they'll pour themselves out for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All those music channels nowadays, anyways, they're just all reality TV, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: You think that's worse?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, G4, for G4, you know, Guitar Hero's being nominated for Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, that leads me to believe that they're gonna, you know, they're gonna bow down to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought G4 wasn't doing an awards show anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, they're doing G4ia.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: And according to... I thought G4ia got cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network,
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, it's an economy based, the whole thing is now based on the almighty dollar and they lost touch with themselves, you know, they lost touch of who they were, you know, for years now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It used to be all about music and, you know, now it's just whoring themselves out, but that's besides the point.
[SPEAKER_07]: MTV lost touch about, what, 1994, 1985?
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting comment in chat room, interesting comment in chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blaze says MTV owns X-Fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like X-Fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I use it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's 1.2 MTV.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their suck actually started in 96.
[SPEAKER_01]: In 94, we still had Headbangers Ball and 120 Minutes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and we still had really good shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: We still had Amp in those years, too, so... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: The downhill trend began when Remote Control went off TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, when Remote Control lost it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I gotta take it back on video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Zaku, anything else?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, not really, just, you know, the whole thing about... Maybe, you know, if you... For, like, anime conventions, shouldn't they just give out deodorant sticks at the door?
[SPEAKER_03]: They have before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, just... I mean, antiperspirant, not even deodorant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Antiperspirant does a good job at, you know, absorbing sweat and thus killing odor before it even begins.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maxes.
[SPEAKER_10]: A wise person, a co-worker of mine who I really respect, once told me, you can lead a horse to water, but you can't make it drink.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: They can put baking soda in the sprinkler system.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's a good thing I'm not that hardcore about gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that at least I bathe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, this is going to be the geek analogy here, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: To keep hygiene before, you know, before anything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, last thought, Magus.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is going to be the geek analogy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just as you cannot move the blob, you cannot get rid of Confunk.
[SPEAKER_07]: G4A2006 is going on and their theme is Fake News Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad that's very original.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you mean their theme is fake news show?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fake news show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like their G4A 2006, Unite, Vote, Award, Argue is their theme.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's go to at least one more call here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good afternoon or good evening from Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: DMN, my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm upset with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you upset with me?
[SPEAKER_01]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura's pissed.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're supposed to love me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't return my calls anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I can't help changing my number and you not going to the trouble of stalking me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look, it's the new hairdo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now the boys won't leave her alone.
[SPEAKER_01]: My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what leads you to be calling our lovely program tonight, Mr. DMN?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I call first off with terrible, terrible news.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo decided to make me work Sundays now until about 5.30, so I don't get home until 6 or 7.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that means ATH is on hiatus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but I'm going to give that Wii away one Wii or another.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Could we write a letter to Nintendo begging for clemency or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I doubt it, but I'm calling for several reasons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a laundry list, but I'll try to keep them as short as possible.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, the $299 Wii, total, total garbage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why is this garbage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Reggie Philane, our company president, has made it quite clear that the Wii will not be priced over $249.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much all I can say on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much all that needs to be said.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, you know something we don't know, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You do!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God, I'm so jealous that you work for Nintendo sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the same time, I'd hate that, because, you know, on this radio program, I would...
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably get fired so fast by saying that crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so anyway, change the subject.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the things that I share with you guys, I'm very, very selective about.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But also, you guys were talking about EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: EA could make a lot more money if they decided to stop spamming everybody with Madden and actually not kill their franchises.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, oh, I don't know, SSX?
[SPEAKER_10]: At the same time though, EA has Spore coming out and they have said that they are going to develop more for the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: So maybe they are changing their tone a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I would think that $50 as a price point for software is pretty much going to be the norm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think what Loki said earlier, if it goes any higher than that, developers are going to have to take a second look at their price points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anything else you want to say to our listeners tonight, DMN?
[SPEAKER_06]: Snakes on a Plane is in less than two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go see it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, except this is the day I'm going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_06]: I promised somebody weeks ago bacon, and yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye, DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you didn't get in tonight, go ahead and try it again next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate you guys trying to call in and participate with our program.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anybody want to get out there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Before we wrap up tonight's program?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_10]: All things considered, it's been somewhat of a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_10]: When the big news is all coming from Xbox Live Arcade, which I think we had like five stories on tonight, I think it's kind of a slow week.
[SPEAKER_10]: No offense to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the Xbox Live Arcade, but that's not the center of gaming right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameTap
[SPEAKER_08]: partnered with Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I checked out GameTab.
[SPEAKER_08]: Castlevania, Frogger and Contra, Hard Corps.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they have the Genesis Castlevania game on there now, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else do they do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I was going to say, there was that new device, I guess you would call it a device, Exploder HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're putting down the PlayStation 2 to upscale all their games to 720p or 1080i, which I thought was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how great they're going to look, but that is something that's coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess watch for reviews on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the other thing, too?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I think we mentioned last week that Test Drive Unlimited, that the price was dropping down to $35.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, apparently that only applies to the U.S., so if you're in the U.K., you're still paying full price for it, so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Funnydale in the chatroom wants me to point out, and I remember Extifer of all people showed me this earlier this week, World of Warcraft now has a MySpace page.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can add music from the game to your MySpace and I guess other little animations and things like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can pimp your MySpace with World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Rockstar canceled the Xbox version of Bully.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is funny because I still haven't even seen the PlayStation 2 version of Bully yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And waiting for that one to come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope they do a 360 version, but they said they weren't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll have to wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then I believe that is going to bring our show to a close.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening to Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's that time to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Drew, thank you so much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, I can't call you Dr. Drew because that name is taken.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's unfortunately taken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Reverend Drew or something or Professor Drew.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I like Professor Drew.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you kind of look, you know, the glasses.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can have that professor look to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I got to ask a certain somebody for a certain something that I want.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is A, you're not going to get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: B, die monster, you don't belong in this world.
[SPEAKER_10]: And DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: A, reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_01]: B, it was not by my hand that I was once again given flesh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting Independent Radio and podcasting.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys rock and we do this show week in and week out for you guys that listen to us and support us and make the chat room so much fun and make the whole live experience fun and sending us the emails and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just awesome and we're on our way to episode 200.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Got lots of good stuff coming.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!