Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk and then some.
Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted and mildly retarded content.
You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
Yes, I will spank your child. If you're not going to do your job, God damn it, I will.
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
Thank you, F
Well, here's my big opening.
A sphincter says what?
I'm super. Thanks for asking.
Oh, you little bitch-troll from hell!
What am I doing here?
Haha!
Nooooooo!
Eh?
Dodge this.
Mm-hmm.
This is a tasty burger.
Look, you stupid bastard, you've got no arms left!
Yes, I have!
Look!
It's a flesh wound.
Searching for a boy in high school is useless.
It's purchased for meaning in a poly-shore way.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
Dark Sakura.
I had a sniff, Sky, but I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer, Loki.
I hate you, Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live and this is episode number 68 for November the 9th of 2003.
You're tuned in to the Bimani scene's most female challenge tonight,
Radio Station of all things Bimani.
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
And joining me as always are half of my awesome co-hosts in this corner, the happiest bunny
on the farm is Jamie Summers, is all the way in that corner that's in Alabama.
She's out tonight.
She's on vacation.
So no Jamie tonight.
Sorry everybody.
But we have some more guests here to help kind of fill that void that Jamie has left.
Is this mic on?
Yes, the mic is on.
Hello?
Yes, like you said.
What?
Testing?
There we go, yeah.
on
the fuck up. Just kidding. Say a little likey style. You know him, probably, if you listen
to Vanilla Sky on Monday nights, right? Because he's always here.
I hope you know me. Probably just like that annoying guy who always gives us his stupid
opinions about how games are cool and some games aren't. That's right.
Also, if anything, he's cool and you all suck. Thank you. Also here tonight, say hello
to Bradley. Also known as Sarcadia32. Hi, how are you?
Well, we have someone who has never been to the show in the house before.
He says, join us for some of our live remotes, but never in the house.
Say hello to Vanders!
Mahalo!
How are you?
I am well, thank you.
That's good, I'm glad you could make it.
Thanks, I'm glad to be here.
This is exciting!
Our home base is exactly what I thought it would be.
Lots of anime, lots of DVDs, lots of games.
Soundtrack for our breaks because I know you guys have been wanting to hear some of the new stuff
During this break. We're gonna hear a brand new mr. T song doing the goonies are good enough. This is awesome
Shut it is awesome. You're outvoted Loki also in this break. We're gonna hear an artist called Noki Noki. Oh with a song called
pata pata mama
pata pata mama is the name of the song we're gonna hear second and then also in this break we're gonna hear a really cool remix of
Oh
Ba-da-ba-da
Ba-da-ba-da-ba-da
Yo, Kuji
Amado ba-da-ba-da
U-da-da-i-na
Kichi-ji
O-na-re-ke-do-ke-do-da-i-do-koro
Hachi-ji
La-ba-lo-ki
U-o-me-ka-me-ka-ku-su-me-ga-ki
Ku-ji
You didn't have to believe in how you were dead
Let it stop, let it stop, let it stop
It might be still what it could be
For you I thought that there's been an open
If you wanted to live in a higher world
You'd be the one that you wanted to be
But at least I'm doing what I can tonight
To watch it when it starts
So I don't mind that it has got to
To do the best that I can
Do okay
Do what I can
I'm not getting out of here
You turned away
You're gonna see me
And I won't let it in
And if it isn't that I didn't even know you were falling in love
I'm believing that you're missing me while you're standing with me alone
Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
No!
Do we show what people think of us?
Do we want people to kiss our ass?
Yes!
Extreme Bimani Radio, that's us, Orange Lounge Radio.
Hello and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio and that was some music from the new Popin
Music Part 10.
I can't believe that game has gotten that high, all the way to 10.
That's more than I think any other Romani game has gotten yet.
What is it about popin' music that makes it so damn popular?
Any thoughts?
Retards like to smash their heads against round buttons.
Find a mic.
Yeah, get a microphone.
Look, you've already said it.
Come on, say it again.
Because retards like smashing their heads into large round buttons.
I'm not quite sure why it's so popular.
I guess maybe just the music is more popular over there than say 2DX's music seems to be
more popular over here, from what my little sphere of influence.
I personally, I don't know, since there's so much music in pop music, since there's
ten versions now, plus the anime little ones, yeah there's a lot of good tracks, but overall
I think the majority of the music isn't my style, whereas 2DX is more my type of thing,
more of a dancey, techno, trancey...
You and your rectangular buttons.
Yeah, I know, not the big round tap light ones.
Instead I've got little tiny like keys, you know.
Well, your game doesn't have any characters dancing around.
Well, in some of the videos it does.
Ha! Some!
Or as I have all of them.
I think that's probably one of the points right there,
the pop music thing.
It's so marketable.
I mean, there's hundreds of characters,
for almost every single song ever made on it, and there's like 500 plus songs probably
all made.
I don't know, it's crazy.
I was just looking at, Naby was over at a little gathering we were having last night,
and Naby, who's been on the show before, he's kind of known as the local Papa Music whore,
and he buys everything really into Papa Music.
He bought this new Papa Music calendar.
Okay, this new calendar is like the size of a small poster.
It's not the size of your typical calendar, it's bigger.
It's like the size of a small poster.
a huge W.A.B. poster, but like a fold-out poster type thing. It's pretty big. And the
cover of it has every single character from pop and music, and it's like looking at a
Where's Waldo picture. Honestly, there's so many people just packed in there. It's kind
of like, I want to find this one. I want to find the girl that looks like she's flicking
her clit in that one song. And I'm looking, and it's like playing Where's Waldo. There's
so damn many characters. And yes, I swear to God, there is a girl that looks like she's
flicking her clit in one song. Just wanted to share.
No, it's more like she's smoking out of her pussy. She keeps going like this. You know how people smoke? I'm doing the sign with the two fingers out like a peace sign. They're smoking.
Except she's doing it from her, you know, under her skirt area, if you can imagine that. You on the radio side.
The best, though, is the character Liddell, who is in, I believe it's pop music, 8? I think it's 7 or 8. I can't remember. But it's a song called Galaxy Forest. I think it's 8, too.
No, you know what, I think it's seven because I think I've known of Liddell for a while.
Okay, so I think it's one of the consumer tracks from seven is Galaxy Forest and there's
this chick Liddell who looks like a sheep herder but with no face and just two little
lighting eyes, so kind of like a black mage, like if you imagine Vivi, right?
It's like Vivi is a sheep herder but a girl and she wears a skirt but if she loses, like
rats fly out of her cooch.
Like these rats drop from her skirt and scurry off.
really disturbing like pop music has a lot of very disturbing trends of it like
Donatello Versace that one part I can't stop you know bats flying out of my
couch you're thinking that one Saturday Night Live with Donatello Versace in the
backlight yes it was just like that okay it's time to end the show but I draw the
with a line of bats flying out of my coach.
Anyway, sorry.
So I thought maybe we could go through these songs
we just played and see what you guys think of them.
We haven't really ever done that with new songs,
but you know, we're desperate for material tonight.
So let's see, what do you guys think of Mr. T
with Goonies Are Good Enough?
Crap!
Crap, crap, crap, crap.
You think this is crap?
It is crap. You're crap.
Let me just play some MIDI for you.
We don't even do anything with it, we just play MIDI.
Crap.
Okay.
That's your opinion.
This song brings me back to my days when I was a little kid
and used to play Gooey's 2 on Nintendo.
Oh, it's awesome. I've always liked Mr. T,
but he's been bringing out some cool stuff ever since, like,
I don't know, Burning Heat and stuff like that.
So good stuff. It just reminds me of like kind of like a kiriyama oka's feel of his little 8-bit sounding music and stuff
I have a question for Loki. Do you consider this crap?
Yes
Wait a minute. You like this song. I've seen you play it before
Yeah, like once ass you don't like that song
song? So many Goonies are good enough, it's kind of like the next chapter. That song right
there, that has actual synthesizers and stuff, and it actually looks like, you know, they
spent more than two minutes on it, okay? Whereas the Goonies song is just like, oh, let's play
it straight up Nintendo. And no, it wasn't hard for him to do that, all he did was just
throw it into a MIDI player and go. Okay, here's my next question, what do you think
of this
you gotta keep it
keep it with those faggots
well if you're gonna play a faggoty song anyways, at least play it so it sounds like a faggoty song instead of a faggoty 8-bit shit
the opinions and
But whatever, Loki, do not. Yeah, you get it.
No, I don't care. I'm gay and I think it's funny.
We all know Loki's tight with the queers.
Last time we asked is queers. No, I love my goonies, okay?
He's friendly
with the queers. I love goonies. That movie rocks.
And to totally take that song and just take a huge dump on it, it's just awful.
Okay, but doesn't that song, isn't it even remotely retro to you?
Didn't you ever play The Goonies 2 on Nintendo?
No, it doesn't exist.
For those that are-
She turned into a fucking mermaid!
Come on, it does not exist!
For those that, um, I've read online that people think that that song is The Goonies
2 song just lifted from the game.
Okay, I hate to break it to you, but 8-Bit sounded a lot worse than that, so that has
been redone.
Now, to me, not enough in my opinion.
Shut up.
song is to Goonies 2, like Burning Heat was to Gradius 2. To me, that's just kind of the
next chapter of the Burning Heat. It's taken another old school Konami theme and redoing
it. So let's all hope to God that next Mr. T tackles Castlevania 2, because I would poop
my pants.
Oh my God. Here's the thing I've always been pissed off about. Akumaju Dracula immediately
from, what is it, Keyboard Mania 2nd, is like already perfectly suited for Guitar Freaks
and it never showed up.
It's got the, you know, come on man, more Castlevania music in Bimani games, please.
Or Gradius, or Goonies.
Gradius was cool, the music in Gradius was cool.
You know what, that's one thing I have to say I really like about Konami
and that's one reason they're so well suited for DDR
is that their music, typically, is pretty kick-ass.
It's all classic, you know, I can, you can name off, like, any old Konami game
and it's always got good music, even like, uh, what was that, uh, Roller Games, stupid rollerblading or, you know, roller derby type game that they made.
Or yeah, Resh Attack or Metal Gear The Original, they always had pretty good music for like the hardware that they were putting it on.
And yeah, Gradius' music was cool, even the 2DX songs are very good and stuff, but I want Castlevania music.
And if you haven't played it yet, go play the new Castlevania, good stuff, get the soundtrack, it's awesome.
Do they actually have a CD soundtrack for that?
Uh, Japan will, we won't.
Um, the game came out here in America first, and they're gonna release it over there like a month later,
with a CD soundtrack and like tons of frickin collectibles and stuff, cause we don't get that cool stuff over here.
Damn you, Konami of America.
Yeah, here.
We stupid Americans. We not good enough for collector edition.
Let's go to the next song. This is um, I had to play this just because of the name alone
This is a song called pata pata mama. This is the next song we played on that break
What do you think of this one
What do you think of this one now, we know why those school girls jumped in front of the train
that bad huh? I think it's cute in a pop music way and only a way that pop music music can
be that song is cute
pop music belongs in the twilight zone because seriously it has like the worst music ever
and then yet they keep releasing more sequels for it
MURMUR TWINS
the other one was. Yeah, I don't even know what the other one was. Screw that. But yeah,
this is good. DJW is awesome. Murmur Twins, Spica, all the Linus, all the cool stuff he's
done. Murmur Twins has probably always been my favorite of his, so this is pretty cool
that they actually remixed it and such. Just don't do a trance remix of it ever, please.
I imagine that'll probably fit in the next 2DX, because remember how Night Style was
just like remix hell like everything was just remixed and the shit out of it in
night style well I don't know I think DJ W's little forte is using kind of like
keyboards and piano a lot almost like in a song of Kubota ish but not this
classical sounding and so I don't think they would do like a trancy version
really it would I don't know then again moon child is kind of different from his
other stuff, so whatever.
You know what, actually my mom and dad were going to give me an old car of theirs too
when I got my license, only we had a big flood and it drowned.
It drowned.
The car drowned.
Oh.
Yeah, so I'm just bitter.
Don't listen to me.
Maybe you shouldn't have living cars anymore then.
No, my car, it died and when you turn the key in it won't start anymore because there's
mud everywhere.
You shouldn't drive the car into the river again then.
I did not drive the car into the river.
My dad parked it near a creek, which is typical because there is a parking lot next to the
creek.
What do you do in the parking lot?
You park your car.
That's what he did.
No, he did not park his car in the creek.
He parked his car next to the creek and then it rained like what?
eight inches in twenty four hours or something fucking crazy
no this was in nineteen ninety five when california had those huge floods like
president clinton came out here and everything
and the car just floated away
too bad the floods didn't sweep him away
i cried but my car now is cool
actually the the car was supposed to have was a ford explorer
it was a ninety two ford explorer
and my friend my friends and i always called it the jurassic park car because it was the same car
they used in jurassic park and
You know, we always used to get in the car and go...
I know, we were dorks. What can I say?
No, actually, it never got old.
Kill yourself now. Awful.
I hope a dinosaur eats you while you're on the crapper.
Oh, Jurassic Park 4 was awesome.
There was no Jurassic Park 4, yet.
Yeah, there was no Jurassic Park board.
That's what's so great about it.
Yeah.
They're making one so far.
I know, I know.
But I do, I miss my car.
You know, whenever I think about my car, I get all nostalgic.
Why do you have this?
Are you a closet Jurassic Park fan? Do you like dinosaurs? Pink dinosaurs?
No, I just happen to like John Williams.
Welcome to ten years ago.
I happen to like John Williams, is that so wrong?
I reorganized my MP3 collection not too long ago.
That's right, John Williams is one of the greatest composers ever.
They are really making a Jurassic Park 4 though, you do know.
You do know this, because Jurassic Park 3 did really, really well.
So, of course, there will be a Jurassic Park 4.
did well, I didn't know anybody who saw it. Really. I would only see it because William
H. Macy is in it, that's all. What the hell? What is this showing? What is that? Are they
See raccoons?
Hold on, get this on the mic.
Is this Satan worshipping?
This is weird, it sounds like Silent Hill music.
Excuse me.
I'm dying.
Too much nostalgia is bad for me.
Anyway, why don't you post a link to that badger thing in the chat room, so if they...
Oh, did they get...
Oh, okay.
Oh, somebody else put it in there.
I see.
Okay.
Oh, I see what happened.
It's all Wampa's fault.
I get it.
All right.
Do the badgers ever do anything other than just stand there and dance?
No, they just badger.
Oh, they just badger.
That's cute.
Random snake.
That's good.
Random Snake.
Okay.
Now this is a part of the show where we usually like to kick off the show with this, but you
know, we're a little late tonight.
Oh, well.
I thought we'd play a little bit of How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day.
This is the part of the show where we go around and ask everybody, how was your week, how
was your day, Loki?
How was your week, how was your day?
I think that mic is off, Logie.
I think you're disconnected then, because I'm not hearing it.
Damn you. There we go. All right. How was your week? How was your day, Logie?
I had bacon grease in my hands.
Anyways, um...
Let's see. The only thing worth mentioning this week is I went and saw Matrix Revolutions.
It was okay. It was good.
And I went and saw Elf yesterday.
That was good.
And it looks like a movie that's going to be really manipulative,
though.
It's going to have one of those crybaby endings, and like,
family, feel good, family fun.
OK.
I don't know what it is with people making Christmas movies
and thinking that at the end of every Christmas movie
has to be, for some reason, you have to get the Christmas spirit
and then everything is message.
It's like, the whole movie was good until they threw out, like,
Oh, everyone must believe in Santa or else Christmas will not be saved!
You know, it's just so awful that they do stuff like that, but the rest of the movie
is awesome.
Yeah, why don't they make movies about real life, you know, like some people don't get
to have Christmas because they're so poor and they don't get to eat like once a week
and stuff, and you know, that's a nice uplifting Christmas story.
I like it, they had a part in it.
Okay, what about the Jews?
I don't know.
We'll go see the movie.
They had a part in the movie, though, where he's talking to Santa.
He's like, there's been rumors going around
that parents are telling their children,
or that people are believing that their parents are putting
the presents under the tree, and they're all,
how is that possible?
How would they even be able to do that in one night?
He's like, I know.
And they're all, then what about the cookies?
Do they think that they eat the cookies, too?
I guess so.
They just said it so sarcastically, it was funny.
Because there was no Santa Claus!
Thank you, thank you, Loki, ruining Christmas everywhere.
I'm not gonna go and let my kids believe that there's this fake Santa Claus or Easter Bunny.
I'm gonna let them, I'm gonna make it a little more realistic for them.
That mom and dad have to take out another loan on the house because you want your fucking
presents you little brats.
This is a fun little side topic, I want to pose this question to everybody in here.
How old were you when you found out there was no Santa Claus, and how did you react?
Loki, how old were you when you found out there was no Santa Claus and how did you react?
Oh damn, I don't even remember. I just don't think I cared, so I was getting presents anyways.
But, um, I don't know.
Alright, bad.
I think it was like four or five, you know, as far as I can remember, and I reacted pretty
well.
I was like, oh, cool, a new four-in-a-row hidden in my mom's closet.
So I took it pretty well.
Vandalous?
What are you guys talking about?
There's no Santa Claus.
What are you talking about, man?
I know it's like a big joke, isn't it?
Yeah, it's a joke.
That's what we do on the radio.
We kid.
I kid.
Anyways, I actually found out because my parents told me they got tired of trying to play it
off like there was, and so they said, hey, you know what, we just put the presents under
the tree for you.
So I'm kind of jaded about that kind of thing.
So that's why my kids don't think there's a Santa Claus either, because that's all kind
of, he's a silly little red elf.
I was about to say, since you actually have kids who are the age where they could, they're
not babies, they're toddlers now, and they're thinking about Santa Claus and all that, did
you try the Santa Claus thing with him or did you just say, screw it, you know what
kids, I'm going to tell you a secret, the other kids are going to try to feed you the
Santa crap?
That's pretty essentially it, we told them, you know, he's a funny little elf, who just,
people look like him at the malls, he doesn't do anything for you, and we just go ahead
and let them know we give him the presents and things like that.
Same with the Easter Bunny, same with the Tooth Fairy.
All he does is beg for money to give to the Red Cross, that greedy bastard.
Will, I know you're the youngest one here, but the news has been broken, yes?
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding.
Of course.
How old were you and how did you react?
I don't know.
I was probably like nine or ten.
I can't really remember.
Oh, presents.
You didn't care because you were still getting presents?
Yeah.
It wasn't a huge shock.
I mean, by that age it's not very believable anymore, anyways.
I see.
The logistics of it just is what clued me in on it.
I'm like, how can a fat fuck fit down this goddamn chimney anyways?
Oh, he uses his magic powers.
Oh, yeah, magic powers.
Isn't that convenient?
All right, Bradley, want to share?
I don't really remember.
It was probably around five or six, maybe.
My sister told me and I said, oh, okay.
I don't think I was really shocked.
That sounds very like you, Bradley, where you just would have been, oh, okay.
I'm kind of surprised by that.
You didn't become emotional?
I was five years old when I found out because my mom just started putting the presents under
the tree that said, from Santa, under the tree on the 23rd because she was just getting
lazy and she didn't want to play the game anymore.
I was kind of like, why does Santa and you
have the same handwriting?
And she'd just ignore me.
How come the presents are under the tray on the 23rd?
How come the cookies are still gone
and we have to leave them out on the 24th?
How come the reindeer hooves look just like the rabbit hooves?
Because I was totally that kind of kid,
where whenever anybody would try to tell me something,
I'd be all, why, why, why?
I was that annoying little shit.
One note I did.
Why?
I was real into spying and all that cool shit.
So what I had is I had ultraviolet pens, and I marked all the packages that were hidden
in the closet to prove or not if they were from Santa or whatever, because they weren't
marked who they were for or who they were from, so you get the from Santa ones and you
take my little ultraviolet light and you're like, HA!
HA!
You tried to trick me?
Ah, you saw right through it.
Low-key, ever-the-conspiracy-theorist.
Oh my God.
My parents used to leave the tags on the presents because they wanted to be able to return them.
When I saw that Santa Claus shopped at the commissary on base, wow, he really saved some
money doing that.
I thought he made them.
That's a nice revelation there.
Santa's military.
I didn't know that.
What a nice sweater from Santa.
I didn't know Santa's workshop was called Mervin's.
kostjamrh And why isn't Santa contributing to the US economy? If he's using all this
elf labor and stuff, do they have unions? Because he's making a lot of knock-off goods and stuff
and selling them, calling them name-brand.
p0k3smot42o you can't find a fucking place to park at the north pole on a saturday
Thanks to piracy!
Thanks to piracy, because all those methods that they put watermarking the god damn film
and checking people's bags and stuff, you can see it's totally put a stop to piracy.
You know what, it's one of those things where I wanted to try it before I buy it, and I
tried it, and I've decided, you know what, I think I'll just watch the other half at
home.
You know, here's what it is, it's like, I'm sorry, I don't want to go to the theater and
pay $18 every time I go see a movie. I'm going to watch it once in the theater, so I remember.
You pay for your date? Yeah. Wow. You guys are going to hell. You're stealing from people
who work hard to give you this stuff and you're just like, stealing it. You know what, I saw
Kill Bill three times in the theater to make up for it, so... But that place is not going
to the Wachowski Brothers, or Warner Brothers Entertainment for Warner Brothers.
They've made almost $1 billion on the franchise. They can go to hell. I don't really care.
And they spent about $1 billion making the second and third movies.
Think of all the starving children that could have fed.
yeah like Keanu Reeves
yeah I think of all the acting classes he could have gone into his own
oh that's funny
well if anything I want to see the Wachowski brothers take on Bill and Ted three
okay
that's what they need to make
that's all that he's good at
just bring it back, bring it back to old school
yeah seriously just have it like
Bill and Ted do something you know
three
but anyways um...
So what else did I do? Oh, I made two more remixes. The only one was tonight. And I did
a live show last night, an impromptu livewire show at like one in the morning. And that
was cool because I was bored. And I took the chat room and then thinking I was a person
called Death By Syrup from Canada.
And they should have known right there that that was your super bacon right there. Because
that was the bacon you made tonight, right?
No, well, I got the syrup idea from seeing Elf because he, like, would drink syrup, so...
No, that's good. Syrup shots, man, I want to do some of those.
Oh my God, we did that at, um, in LA. Yeah, we went to Roscoe's Chicken and Waffles.
It was right after Cyber Zone, the big tournament there. A bunch of us went over to Roscoe's
Chicken and Waffle, and, uh, it was like, what, me, Brad, Irene, Mel B, who else was
at our table? Tons of, uh, Bay Area people. But it was mostly our table that did the syrup
You, me, Irene, Fury, Wendell, Mandy, they give you these little shot glasses full of
syrup and warm syrup to put on your waffles and chicken.
Nice warm gooey bottle of soup.
The thing is, since it's warm, if you've ever cooked soup or something that's thick, when
you're heating it up, it starts to create a film on top, like it's kind of hard.
That's what happened to this syrup, so you had the nice little, it's almost like a tequila
a Loki so he can finish telling us about his weakness day.
in
yeah
that's it i'm done
all right uh... i guess i'll ask brad since you know he kept putting in on
that last one how are you how's your day you already know
but listeners don't like they care okman
i went out and last week i believe it was one hour and
use my wonderful city critic card and bought
a PS2, an American one, because I haven't had one for the longest time, I only had a Japanese one.
So I got that, and Castlevania, because I was fiending, I had to finish Castlevania, because I've been bumming it off of you guys here.
I want to loan it to me.
That's alright, I had to buy it. Matt's saying he'd loan it to me, but that's fine.
So I bought it, and finished it up, I beat it pretty much every different way you can, except for crazy mode, because it's crazy and whatnot.
I beat it with the two hidden characters, like four hours is all it took me to beat it with the second hidden character, and three hours is all it took me for the first hidden character. You can go through it so freaking fast.
Anyhow, so, got that. I've got a job interview tomorrow, so I will have a life for once! Finally! Yay for me!
Congratulations.
Yeah, I'm gonna work for the man, so
And that's pretty much it we had
friend over from
Old-school friend over for you know the weekend and watched movies and and you got the strangers with candy DVDs, so we watched that
You know oh my god
Please I this is my highest recommendation
I could ever give a DVD go out and buy the strangers with candy season 1 and season 2 box sets
I almost peed my pants at that episode we watched last night.
Oh my god, that was one of the most disturbing things I've done before.
It was the most morbid thing I think I've ever seen on a broadcast television show.
Well, it's cable, whatever, basic cable.
But still.
It was great. It was great.
I don't even want to describe it because I don't want to ruin it, but one of the funniest shows I've ever seen.
Strainers of Candy. Go buy the first episode.
We'll watch it after tonight's show. We'll watch that episode because it's just great.
I had to go to the bathroom from laughing so hard after the ending of that one.
Yeah, it was like two or three in the morning, and you're like waking up our neighbor.
I have an infectious laugh, what can I say?
Eddie was pretty loud too when he laughed, though.
I love Eddie's laugh.
I'm sure we'll talk about this later.
I wish Eddie was here tonight so I can make him laugh so you guys could hear, because
I love his laugh.
I'm sure we'll talk about this later, but we also sang karaoke.
Yeah, we'll get to that.
We'll get to that.
Yeah, well, that's a good topic right there.
Next, next segment, we'll get to that.
Yes.
I'm awful.
So am I, but anyway.
Okay.
Anything else you want to say about your weekend weekend?
Um, I started playing Final Fantasy X because I am way freaking behind.
All you people who have played it already, good for you.
So.
I, I quit.
Final Fantasy XI's taken over.
I can't go back to Final Fantasy X now.
Yeah.
Hey, if I had Final Fantasy XI, I'd be playing that too, so.
But I don't, because I've got no money, so I'll just play Final Fantasy X.
10 until I beat it. Good stuff. And then I got to pick Kingdom Hearts, because I'm way
behind on that too.
Remind me, I've got to give that to you before you go.
Yes, give it to me.
Give it to me now!
Give it to me in the butt.
Ew.
Anyway.
Okay.
Stick your keyblade in my butt.
Anyway, is that it?
What else happened? Did we do anything else?
Not that I remember. I mean, we didn't do Vanilla Sky this week. We took a week off
of vanilla sky and by the way on a rerun of vanilla sky had our highest listener count
ever on the show and it wasn't even on the right night that's why i know jamie's show
whoops mine in the ratings because we moved to tuesday for a night through the roof there's
a little ego stroking for jamie yeah jamie if you're out there listening wait is somebody
asking me um if i'm gonna play x2 or is somebody asking somebody else um well let's let's pretend
they're asking you that you want to play phone se x2 i was not interested at all when i saw
I saw this, I was like, what the hell, let's just make the three main characters girls
that dress weirdly and stuff.
But after reading about it and how they're going to have a job system and stuff like
that, it sounds interesting.
I still, since I haven't gone through Final Fantasy X yet, I don't understand what the
connection is, but I noticed a lot of the characters are missing from Final Fantasy
X.
Yeah, and they can kiss my bad ass for not having Lulu a playable character.
Well Lulu's going to be in it, but she's not a playable character.
Fuck that.
What I'm pissed off is, where's Oren?
And don't say, I know people are probably going to sit there in the chat room and spoil
it for me, because you guys all suck.
Yeah, remember, Brad and I have not beat Final Fantasy X yet, I've picked up on some things
that might be happening, but let's not spoil, okay?
I don't know.
So I will play it, if you were asking me.
If you weren't asking me, I don't fucking care.
Fuck you.
I'll tell you my opinion anyway.
Sorry.
I'm really not this angsty and all that, but it's okay.
No, you are.
Fuck you!
See?
Please.
Alright, Will, how you doing? Slinky wizard? Are you still slinky wizard, or just slinky
now?
Whatever.
Such an apathetic little teen you are, go ahead.
I don't care anymore, it doesn't matter.
Will, how was your week, how was your day?
Well, high school. Yeah, high school is high school, and high school sucks.
And, you know, on Tuesday I got my license, barely.
Missed 11.
Oh yeah.
Hey, what score is that, 89?
I think the most you miss is like 13 or 15.
Oh.
Yeah.
Wait, on the written test?
The driving test.
Really?
God.
You used to be able to get a 70 and still pass because I got an 80.
Yeah.
They're evil.
I got a B- in driving.
I got like a 70.
I got like the lowest you can get.
Here's what happened.
I got a, let's see how we did this.
I got knocked off probably four points.
I probably would have had like a 90-something.
And I finished the entire test, and I parked.
And I parked like shit.
I parked all crooked and stuff.
And I didn't take any points off that.
And we're right about to go inside and get my license,
because I got like a 90-something percent.
And he's like, actually, you didn't move your head enough.
and then knocks off like 20 points. I was like...
Was he just mad because you weren't moving your head up and down his crotch?
I wasn't moving my head like this, and this is only for the people in the studio because
you guys, you know, over there can't hear it.
You can kind of see on the cam.
But I was moving my head like this because you have to look, you know, you have to look
down a street when you drive through an intersection, you need to look down both sides. I was moving
my head like this. He wanted me to move my head like this. You know, apparently, and...
Did you take it at Florin or something?
Did you take it at Lauren Mall?
weekend, and trying to cause trouble, and stuff like that. So, fun stuff.
Alright. That's about it.
Alright, cool deal. Have you played AMDDR at all lately?
I know I haven't. No, actually, no. We went on Thursday, and I did play two games. I'm
working on my doubles. For some reason, I'm in this mood where, like, I have to play doubles.
But enough about me. What about you?
Yeah, I went Saturday morning, just for the hell of it.
Yeah, I haven't been in a while, so I was sore.
Do you find that when you haven't played in a while, like when you start playing those caddos back to back, you're like...
Yeah.
Because that's me.
Smoker.
Smokers.
Well...
Yeah.
Did you take up smoking?
No.
Oh, okay.
I would compare it to that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
And then if you are a smoker, it's like twice as bad.
I see Terry sitting on the computer, so I'll go to Bradley, if we can get a mic over to
Bradley. Can we get a mic over to Bradley? Bradley, how was your week and how was your
your day? Mostly blah, of course, as usual. Monday was not much. Tuesday I called a temp
agency and set up an appointment. Wednesday I did more crap. Thursday I went to this temp
agency, basically an accounting-type temp agency, maybe find a data entry job or something
of that sort. I did well enough on their excel test. He basically gave me the advanced accounting
test instead of the basic one they were supposed to give me. I did well enough on that even
though I had studied accounting terms the day before. He also gave me an excel test
so he said, hey, you did well enough on this. Why don't you go take the certification? So
I took that and passed that. So we certified down for the general, like the specialist
And then Friday I didn't do much of anything. I set up eBay auctions and such. Then Saturday
I went and saw The Matrix and Davis and watched The Matrix. I was sort of just sitting there
watching it. I don't know if I was really paying attention to it. I was just like, ooh,
pretty things, like ships flying around. The action scenes are good, but the dialogue scenes
are kind of stupid. So, I sort of liked it and sort of didn't like it. And then today,
more crap. And that's basically everything.
Let's go over to Terry and see how your week was.
Hello, my week has been very busy.
Hey look, there's boobies on the web cam.
Boobies on cam!
And how that's possible when there's no women here tonight, I have no idea, but go ahead.
Brad stop showing the boobies.
Okay, I've been very busy at work.
I'm going to bore you guys on my work, bullcrap, because that's what I'm dealing with is hiring
new people and being in a new organization and fun stuff like that.
I watched Matrix Revolutions, if you don't see my LJ, which is Vandalous.LiveJournal.com.
Oh, nice plug.
Hey, thank you.
And that is, we watched IMAX, or Revolutions on IMAX.
Ah, how was that?
It was freaking unbelievable.
I bet.
I bet even a shit movie would be great on IMAX.
The Defense of Zion, if you've seen this movie and you watch it on a regular show, on a regular
screen, and you go watch it on IMAX, it just blows you away.
The Defense of Zion is unbelievable on that screen.
I bet.
Anyways, the other kind of cool thing about going down there was, we had one of my friends'
roommates go with us, and he's a guy that'll do anything if you start giving him a little
alcohol.
Oh goody.
And so, this guy's about 240 pounds, about 5'7", he's got about the geekiest glasses
you can find, and they got him to take two triple shots of tequila, and so his ears were
pretty red.
Of course he's over 21 and all that, this is completely legal.
And he proceeded to, they convinced him to take off his shirt.
This is Gordon Biersch.
Oh my!
You know where Gordon Biersch is?
On San Francisco.
It's right on the corner from Barcadero and Harrison, which is right by the piers.
And we took a box out of a trash can, he took off his shirt and proceeded to belly flop
it for us.
There was a nice light rail going by, it was about 3 o'clock in the afternoon in San Francisco
on a Wednesday.
And so we needed webcams because we really wanted to capture this and put this on eBay.
He would have been the next Star Wars kid, but we were unable to do that.
I'm sure someone will post a link to Star Wars Kid if someone starts asking questions.
Oh my God.
Other than that, my week has been just busy with work stuff and everything and family
stuff and home stuff and boring stuff.
But I managed to make it here because I'm a day shifter next week.
I work nights and so I work 11 p.m. to 8 a.m., if you can imagine that, the vampire shift.
My older roommate used to work at vampire shifts, but it was at Wal-Mart.
It wasn't a job nearly as cool as yours.
It was enjoyable.
I got to, you know, I like working nights and everything.
It's nice.
But I've got to be on day shift all this week because I've got to hire somebody and do all
that fun stuff.
I got you.
Anyways, that's about it.
Boring.
No, it's good to have you here.
Well, thank you.
I'm glad that they switched you to day shift so we could get a chance to have you here,
I am glad for our own selfish reasons we finally got you on the show.
Thank you.
I am glad to be here.
As far as my week and my day, nothing too exciting.
Thursday went out to golf land and I have been working on my doubles game.
I noticed there was one high score list for one of the doubles that had no scores on it.
I thought I would play just to get my name on it.
That was kind of funny.
My ego talking there.
and um...
What else did I do this week? Not really a whole heck of a lot, but I've been playing a lot of Final Fantasy 11
Shane, if you're out there, hello, he says, my buddy out in Kansas, we've been playing Final Fantasy 11
like non-stop through the thing
and the nice thing is we've been using this program TeamSpeak
Vandalus, you're a big multiplayer game player, you probably know about this one, right?
TeamSpeak, the one that allows you
it basically turns your computer into Xbox Live, where you can use the microphone to talk to
people and stuff like that, so it's cool
it's been working out good for Final Fantasy XI.
I know I haven't really gone into too much detail about Final Fantasy XI yet, that's
because I still, even after two weeks of playing the game, I still feel like I have not scratched
the surface.
There's just so much more to discover in the game, and it's just so vast, there's so much
to it.
It's unlike any other Final Fantasy game, I still say it's kind of odd that they chose
to go with Final Fantasy XI as opposed to Final Fantasy Online, but other than that,
I mean, the game's terrific, it's just not what a lot of you are going to expect.
So that was pretty much my week and my day.
I didn't get to go see any cool movies or anything.
Last night, I hung out with the out of town buddy who was here, played a lot of Karaoke
Revolution and iToy, the new webcam tool for the PS2 is out, and we've been playing iToy
a lot.
And those of you that sit in our chat room during the week saw a random webcam was up
You save it as a file, and then you upload it as an attachment to your email through broadband.
You get what I'm saying?
Wow.
And then you would download it to your memory card using whatever software they have for the PS2.
I don't really know.
And then that way you can say, hey, fuck you, and then there will be an attachment.
Can you imagine the social hacking you can do with that by convincing these kids,
These kids say, hey, turn on your camera and click on this really cool link.
And all of a sudden you can get all kinds of really fun voyeur stuff going on in the
house.
I'm being kind of sick.
My friends actually told me about that, not me, sorry.
Live triple X iToy, people having sex and stuff in rooms with the little bubbles and
stuff floating around and you're popping them.
Let's go out to the street and find a couple of whores and make the first iToy porn.
No.
Remember how they have the little rainbow feature and stuff?
The guy does the cum shot and is all rainbow-y behind it.
How about Itoy Fight Club?
Now see, somebody's telling me that the longest you can do a video on Itoy is one minute.
You know what?
One minute's long enough for some guys.
That's a money shot.
We can not only invent a new form of internet porn, we can invent a whole new porn genre.
one minute porn film in segments just like you know like 24 you know where
it's like five second segments or whatever we really need Brad and he's
not here to be able to provide some commentary to us that's all right he'll
we can we can ask him later if we remember angels got a good comparison
though she says I toy reminds her of when you remember the old game show Nick
arcade that they would go inside the game and they'd have to do some kind of
stupid thing inside the game. She says the iToy totally reminds her of that and I think
she's right on the money. I think that's a damn good comparison. The iToy is like the
last level of Nick Arcade. Wouldn't you say so, Loki?
Well, if by making that comparison, if you're saying it looks like bumbling idiots playing
the game, yes, that would be a perfect comparison. All right. Okay, so I think what we're going
to do now is we're going to go ahead and take a break. We're going to do some more pop and
music part 10 music and when we come back we're going to talk about karaoke revolutions
all the rage this week. We're going to have to give our thoughts on that and the cage
match too when we come back. In this break from the pop and 10 music soundtrack you're
going to hear the new revenge song. Yes, Naoki's little pseudonym revenge has a new song on
music 10 break. You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio. We'll be back.
Hey!
This is the end of the video, if you like it, please subscribe to my channel.
Oh
No shit, don't see me, bye, bye, bye
Where there's nothing on the way, oh you're there
To be thoughts when they're dead
Time has come now
We must go back there now
To save the place where we end up and die
Out in the sky
To the rest we can fly
For the light
Change is still a legend
Keep your peace and send it
Evil beckons to the night
This is the end of all
Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because Real Radio makes Captain Jack cry.
Hello, and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
Some more music in that break from the Pomp and Music 10 soundtrack.
What did you guys think of some of those songs here?
Let's start off with the Revenge track.
It was Ara Bhatia. What did you guys think of that one?
This is interesting. It sounds just like a God of Death info with fucking Max Unlimited samples.
Seriously, they need to get away from Max Unlimited.
Let the max die, step away from the max.
Yeah, good stuff. It's exotic ethnic, which is already good, so good stuff.
Whatever, if they want to use samples from another song, it's fine with me.
I mean, all these popular European and American DJs constantly use samples.
Yeah, but they use good samples. That's such a bad sample.
That sample right there makes me really pissed off at the song.
Just like the ending of Matrix Revolutions, how they fucked up that song and made fun
of the Hindus and stuff.
It makes me hate the movie.
God, some people.
You know...
I haven't even seen the movie yet, so I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about.
What kind of irks me about the...
It's a decent song.
It's kind of fun.
It's one of the better songs on the soundtrack, but I still picture Revenge as always doing
these DDR songs and stuff, and there's no kind of backbeat to it, so I can't imagine
myself dancing to it, and for some reason that makes me not like it.
It's much more well-suited for 2DX than it is for BAG, but anyhow, that's fine.
Revenge has always been Naoki trying to attempt to do ethnic sounding music, and that's fine
if it doesn't have a beat.
That's why it's in Papa Music and not DDR, whatever.
The next song was from a group called Komo Tomak, and it's the genre of lonely, and it's
Artemis.
And there's actually a long version of this on the Papa Music 10 soundtrack.
Any thoughts on that?
Where's Luna?
And Sailor Moon and Sailor Mercury.
so funny. I want to see it. It's so cheesy. It's as he says, ill-conceived. It can't be
better than Strangers with Candy, though. Oh, well, no. It's not trying to be funny.
No. It's funny because it's stupid. I thought you were telling me that the people that translated
it or did the fan sub or whatever, that they tried to make it funny. They skipped. They
did some parody. They left in some commercials that are showing over in Japan, like a McDonald's
commercial with this Japanese Ronald McDonald and they they left in the
commercials and they did a little parody fan sub to it like the McDonald's one
shows the Ronald McDonald coming over and helping this little girl play with
their friends because no one was like playing with her so she goes and plays
with her and at the end it's got a little monologue by by Ronald McDonald
and he says something Japanese I don't understand Japanese I don't know what he's
saying but the subtitle says I'll always be watching you especially when you're
And then there's this other one where it's like these girls in panties, little girls
wearing diapers, and it's a diaper commercial or something, and it says,
Pansufaito!
And at the end it goes, it goes, buy these panties guaranteed pre-worn by a petalicious
girl just like this one.
It's so great!
Or the Sailor Moon memorabilia they sell, like these wands and stuff.
Oh yeah, but they sell the memorabilia and it's like, what does he say, buy our Sailor
Moon toys so you can transform, just like Sailor Moon.
And then at the end it goes, successful transformation, not guaranteed.
Or the Hello Kitty one where it's like, hello kitty, hello kitty, or it's like, I don't
know, something Nick, hello kitty, hello kitty.
the bottom it says evil kitty, evil kitty, evil kitty, and then it's like buy evil kitty
mind control candy so we can control your kids and stuff like that. It's great.
The last song we heard in that break was Sastro with Holy Forest.
What did you think of that? Holy Forest, Batman.
It's very J-Rock to me.
I picture G.A.C.T. and ambiguous men singing high-pitched songs.
It sounds to me like a melismizer thing, which is what G.A.C.T. is from.
Good stuff.
I'm not quite sure how it will play on pop music, but we'll see when it comes out here
or not here for home.
Interesting point you brought up when we were listening to the soundtrack last night was
I hear this with 2DX, but you said that you hear a lot of songs in pop music that really
are better suited for guitar freaks.
Almost like they didn't make the cut for guitar freaks, but they really should have.
That song strikes me as one of those.
Or the good, cool, and Jeff Kootz song, Blaster.
Which we'll hear later.
We're going to hear some Taka and some Tack and Desro too.
Oh, the Des-Q song.
Yeah, the Des-Q.
The Desro with DJ Taka.
I mean, not DJ Taka.
Tack.
And, um, yeah, like, these songs should really be on Guitar Cookies and Drummania if they're continuing to make these games.
I mean, why put, whatever, I don't know.
Konami's kind of losing their mind.
So, whatever.
Okay.
Alright, so that was the music in a Popin' 10 soundtrack, and we'll do some more later,
but first, this is all the rage this week. Out now, just came out this week, a brand
new Bomani game. Something brand new, and it's not in the arcades, it's only for the
home, and America, shock, got it first. Because the Japanese are getting a better version,
but that's alright, America got something first. We got some new Bomani, and yes, it
actually carries a Bomani logo, so this is an official new Bomani game, so we can talk
I'm sure you've heard about it by now.
Karaoke Revolution, out this week.
What are your guys' impressions of Karaoke Revolution?
First, does somebody want to try and describe the game?
Because I know not even all of us here have played it yet,
but does somebody want to try and describe the game?
Like how it plays?
Yeah, how it plays.
Because I think a lot of people still haven't gotten how it works yet.
You want to try and explain it, Brad?
First you go to the store and you shell out $70.
Okay, after that.
Then you bring it home and you look at it, you ooble it, you rattle it, you get a microphone-headset combination like what Britney Spears and Madonna uses.
You put this thing on and you go into it.
You pick levels, you pick a song and you pick a level and it's got a crowd of people.
There's a band behind you, there's a character you pick who dances and they're over-developed in the head.
head, and they sing, and at the bottom is, like, you know, if anybody's ever seen karaoke,
words go by, or usually words are there, and then they light up as you're supposed to sing.
Yeah, the words, like, do this whole screen full of words.
Yeah, except with this, at the very bottom, there's, like, a rectangular section, takes
up probably a third of the screen, or a quarter of the screen at the bottom, that has the
words that go from right to left. They scroll across the screen.
It's like watching the news on CNN and the words throw by on the bottom.
And on the left is a line similar to any beat mania or DDR, it's a judgment line where you
have to start here.
And then from the top to the bottom where the words are, are lines of how long you're
supposed to hold a note.
And they move up, they go up and down depending on if the note should be high or low or whatnot.
And some of the notes, and I'm not going to sing, but they'll go like, mmm, they'll rise.
You'll see the little line go up or down.
So you kind of have to follow the tone of it.
It just judges on the tone of it.
So you can pretty much make up any word you want or go la la la la, or like I did for
It's the End of the World.
Instead of doing the rap thing that he does, I go da da da da da, land on Burt Stein.
The whole thing and I got it.
It's the only part of that rap I know is,
Na-na-na, na-na-na, Leonard Bernstein.
Exactly.
And it is so much fun.
This is like the newest and best party game.
They were right.
I was kind of like, hmm, I don't know,
when they were saying that it was going to be this big hit.
But as soon as we turned this on, I was like, oh my god,
this has so much possibility in America.
I never thought I would hear you sing,
but this game finally got it.
Well, I tried it, and I realized, like I thought
before that I can't sing.
So I just started to fuck around.
I started like saying.
Pretty good!
Fuck this game, this game fucking sucks, and it would still judge me right, so I was like
cool!
Because it just grades on tone, and if it sounds like, because you can put lead vocals
on where they have a pre-recorded, it's not the original artist, but a lead, a person
singing along, if that's on and that person is singing really high, you can drop your
octave and it still grades, because it's got a pretty sophisticated tone recognition system
in it.
It's really good.
So, good stuff.
really funny to see because each song only has the lead vocals is only sung in
the gender of the person who originally wrote the song or sang the song so like
hmm let's see here the Madonna song what which one is it like a virgin like a
virgin is sung in it by a girl and if you pick a male character they're up on
the screen singing and there's a female voice coming out of their mouth and
their lips are synced to the singing so it's really funny to watch like this
black guy get up there and go like, La, la, la, la, like a virgin, ooh, ooh, ooh, it's
good stuff.
I have to agree, this is a great game.
I was really skeptical about it at first, but it's fucking great.
It's a great idea.
My only kind of, I have a couple of concerns with it though.
I mean, it's a great game, great party game, but as a solo game, it's not something I could
see myself kind of motivating myself to do solo.
So it will, whereas DDR will not make you a better dancer, Karaoke Revolution will make
you a better singer.
Maybe.
I don't know yet.
It'll help, it helps show you if you're on key or not, A. B, it helps you to kind of
hold your pitch and maintain your pitch.
That's the biggest thing about it, is it really, really the way you get better at singing is
by singing more and more.
So Karaoke Revolution will help you be a better singer.
It won't turn you into an all-star, but it will help you go from not so great, but to
decent.
Well, see, on the songs that it's got on there, it will point out to you that, hey, you're
not supposed to sing the song this certain way.
It actually shows you the way the song is supposed to be sung.
For most parts, I noticed that in some of the songs, it looks like they programmed the
lines in, the grading in, like maybe a little different than the original singer sang it.
I got kind of confused on some of the songs, I was like, wait a minute, the line is going
up, or it stays straight when the singer is actually raising their pitch or lowering it
and whatnot.
The biggest thing I don't like about it is that it's coded, the lines that go by that
you're supposed to sing are coded in only one way, so you can only sing the song in
one way as far as your tone.
You can't improvise, you can improvise words, unless you play non-judge mode.
There is a free mode that you're not judged.
And you say you're not judged, so it's almost like not even really worth playing.
It's like, might as well just sing along to any song.
I wish that they had kind of like an edit mode where you can edit the lines in any way
you wanted to.
Like say you sang it without lines, and it would record those lines as you're singing
it.
Like an edit mode.
Like an edit mode for steps.
That's kind of weird, okay.
Like one person in the back, you'll hear somebody yell, you rock!
It's really funny.
You have to listen for the small things in Character Evolution.
I think it's advertisement for the Matrix, though, because most of the people in the
crowd are all agents.
They all look exactly the same, wearing the same thing.
Yes.
For the best, when you suck, they start walking away.
And then if you totally fail the song, your person breaks down and cries on the stage.
They fall to the ground.
It's great.
What do you think of the song list?
I've heard some complaints, and this is kind of one of my chief complaints, it's kind of
not enough songs, but all things considered, they only licensed 35 songs or whatever.
There are 35 pretty solid songs, they have a pretty damn good mix of music in it, I think.
I think there's at least one, two songs that everybody's going to dig.
Like when we fired it up and Broken Wings was in it, Loki was like, oh my God, cool.
Yeah, exactly.
are some great classics in this. I mean, some of the best classic 80s music and some of
the better pop music, because I'm not a big fan of pop, you know, but some of the better
pop music in here. I'm kind of a mild fan of Top 40 pop. There's
a lot of it I don't like, but there's a lot of it I do like, and I was really happy to
see that there were a couple of Michelle Branch songs in there, because I dig her and stuff.
They have some good... Yeah, actually, I think they did a very good
job in the song selection except for, and I understand the reason why they did this,
I think, if it's the same reason I'm thinking, putting in songs like Son of a Preacher or
whatever.
You know, whatever it's called.
You are still mad that you got the Chain of Fools song on random last night.
You are still mad you had to sing that last night.
Like they put some really stupid songs in, but that's just my opinion.
I know there are people out there that love these songs, these are classics.
I understand the purpose, it's just like, what?
I don't want to sing to the pool.
There's going to be just as many songs that you hate as there are going to be that you
love.
There's less songs that I hate than there are songs that I like.
And like Bazaar and Love Triangle, it was like, oh my God.
Yeah, some of the great 80s songs like Bazaar and Love Triangle, there was some other ones,
but there's some good songs in there.
Pardon me for saying, but they've done a better job licensing music for Karaoke Revolution
than they have for DDR.
For anything they've ever done.
revolution than they have for DDR for anything they've ever done this is it's
good stuff and and I just hope that we get some good expansion discs here in
America because yes there will be expansion discs because in the options
menu if you go to an options menu in the game there is an option to put in an
expansion disc if you hit the option that the machine will eject and it just
like a pen mode in DDR just like that I hope there's some really good stuff on
the expansion. If it's anything like what they released on the core mix that they just
released, then we've got some good music coming out for the expansion.
It really depends, I think, on how this game takes off. If it's really popular, if it goes
DDR style, then I think we'll see really specialized discs where it's going to be like women hits
of the 90s type thing, expansion discs, then male hits of the 90s type thing.
It's all dependent on how they advertise this thing, and Konami in America has not been
been known for the best advertising campaigns, so it's, well, UltraMix, Microsoft is backing
it, so it's everywhere.
Yeah, UltraMix has just the Xbox thing, because I think Xbox kind of knows, like Xbox is still
kind of struggling a little bit, and I think they know if they can take the DDR market
a little bit, then they're going to have some more machines being sold.
Unfortunately.
I never, never considered buying an Xbox until UltraMix was announced, and now that I've
I've seen the video which is out on the official site, maybe we'll have to have this later,
but there's a video out on the official site and it's, wow, I'm very impressed that they've
kind of just done what they've needed to do for DDR for a long time.
Give it a facelift.
Yeah.
Something I'm kind of interested in, and I know there's a few other dorky, otaku type
people out there who agree with me, people who listen to J-rock and other Japanese J-pop
and Japanese music, because I solely listen to Japanese stuff because I think America's
making bullshit music right now. There's nothing good out there right now. So I'm listening
to other countries' music and stuff. I hope that the Japanese versions are worthy of bringing
over, well not bringing over here, but for me to import, because there's a lot of J-Rock
and J-Pop songs that I really, really like that I would love to get to play in Karaoke
Revolution, you know? I hope some Lark and Seal stuff shows up, or you know.
I was going to say, in Japan, they are doing karaoke revolution in Japan too, and if you
go to the official karaoke revolution website for Japan, six expansion discs are coming
out this month.
I think later this month.
Six discs, and we're talking, and they kind of do the genre thing a little bit because
there's one that's specifically for ballads, and then there's a couple J-pop hits, and
things like that.
And there are groups, Morning Musume, Ayumi, of course, Ayumi's on there of course.
What were some of the other bands?
You remember any of them, Loki?
I don't know, but...
I just remember Morning Musume.
I can't wait to sing, uh, Chokoto Love, what Petit Love was based off of.
I don't think Chokoto Love was on there.
Really?
No, I don't.
I would have recognized it.
I think.
I may have missed it.
Or the original Freckles Suboxis.
Uh, however you pronounce it.
Yeah.
All right.
That would be great.
Terry, uh, comment?
Oh, actually.
My parents have something that's kind of like this.
It's a, um, this stand-alone DVD karaoke-based thing that does the same kind of thing.
It measures the tone and the timing that you do.
It's got nine DVDs of Korean, Japanese, Filipino, Chinese, and American music.
The DVDs are swappable.
The thing is, it's about $400.
It's totally awesome because every time we go down there, we spend the first day just
doing this thing.
I'm doing gangsters.
It's great because the backgrounds have absolutely nothing to do with the show.
They had Gangsta's Paradise, and the background is showing this peaceful little farm, almost
like it should be Amish Paradise, and it was, it's just great.
That reminds me of when we went to, was it Cyberzone?
Yeah.
And they had the karaoke booth.
Oh my god, the karaoke game?
The karaoke booth?
And they had all these songs you get to play, and it does grade you, but we couldn't figure
out how it grades you, because at the end it would give you like a really high grade.
It just gave you a score, and we didn't, no, because I remember Irene and I found Smile
D.K., Butterfly, and Boyz. We found Smile D.K. in the book, and we're like,
hee hee, we're going to sing the DDR song. And we sang Boyz, and we got 100.
And we got the big fanfare and everything. That's the thing is, I noticed you guys suck,
and you still got high credit. Shut up!
Anyway, well, I mean, I read some of that. Oh my, you don't even want to know how much
time I spent in that stupid karaoke room at the tournament.
I was there, man. You were in there all the time with her. I was like, man, get out of
there. It was so much fun. We had a blast. We were
laughing our ass off in there. Like, the great thing is, just like Terry
This video has nothing to do with anything, it's to throw you off, totally.
Yeah, that's the thing though is that this game if you've any if you've played I don't know about the one that Terry is talking about
But I would assume it's kind of like the one that we saw in cyberzone where it grades you
But this thing is like a really really accurate grading system this karaoke revolution
I was so surprised at how much work they put into it. Why don't they put some more work into DVR like they did this?
Some some other comments from chow and address some comments that came up in the chat room one comment
Why don't you buy karaoke revolution for the Japanese ps2?
So not likely to happen unless they release some kind of American songs expansion pack
because I can't sing in Japanese and I'm not going to just fake it, I mean I don't know
any of the songs.
I don't listen to Jay music as much as Brad does, maybe he would like it, but I just wouldn't
know the songs well enough to necessitate buying it.
I think this is one of those rare cases where the American version has something for me
and the Japanese doesn't.
It's just for those people like me, I don't understand Japanese, but from listening to
a lot of Japanese music, like Aimee Miyazaki, Lark and Seal, tons of Japanese pop and rock
artists and stuff, I can pick up a lot of these words and I start to know the lyrics.
I'll look at the lyrics and I can sing the lyrics in Japanese.
I have no fucking idea what they're talking about, they could be saying, you stupid hunky
bitches from America stop buying our shit, or doing this stuff. But for me, or for anybody
like me who's that into it, yeah, you could go ahead and import the Japanese versions.
I might, depending on how good the Japanese versions are, what kind of songs are on them.
But somebody like Rob, I don't think he really cares to fake singing in Japanese.
I think my time's just better spent making myself better singing American songs, because
I go to actual karaoke bars and sing sometimes.
You're not going to go to a karaoke bar and start singing something in Japanese.
People would be like...
I have seen, because they do let you bring in your own music, and I saw somebody once
they brought in, it was an Indian song, it sounded like it was straight out of a Bollywood
picture type thing, and he was doing the dance and everything, it was great.
I mean, I was entertained by it.
I didn't know what the hell he was saying, but it was totally entertaining.
Yeah, well you get your freaks in there every once in a while.
Well, you know, I wouldn't say he was a freak.
He was...
He brought up forces.
Confusing language.
You're an ass.
Seriously.
Okay, what were some other things I wanted to address in the room?
Oh, yes, Mel B, a favorite guest of Orange Lawns Radio, has a cameo in KOG Revolution
and it's actually in a video that you unlock.
We haven't gotten it ourselves yet, but apparently you can unlock the song one week when you
beat Solo Mode and you get a video with it, too, in the video section, and apparently
Mel B is in there singing a little bit of one week.
It's a clip of all these people singing one week and apparently he's in it, so of course
you know we're going to unlock that shit this week.
do it now and we will play it on the show for you next week and maybe we can get Loki
to remix it. Sorry guys we're cutting off the show now
we have to go unlock Mel B's video. I want to wait until the next time he's actually
here on the show which might not be hopefully in the next couple weeks.
Tell him to unlock it now. I'm going to unlock it now so I can see it
but I want to get him here and then play it over and over and say hey Mel and play the
sound and then, you know, embarrass the shit out of them.
I don't know. I don't know what it is yet. We will see soon. But I hear it's really cute
that they even have like a, they have a dog wearing the headset at one point, and it barks.
Aww, cute. Arf, arf, arf, arf, arf. Which is, you know, what the original song kind
of sounds like to me. Any other thoughts on Karaoke Revolution?
Thank God they don't have that stupid song All Star in there. That's all I gotta say.
hey now you're an all-star that one
yeah why such a hatred on that specific song
cuz they use it like every single fucking movie trailer and shit for like
all these lame ass movies you know you have mystery man and shrek
i like the movie too but the trailer was lame garbage
okay and shrek 2 which i just saw before elf
also had that
yeah shrek 2
also had the god damn song on it too
It's just like, ugh!
Hey Loki, Shrek 2?
Hey now, you're an all-star, get your-
I'm gonna punch you.
I don't like that song either, I don't-
I hate it too.
Is that Smash Mouth?
Fuck Smash Mouth.
No thanks.
They're doing all these commercials now because they can't make any more music.
They're constantly doing educational commercials and shit.
It's so stupid.
any more thoughts on karaoke revolution Brad?
being one of the only other ones that's played it, the other ones I can tell were boring
everyone else here they're like yeah haven't played it, go out and buy it
please everybody, cause we want Konami to get more money off of this
so that they can go ahead and make more stuff like this in America
then again maybe if we tell them to not buy it and it does bad, maybe they'll put more of their
time and money into games like Castlevania instead of... and DDR
No, I could give a fuck about DVR as long as I'm getting my Castlevania on.
pretty darn good song. It's a group called CyberX and it features somebody named Rupina
and it's called Little Flower. The way the cage match works is that we're going to play
three songs for you guys and you vote for your favorite and that song goes into rotation
all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bimani Music and More program. But you have to be
in our chat room to play along so head over to www.calibimani.com, click on Orange Lounge
and click on chat. Whole shitload of people in our chat room tonight. It's more crowded
the first song you can vote for tonight.
I can't believe this is the last time I've ever felt like this
fights with every was about the cheese
I know you haven't
called
Oh
Alright, that was about half of last week's winner, CyberX featuring Rupino with Little
It was huge. A lot of you liked it. It was Sandstorm.
And Darude has a new song out now that is my pick for tonight's cave match. It's called Music.
And it's not like, hey Mr. DJ kind of music, but it's, you know.
Or, I got a music, don't stop.
I don't think there's, there isn't, Darude's not in UltraMix.
No.
Well, whatever. I don't care if it's going to be in DDR in the future.
I think it would be good for DDR, though, but anyway, here's my pick for tonight's cage match. It's Darude with music. Enjoy.
to
the
Don't you think, B.J., live it, record to the fact, don't you think, live it, don't you think,
Oh
Let's go around and see what folks thought of that, we'll start with Brad.
Pretty good. I don't think I'm a huge fan of Darude, because they're kind of a cookie-cutter trance for me.
But it's still good. I would have to vote for that if I could only vote for the last song or this song.
Alright. And scale 1 to 10?
Scale 1 to 10? I'll give it a 7.
Alright. Will!
pvtsteve didn't you send this to me a long time ago?
pvtsteve it's not bad though
kostjamrh I remember when we used to do the secret word of the day and stuff, when we used to be falling down laughing because we'd be making fun of ravers.
kostjamrh I remember when OrangeZion's radio was funny.
kostjamrh I gave it a 6
I thought it was very trance-y and very repetitive, like trance-y songs can be.
And I'd give that one a 7.
I definitely liked it better than the first one.
Bradley, your thoughts on Darude music?
Pretty much the same as everyone else is kind of saying.
Sort of there and repetitive, but not too bad, so a 7.
All right.
I give it an 8, because no song named Music is allowed to be a 10 unless it's Madonna.
Now if it was Madonna remixed by Oak and Fold, because I know they have one of Music.
Oak and Fold does some great Madonna mixes.
Oak and Fold can take anything and make it good.
God dammit, I almost picked the Oak and Fold song for tonight's
I would come!
Kill Bill, Battle Without Honor or Humanity, The 88 Severed Limbs Mix
The light and knowledge that we need to be the best of a black man
This wizard was a fan of the waves of a dark land
The terror that had us through it, everything we proved
It's Friday the first day, you go a-fucking-through
It's dangerous if I don't mind, it's pretty dark and fine
It's same with the sirens, dance with the gooey swine
This thing that's only once vain
This body, I'm at the hop, bummer and sing a song
I wanna run the father, maybe it'll be wrong
2. Battle Without Honor or Humanity 88-Severed Limbs Mix
That was awesome. That's all I have to say. That is getting 5,000 out of 10.
So there you go. I'm stroking his ego.
Looks like you're stroking your dick there, too. That's what made you so happy.
Well, I got some sticky stuff on my fingers from licking something.
Will, your thoughts?
kostjamrh Yeah, that song pretty much owned the rest of the song, so I'd give that one.
kostjamrh I give it a 1 and then a 0 for a 10.
dukeofthebump
Alright, let's review. But you know what? As much as we might like that song, it's really up to you guys in the chat room. You guys have the votes.
So here it is. We're going to recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
You send your votes over private message to Sky in the chat room. Hello, I'm there in the chat room waiting for your vote.
Song number one you can vote for tonight. Last week's winner, two weeks in a row now, CyberX featuring Groupino with Little Flower.
All right, song number two that you can vote for tonight is Darude with Music.
All right, and song number three that you can vote for tonight is Battle Without a Honor
or Humanity, the 88 Severed Limbs mix.
This is the newest remix from Loki.
All right, there they are.
Send your votes now.
Place vote now.
Send those over private message to Sky.
I'm looking at the directory of Loki remixes and it looks like he's got about 12 of them
now. Almost enough for a CD. Almost. Something. That's alright. I think, actually, why don't
we play that other Loki mix? Do you want to talk about your other remix that you did this
week, Loki, that you wanted to debut tonight? I did this one this morning, because, actually,
it was something that Angel's working on right now, and so I give her credit for the name,
and DarkTuxedo also came up with the name, and IDA last night, but I just threw one together
to see how it would end up, because they were working on it.
And so I was like, OK, well, I'll work on my version of it.
It's QQQ and Quasar.
They don't really go together, but I just
figured for the hell of it just to try it and see if it worked.
And what else is QQQ?
This is QQQ Quasar, I guess.
Whatever.
QQQ Quasar.
All right, so this is kind of an idea you ruthlessly stole
from Angel, basically.
Well, actually, just from the chat room in general.
I just did it for the holidays, just to see, you know, what it was. I don't know, whatever.
Alright, let's check this out. This is the other new Loki remix we have today to be with you tonight.
tonight it's Loki vs. Tack with QQ Quasar.
Alright, that's the other Loki song we want to debut tonight, Loki vs. Tack with QQ Quasar,
an idea that was ruthlessly stolen from our chat room, but you did a nice job with it.
Very nice job.
It's just as some folks are saying, well, Brad, tell listeners what you've been saying
while that song's playing.
QQQ would have a lot more potential with this other song, I can't think off the bat what it would mix better with, but still a good effort, I like it.
No, not electrical parade music, I don't know, maybe you could make it sound good, but we'll see.
electrical parade. It was something like that though. I don't remember exactly what it is,
but that song would go good with this because it sounds the same. Okay. I'm going to give
a couple more minutes for the cage match votes to come in. In the meantime, gosh, I'm stretched
for topics to talk about tonight what what's on your what's on your guys's
mind anything guy related well I've been working on my little thing I didn't get
to meet with Keith this week so that made me mad but I've been working on my
list for this thing that I'm doing and it sucks because I was going on DDR
maniacs because they're doing they have a threat about remaking banners so
work perfectly for what I'm doing. The thing is is a certain some way that we
used to know that used to be in our chat room but got banned from our chat room
went ahead and went and fucked up the DDR maniacs forums so if you take a look
at DDR maniacs forums you'll see that a certain somebody that goes by the
name Newt decided to take it take a poop on the forums there and fuck them all up
The next game that will be coming out for itoy is a full on dance game that will have
It's more of a party game like it would be the best thing ever drunk like I could see myself
Drunk and playing that sparkles mode where all your motion creates little rainbow sparkles on the screen
I can see that entertaining myself for hours
That's so a stoner game too. You know with the bubbles
Oh
Sweet
It's just like so
It's just a stoner game
It's like a game for everyone that you can play this game and no matter what, you know, just find something that you'll enjoy in it
I mean, they've got some pretty fun stuff and they have a mode in there. It's a game. That's just like that
FantaVision where it's with
Fireworks the music and that's really good. No, it's kind of neat. I like FantaVision. That's a pretty cool game
They actually made a sequel to that too weird is kind of neat and then they have another game. That's like a kung-fu thing
That's kind of fun kung-fu. That one's awesome. Yeah. Yeah. I love when you have to break the um
you have to break the boards. It's just so funny because on the screen you can see yourself
mirrored in doing what you're doing. Everybody, when they break the boards, they're using
their hands like this. You can't really see it, but they're pointing it straight out like
they're doing a paper and rock, paper, scissors. And they poke it with their fingers. Poke
the board, and it breaks. And they'll hit it with their elbow. It's good stuff.
The one that was hilarious to me was the Ice Queen was over and he hates spiders more than
anything and there's a spider thing on there and it's great because what the spiders do
is it puts a bunch of spiders on the screen that are attracted to motion so if you move
a little bit, the spiders will jump on you really quickly.
It's so funny.
They attach their sides to your head and they don't get off.
It made the Ice Queen run out of the room screaming like the faggie is.
It was great.
I loved it.
Then they have the bees.
You can play with bees.
Oh really?
I didn't see that.
That's what kids need to learn to play with bees.
Yeah.
I did.
And I paid for it when I was a kid.
What other ones did they have on there that were pretty funny?
Garrah's playing with a, they had like a mirror thing.
It was like a carnival mirror.
I played with that thing.
Yeah.
That was funny.
The mirror.
Oh yeah.
The mirror was great.
So, iToy, good thing, bad thing?
What the hell is this thing?
Is it going to go the way of the Super Scope and all these other peripherals that only
ever had one game out and just died?
There's no way to know where it's going to go, but I think if we get some imaginative
game developers to use this peripheral for something else, I think there's some huge
possibilities for this thing.
If anything, you're going to see it used for a bunch of different applications, not necessarily
as a full game, but like add-on things.
For instance, I'm sure they're going to do this, you'll be playing a first person shooter
and you can take a screencap of your face and post it on your character's face.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, mapping the face, your face onto the character's face
so it gets even more personalized. You can go and kill your friends.
Yeah, and you could do Para Para with this thing, the more that I think about it. The
dance game that comes with it is very Para Para-ish. It has sensors in the same space,
but instead of sensors coming from the ground, it's just measuring where your hands are on
the cam. You could do Para Para with this thing.
It's like Parapar, where the five sensors, instead of being in front of you, they're
above you, like a corona all around you, but it plays, to me, more like Space Channel 5.
You have, she'll do something, and then you have to...
It plays like Parappa to me, more, well, okay, Space Channel 5.
No, I can see Space Channel 5.
It's exactly like Space Channel 5.
I can see Space Channel 5.
I was thinking more Parappa, but, yeah, Space Channel 5's probably a better description
for it.
And then there's a beat mania, quote unquote, came in there, too, which is the same thing,
except it's four speakers in the corner, and it has a licensed song in it.
Singing it back, swing it back, sing it back to me
That game reminds me kind of a little more like Slamade Amigo
Because the things come from the center like Slamade Amigo
And then go to the outside
So yeah, good stuff
I think my favorite game in the whole thing though was the Fantavision one
The fireworks one
Yeah that was cool because the little detonating things on the side
That one's really fun
Touching the fireworks and then BOOM
And the music's great, it's hella like ravery, hard and snowy
It's really good
I love taking the pictures of yourself with little profiles.
I think if Xbox should do one of these for Xbox Live, they would have a ball with this.
And the greatest thing ever is when they do a picture for the high score.
When you score, you know, top score or whatever, you take a photo and their photo gets stuck
with the high score.
That's the greatest.
It's funny.
I love how for the profile you get the pictures.
There are three pictures that will tell you the picture of like a, it says do a happy
face, then a sad face, then a silly face, and so when you go to the profiles to select
your character you want to play as, like Matt will have his own and Rob will have his own,
it shows their faces changing from like happy, silly, or then they have some really pointless
modes but they're kind of fun even still, like the window washing, oh the window washing,
the weird song in the background, it's like this old 40, when I'm washing windows, it's
It's like this really hella old 40s or 30s song.
It's just perfect though, it fits.
Good stuff.
Yeah.
Good times.
Very.
But actually, I remember a long time ago, we were reading up on, they were developing
a dance dance revolution type thing with motion capturing just like this and I remember looking
and going, that's stupid.
And you know what, if I think when I see this new dancing game, I think I'll think the exact
the same thing. It'll be stupid. It's a good concept, but it's not for people doing it
for accuracy, like all the PAers out there. It's not going to work.
Yeah, it's not super accurate. I was getting kind of frustrated because I felt like I was
hitting it on time, like rhythm and stuff. There's a game in there where it's a mirror
game where you have to hit these, you have to hit the green ones and not the red ones
where you get penalized, they're like these little bubbles, and what happens is it creates
like a mirror effect where one half of the screen changes upside down and what not, so
you would expect when you raise your hand to touch it, like it goes in a completely
opposite, it's hard to explain, you'd have to see it, but the thing is that since you're
raising your arm, any part of your arm can touch the sensor area on the screen and you
you fuck yourself up, so it's just not a very accurate type of sentence.
Or, depending on the lighting in your room, a shadow could set it off.
Yeah, exactly. It's not the most accurate style of whatnot, you know what I mean?
What the hell? Oh, there. Okay, anyway.
Okay, I think it's time to announce the winner of the Orange Launch Cage Match. What do you guys think?
Here is tonight's winner, the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
I think this one isn't too difficult to figure out.
It wasn't unanimous. I thought it would be, but it was not.
But it was a pretty big landslide nonetheless.
This is tonight's Cage Match winner.
Battle Without Honor, Humanity, The 88's, Evers, Limbs, Mix, of course.
Wins tonight's Orange Lounge Cage Match.
You guys cool with that?
The DDR Megamix that we're going to hear, the artist is credited with DDR and it's all
these DDR songs mixed together, so we'll hear that.
Good Cool featuring Jeff Koot with Blaster, I promise that one.
So we're going to hear Blaster this break.
And you know what, hey Brad, I need your help here.
Is Iconoclasm, is that the Taka featuring DJW one?
They totally changed their name, I'm not sure if it's that or not.
The anthem trance?
Taka and DJW.
Okay, we're going to hear that one too.
The Taka and DJW in the genre of anthem trance, it's Vatam Stelaru.
And they call themselves iconoclasm, which is why I was thrown off because I couldn't
remember what they had called themselves.
So we're going to hear all that this break.
The DDR Megamix, Good Cool and Jeff Koot, and Taka and W.
When we come back, the FUs of the week.
We'll be back.
I'm telling you I know it's true
That I'd die for you, die for you
Baby, let's love, love, love again and again
Tonight everything's alright
It's too almost here
Remember sweet, sweet love
Life's wire, your powder's dry
Another fire and I'll blow you sky high
I'll blow you sky high
No cues to a sonic boom
I feel a tremor at shakin' the room
Shakin' the room
Everybody, are you ready for the beat back?
Everybody, are you ready for the master blaster?
I won't need you where I'm going
I don't need you, where I'm goin'
All I'll leave behind is a drain of dust
All I'll leave behind is a trail of dust
Are you ready?
For the master blaster, oh!
yeah
Hello, we are back and you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 68 in
Dude, it's like a guy show.
highlight of DDR it's alright but the thing is is that like do we need to hear
like before you anymore or d2r or whatever was all those songs in there
like we've heard those so many times we don't need them again yeah I agree now
you can make some new before you remix type stuff okay anyway do you have any
thoughts on that movie it was okay I don't know I just I could see them
putting this in like another version of DDR just as a thing okay cool the other
song we heard in that break was good cool featuring Jeff coot with blame I'm
sorry not blame that was their other song this was a blaster what do you guys
think of blaster I don't know about blaster but hi angel what'd you think of
I am a huge Jeff Koot fan dude, he makes me warm and gooey inside.
It's nothing compared to his turning the motor over, or blame, or blowing my heart away,
but since it's Jeff Koot I'll still deal with the fact that it's stupid hair rock.
Yeah, it was total butt rock to me.
It would be good in Guitar Freaks and Drummania.
It was Total Guitar at My Ass Rock, that's what it was.
I still say they need to put Roller Coaster of Luck in Fucking Guitar Freak.
By Jeffy.
That's true.
Yeah, I, whatever, I mean, I like the Chili Pepper version, though.
That's, yeah, that'd be cool, but.
Yeah.
And they should have a Be as in Butthead video in the background, because it was in the movie,
I think.
Well, I think they were in the, well, the video was animated, I think.
Yeah, it was, actually, yeah.
Yeah.
somebody in the chat room says jeff cooch
also in that break we heard Taka and DJW coming together as Iconoclasm
with a song called and this is kind of tricky it's
Vatum Stellarum
a little bit of latin there
what did you think of the Taka and DJW one?
uh... i like DJ Taka
But he's been bringing out a lot of more generic stuff lately, and I think he kind of poisoned DJW with that generic-ness he's been bringing out.
So I'm not blown away by this song, but it is still pretty good.
It's no Rainbow Flyer, which I think is the best song he's done in a long time.
Because it has the word rainbow in it.
Oh, shut up. But it is decent, I guess. But it sounds just like emotion.
I don't hear DJW really in it at all. If you had just told me it was a DJ Talka song, I would have believed you.
You would have what?
I would have believed you if you had just told me it was a DJ Talka song, I would have believed you.
Well yeah, the DJW part is very subtle. If I can recall, I heard some quick piano-y stuff in there. That's kind of like a DJW thing to do.
Really fast piano playing is DJW's thing.
Did you have any thoughts on that, Loki?
It was okay. I liked it. It sounded kind of trancey and nice.
I don't know, Taka just hasn't really... I just don't really care about Taka and Tack anymore.
It's like Tack did better stuff on his album, you know, the remixes, like paranoia and stuff,
than the actual stuff that he does in, you know, the arcade versions.
It's like they kind of waste themselves on their albums.
I think DJ Taka's last really, really good song was Stuff Off, maybe Rainbow Flyer was
the last really good song.
Like, Fifth Mix was good for both of them, I mean, that was some good stuff.
Was it DR Fifth Mix?
No, Beatmania.
Beatmania Fifth Mix?
Or 2DX, I mean.
Oh, Fifth Style.
Fifth Style, yeah.
Like, what songs?
I can't...
V?
Yeah, like, Absolut was on there.
Well, Absolut's from, yeah, Third.
Whatever.
That stuff is so generic and repetitive sounding.
Why does it have to be Naoki Underground?
Why don't you just say Naoki?
That's as old as generic as you get right there.
Well, at least he does different genres of music even though he may put himself under
different names and stuff.
Well, DJ Taka's been doing a lot of, like with Night Style, these more J-Poppy sounding
songs lately, so he's kind of changing up the genre, but I don't think he's doing very
good.
Sylvia Drive ever again.
I was pissed off that they did even Emotion 2003 anyways.
They've already done a romantic style of Emotion.
That was in, what was it?
Corey.
They made romantic style and that was pretty cool.
I like that better than the original.
But then they're like, we need it to be a little more trancy.
So let's do romantic 2003 or whatever it's called.
Lame.
Yeah, I think it was a little overdone.
So what are we talking about?
Well, you guys are having an argument about whether Taka sold out or not, or whatever it is.
Well, I think Taka's just getting soft.
Alright.
Okay, let's do the FUs of the Week then, speaking of ranting about things.
I'll leave now.
It's time for the FUs of the Week.
Oh, look at that.
Here is justice.
Here is punishment.
Here is...
This is fucked up.
Well, this is the part where Jamie would usually do her FUs, because this is her little retarded
baby that has grown into an hour-long segment every week's show, but she didn't send me
anything over mail, or I haven't gotten anything on email, and I didn't get a phone call or
anything.
So, FU to Jamie for not sending me FUs!
No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding, we'd miss you.
I'll do Jamie's.
Alright.
Fuck you to traffic, fuck you to being sick, fuck you to Xbox, there you go.
Fuck you to bad Chinese food, fuck you to Roswell Golf Land children.
Christmas music is even worse, because I hate Christmas music. Why the hell does every
store in the face of the earth have to play goddamn Christmas music like right after fucking
Halloween, okay? It's not Christmas yet. I hate that fucking music. Stupid dance media
is... What is the draw with speed music? Why do people like speed music? It's just like
a song crammed down your throat. It's like fucking taking a beer bong and filling it
music and that's what it is you're engulfing the whole song in like a few
seconds but no you know instead of having the songs nice and short they
have to know make extended versions and just speed them twice as fast of their
regular size your boss hey now you're a rock star get your game on oh sorry
My second F.U. of the week is going to be going to G4 for their poor programming.
I watched a nice segment on Dance Dance Revolution and these people covering it knew nothing about the game.
I don't think anything knew what they were doing there.
They were talking to these people asking them,
So, what's your highest score?
And the guy's looking at them like,
What the hell? What are you? Huh?
He just had a confused look on his face and it was just awful.
Also, FU, that stupid game Tetris Worlds, not every game needs to have a story.
Tetris is not meant to have a story. It is a puzzle game. No story needed, you play the game.
Dude, have you seen the new Tetris game? Aeris dies.
It's just stupid, it's like, we have to recolonize our planet. It's not a planet, it's a puzzle game.
Puzzle game. No need for anything else.
2. Who wants to watch Russell Crowe be a stupid sailor?
kostjamrh No, that's not worth saying.
I hate them to hell and old people just really suck. I hate reality TV because these new shows that they come up with like this stupid bitch that has to marry some ugly guy. I don't really care if she has to marry an ugly guy because you know what? Ugly people are all over the world and people get married every day. So there's ugly people getting married to hot people all the time.
quackparty2...
also just they have like studies about like different things like games are
addictive you know that's it it's really lame like this is what I'm saying if you set
fire to yourself it will hurt so I'm done
I like boobies too but just because I like boobies doesn't mean you have to
keep writing movies
and burn this fucking CD
they sent you Beethoven
alright uh... hold on
think of something else real fast i'm dealing with some things in the chatroom hold on
Let's watch some gay porn so we can get our hate back.
The only spam I get is TUBGIRL!
What's your email?
I, well, I'm not going to give it out over the air, because who knows, and everybody's
going to send me Tug Girl, because they think it'll be funny.
Okay, everybody, go to www.goatsay.cx.
Jesus Christ, just kill your, oh, that's it, my turn, my turn.
My old few of the week goes to these fucking retarded internet jokes that are five years
old.
Hey, go to Goatsay, it's funny. This guy is stretching his ass.
God.
Top Girl, oh, it's so funny. Hey, she shit herself, isn't that great? Look at that.
God, shut the fuck up.
If you're going to send around an internet joke, at least make it a funny internet joke, like Ghetto Barbie or whatever that once came out.
No, I'm sorry. I know a lot of people hate it still, but you can't go wrong with All Your Base. It's a classic. It's the original.
This is funny because Japanese people actually wrote this this way.
All Your Base was not part of my F.U. That can stay.
Okay, thank you.
But Don't Say and all this other stuff has to go.
Yes, that's done.
Or at least come up with something else funny.
Well, there's like, you know, how about how about a woman in a new compromising position or a guy doing another amazing thing to her body?
Okay, send me that no one sent me that yet
There's there's the new fetish where women kick guys full-on in the groin really hard and they get off on it
That'll probably be a new joke. Yes, somebody send me bum fights. I haven't seen this yet. It might still be funny. See?
All right, God
I just hate it when people post this on forums to try to, like, there's something new that
you're like, huh, this is so funny, my friend just showed it to me.
Chances are, if your friend just showed it to you, it's like five years old, your friend's
just retarded.
Unless you're mean.
Have you seen part putting?
No, God, I don't want to.
My favorite ones are the ones where they post stuff like about new DDR extreme skin for
steph mania and it's the link to go say her redirect oh yeah if you're the one
that's those are the best hey you can go to hell with that too doing that there's
a special place in hell we're just for you i want to do one that sends you to
like install gator on your computer that'd be the best dude i don't even know
how so many keeps going on my computer did the goat say go down i'm gonna buy
Fuck you to shitty news sites and their false articles and stuff.
Fuck you to Supreme Court for the regular bullshit.
Fuck you to the President, like always.
Fuck you to stupid customers that come into games, stop asking about six billion video
games, and have them tell you everything that's new, and then they decide they don't want
that game.
They want Halo for the Xbox.
Fuck you to stupid people, bad drivers.
Fuck you to angry drivers.
Don't know what I'm talking about if you're listening.
Sorry, princess.
Fuck you to computer viruses.
Fuck you to people who are getting a nice new laptop and are getting a 59 inch TV.
Fuck you.
That's about all my fuck yous.
Sounds good.
Fuck you to...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Fuck you to the group that I have to talk to everyday.
This group is called Movie Gallery.
Vambulus, your FUs. Do you have any FUs of the week?
I like to outsource everything to India, to save money, they put all people out of jobs
and they all wander around.
It makes it nice for when I'm hiring, but it still sucks when people are out of jobs.
If you do lots of bills, if you do triple car tax, my truck tax bill came in this month
and I owe $600.
Oh my God!
Yep, it tripled.
If it's tripled, Square Brides Princesses is tripled.
How about...
That's all I have, because I can't think of anything.
Alright, fair enough.
Bradley, Arkadian42, what are your FUs of the week?
Fuck you to be on the edge of out of money and all that other stuff and various things like that as usual.
Fuck you to not have any dog yet.
Fuck you to my laziest...
We're not getting the dog yet.
Fuck you to bad drivers of course.
The guy always tried to hit me when he was chasing lanes, but I think the cops caught
him saying, fuck you to him, and thank you to the cops for catching that idiot, uh, fuck
you to disappearing pencils, and he just ran away from me and disappeared to different
rooms saying, where do the people go to when they have, like, more pencils than they disappear
in various ways, and, uh, work, and, uh, say it again.
Hey, um, up next, let's hear from Zero, your FUs of the Week.
It didn't matter because I wanted to get out of it. I needed to take a break anyway.
Um, uh, because we were out.
Um, yeah, fuck you to having a car now because I have to go and fucking park all the way at Cal Expo
because the stupid fucking mall security little fucking police squad dropouts
come up and harass our store specifically and tell us
If you park your cars anywhere else with Calitro, we're gonna tow it.
And they're, like, picking on us, so we're making their job harder.
Yes, and fuck you to people who tell me to fuck you because I'm getting, like, a TV and a computer.
You know what? Those are gifts. Dick.
Anyways...
Jason! You're a dick!
And by the way, that stuff that I'm getting is a gift, so fuck off.
Not like you don't get to benefit from it anyway, so shut up.
p0k3smot42o you can have a line sugi
Oh wow.
Alright.
FUs please.
Okay, uh, of course the old classic FU does this segment, it's stupid, um, and to be the
great hypocrisy type thing, you know, I'll go ahead and give another FU.
FU to you people who complain about G4, at least you got the money to or have G4, like
and have cable, cause I have to watch the same three channels over and over again.
Thank you network local television.
But then again I do get at least CSI and cheaters.
What's this?
Hell yeah.
Fuck both of you because my TV doesn't even get the reception for those three channels.
Mine doesn't, my TV doesn't, but they have like this little cable thing that's an antenna
that's like this huge, supposed to be a huge antenna on top of the whole apartment complex,
but you know what I think it is?
It's just like a piece of tin foil that's attached to this cable because I cannot get
Fox, like hardly ever, which sucks because Fox has like I think Simpsons on it and stuff
and
but anyhow
doesn't work for is awesome
but seriously man
watch cheaters sunday night at one o'clock or something like that
no
it is
picture
If you liked this video, please like, share, and subscribe!
I have a little man!
What do they know just kidding just kidding just kidding if you lose it what?
Just scares me with pictures of Kelly Osbourne, and why why does he have them on his computer? That's what I want to know
Oh my god. It's a new picture of Kelly Osbourne
I accidentally downloaded her album because it came up as such an elf
You guys are so gullible like three guys took up the gym. Oh my god. You'd picture Kelly Osbourne. She's like 17 you perverts
That's exactly why I want to see it.
Dude, it's like fruit. You want it just before it's ripe and ready to be eaten.
Oh my God!
She got
ripe a little early, okay?
DJ Specter would like to say, F you, my stupid Spanish teacher
whose name I can't pronounce, I'm not going to try to, and DJ Specter would like to give
darceus u would like to second the f u of the week to christmas speed
I got the F.U. Depaltaire. I guess that was it.
Can I get one more?
Baca wants to give an F.U. to a family member who will not let him listen to the rest of the show.
So it did me no good to read that because he's not listening anymore.
That's too bad.
Nothing comes between you and your Orange Lounge radio, God damn it.
All right.
That's it. We're done with the F.U.s of the week.
Don't send me more. I don't want to hear them.
Alright, we're going to do another break of Poppin' Music 10 stuff.
So here it is.
In this break you're going to hear, I know a lot of you guys have been looking forward
to this one, the Dez Q and Tac song.
Dez Q with Jack is the first song we're going to hear.
And we're going to hear Girls Band, it's a genre called Girls Band.
It's Milk.
Kind of like the character.
Milk.
Threep with Milk and then we're going to hear another Dez Q song because I know they have
so many fanboys and girls thanks to Dyke and Kai.
We'll hear another Dez Row song featuring Shingon with the place to be, and it's a genre
called Core Groove.
So enjoy this new set of pop music, 10 music, starting with Dez Q.
You're listening to Orange Launch Radio. Thanks!
I need to take one, to take many more Souls, the rage, I can't bear it, can't make it grow
Don't let me down, this is a dream life
I can't shake you anymore
Oh, I don't know how to own
Gada logan genki ni narutame ni okihima wai sakashini ugu
Do-gi-do-gi, yo-i-mi-chi-si-te
Kon-e koto, jare-a atari
I've been waiting for you
I'll never see you again
If I had you, I wouldn't have had you
Mr. Random person on the street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think
What do you think of the Orange Lounge Big Money Music and More show?
The music is like being transported to this dancing spaceship place.
It's unearthly. It's like being at a club, except you don't have to ask someone to dance.
Alright, we're back on Orange Lounge Radio.
I'm opening up the floor for some quick Ask Orange Lounge before we go off air tonight.
But first, while you guys send those questions in over private message to Sky,
Let's see what you guys thought of those songs.
The Chat Room certainly had some strong opinion on these.
The first song we heard in that break was Dez Q, that's Dez Row and Tac, with a song
called Jack.
Um, Brad, what did you think of that?
The Dez Q with Jack.
I like it.
It's distress and freaking gravity mixed together.
You know what's interesting?
The Chat Room worst reviews of the night.
They said that song is god-awful.
don't like it at all. Fuck them. This shit isn't for them. Big fuck you to the chat room.
You know what? I don't think it's awful, but for TAC, it's pretty bad. I expect better
from TAC. So that's me personally. Why don't you go sit on a dick or two? If I could. Oh,
Oh, oh, hey, it looks like, uh, Bunch of When I Lost was offering.
I'll close my eyes.
Uh, Loki, what'd you think of Dez Q?
It's okay, it's just like every other fucking tax song on the face of the earth, they all sound the same now.
Um, I should remix it, I guess. That'd be fun.
Alright.
Uh, anybody else have a thought on Dez Q with Jack?
What?
I should just listen to Captain Jack.
Yes, Captain Jack is much better than Jack, in my opinion.
It does queue with Captain Jack.
Oh!
The next song we heard was a band called Threep,
and the song was called Milk.
A nice, happy little uplifting song.
I remember that movie.
Anyway, that was Milk Money.
Where they, like, saved up their milk money to go to a prostitute.
That was cool.
That has nothing to do with the song. Nothing at all, Loki.
Uh, Brad, did you have a thought on Girls Band With Milk?
I wasn't paying attention to that song, sorry.
Well, what the fuck? Pay attention.
Alright, um, let's see what you guys thought of Desrow featuring Shingon with, uh...
Oh, what the hell's the name of this song?
The Place To Be!
and the certainly those you that were visiting the money stop for a while
probably got fucking sick of this song really fast yep it's just a few of the
whole thing
uh... you say it
well after that reason only met up and i forgot some
fuck you but my server so the music on your opening page
yep they hate you know what
i love the money style
got a good guy that runs it can i ask you how i think that's a great site good
stuff but i don't like that
choice to put the music on the opening page and the biggest problem is if it
would be nice here's a suggestion for my spell folks if you're listening instead
of having the one song in there and changing it every two weeks or so put
like ten songs that randomize so every time I heard that no better yet turn off
the fucking music I get it do it do you know maniacs did it's it's got like a
cookie on your computer okay you if you disable it it doesn't play until you
enable it again and it does it automatically and I love that otherwise
nice, great sight. Or even better, just have it load Orange Lounge Radio when they go to
the front page. Just have it load. The problem is the thing to turn it off, it takes a while
to load up after no animations and stuff. Bad business decision, whoever did that. Brad,
what did you think of that song? The Desiro, core groove genre one that got played the
hell out on the Monty style? What did you think of the last half of it that you didn't
I think I'm bored too.
e-mail me
Don't email Konami, they have a request on their website, click here to request a song
for your donation.
Here's the thing, if you really want to do it, try and get a hold of Short EMC or Shintenshi
or any of those other old school Bay Area MGL guys from DDR, because they all work for
fucking Konami right now, at least until like Christmas time because I hear they're getting
laid off.
But hey, while you're working there, why does Mo bug the shit out of them?
My only thought is that if you're going to request a song like that, like the total gibberish
song to be in Karaoke Revolution, Murmur Twins isn't funny.
I think they're trying to be funny.
I get the thing that it's trying to be funny, like, ooh, teehee, let's request Murmur Twins.
It's not funny.
Wouldn't it have been more funny to request Last Message, or?
See, yes, Last Message I think would have been a little funny.
Murmur Twins, not funny.
I'd like to request DMX be put in DDR.
I'd like to request that no Bamani songs be put in Karaoke Revolution so that we don't
ruin the series.
DMX, the singer, the rapper.
No, I'm just saying.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Am I the only person who agrees that Konami's original music is better than 98% of the music
that comes out nowadays?
All I'm saying is that DDR music needs to stay in DDR.
Check this shit out.
DDR music needs to stay in DDR.
It does not need to be in Karaoke Revolution.
We like Karaoke Revolution because it has the pop songs in it.
Check this out.
A new version of Somba Money Game comes out, DDR, pop and music, or 2DX.
People go, have you heard the new license tracks?
I'm like, what, there's license tracks? I don't give a fuck. I like Konami's music.
I like the license tracks.
Yeah, because you're a consumer whore.
Fuck off.
Alright, can we actually answer the questions now?
Hey, can I ask a question to the chatroom first?
Yeah.
Could I have everyone in the chat room who plays FF11 to please tell us what server they're on and their character name?
I'm on Bismarck.
Oh, Bismarck. Fuck Bismarck. Everyone jump over to Ragnarok.
Fuck Ragnarok. There's already a game called Ragnarok.
Yeah, well, there was a...
Yeah, and fuck Ragnarok while we're at it.
Yes, Ben?
I don't know.
Alright, let's get to the question.
No, too late.
Same question came from both 20th Magus and Zodiac Knight.
Plus you to the player in Star Wars Galaxy who unlocked the first Jedi.
You fucking grinding bastard.
You like mastered every profession in the game.
You suck ass.
And fuck you to Sony online for making that the secret way to unlocking the goddamn Jedi
character.
Jealous?
Table of one?
No, fuck that fucking piss off because it was just about grinding profession.
It wasn't some super secret- I thought you enjoyed grinding.
I do.
your profession is when you just sit there and build biological chemical effectors all
day long instead of actually playing the game. You just sit there building things forever.
And it sucked because it was supposed to be some kind of cool, different way for everyone
to unlock the AI and it was just mastery of four different professions.
I don't give a shit. I don't get a few segments done. Alright, same question from Magus and
zodiacknight asks the same question
best song in karaoke revolution so far?
they want to know
zeroesaysnone
loki
you're the one that i want
because it was in greece
and she loves greece
i really don't like much of the songs
because i can't sing them
so it kind of sucks
i like jennifer lopez's waiting for the night
because that's the only song i like of hers
and then
Broken Wings is alright because I listen to that all the time.
As far as non-game music, I'd have to say Lady's Night, man.
That's awesome.
That's the first time we got Lady's Night.
I would say it's a close tie between Like a Virgin, because I love singing that song
because I'm so virginal in here, and Girls Just Want to Have Fun.
Girls Just Want to Have Lunch.
Yes.
Both were weird-out parodies, too, so you can sing the parodies.
The songs on there, I think, were parodied by Ria, complicated songs.
Yeah, complicated is on there. And I like complicated, too, because it pisses Nelly off when I sing it.
Brad, your favorite, because I know you've played the game, too?
Well, it sure wasn't that friggin' Jennifer Lopez song. God, Matt, you faggot.
Anyway, um, wait a minute, what am I talking about? My songs are pretty faggoty, too.
I'd have to say, probably, I don't know, there's three really good ones on there. Bizarre Love Triangle, Huey Lewis in the News with Power of Love,
of love, and, um, what was that other one I sang? I did the, the Hulu-less one, Bizarre
Love Triangle was on there, and, what was it? There was another one, but yeah.
Uh, it's the end of the world, does he know it?
No, uh, no. REM isn't that great.
Uh, you just saw me do it!
Chain of Fools?
No! Chain, chain, chain!
I don't remember the other one.
You're under where?
I don't remember the other one you did, I'm sorry.
Uh, frickin' A, I don't know, but yeah, you get it. You get the point. There's, there's
some good songs on there, so.
The one from Back to the Future was that you already said that one, right?
I already said that. Power of Love. Power of Love.
Alright, a couple more questions, both coming from Azie and Buddy Paul.
These are the last two of the night, so no more questions for us.
I'm hijacking. Here we go.
I'm hijacking.
Tef, Julian.
This is a live show.
We're coming to you live from the hizzle for shizzle.
Weird dog.
Such a piehole.
Alright.
Azie and Buddy Paul, have any of you had a near-death experience?
This is a pretty heavy question.
Yes.
want to explain it? Hold on. Okay, I'll go first. I went on a groupish date with a friend
of mine. It was this one guy and his date and my date. And he was driving his mom's,
thank God, Grand Prix, Pontiac Grand Prix. And it was the first, yeah, well, I say thank
God because the Grand Prix's actually hold up pretty well in a wreck. We went on a date
We went to a movie then we came home and right after we got out of theater
It was the first rain of the season so in the first rain of the season
Everybody starts driving like complete idiots and since it's the first rain. There's a lot of fresh oil on the road
So we're driving. He's driving too fast for conditions
tailgating somebody and
He's looking behind him talking to the two girls in the rear seat whereas. I'm the only one watching the street
He's the one driving, but I'm the only one watching the street, so
So some truck got an accident up ahead, they were parked in the middle of the fast lane,
and I look and I say, oh shit, look out, stop, and so he turns his head just in time for
him to swerve to the right a little bit, so only half of the car got hit, this truck with
an iron bumper, it destroyed the front half, gave me some bruises, but if we had gone straight
into it instead of to the side, we would have been under the truck and it would have decapitated
all of us and we would have been dead.
So thank you to me for saving these three worthless people's lives and myself.
Mine's not as exciting as that, but it's a little closer to death.
See, I actually died at 18 months old.
I'm serious.
I drowned, and I was pronounced dead.
And I was out of my brain and stuff for five, ten minutes before my mom put the oxygen mask
over me and somehow brought me back.
But I actually died.
I don't remember anything.
I was too young.
But apparently after that, when I came back, my mom taught me to swim pretty quick.
interesting
there is one time
and then i said near death not death
next time pay attention
uh...
and such a dick
working at one
uh... yeah sure
uh... there is this one time where uh...
i came home
and like
no
No, there was one time I came home and we were out of Captain Crunch and I thought I
was going to die right there.
This one time I had to listen to Christmas Speed.
Other question from Azie and Buddy Paul.
This is pretty easily answered.
What is the song we use for the Ask Orange Lounge theme music?
We get asked this, I swear to God, every other week.
This is Journey to the Wonderland from Keyboard Mania Second Mix by NPB.
zer0, your final thought of the evening?
metal slug just ain't metal slug without the blood
my final thought of the evening is
MORTAL COMBAT!
and uh... Loki your final thought of the evening
I had too much strawberry soda during this show
I think I've had a whole six-fashioned... Does your pee smell like strawberries?
I don't know! Let me get a thrower right now!
Alright, I'm going to give the final word of the evening, one word, to sum up the whole show and we end on that note tonight.
No, Dark Child.
I give the final word of the night tonight to Vandalous.
You can't have it, Dark Child. You don't get it.
Goatsy.
No. No goatsy.
Vandalous gets the last word of the evening because I know he'll keep it clean.
Vandalous, the final word of the evening tonight?
Apple pie.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sabra, Sky, and Loki.
We expect you a nice play again.
And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
Trying to save the relationship by talking about having a baby.
You know, like, that's going to work.
I had a great, great experience recently.
I helped deliver one of my best friend's children.
And, wow, when you witness something like that,
You see how powerful women are, that we bring forth life.
I mean, it's awesome.
And I just was so amazed by my friend,
because she was not just a woman.
She was not just a mother.
At that moment, she was creation.
She was life.
She was God.
And as I looked in her eyes, her pussy exploded.
a piece of it hit me in the head
A piece of it hit me in the head!
Everybody else was like holding each other and crying, and I'm like, I'm fucking with
The nurse was running around collecting pieces of her pussy in a basket, she's just panning
for pussy. They had to sew it back together.
frankenpussy. IT'S ALIVE!