[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, September 18, 2011, Nintendo reveals the future of the 3DS and its pink, the PlayStation Vita preps many games for launch, and Sony adds a controversial new section to the PSN Terms of Service.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and joining you live here on this September 18th, 2011 for episode number 428 with my co-host, first off, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're also the show where every gamer has access to chicken.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can have some if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's eating chicken.
[SPEAKER_04]: TechMasterLoki is in the house over here as well and he's eating chicken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I am chicken-less, but I do have... You can have some chicken.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually don't really want chicken.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a pumpkin spice frappuccino.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a pumpkin spice latte.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had one of those brunches that was so big, like I'm still full.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just like, I'm not even hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, I'm still laughing my ass off over that cracked article.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this article you were reading about?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was one of those little Photoshop things where they do rejected book covers.
[SPEAKER_10]: And one of them was, it's okay to be a douchebag by Ayn Rand.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's interesting about that website is they have really made, you know, I'm not knocking it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just what I've noticed about them.
[SPEAKER_04]: An observation, if you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really seem to have made a name for themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always thought, wasn't Cracked like a magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the answer to Mad Magazine like 20 years ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was Mad Magazine and Light.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that still exist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Cracked Magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cracked is on Dig and those websites all the time because they specialize in top 10 lists or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all they do is lists.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to do one for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they take user-submitted articles?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they do, but the better that they are, they'll start paying you for them or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: New industry for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, why don't you join our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com We do tape our show live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, live at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, to be fair, Bobby had the night off tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: but never mind if you're listening on the podcast and you've never heard a live show before he'll be back next week so again if you are listening to us live at All Games Radio though join us in the chat room again that's chat.orangeloungeradio.com where we do often read comments from chat tonight which actually I gotta admit chat's a little more dead than I usually see it and I don't know if that's just we didn't have a lead in tonight because Bobby was off or is it the Emmys like is everybody off watching the Emmys like I know that's our competition we are always up against some stupid award show
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait till it's over so I can see Kathy Griffin's roast of the Emmys She's doing something now where she like bashes the Emmys when it's over
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's part of the shmemies
[SPEAKER_04]: Nick Arcade Video Game TV Shows
[SPEAKER_10]: I was, um, I watched that one, and I can never remember the name of it, where, um, they would send the team through this, like, labyrinth with, uh, these Velcro vests, and they would attach the prizes to their vests as they went along.
[SPEAKER_04]: I vaguely remember that, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was on Saturday morning after my cartoons, so I would watch it all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I was like, you can't stick a TurboGrafx to your front, put it on your back.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were empty boxes probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just all props or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I mean, they'd grab games and stuff and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_04]: The Biggest Loser is his thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: How appropriate for him.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was another show that was on too that he switched.
[SPEAKER_04]: He will always be Funhaus to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it wasn't Funhaus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funhaus was like the double dare turned up to 11.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was also, well, you remember that show, what was it, The Quest of the Kingdom or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's not one of the thing of, there's another guy who had brown hair.
[SPEAKER_10]: He'd always wear like a members only jacket.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was the 80s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that John Davidson?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't he on Hollywood Squares?
[SPEAKER_10]: He sat in a chair that looked a lot like Captain Kirk's chair.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I remember this show very much because they did a big special on the Neo Geo and about taking the cards and switching them out you know putting them in the machine saving your game and coming home and playing it at home and for the life of me I cannot remember what the name of the show was
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask this question while you guys try to think of the show or while the chatters at chat.arnstalksradio.com shout it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it that video game television hasn't really seemed to work?
[SPEAKER_04]: There has been a few exceptions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know some of you guys dig X-Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there's that show on Spike TV that gets to break a lot of exclusives, the one that Jeff Keighley does.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been a few things here and there but G4 TV was supposed to be all about video games but it didn't work because it went this whole different direction where it's aimed towards young guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it just that we're too busy wanting to play video games than watch people talk about it on the TV?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why doesn't it work?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Internet's faster than TV or print media.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless they're breaking news, that's kind of the way it goes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm positive one of them was video power.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a story coming up later tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to totally get into it now, but one of the big consoles is launching a TV-related thing, and we'll talk more about that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: but that does kind of seem to be like the future especially when we talk a lot about like video on demand and how huge Netflix and Hulu and all that stuff has been on PlayStation as well as Xbox and do you think it's possible that as these consoles become more like entertainment devices like almost for some people maybe replacing cable someday I don't know do you think we'll see more gaming related content on those consoles?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, if it's on a console, I can imagine that they're going to try to put some gaming-related content on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll probably feel like infomercials more than anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of like the Majors Minute on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: As nice as that is, let's be real, it's just a product awareness thing for Microsoft, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to find... There was an article I saw talking about some new video game show that's coming and it was by the guy that did The Room or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not Silent Hill The Room, but actually... Like the horrible cult movie The Room?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the horrible cult movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually him.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks so fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just can't remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then it's parody or it's a joke or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's something to take too seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am your something interest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just retarded.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the record, both shows I was thinking of is actually the same show but different seasons of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Video Power?
[SPEAKER_10]: Video Power because it started off as like a tip show and then it became a game show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was like a game show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had tips.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
1990-92
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, was it really?
[SPEAKER_10]: In two different formats from 1990 through 92.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh, I'm with Dan in the other room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was way earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Wikipedia is always right 100% of the time, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Presented by Stevie Poskoski.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to double check IMDB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me hit on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know one thing that I think would have made an awesome television show would have been the 1 vs. 100 on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really feel like Microsoft was sitting on a goldmine with that and they let it go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's because of licensing reasons or what have you, but
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, I know so many people that were so into that, and it's really weird that they let it go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it really made me think, like, why hasn't, like, Game Show Network tried to pick up, like, an actual game show that runs through consoles or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, I found it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called the Tommy Wee Show, and it's featuring Tommy Wiseau.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, it's supposed to be this weird...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying it's going to be presented by Makima, and it basically follows him as he repeatedly gets abducted by different races of mysterious aliens transported to distant planets where he's forced to test popular video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's a terrible idea ripped off of Mystery Science Theater 3000 with this guy that looks like he's the Undertaker or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: No one cares.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get into our gaming weeks here in a minute, but one other game-slash-TV-related thing that I can think of that I know is coming soon is the whole sci-fi TV show that's supposed to be tied into an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: It popped in my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something I think they had talked about at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember anything about that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what you're talking about, but I don't know what the hell it's called, and nor do I care.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a sci-fi show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: X-Play
[SPEAKER_03]: um what was the other one that was yeah Portal was kind of lame they had that on there um
[SPEAKER_03]: Just watch all the online reviews now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dave, where he'd go running around in MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't that the one that Wil Wheaton hosted?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just really watch YouTube like the angry video game nerd and, you know, crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that other one that you watch?
[SPEAKER_10]: Classic Game Room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's turning to YouTube now and amateur programming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such as the show you're listening to right now, although we're more radio than TV, but hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a YouTube channel, we just don't really do anything with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I use mine to post videos of Shermie and my best friend's son.
[SPEAKER_03]: My post-grant, I thought, are related videos.
[SPEAKER_03]: and one video that I had to upload a trailer so I can link it on a newsletter I was doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny enough, that trailer got more comments than most of my other videos I put on there because it's some really crappy hunting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care if it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to put the trailer up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tiger Claw mentioned something about a Gunstringer game that was put out by Troma.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what Troma did, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Toxic Avenger movies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, they do all the really campy B-movie stuff, like Troma and Juliet and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just that Sars, what's his name from Troma, Lloyd McCoffman or whatever, he's in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop trying to get into stories that we make up for later on, bastard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't control the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think we're even talking about that tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I always like to start off the show talking about what kind of games we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: As in the worlds of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you're a nerd.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, get a life.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been playing Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I played some Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, these are all the same games I play, but I like to make them.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played Espagaluda.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can never say it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Espagaluda 2 on my phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you check out Radiant Silvergun on Xbox yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems like something that would be up your alley.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that came out this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've already got like
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't you want to see the super uber HD version prettiness?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that we got it yet, now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was thinking of you when I saw that on Xbox Live the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to play the crap out of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I was actually going to sit down and play some Symphony of the Night today, but I've had a bad headache for most of the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn Dracula causing those migraines.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn him.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is not by my hand that I was once again given my migraine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't really play a whole lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mainly just three things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Earth Defense Force, Insect Armageddon, played lots of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I have my jet guy now almost level 7.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Grand Theft Auto, we went back to Lost and Damned again because they got tired of getting punked in Battle of the Gay Tonys, so now they're getting punked in Lost and Damned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mixing it up a bit, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and then I played Zelda on, um, Virtual Console on the 3DS, so I've been playing that right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on the fifth dungeon, and, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: The virtual console stuff is alright, but it does make you realize one thing, and I don't know if anyone's really covered it before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, man, that D-pad... I mean, Nintendo is known for pretty good D-pads, especially with the NES and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great D-pad work, I think, pretty flawlessly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: but that d-pad on that 3DS is terrible and that what are they calling it now the circle pad or whatever not good either so it's just kind of like okay which terrible control method do I want to use so I end up using the circle pad for most things but it is not not good at all aside from that though the emulation is good it's just that d-pad is terrible but no d-pad looked good the one with Vita
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's a lot of neat looking things about the Vita, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess we'll get into that a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's lots and lots of news about handhelds.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, this is like handheld week.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's tons and tons of news about both.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get into that a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, my gaming week was mostly uneventful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a lot of the same stuff like WoW and so forth too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to really talk myself down from buying Magicka on Steam today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although the game looks kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might still buy it when I get home.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: only like nine bucks for the uber edition right now on Steam or you can get like the buy four copies of the game for seven dollars and like it's it's some obscene sale going on on Steam right now and man I love and I hate Steam you know what I mean like I love that I'm getting so many games super cheap I hate that I'm keep spending money on games I'll play like once or twice and then it'd be all like oh I gotta go back to WoW
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as other games I've been playing, I've been playing more L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire on the consoles, did a couple other cases and so forth, and found that I'm really horrible at the action sequences, and I'm so thankful that the developers decided to put in a way you can just skip the action sequences, because I just wasn't getting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the end of one of the cases, you finally figure out who the suspect really is, and the suspect just bolts.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: because the thing I like best about that game is going to look at the clues and going to investigate the suspects or excuse me, interrogate the suspects and put that all together.
[SPEAKER_04]: And investigating.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like, you know, like putting together the pieces of a logic puzzle or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's amazing how exhilarating or how frustrating it can be when you hit the button.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I literally sit there and it's like being on Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's like, your final answer is truth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it goes, do, do, do.
Fuck!
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew the bitch was lying.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just have a casual mode in there where you pull back a slingshot and launch a bird at the guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I gotta say, as far as Rockstar Game goes, I don't usually get into the Grand Theft Auto games and all that stuff, but I'm really liking L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the detective thing, and I'm all into the stories and the 40s stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I'm going to play some more of that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments on Magicka in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Infinel, I hope I said that right, says Magicka is crazy fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Kaijudo says Magicka is crazy lag for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure they fix that lag before you buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if that's for everybody or if it's like a system-related thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: so yeah I've been playing that now there's another game I've been playing quite a bit of this week and I didn't know if I wanted to talk about it on the show tonight because I'm gonna kind of like open Pandora's box here by saying what I've been playing but I figure what the hell I'm not gonna be here the next two weeks anyway so if any hate mail comes in I wouldn't see it anyway
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you've listened to the show for any length of time, I told you guys I don't pirate games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't download a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't pirate games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except I have downloaded in the past, like during the PlayStation 1 era, I downloaded a lot of the Bomani games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to bring you something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to bring you President Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot both things.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was going to play the – you used to back in the day I would download – because I'm not paying $80 to import all these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mindset is if you want my money, release the game in my territory and I'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xenoblade Chronicles Xenoblade Chronicles
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it something the Wii needs on its system?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the honest reaction I had playing Xenoblade Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first thing out of my mouth, because Salacious Pop, you know, I was sitting down playing it for a couple hours, and Salacious Pop goes, well, how was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It feels like a really, really awesome PlayStation 2 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's kind of how I felt about it is that the graphics really not up to par with what you see on the 360 and the PlayStation 3 which you know is understandable it's the Wii the game itself feels a lot like I don't know it's kind of like Final Fantasy 12 with MMO elements and a pretty neat battle system reminiscent of the other you know Xeno games so
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot to do in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of quests.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of things you can do in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the world is vast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're an RPG fan, you really have a right to be mad that they're not putting the game out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And quite frankly, if they're not going to put it out here, you should do what I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't miss out on a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I know I might get hate mail for encouraging that, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will happily buy this game when they release it in this country.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to mod our Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really easily being adapted for the Wii U There's a lot, like the menu system There's a lot to it, there's a lot of subscreens You could use that second device The little controller, very easily To do a lot of that, and then you could have The really nice souped up graphics And to be honest, if Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Enchanted Arms was the only remote RPG available for like six months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, but I'm thinking Japanese RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not thinking... There's a big difference in my mind between a game like Final Fantasy, Enchanted Arms, Xenoblade, and Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion's its own thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, you're right, you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion is a pretty kick-ass RPG launch title.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, here's what they're gonna do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, yeah, this is Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, I can see them doing that because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They have nothing to bring to the table right now for the Wii U. They've got nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they can't hold back Zelda Skyward Sword any longer because people will just be really pissed off then.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: All they're going to do is they're going to fucking upscale that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to redo the graphics.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to upscale the polygons, and you're going to have low-res textures.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like you've seen with the Metal Gear Solid HD collection, there's different ways that they do HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of them, they'll actually go to the Microsoft website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all they're going to fucking do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're going to maybe add some support for the Wii U tablet thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: People will be like, Oh my God, that's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're holding out so that they go, Look it, we understand what the hardcore fan wants and we brought it to you with the Wii U and you're supposed to go...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, Nintendo, my savior!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna go buy your system now!
[SPEAKER_03]: But you need to see through this shit and you say, fuck them, they're just trying to hold this little carrot in front of my nose so I buy another fucking system that they end up catering to the goddamn masses for and make all these casual games and completely forget about the hardcore user that actually buys product for their damn system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing though like I agree and I don't because the thing is at the end of the day it's not just about the graphics and the game itself is pretty freaking awesome especially like if you like JRPGs at all or you like these kind of like you know very open world do the side quests and battles in real time without going into cut scenes for battle and all this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The presentation of the game is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game itself, story and everything, is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they need to do... I mean, the graphics do look dated, but even up-rezzing or whatever little tweaks they can make to it that bring it a bump up, I think it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because at the end of the day, the game itself speaks for itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: System is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then if that's the way they want to go, they want to bring it out over here and they need to bring it out on the Wii like it is now because it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can be put out now and then they can do a special edition later on that has better graphics or an HD version and that would come out like a year later.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the problem with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: You get to sell it twice and people may buy it twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is, and I'm just being real with y'all here, the more Nintendo, I feel like they're ignoring the type of game that I want to play, the more it makes me want to turn to the dark side to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how easy was it to do when major gaming websites are posting, here's how to play Xenoblade in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Nintendo is just being fucking deaf.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's fine if their ultimate grand scheme plan thing is to release it on the Wii U but I think they should have announced that by now and like I would have waited to play this game if they'd announced it on the Wii U I would have said cool it'll give me a launch game that sounds like it'll be pretty kick-ass based on everything I've read online but seeing as I'm getting to this point where I'm like you know what this game is never going to come out and I really want to play it so gosh there's this ABC how to run these games on my Wii right in front of my face I
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, be mad if you want, but I'm just being real.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not the only one out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or major gaming websites will not be publishing how to get away with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, it was just how to play the import copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, no, and that's fine, and I understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, let's be real...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: You surely, you know, there's the thought of what you're really telling people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be ignorant.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I say that to everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So will I buy the game if it comes out on Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That depends if we want to buy the Wii U. Yeah, right now the question is, will I buy a Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing with the Wii U. I mean, look at some of the games that they're talking about coming out of the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's like Batman Arkham City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to release a game that's been out for a year now on that system?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't even see a point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Release Skyward Sword on there then.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one's going to fucking care because it's been out for a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now they just don't have much to bring to the table for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be surprised if that system comes out next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm going to say for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Xenoblade Chronicles is a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really too bad that Nintendo won't release it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else can I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on and get some quick housekeeping before we get into tonight's stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will not be here for the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually, after last week's show, I realized, oh crap, I've got the concert next week and then I actually have a scheduled trip to LA the week after that and it's the one I do every year, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: yep I'm taking a little break sorry guys but I believe the one and only Tiara is going to be here covering at least next week if not both weeks I don't know yet just next week so there will be some type of live shows so tune in as always and I'll miss you guys but at the same time damn we need vacations once in a while give me a break
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Add us on Facebook, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we can get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start it off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't take vacations at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Nintendo announced a lot of stuff at their pre-Tokyo Game Show press event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the stuff they announced, hey, you know those big games that you're waiting for, you know, ones that you may have purchased a system for?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're not coming this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kid Icarus Uprising has been delayed to 2012, and that's for all regions.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, you know, it's critically acclaimed, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had new video footage for it, but yeah, not coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, there's going to be a new system update coming for the 3DS in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is going to add 3D video capture as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And definitely kind of a cool thing, because I know the 3D photos are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that next year when there's the 3DS Lite or the 3DS XL or whatever crap they come up with, there's going to be better cameras in it, I'm sure, that will help with the 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because let's be real, not a lot of people have 3D cameras or 3D video cameras right now, so Nintendo could kind of get a jump on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the whole thing, the 3D craze by implementing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really surprised it didn't have video at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised at all that it's being patched in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're surprised?
[SPEAKER_03]: The device didn't have all the features that they talked about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, eShop, you want to buy stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, that's not coming for a few months.
[SPEAKER_03]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hey, you want to browse the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we didn't put the web browser in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't quite done yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rush?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we didn't rush the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: This was always planned like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, November.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, they don't like to rush things.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're taking their time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, one of the things that came out was this god awful ugly circle pad attachment for Monster Hunter Tri-G And of course, it's been announced that several titles will actually support it Including Resident Evil Revelations, Metal Gear Solid Snake Eater 3D, Ace Combat 3D, Dynasty Warriors Versus, and Kingdom Hearts 3D Dream Drop Distance
[SPEAKER_03]: and of course this device is going to require an additional AAA battery to use because it's got to communicate with the 3DS via the infrared port on the back and it will also add a couple extra shoulder buttons and of course the circle pad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny thing about the circle pad is it's not needed for Monster Hunter.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact all the demo kiosks at Tokyo Game Show didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: interesting this this thing is so interesting because well a the whole fact that it requires a separate battery to run like you could just hear the face palming going on across Twitter and the blogs and so forth when that was announced so I'll just kind of let that speak for itself and the whole yeah yeah sure they plan to do this the whole time I'm really sure because they thought about adding that port on the back that could interface with this and power it but oops um of course then again you don't want anything else sucking the power out of the 3ds because it's not like it holds a lot to begin with right um
[SPEAKER_04]: but it really is sounding more and more like this is the 3DS's version of Motion Plus only it's happening a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I really wonder how long it's going to be before this thing is mandatory.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know on the remake next year there's going to be better cameras and the second analog pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Second analog pad can go right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice little home for it right on the device.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because the way it looks right now is just like a Wii U controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but see, I believe that the buttons are... Oh, actually, the buttons are above, or below the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll move the buttons down, and then they'll put the circle pad there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, but they got you to buy a system because they dropped the price, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha, suckers!
[SPEAKER_03]: And you'll buy it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what Nintendo likes to do, sell you hardware over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember Game Boy?
[SPEAKER_03]: coinora chatroom at chat.orangelandreda.com Randy says that 3DS attachment makes the thing look like a Game Gear a little bit I think the battery life might be a little better on a Game Gear though, not sure and then of course, you know, the best way to target your female audience is to put it out in pink so they have a 3DS coming out in pink in October yeah cool
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not in the U.S., in Japan only.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are people really that shallow?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I understand people like pink things, but it's like, oh, I'm not buying that system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's in pink!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, people are that shallow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just accept it and move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I shake my head at you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, this is how they deal with all that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Put out a pink box for a game, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever blue systems come out, Miklatov's right there ready to buy one, so I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on, Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Except it's muted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pink Systems, giant sellers at Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are they really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't get the pink DS light.
[SPEAKER_07]: You couldn't beg, borrow, or steal one of those at Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the other time of the year, nobody fucking wanted them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't it really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, remember when I got my GBA?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh dear God, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: My pink GBA.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: And no one else could find them.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, it's not really just... GBA, that was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't this pink and hard to find?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really just about the colors, though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know how many of you guys were watching the press conference that was going on, but they followed up this conversation on pink 3DSs with the girl-tailored games, which were... They looked really creepster to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, you know, it's a different culture, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, some comedian-based game, I think, was one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have...
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of girl-based games already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Ubisoft puts out a ton of girl games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there is a ton of DS games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to preface by saying, like, tween girl games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't want to infer, because DarkSakura might kick my butt, that girls, like, play different games and, like, you know, all girls hate Metroid and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, like, you know, the ones that are aimed at, like, the little girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna punch you with this microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, let's be real, she did say she played a lot of Sims 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's stuck on that Facebook Sims game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually didn't touch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people are stuck on that Facebook game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You lie like a rug.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't play it at all yesterday.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why so many of my sims hated me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the DS, they did really try to market the DS at girls for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't they have Beyonce and Carrie Underwood doing commercials?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, girls and women.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Beyonce does it, then I've got to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Girls and women were a huge marketing push with the Wii, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo was just all about...
[SPEAKER_07]: 40% of the consumers out there, or 50% or 60% or whatever, are women, and we're not marketing to them, and you gotta sell to women, sell, sell, sell, recommend games for girls, girls, girls, girls, sell, sell, sell I'm like, you fucking people, have you seen the customers that come into my store?
[SPEAKER_07]: 99% male If there's a girl in my store, they stay out until the girl leaves No, that's not, that's not true Well, it's often true
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But now they can see women in 3D on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: In 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3D boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: This will probably be the first time they ever see 3D boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, I kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know how many of you guys again watched Nintendo's conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously there was a lot of focus on the Monster Hunter games that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games, because there's Tri-G and then there's 4 that they announced is going to be a Nintendo 3DS thing as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then I gotta say I was totally thinking of DarkSakura because after the press conference there was like 15 minutes of Monster Hunter commercials that featured Gatchaman like for 15 minutes like all these little Gatchaman ads for Monster Hunter games that made me laugh okay I need this if there's Gatchaman involved I watched them all thinking that that's when they were finally going to show that 3DS peripheral but what was very interesting that add-on completely absent from Nintendo's press conference that they did for not Tokyo Game Show
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care about any of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You lost me at Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally being honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should have called you when it was on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to find them on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got to see this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might find them on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were all... It was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Kevin6L8 in our chatroom, maybe that's Kevin6L8 in our chatroom, says, In my store, about a good third of the people buying are teen to young adult girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buying what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming like DS and related systems, or maybe Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, why not Xbox?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's the same thing I was watching, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: She brought it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just to preface, I worked at a game crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I also worked at a store, you know, a few years ago, back before girls started playing games.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the scariest looking kaze I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_07]: She didn't even pay attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody cares.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a 70s show about a bird ninja team.
[SPEAKER_10]: The science ninja team.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's talk about the Vita a little bit, because there's a lot of news on the PlayStation Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, at their conference, they had this slide talking about 100 titles already announced for the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things like Ninja Gaiden Sigma, Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3, Katamari, DJ Maxx Technica...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sound Shapes, Super Stardust Delta, Wipeout, Ridge Racer, Zone of Enders HD, Metal Gear Solid HD, Gundam Games, Super Robot Taisen Games, Tales of Innocence, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very interesting watching the Sony conference because they are doing everything they can to not fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they are trying to just punch Nintendo into jugular and I tell you what the delay of the Vita in the US I'm telling you is so that the lineup looks as strong here they are doing what everybody says Nintendo should have done and everybody is saying Nintendo should not have launched a 3DS until Christmas and so what the Vita is doing is the Vita is waiting and it's building up an arsenal of games so that when that thing launches here it's going to come out with a bang it's really interesting
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, the Vita does come out December 17th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The date has been announced in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are cutting it really close there with the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be way too late here in America to make the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think it would sell tons anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Sony's doing the right thing by waiting until next year because they're just going to dump a crap ton of games whenever it launches here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did not announce the date here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, something to think about, it was reiterated this week on Twitter, in a Twitter conversation with Sony Computer Entertainment President of Worldwide Studios, Suhei Yoshida, has reiterated the Vita is region free.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to import one of those fuckers on December 17th, you're good to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting the shakes already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Giving Nintendo an unopposed holiday season is not smart.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to at least, I mean, I'm sure that before the holiday season really kicks in that we'll at least know a date.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not going opposed in Japan, which is going to be the biggest battleground, I think, of sorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not too worried about the 3DS in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: because I think the games that they have coming out, they have, was it Super Mario 3D Land in November?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And other than that, Mario Kart's coming out in December, but later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario definitely is a draw, but is it a system seller?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing a Smash Brothers for that thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're doing a Smash Brothers for that thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: At some point in time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know how many fucking people bought the Wii because they put Smash Brothers on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I understand that, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: All Nintendo needs to do is find that one fucking title.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they've done with every system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every system people are just like, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Nintendo comes out with that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: One title.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which on the original DS was like Nintendogs or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everybody goes, I gotta have one of these fucking things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or fucking Brain Age.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: What happens if at Christmas that one title comes out and Sony's just left holding their sack?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not gonna, I'm sorry, it's not gonna First off, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: at E3, which they shouldn't have even really announced at E3 They were like, yeah, hey, I'm thinking about working on a Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: game Is it in development?
[SPEAKER_03]: No Is it coming out anytime soon?
[SPEAKER_03]: No But we're thinking about it, yeah Just like, we're thinking about doing a Pikmin game Where the fuck is your new Pikmin game that you promised us two years ago for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's never coming out
[SPEAKER_03]: So Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: for the 3DS, yeah, they promised that game's coming out now, but two years from now when it's like, hey, where's the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: game you promised us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're going to put it on the next 3DS system that we're going to put out, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: The 4DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think the internet as a whole... Were you trying to say something, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think the internet as a whole is being a little hard on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said hard on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, for real, because... Believe me, I have my issues with Nintendo as well, but I think the 3DS is going to sell bucket loads this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people are seriously underestimating the power of that Mario Kart and the Mario Land 3D games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's going to sell...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of systems this holiday, especially with there not being a Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong, the Vita is going to be an impressive thing and going to have a huge launch next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't do anything for this Christmas here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think those, like Mario Kart especially, is huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think they need to bring out motion sickness pills with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've gone through 10 holiday seasons in-game retail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Second Analog Controller
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's a whole other issue, but I'm just talking format stuff-wise, is the 3D movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were showing off a lot of this at E3, the year that the 3DS was shown.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Netflix on the 3DS, but yet we don't have 3D movies yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soon we're going to be able to record 3D movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, have you checked out the Nintendo video service that they've got on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but little five-minute videos?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking...
[SPEAKER_04]: When we were 83, they were talking about putting Tangled in 3D on a little cartridge.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Lion King in 3D was the number one movie at the box office this weekend from 94.
[SPEAKER_04]: They put that thing on a 3DS cart.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to sell like crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's so much cheaper right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they need to strike while the iron's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so much cheaper right now to invest in the 3DS as a 3D device than go get a freaking 3D television and glasses.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not going to be the case much longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come a year from now, next holiday, I think 3D
[SPEAKER_07]: Man, I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a 3D TV because, kind of like Matt, I'm a sucker for technology.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same time, as I've gotten older, I've gotten cheaper.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm just like, oh man, I am not going to spend $3,000 on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially as fast as technology is getting better and better, you're definitely in a better position to wait because as soon as you buy one, it's just like, oh, hey, look, we came up with this technology that's even 10 times better and it's cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I even waited and waited and waited about my 120 hertz TV because 120 hertz was supposed to be the 3D rate.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, on this TV now, we can do 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: When the 3D comes out, this TV will work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_07]: Great!
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gotta be 240.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you guys!
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you right in the ear!
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chat at chat.orange.com, HitStun says, Netflix is in 3D, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you would think it would be, but outside of the title screen and I think the menus, the content itself, not in 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows what might happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Kevin68 in our chat at chat.orange.com says, I'm not really into 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's more of a novelty to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I'm kind of there too, and I feel a little weird talking about hyping up 3D and everything, but I think for games, 3D might actually kind of be neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I got to admit, some of the 3DS stuff's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's a little bitty screen and so forth, but it's neat, at least for a little while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the Mario Kart game's going to be kind of neat, but I think there probably will be a point where I'm like, okay, let's turn the 3D off now.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, with Mario Kart, it's a perfect example of what Nintendo does wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Mario Kart, what they've done... Yeah, because every game only sells like 11-gajillion copies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that, because people are suckers and they're like, oh, it's a Mario game, I want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's not why it happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's because the Mario Kart games are good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not creative.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not innovative, but they're always super fun and anyone can play them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they just last.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one series that Nintendo really doesn't need to do anything to.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how they put out stuff and don't really do anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Animal Crossing, they change absolutely nothing and they put out the new game on another system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the new Animal Crossing you'll get to sit on a bench.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Swim.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's in a different camera perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoop-dee-shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But one series that they don't really need to do anything to is Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Mario Kart was always good as it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Hang Gliders!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Hang Gliders.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, you know, they've ruined Battle Mode after the 64 versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Battle Mode was ruined after the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 64 version was still fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was so good on
[SPEAKER_07]: Mode 7 Battle Screen.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was so cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Kart 64 is an awesome game that I haven't spent enough time on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, Block Fort was awesome in Mario Kart 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's where it was at.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, now they're just, they're trying too hard, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because with Double Dash, it was like, oh, look, you can have a partner, you can switch back and forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that was terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Double Dash was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then now they have, like, oh, look, hey, we're going to have motorcycles and monster trucks and hang gliders and underwater sub things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: One year that we set up like an eight-player system-linked Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was so great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody controlling the rear guy and just punching people in front of him was like amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me try to kind of move on the conversation a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Jamie, I want to hear from you for a minute because Nintendo is targeting women.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think the 3DS's chances are this Christmas?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be good because it's a Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, people buy Nintendo systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people are going to buy the shit that comes out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, imagine babies and fart monsters or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have a game called Fart Monster 3D?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they have... Let's see what would be the closest thing to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have pet zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can raise your own pet zombie.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're shitting me.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesomely bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would play that because it's awesomely bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, we got to get back to some of this stuff on the Vita because... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say if they want to sell me one, just give me my Kid Icarus already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, some of the chat is pointing out that Dan's audio is in and out.
[SPEAKER_04]: He does have the busted mic right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to put a mic by the door so that Dan would come in here and yell random shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: He might be encouraged to pick up a mic and say it into the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, the only microphone we have is the half-busted one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I apologize for the shoddy audio quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, now we can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just hold the cord in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you just have to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to kind of just kind of push it together like it's falling apart.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: More Vita news.
[SPEAKER_04]: My husband's a prevert.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mentioned this in the overview of what all games are coming out, but I just kind of want to revisit It was announced that Zone of the Enders HD Collection and Metal Gear Solid is coming to the Vita As well as Ninja Gaiden, Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3, Katamari, and this was the huge bombshell that was dropped
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy X Remake or HD version or whatever they're calling it is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to do a remake of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy X. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't go with one everyone wants.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just go with one that all they have to do is update a few textures on and boom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think you hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's far less work to be done with Final Fantasy X and they can get it done a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not even updating the textures.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just uprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just going to be up-res textures and polygons.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be Konami quality.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a lot of Twitter rage on 7 fans versus 10 fans this week when the remake was announced, I noticed.
[SPEAKER_04]: The answer seems obvious to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: 10 is just an easier thing to remake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both games are equally popular in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: well yeah, um, up-rezzing it to HD is a little different than remaking the whole damn game, you know, one is a lot easier to do than the other, so that's why you don't have a set, because if you up-rezz 7 it's gonna look like shit and I don't know why there's so many 10 haters I don't know if it's because of like the whiny emo voice acting and stuff, but like Lulu is like one of the most badass characters like in a video game I really like 10-2 I really like 10-2 10-2's okay 10-2's fun and festive
[SPEAKER_04]: Some days you want to have crazy hat day.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the girl fest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: especially because there was like this whole area like when you're on that long road that you could just cycle back through your dress fears and like level them all up super quickly like over and over again if you had a couple hours to spend on it well who knows if Final Fantasy 10 sells well enough in a remake edition or what have you they might have 10 too give us 7 you whores here's my other question is and I don't know if you know this Loki but some people are saying that this Final Fantasy 10 remake is not just for the Vita that it's for the Playstation 3 as well yes it is wow
[SPEAKER_04]: That's neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kevin68 makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Arun was badass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was so badass they put him in Kingdom Hearts as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: He was like the only, because you know I leveled through the game so quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I went through the game without leveling so quickly that by the time I got to that last, what was that fucker's name with the blue hair?
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, what about that Final Fantasy musical game they are making?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a 3DS, not a Vita game, but it's that Thetra Rhythm or whatever it was called?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looked dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the game was like $20 maybe, but $40, no thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to last week's show and the whole price tag rant because what are the Vita games going to be priced at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they all going to be $40 too?
$50. $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real?
[SPEAKER_04]: Vita games are going to be $50?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP games were fucking $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where have you been?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently my head's been in the sand.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't buy a whole lot of PSP games.
[SPEAKER_03]: $50 and $40.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be PSP priced, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe $60.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only price I've seen so far is on Lego Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was $50.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Seymour Guado.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, it was Seymour.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you want to see more Guado.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like fuckwad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seymour fuckwad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, that's the only one that... Because the only two titles that I actually have info on were Lego Harry Potter 2 and Dragon something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember the hell the other one was called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Dragon Dust or... Suddenly buying the Magicka Uber Edition for $10 on Steam doesn't seem like such a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, like, game pricing is so fucked up right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: it's we're in such this crazy state that we haven't been in gaming's history games have always kind of been around that same price but now we've got 99 cent Angry Birds versus $50 Vita games it's all about projection value though I mean look at look at the games that they're putting out now what they have to do they have you know Hollywood voice actors and not all games have that but they have you know
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: What about movies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Blair Witch Project was made for what, like a nickel?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you had Titanic, and it cost the same to see both of those movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I guess I understand now that with the 3D is throwing this interesting monkey wrench into it, you're not going to see independent 3D movies right now anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I understand that movies, when they come to theaters, are all the same price, but that's up to the studios to make that decision whether they want to have a high-budget movie or a low-budget movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because they've already had it out there and they've already made some money back from it already before they've gone and sold it on DVD or video on demand or however else you consume your entertainment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it really just depends on what the quality of the game is though and how much you're into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the interesting thing about Steam too is that it's kind of like one of those, well, once we've sold it to everybody that we think is going to buy it for 50 bucks, let's try to knock it down to 40.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can name that tune.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll buy that game for 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the same time, though, I have a problem with a game that's terrible that's being sold for $60 when it clearly looks like it's an up-res PlayStation 2 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, in the case of Activision and EA, where they put out Rock Band and Guitar Hero and they sell it for $60 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, dude, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's less production quality for that version of the game than it was the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Depends what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you're talking about games, there's no money to be made anywhere, but if you're talking about movies, then that's a different story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on with some more news stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could talk all night about how games are really expensive, but at the end of the day, seriously, if Civilization 6 was announced and they were going to charge $100 for it, I'd probably still pay it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't actually import that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought it at an import store and I didn't pay that much for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excusez-moi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, are you a fan of Lord of the Rings?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they've got a Lord of the Rings War of the North thing that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It comes in a quiver, a leather quiver.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember you mentioning that.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the record, I am not a Lord of the Rings fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: The movies were okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you a fan of leather quivers?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: The movies were okay and the books, the stories were great, the stories, but Tolkien's writing pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a fan of guns?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's a Red Dead Redemption coming out with a six shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want a gun?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just made that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You totally made that up.
[SPEAKER_10]: We actually went looking at guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want DarkSakura to get excited about a gun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want a gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want DarkSakura to own a gun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you'll shoot me.
I won't.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because someone has a gun doesn't mean that they'll use a gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but we're talking about you, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be safely in a locker.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I would go outside to shoot it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're red in the face.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're waiting until you get outside of the house.
[SPEAKER_03]: That way we can say you were a prowler.
[SPEAKER_04]: The next time Shermie shits on the floor, she's gonna get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, she can absorb a bullet.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be nice to the cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't shoot the cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like her better than anyone else in this room.
[SPEAKER_03]: As they put it in It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia, she's cultivating mass.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's cultivating sleep right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, let's move on with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony or bitches, wait, they actually amended their online terms to block class action lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually a section called Binding Individual Arbitration.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, to quote, it says, any dispute resolution proceedings, whether in arbitration or court, will be conducted only on an individual basis and not in the class or representative action as a named or unnamed member in a class consolidation, representative, or private attorney general action.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, if you want to use our shit, you can't sue us in a class action.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can opt out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can opt out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can send Sony a postcard or whatever and opt out of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to make specially made postcards to Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a big middle finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Opt out of this, bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's what it says.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you do not agree with the new terms of service or privacy policy, or if you do not wish to enter into an agreement with Sony, you may decline the TOS and privacy policy, and we will close your account and return your funds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so in other words, if you want to opt out, then fuck off.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't use our service at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not just a opt out because I want to sue you someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the only reason I'm like, whatever, Sony, is because the PlayStation Network is free.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of one of those, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, there is PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it also...
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says more, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says, if the class action waiver clause is found to be illegal or unenforceable, the entire section 15 will be unenforceable and the dispute will be decided by a court and you and the Sony entity, you have a dispute with each agreed to waive in that instance to the fullest extent allowed by the law in a trial by jury.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, this may not actually be legal and if it ends up being illegal, then forget I ever said anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: But AT&T, there's a court case with AT&T that already set precedent that this is legal, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much you can do there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does seem a little bit wrong to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: When am I actually going to sue Sony?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are they going to do to me that's really going to have me sue them?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can sue them individually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still waiting for money back from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm more likely to sue them before I sue Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's basically saying... Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, but you'd be suing on an individual basis and not as a class action.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Microsoft has nothing to do with Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, you can hire an attorney and you can spend all the money to sue them on your own and get, you know, maybe...
[SPEAKER_10]: $15,000, I'm just using an arbitrary figure, $15,000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where as opposed to a class action lawsuit with maybe a million users and each of them get $5, that's 5 million bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, think about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a way to basically save their assets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not asses, assets.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also because they're a bigger company and they have money to throw at this type of stuff, they can just drag it out forever until you run out of money to fight it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, it's kind of an intimidation thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of one of those, we're bigger than you are, so you can sue us and we'll just get scarier and scarier.
[SPEAKER_04]: But guess who doesn't use PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_04]: But, well, you may not use PlayStation Network, but as Loki said, AT&T set a precedent for this, so maybe Sony's setting a precedent for this in the gaming world, and by the time the Wii U comes out with its online service...
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll have something like this as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Xbox Live may adopt a similar policy when it does its whole little remodel.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think this really needs to be... Because basically it's like they're trying to manipulate the court system.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should have no jurisdiction in determining how someone can legally challenge...
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Pop is just rambling about this in our chat room, so I want to read some of these comments here at chat.orangelunchated.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is embarrassingly dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only reason why you'd ever need to be approached to be part of a class action and having that class action go to trial is because there's obviously clearly incompetent shit going on on a wide scale.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the point of a class action.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you try to form a class action and you don't have a case and you're just a butt-mad neckbeard, you'll be laughed out of court.
[SPEAKER_04]: Class actions are the only real way you can make a company pay huge punitive damages as punishment for their shady dealings.
[SPEAKER_04]: In an individual case, if you're in the right, yeah, you'll get paid well, but it won't be punitive damages kind of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Sony is trying to protect their wallet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like butt-mad neck beard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Makes me think of those guys that get up and ask questions at BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that was pretty much the point I was trying to make.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're trying to save money and not basically have to take any responsibility for the shit that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the end of the day, I don't really like it, but I hit accept anyway because I wanted to play my games online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_10]: That right there is the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, no offense or anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not pointing at you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's why they can get away with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because people will say, oh, I just want to play my games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's how they're going to get away with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's going to be too many people doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: How can you hold this company accountable?
[SPEAKER_04]: I still believe, even though whatever AT&T set a precedent, if they fuck up on the scale of the network breach again, I'm sorry, this little passage 15 isn't going to hold up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congress is investigating Sony for their fuck up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like they don't have a deficit or anything to worry about.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just... But the whole point is that by sitting around and doing nothing, they're going to get away with this as long as they can, and a lot of people are going to get screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is internet rage, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is how we're responding with internet rage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am very upset at Shoni.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there actually is a number of things you can do.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can write your, you know, your representatives to, you know, double check the legality of this because clearly they're not going to, you know, they'd have to evaluate it on a state-by-state basis too to see if any of that's going to fly because they have to deal with state laws as well and they can't stand in the way of, you know, legal proceeding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can send Loki's card with the giant middle finger.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to be serious.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: The whole point is that it's something that should not be allowed to pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marisa Congusto in our chat room says there is pending legislation about word salad legal agreements but this won't stop arbitration clauses which you are a part of in many areas that you don't even know of.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very common like cell phone agreements and just all sorts of anything you sign probably has some stupid arbitration clause in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: this country I'd be interested though how does Sony protect themselves in other countries because if they were to screw up again that might hold a legal thing in the US but did they have to do the same thing in Canada or they'd probably do whatever the equivalent law is you know have something hmm kind of interesting all right let's move on with some more gaming news we could talk about this all night but
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy X, the remake, is not the only Final Fantasy that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also, well, Final Fantasy XIV, I guess, is never coming out, but never coming out working, that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Final Fantasy XIII, too, though, is on its way out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is 90% complete as of Tokyo Game Show, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be available.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess the game itself will feature time travel, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is launching next year on the North American region, January 31st, and also Europe is getting it February 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Japan is, though, seeing it this year on December 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, they're also launching in Japan with an exclusive...
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 3 system that's pink and black and it's got a laser etched lightning on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Lightning Edition version 2 which will include a 320 gigabyte hard drive, the game, and a controller for the price of 37,960 yen or $495 dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does seem a little weird that they're releasing a whole new PlayStation, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't the Final Fantasy fans have already bought one for Final Fantasy 13, the original?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, as we said earlier, Final Fantasy X, the remake for PlayStation Vita and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad on that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: No big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had to mention it again because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something I'm going to probably pick up, no doubt.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I would love to see?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously this won't happen until they kill off the PlayStation 2 version of it, but an HD remake version of Final Fantasy XI that's free to play would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't I talk about this a couple weeks ago on the show that they were investigating dumping the PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you did mention that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, hasn't there been a rumor about XI on the Vita already?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there has.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you imagine if that game goes free to play?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wife won't have a reason to stop you now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: See, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only reason I stopped my subscription is because I don't get a lot of time to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it may be an hour or two every few days.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if it's free to play, who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't play for a few days or weeks or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not paying for it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go to this next story, which is, yeah, this is interesting, because this is about reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so we're going to talk about game reviews for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you know, Gears of War 3 is on its way out, and it's kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you're into these types of shooter games at all, it's kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game's getting good reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's getting a lot of great reviews, glowing reviews everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was an article, however, with VG247.com that Cliff Baczynski, or Cliffy B., did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking about Gears of War, let me read the little passage of the interview here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you pleased with the review scores this morning?
[SPEAKER_04]: Asked the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cliff B. said, doing great, apart from a couple of haters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Magazine asked, who were the haters?
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said, a certain gamer of the Euro.
[SPEAKER_04]: So kind of calling out Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was their problem with the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't read the review, asked the magazine, to which Cliffy B followed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I don't quite gather it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to come across as defensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do I phrase this properly?
[SPEAKER_04]: When people rated Gear 2 higher than Gears 3, it kind of upset me because I know Gears 3 is a better game on every level.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, here's the punchline.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like Eurogamer really trashed the shit out of this game, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which they have done to some games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that they put this game in the toilet.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game got an 8 out of 10 by Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they are haters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the game got an 8 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Care to elaborate?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it stupid?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want someone to start this off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, I mean, 8 out of 10 is good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's well above average.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, maybe it's like, oh, I wanted a 9 out of 10 or a 10 out of 10 because it was exceptional, it was perfect, we can do no wrong, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds to me like the issue is Gears 2 must have got a 9 or a 10 from the same website, and they dared to rate this game an 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Review scores you kind of have to take with a grain of salt anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not like they rated a game a 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there were some reviews out there on the internet that rated Final Fantasy XIII a 4 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Perfect example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, there's a ton of shitty reviews and there's a ton of really good reviews for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to look at your reviewer.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I always thought that one of the most fair reviewing systems was how GamePro used to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: With their little faces, emote icons?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: How they would pick one game and have five people score it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was an EGM thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was EGM, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is basically Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, GamePro used to do two people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did they?
[SPEAKER_10]: Back and forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I liked how you would have the main reviewer who would go over the major points in the game and then you'd have what everyone else thought of it and the average score is this.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, why does anyone give a shit what Cliffy B wants?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Cliffy B's a fucking douchebag.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is a fucking douchebag.
[SPEAKER_03]: He thinks he's a goddamn rock star because he has a few good games under his belt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yeah, Epic Games makes some pretty cool shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you act like a fucking douchebag.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, wah, your game got an 8 on one website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go fucking cry in a corner then, you little bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting, though, because if the game is that good, then the review shouldn't matter, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're so hard up on it getting an 8.0 and stuff, fine, why don't you blacklist Eurogamer then if you're going to take the high ground with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, my game was better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought so because I made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet the people that worked hard on Duke Nukem have ever thought it was a great game too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't see them fucking crying.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number one movie at the box office every year is rarely the most well-reviewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because a lot of people have no taste.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is a fucking douchebag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really know the guy and I don't watch a lot of television which we talked about earlier video game related stuff so I don't know I saw him once at E3 doing a demo I think at the first Gears of War game like a long time ago he seemed fine to me whatever I don't got a problem but I don't think an 8 out of 10 makes somebody a hater I understand you know I understand he's passionate about his game that's fine but you know what if I made a fucking game and one site reviewed it you know a point lower than everybody else
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't care I'd be like okay that's their opinion fine you know what if everybody rated it like a 1 or something like that or if like they came out and said I fucking hate the Gears of War series so I'm gonna give it a 1 out of 10 or something like that then yeah he could be pissed off but 8 out of 10 is just fine I don't understand what the big deal is well it was like when the websites were giving Final Fantasy 13 a 4 out of 10 I was like okay these are the websites I can't trust their reviews ever again because they're smoking crack over there they don't like the same games I like clearly remember
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, but if you're a gamer that's like, well, this thing can get a 9 out of 10, I can't buy this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I don't think there's anyone out there that's like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to buy Gears of War because you like Gears of War, it's not because someone gave it an 8 or a 9 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think an 8 out of 10 is just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the fact that he just went out there and said, Wee!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: 8 out of 10!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what makes him a douchebag.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw in our chatroom at chat.org.com says, You should never base your views on a game based on a game review.
[SPEAKER_04]: You play these games with an open mind and form your own opinion about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm mostly inclined to agree with that statement, and in theory, that's a really good statement.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the only thing is that games cost $60.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're on the fence about a game, you gotta go off something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I prefer that to be hands-on experience, be it game rental or game kiosk or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, usually I only drop $60 on a game on launch day because I've either A, played it at a trade show, or B, really liked other games in the series, so I've got to get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Civ V, I bought right when it came out because I like...
[SPEAKER_04]: the other Civ games Skyrim I will buy day one because it's an Elder Scrolls game I've seen all the stuff online I don't think it's going to disappoint me but games I'm on the fence about maybe I want to see some reviews on before I spend the money on it you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Out of 10
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll like this game if you like Japanese RPGs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then sometimes there's a game where it's like, wow, I don't care what type of games you're into, you've got to check this out because it is doing something that no other game does.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I think that is the best way to sum up a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's more fair, but the typical person wants to just say, oh, too long, didn't read, and go to the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't translate that into a Metacritic score, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you... Well, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metacritic's calling it an 80, but I don't know Destructoid's review scale.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could also be 4 out of 5 stars.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that's still 4 out of 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not 5 out of 5 or 4 and a half out of 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's still 80%.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a friend who basically, like, whenever, you know, we talk about a movie or something, he's always talking about, oh, well, Rotten Tomatoes rated this and blah blah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, yeah, but what did they say about the movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: What did they say about the acting?
[SPEAKER_10]: What did they say about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I don't really give a crap what the score is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I care what the part, because Vinny and you know me, I like, you know, movies that people have blasted, if there's fun parts in them, I'll watch the movie again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go see it again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care, because I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite movies are like stupid movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Mystery Science Theater 3000 types of events.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I like Showgirls so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Showgirls is a terrible fucking movie, but it is so much fun to watch.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: With friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you remember my bachelorette party.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did we watch?
[SPEAKER_10]: Barbarella and Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we went to the goth club.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was the last time I went to the goth club was your bachelorette party.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, I think that was the last time I went too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, to that one anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: let's move on, let's move on DarkSakura, you got a quick story for us and then release dates
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, basically, Microsoft is saying that Windows 8 will support Xbox Live, but they're not really saying anything else about games for Windows Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just basically like, their actual spokesperson said, and I quote, we currently have nothing to announce beyond the statement that Major Nelson posted on his blog.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, what I'm thinking is that you're going to be able to manage your Xbox Live account and maybe some games will cross over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I could see some type of messenger or video chat tie-in or Skype or whatever ultimate direction they go in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think just a way for when you are signing into your computer, you are still within the Xbox Live network.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I'm wondering about is that does this mean that they've talked about going more an app-style direction with Windows 8, which obviously is something that-
[SPEAKER_04]: You can, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're calling the desktop is like a type of app.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But obviously they're going that more Apple route, which is not too surprising, especially because this runs on tablets.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's my question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that mean, and I'm totally inferring here, but does that mean that apps will be run in Microsoft Points and maybe your points are used across systems?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be very convenient.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's how they did it with Zoom, I thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Zoom marketplace wasn't all together.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could, yeah, and it could.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, you know, games for Windows Live or whatever ran in real dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live does use real dollars in one portion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the buying the old games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games on demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games on demand, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It uses real dollars as opposed to the Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it could go either way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and with points, you know, you're always going to have leftover.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to have an odd amount.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they've arranged it that way to where you buy them, you're going to have some leftover.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you want to get anything else, you've still got to have that odd amount.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not anymore, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have changed the denominations that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but depending on what you're buying, I still find myself left with like 80 points floating out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're buying a card or something like that where it's $20, $50 increments, then yes, you may be left over.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they actually do have it now where you can buy 800, 400.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they want you to do that where like, oh, I have 80 points in my account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could get this stupid little hat for my avatar for 80 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never think of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never think that at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of people do.
[SPEAKER_03]: My only crazy purchase I ever did on PlayStation Network was dressing my character up like a hobo Santa and I am still hobo Santa in home which I have not been to forever so probably dead hobo Santa at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and to be fair, I did buy the Taylor Swift microphone for my avatar on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, the only thing that I bought is I had leftover points and I bought one of the steampunk tops just because I thought it was really cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we've all been guilty of buying some stupid shit online.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Hope Santa is not free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of buying stupid shit, let's travel around the globe and talk about what games are coming out real soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Quest Monsters Joker 2 Kirby Mass Attack Supremacy MMA PlayStation 3, Xbox 360 Touch and Play Collection Nintendo DS Frogger 3D
[SPEAKER_03]: The 7.0 worthy Gears of War 3 Coming out on Xbox 360 this week Also in the limited and epic edition Jewel Time Deluxe on Nintendo DS Girls only on Nintendo DS Shimogami Tensei Persona 2 Persona 2 Innocent Sin on the Playstation Portable
[SPEAKER_03]: Barbie, Jet, Set, and Sile on the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, they have girl games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pinball Hall of Fame on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Harvest Moon, Tale of Two Towns on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brunswick Pro Bowling 3DS for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Formula 1 2011 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 Emily the Strange Strangerous on Nintendo DS They're also re-releasing The Elder Scrolls 4 Oblivion Game of the Year Edition on all three platforms PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC And that's it
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX 360 Gears of War 3
[SPEAKER_04]: That is all coming out in Japan this week, as well as Champion Jockey, G1 Jockey, and Gallop Racer, because they love horsey racing games over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the PlayStation 3, I imagine you're going to see a lot of similar things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you get Champion Jockey there, too, but no Gears of Warc.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Two Heart is an anime series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, well, this is the sequel, DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's regular and limited edition coming out from Aqua+.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of games coming out on PlayStation 3 this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going over to some of the other consoles, I want to look at the handhelds in Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Vita, Sony PSP, Monster Hunter Portable 3rd, Busou Shinki Battle Masters, Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: 5Ds, Tag Force 6, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Not this week, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a ways off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just was reminded of it reading these dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Wii this week, a Biohazard Chronicles value pack that comes with Umbrella Chronicles and Darkside Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are Resident Evil games, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: They call them Biohazard over there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 3DS this week, Loki's favorite, Frogger 3D comes out on the 3DS this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't like that, maybe you'll like Senran Kagura, Shujotachi no Shine comes out this week, which is a, I don't know, what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Little schoolgirls partying in 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much what it is, aren't they all?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's go to Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Europe, we have games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And starting on, when does the week start again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Starting on the 20th, we have Burnout Crash on 360 and PlayStation 3, Fallout New Vegas Lonesome Road on PC, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3, Gears of War 3, and Resident Evil Revival Selection.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 21st, we have Rotastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the 23rd, we have Supremacy MMA, F1 2011, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, just a few more stories for you guys before we get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I think we talked a little bit about it last week, how there was a cable company in Canada that was actually throttling internet speeds with gaming on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's actually a little bit of a follow-up to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Canadian Radio and Television Telecommunications Commission, that's a mouthful,
[SPEAKER_03]: cited that Rogers' own policy which claims that the online games like World of Warcraft should not be throttled and telling the company it has now until September 27th to present a plan that keeps World of Warcraft traffic and that of other games unthrottled.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess that's good news for Canada.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wish we had people that actually had power over here in the United States do that kind of thing because internet cable companies are running like crazy and
[SPEAKER_03]: GameAustralia GameAustralia
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Clearly this is all just to be provocative and I'm kind of surprised no one over here has tried this yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just getting people talking and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, that's really all there is to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, you know, to look like a wiener and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, it is drawing complaints, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not everybody likes this.
[SPEAKER_04]: How dare you use two fingers to look like a butt in the cutout of the card?
[SPEAKER_04]: Complaints have been filed with the ACCC, that is the Australian Competition and Consumer Commission.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game has not acknowledged or commented on these complaints.
[SPEAKER_04]: When questioned about these cards, they just talk about how great the reward program is and all the stuff that they can get back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've decided to relaunch the reward card program with its extra benefits, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wiener is you
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, a winner is you right now because right now we're going to go through the gaming archives and find a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week DarkSakura dives into the gaming vault and pulls out a game that she thinks, hey, you kids need to show this game more respect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw the Vita and screw the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back in my day, this game was the bee's knees.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can make better boobs in chat than Kevin68 can.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, my boobs are a lot better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Today's game is The Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, The Sims, the game that started it all and why we're all playing that stupid game on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, The Sims is a game where... Is this actual game noises?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's actual game noises.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're playing in a fast forward, which is like the best one I could find.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's a life simulation game, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was designed by Will Wright, which you know what else he did.
[SPEAKER_10]: SimCity.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bob the Sim or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you've got NPCs and you've got your actual Sim.
[SPEAKER_10]: And your Sim can interact with the NPCs and get married.
[SPEAKER_10]: You eventually will be able to control the Sim that they marry, blah blah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you have different stages of life.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have an infant, a child, and an adult.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's just in the Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: Babies will grow into children and children and adults never age.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that means that they can stay in their little lifespan indefinitely, but they can die from different stuff like burning to death, drowning in a pool, starving, dying from disease, and the Grim Reaper will come and take them away.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you have to win against them in rock, paper, scissors, or your sin will actually die and stay dead and your tombstone will show up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like in Sims 3 how, you know, if you kill a Sim, they'll just start haunting the house.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, you've got Live Mode, which is where you do all your gameplay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you have Build and Buy Mode, where Build Mode is where you build your house.
[SPEAKER_10]: You start off with 20,000 simoleons, which is their money system.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you've got Buy Mode, where you can buy house parts and do stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So in your lives, your sims do have a little bit of free will.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can, you know, autonomously do stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can control, I think, the level of their free will.
[SPEAKER_10]: But basically, you still have to make them pee.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to make them find a job and pay their bills and work out and, you know, make babies and shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: You!
[SPEAKER_04]: Go make a baby!
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was funny, because this actually mentions that their system of needs follow Maslow's hierarchy of needs, in which the physiological needs must be satisfied before other needs can be attended to.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, they'll piss on the floor if you don't tell them to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if you forget to build a toilet, which I had a friend do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or if they don't eat, they'll die of starvation.
[SPEAKER_10]: And their needs, their physical needs are what govern their mood.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the more that their needs are taken care of, the better mood that they'll be in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got needs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or, for example, if you're playing the SimSocial, you know how you don't get inspired until all your needs are in the green?
[SPEAKER_10]: Same diff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking I'm done with SimSocial and I'm going to block it on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like my house.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate the spammy spam.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's getting bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know they put a feedback window where you can leave them feedback about not liking any of that?
[SPEAKER_10]: So you might want to try leaving feedback first.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got feedback.
[SPEAKER_13]: Block.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, so basically, it's kind of like an artificial life program, if you look at it in that respect.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can keep playing and playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the first Sims, I used to just kill people all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody did that with the Sims at first.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to create creative death traps for your Sims.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a way of getting out of stress.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of my friends actually had what she called the House of Death.
[SPEAKER_10]: And like, it was all kinds of ways that, you know, they could set themselves on fire and things.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she had a graveyard in front of the house.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Julie's house, Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure you remember that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, with your kids, they can study at home and keep their grades up, but if they miss too many school days, they are transported to a military academy indefinitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: and they can't prepare food or earn money so basically they're useless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Children are useless.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, basically, your sims can fight with other sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: They do stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they can actually be locked into an undead state by keeping them from leaving the hot tub or the bed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so they'll keep interacting with other people, but they won't be able to leave.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can't leave.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they don't prune or anything?
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't die.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just undead.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, in the first Sims, it actually did use a combination of 2D and 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Sims themselves are 3D, but everything in it are pre-rendered.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the game clearly has been a success.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sold more than 6.3 million copies worldwide.
[SPEAKER_10]: And as of...
[SPEAKER_10]: As of February 7, 2005, that's 16 million copies shipped worldwide.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, it's been highly pirated.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the music in the game was done by Jerry Martin, Mark Russo, Kirk R. Casey, and Dick Spruce.
[SPEAKER_10]: And these people have actually, I think, gone through and done all the other sim music.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can actually buy soundtracks of all the sim music.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's got its own little unique, perky little style, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, this is the part that I am interested in, in particular, is Simlish.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, they wanted to avoid a way to, um... They wanted to avoid localization of spoken dialogue.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the best way for them to do it was to create a language.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now Simlish... Can I play some of the songs in Simlish?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're really bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Find the Lily Allen one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Find the one for Smile, because it was actually really cute and the video is adorable.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a Nelly Furtado one, by the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: This kind of reminds me of Kidz Bop.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nutley Furtado was actually kind of cool too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Baby language bop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the whole point with Simlish, oh, and didn't Katy Perry do Hot and Cold?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, here's one for Salacious Pop, who I know is a huge fan of this artist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny, that's what I hear when I hear this song.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you play it backwards, it's devil speak, and that's why she's popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, they're... Listen, she's... Listen, play it backwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's saying that she killed Michael Jackson to get that record.
[SPEAKER_10]: So bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: But actually, these little videos that they did for him were really cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, anyway, Simlish is really a bunch of gibberish.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they were gonna actually base it, they created it by experimenting with Ukrainian, French, and Tagalog.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he wanted to base it off of Navajo, but instead just went for gibberish that sounds like the same inflections that you'd hear in everyday speech.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really got those bitches to sing in a baby language?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did somebody convince Katy Perry that's a good idea?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cha-ching!
[SPEAKER_03]: You like money, bitch, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's some money!
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a special about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched one of the behind-the-scenes for The Sims 3 about them recording some of the songs in Simlish.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically, they are just nonsensical things that fit the phrasing of the original song.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're like, you know, it was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, it's kind of neat to see the Sim version of me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, so, like, besides being paid, I've seen a lot amounts of money.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, they said it was fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just showed what the lyric sheet looked like.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was all, me ma boo, ma ma ma me, horgy wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, whatever they say in Simlish.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um... The different expansions were Live Enlarge, House Party, Hot Date, Vacation, Unleashed, Superstar, Superstar, and Make It Magic, which was the last one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Sims 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we have Sims 3 now.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, honestly, I think Sims 2 was kind of better than Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I really like Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except it's so fucking slow!
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: in Sims 2 they had custom build the fucking universe they had a custom Sims maker where you could try on skins and different things and really just do all kinds of neat stuff to them and now like in Sims 3 you can adjust their boob size there's model modifiers built in like you can change all kinds of features on their face and everything but people have gone further and made boob modifiers and butt modifiers and hip modifiers and
[SPEAKER_10]: There's even elven ear modifiers where you can give them a combination between Tolkien-style elven ears and WoW-style elven ears.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or you can just give them really huge Dumbo ears.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, that's just, you can farm.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can, now, the first thing that I did whenever, in Sims 3 now, whenever I just, you know, met some random person and ended up marrying them, like, my Sim was carrying around like a relationship with five girls and two dudes.
[SPEAKER_10]: for some time and finally ended up marrying some girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sim slut.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally ended up marrying some girl, except her model was really crappy, so you can actually go into the stylist mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you saying you bought your wife a ton of plastic surgery to fix her up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I made my wife look not... Honestly, the original Sim faces in Sims 3 were really derpy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now there's all kinds of special skins and hairs and stuff that doesn't look too derpy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, the first Sims is what started it all.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played a good bit of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played a lot of Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Sims 2 was the one where they figured out how to crack the animation code and started having dirty things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like you could buy dildos and a rug that had butt sex animation and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is a well-timed classic game of the week because, you know, The Sims is or was like the biggest PC game ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have got beat by World of Warcraft eventually, I don't know, or one of the Blizzard games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But The Sims is still a huge, huge PC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And obviously with The Sims Social now being like a huge Facebook game, despite the fact that that thing spams the shit out of all your friends while on Facebook, it is topical to make sure you know where that comes from.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure everybody has that story about, you know, terrorizing Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now here's actually a little bit of news that I just found out I wasn't aware of.
[SPEAKER_10]: On May 25, 2007, there's a Sims film rights were purchased by Twin Century Fox being written by Brian Lynch.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fuck would you do in a Sims movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a movie about life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone's walking around with a little plumbob over their head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless it's like a cartoon or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the original Sims site by Maxis has been disconnected for 11 years and is now replaced by the Sims 3 site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that it on Sims?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bork Me Do.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims.
[SPEAKER_04]: By Maxis for the PC, although now it's all EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all part of that big, you know, glomerate.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for Part A here of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got plenty more coming in Part B. We're going to talk a little bit about a new tablet coming out that's very interesting, something that Microsoft's launching at the end of the year, and somebody whining about secondhand sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the FUs of the week, your calls, rapid-fire news, and much more when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live on this September the 18th of 2011 with the 428th episode of our program.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had a pretty fun Part A so far, talking about the latest in 3DS as well as Vita and reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh, there was just a bunch of stuff in Part A tonight, so let's see if Part B will be as much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget your phone calls coming up later in the show at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're also going to get to those emails at Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com and Twitter topics, Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to get in your Twitter topics now, it would be a great time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of looking a little thin on Twitter right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess still everybody's being distracted by the Emmys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Email's pretty thin too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me just spoil it for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Modern Family won everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't really read up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a funny show though, I guess, if you're going to watch something.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get into some rapid-fire news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Saints Row III, of course, it was being shown at a Tokyo game show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, really, it's a game that's kind of more for Western audiences, but one man in particular, though, in Japan, is very interested in the series, and he's kind of crazy himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomonobu Itagaki, you may remember him as the driving force behind Team Ninja and the Dead or Alive series and now his new game, The Devil's Third.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other cool stuff was being shown off at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Project Draco.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what Project Draco is, it's kind of like a spiritual successor or inspired by Panzer Dragoon game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be a Kinect title.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: And looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very, very much like Panzer Dragoon based on the video that I've seen for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: very very cool
[SPEAKER_03]: and then this is kind of neat they've done a remake of Smash Brothers called Super Smash Land not Nintendo this guy named Dan Fornes he put out Super Smash Land features 11 different stages 6 brawlers including Mega Man classic arcade mode and multiplayer up to 4 people and they also have I guess a polygon team style endless mode as well
[SPEAKER_03]: with online leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can go check out the full game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have it available to download as well over at PixieGeek.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it now before the season desists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it is done in the style of the Game Boy, so all that monochrome, grayish-green, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's try to get that chat to the chat room as well as the Tumblr, which I keep forgetting to plug, but it is there at orangelaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a link on the left side called Extended Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a link to our Tumblr, orangelaundry.tumblr.com, because we're hipster as hell and have a Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's it for your news, too, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me get to my rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, Rock Band!
[SPEAKER_04]: Nirvana has a bunch of songs coming out in Rock Band this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heart-Shaped Box, Rape Me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's a family-friendly song.
[SPEAKER_04]: All Apologies and You Know You're Right are all coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are actually some really big Nirvana songs, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a celebration of the 20th anniversary of Nirvana's Nevermind album, although it's weird because none of those tracks were actually on Nevermind, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: If I'm not mistaken, never mind, that whole album was already released into rock bands some time ago, maybe for the 15th or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are doing pro guitar and bass upgrades for plenty of Nirvana songs, including Smells Like Teen Spirit, The Live Lithium, and Come As You Are Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of those are getting upgrades.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually like 10 songs getting upgrades, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can use all three chords?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you are a Nirvana fan, you're going to have a happy week in Rock Band this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard DarkSakura give a little squee at this next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you are a fan of Capcom fighters, one of the missing ones is coming out on the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cyberbots Full Metal Madness.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Cyberbots is Capcom's number one game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a quote from Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Devilot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, that is coming out on the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that coming out in America too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or just Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I imagine it will probably come out in both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Time to hook up to Saturn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you like your Capcom fighters, that's going to be a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not like they have a lot of Japanese change in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tokyo Game Show produced from Square Enix this music sampler.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the music sampler CD 2011 Volume 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: However, there's some interesting arranged music that has tracks on the sampler CD Piano Collections, Final Fantasy 1, 2, 3 An El Shaddai remix album called El Shaddai and the Astrals That's kind of interesting Also, I guess something called Cafe SQ Which is supposed to be some type of musical tribute to Second Detsetsu The 20th anniversary of that as well
[SPEAKER_04]: So, pretty interesting there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's already being given out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The sampler is being given out at Tokyo Game Show, but the rest of those CDs probably throughout the next couple quarters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I misquoted the line.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's what?
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't recognize me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Cyberboss is Capcom's number one game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50 points from Gryffindor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Portal is free!
[SPEAKER_10]: Very, very free on Steam until September 20th.
[SPEAKER_10]: But go get it now because it's Steam and Portal and it's free and very short and makes me throw up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next up, Knights of the Old Republic is going down to £3.50 on Steam this weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it's a whole half price on all of the Star Wars games and the same goes for the US only in dollars and cents.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you want to get your scrotour on, go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you just call it Skrotor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so mature.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Batman Arkham City will actually have another character in it, Deadshot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he will be in there to take out a series of high-value targets so Batman has to protect them.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also other characters in there are Rocksteady and Joker, Hugo Strange, Two-Face, Harley Quinn, Riddler, Poison Ivy, Mr. Free Penguin, and the Calendar Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That Arkham City game is going to be pretty sweet, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Scrotor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, definitely get the free Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just obviously a draw to get more people on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody already got this like two years ago when it was free before... When it came out on Mac.
[SPEAKER_10]: When Steam for Mac came out, then Portal came out for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if for whatever reason you've been resistant to Steam or you didn't get it last time Or if somehow you're the one person that hasn't played Portal yet You really should just try it I'm not just saying that It is a pretty fucking rad game It's really awesome, it's super cool Even if you hate first person shooters, it's more of a puzzle game I don't like first person shooters and I play the hell out of Portal 2 And Portal 2 is so fucking good I know
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we get back into some long-form news, I want to give a plug for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't talk about this at the beginning of the show because I wanted the people that really stick with the show and who stick with it to really hear this because you're going to hear this on a lot of podcasts over the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that time of year where the podcast awards are coming around, and I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm always kind of on the fence about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like that it's a gigantic popularity contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a lot more fun the first year, and I'm not just saying that because we won, although obviously that helped.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was more about independent shows then.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seriously seemed like all of the independent video game podcasts that existed at the time...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: and possibly win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would really just... I mean, we've won before, so it's cool as long as some independent podcast wins.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's really important.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't want to see a bunch of corporate-funded, paid-for, commercialized podcasts get nominated.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to just kind of bite the bullet and ask, would you consider nominating Orange Lounge Radio for Best Gaming Podcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's www.podcastawards.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe nominations are open until like the 30th, so not too much longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is probably the only time you're going to hear us mention on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please, if you like the show, it's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't shove commercials down your throat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just help us get this exposure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all we really ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: Head over to podcastawards.com and please consider nominating us for Best Gaming Podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can only nominate the show in one category.
[SPEAKER_04]: You maybe can do Best Produced as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even have delusions that we would get nominated in those categories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Produced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, somehow, many years ago, we got nominated for Best of Life 365 Best Station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I know how we did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because our fans are awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And because not a lot of Life 365 stations had...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, he had the rock star type hair, you know, like the Bon Jovi style hair, you know, where they did have really long bushy 80s hair and then got it cut into that 90s cut.
[SPEAKER_10]: He had that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Brad from PodCulture is in the chat saying, I don't mess with the podcast awards.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't stand a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then I'll say go nominate PodCulture for best sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there like a sci-fi category?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got to be, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got to be like a fandom or sci-fi category.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go nominate PodCulture for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: PodcastWars.com, nominate us for best gaming podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nominate us only once.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's uploading.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the award that we won?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, on Pun Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would also be kind of neat, I gotta say, I'm not gonna lie, it would be kind of neat to have won that award in 2005, and then if we get nominated again, if, big if, I don't think any other show, certainly no other gaming shows, could claim that they've been nominated that many years apart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know maybe what other shows from back then are still going I think Video Game News Radio is probably the only one I think they're still going I think they're still live or they're not live on all games they do the tape thing on all games so maybe they they could get in there too which would be cool I'd be happy for them it's another indie show those guys work hard yeah so as long as an indie show wins at the end of the day I'm happy but if freaking
[SPEAKER_04]: Blank, blank, blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Corporate website wins.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to be happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's at least push some indie to the top.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I've said enough about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was four player podcast which I think actually I see some of them on Twitter so they are an indie thing I think they're like a Justin TV related thing they do a lot with that stuff which we used to do the video broadcast but they've taken it all to the next level I think they were the ones that won last year so that is definitely an indie show as well and if they win it again good on them good for them
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on though with more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to talk about that anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've given it far too much time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, so let's talk about GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how they have their streaming service coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we know that because of the whole debacle with Deus Ex and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's a little bit more to that as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've announced that they're going to be doing some sort of Android branded tablet thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: or I guess there'll be an Android tablet that's GameStop branded that's going to be paired to the dedicated controller peripheral that's going to be coming out later next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the thought is that the device will support, I guess, mobile apps and the goal is to allow full streaming of release titles to the tablet, kind of like on live or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting and very unsettling creepy to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, eh, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to release a tablet, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more power to you, but at the same time, the tablet market is pretty crowded.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll pass, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much what I have to say on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's going to be difficult for them to do that, but if they want to try, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not supposed to say the name of the company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how we feel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on to some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this isn't really gaming per se, but it's certainly that gaming device that you use for gaming that's sitting in your living room that's soon going to be your entertainment device, if it's not already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft is launching a TV service for the Xbox 360 this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of already knew that via E3, but it was confirmed by Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer at a financial analyst meeting that happened this past week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft is working with, quote, dozens or hundreds of additional video content suppliers.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a big difference between dozens and hundreds.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you know, working with one or a million.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somewhere in between there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's probably hard because they don't have a lot confirmed right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wonder if this is like Xbox's kind of way to take a jab at Netflix while they're down, which is interesting because Netflix is a big – it's weird because Netflix is a big part of the 360 right now anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of – Netflix has really had a hard past couple months, and it's just going to get worse for them when they lose stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: So –
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, their stock is tumbling.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Microsoft pays out the anus to get all these agreements that Netflix is losing, it could be the thing to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if their service is really popular if they just drop Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there any interest in a Microsoft TV network?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it's going to be included as part of my gold subscription, then sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell yeah, free TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially if they have on-demand stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if it's commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I get it for free, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get limited cable now.
[SPEAKER_03]: FX, I don't get that anymore because they're paying for limited cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually, my box has an error right now, so I don't get any on-demand whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I'd look forward to anything free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell, cancel cable again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would even just be happy if I could watch like shows that are on CBS just later when I want and not have to go on to CBS.com but like watch it in HD on my TV I would really like that like just being able to watch Survivor like the next day because Wednesday nights are raid nights so I can't watch Survivor live shut up don't judge me
[SPEAKER_04]: Cinderwolf is in our chatroom at chat.orange.radio.com a proud Canadian because he's saying and Canada gets shortchanged again as we have been with the internet TV feature included within Windows Media Center well hasn't this similar feature been out in like Europe and Britain specifically for some time like the Sky TV arrangement or is this like is this even beyond that like this is just a step further where Microsoft is now like trying to be the cable provider they're going a little further and
[SPEAKER_03]: I would prefer the latter because, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: If I want to watch on-demand stuff, I can just do it through my TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we're talking about my cable provider, I'd rather be Microsoft's own content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some original shows would be nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or just 1 versus 100 coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm never going to let up on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think Canada will probably get it eventually, but your way of thinking is probably right, because there's a follow-up comment here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cinderwolf says, content will be extremely changed and limited compared to US TV available online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, he's probably right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Canada will probably get it eventually, so will Mexico, so will wherever else Xbox does business.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, you still have tech TV, so stop bitching.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: I will swap you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can have all the crappy content that we have here and I'll take Tech TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it would be kind of cool if it would work the other way and we could get some Canadian shows here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because of the content laws up there, they get a lot of localized versions of shows too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or they had So You Think You Can Dance Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had Canadian Idol and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they have a lot of these shows anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be fun to watch tech TV and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's many countries that have their own version of The Office.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I lied.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on it tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best produced show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: For your consideration, best produced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is where you guys send us email every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura dives into the email bag and pulls out her favorites head first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless there's not a lot to pick from.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have one.
[SPEAKER_09]: One email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Holly D. Most popular podcast, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is to Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have the same birthday as my puppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: She just turned one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Smile face.
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will live longer than your puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_04]: What a rude thing to say!
[SPEAKER_04]: You apologize right now to that poor puppy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just... Well, actually, no, that's not a fact because I eat like crap, so I'm sorry, puppy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congratulations on your... There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnStrader.com if you want to be insulted by one of the hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send us an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always like to follow up the email bag with the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to get ranty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rawr!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I just gotta read some comments from chat real quick, though, because it's so important.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck the chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: SalaciousPop says, the puppy is better at not piddling on the rug, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad says, from PodCulture, says, gonna burn in the special hell for that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Randy says, aw, poor Holly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Holly, you got fans in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got your back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rude, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love puppies.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a cat owner.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a previous dog owner, since I'm a realist and I understand how much work it takes to have a cat versus having a dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dogs are awesome, but dogs actually need work to keep them clean and fed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cats are awesome and they'll wake your baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except Shermie, who doesn't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, FU's the lead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, tangent.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU's the lead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you to my headache that is now trying to come back and the increasing volume in this room.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't know how to use our inside voices on LLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we don't!
[SPEAKER_04]: This isn't my inside voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you're off music of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you to the woman driving a Ford GT car with the license plate.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the best part right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The license plate said, accelerate, love to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great advice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should take it yourself because you're driving 30 miles an hour in a 45.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're an old woman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that Accelerate Love Tube, but I'm an old bat, so I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, and by the way, the topper of all that, she turned into the bingo parking lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, she was going to bingo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to vagueness.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, vagueness.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm being vague.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how I feel about that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, neither do I. So let's get back into the show, get some more news out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get the Twitter topics and the Skype line coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we talked a little bit earlier in Part A about developers bitching and moaning about their games and how they're treated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poor my 8.0.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you get?
[SPEAKER_03]: A 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a different person bitching now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quadratic Dreams co-founder.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not even going to try to pronounce his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some French guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, he estimates that the studio lost between 5 and 10 million euro due to second-hand sales.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, we sold today approximately 2 million units.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know from the trophy system that probably 3...
[SPEAKER_03]: More than 3 million people bought the game and played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: On a small level, it's a million people playing the game without giving me one cent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too fucking bad is what I say to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the rentals or friends loaning their copies to other friends or multiple PSN accounts on the same PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_03]: Too fucking bad is what I say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Make an awesome game that people want to buy day one, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Heavy Rain is a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heavy Rain is alright, but it's... How much replayability is there really with Heavy Rain?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's a pretty linear game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you're done with it, you
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like watching a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you've seen it so many times, unless you're a super fan of the movie, you could probably get rid of it and be fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And his other comment is, now, are games too expensive?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've always said that games are probably too expensive, so there's probably a right level here to find.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we need to discuss this all together and try to find a way that...
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say reconcile consumer expectations, retail expectations, but also the expectations of the publishers and developers who make this business a worthwhile business.
[SPEAKER_03]: But once again, though, I don't feel bad for you that your game sold used.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too fucking bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where are all the other publishers bitching about secondhand sales from their games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Suck it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You sold a couple million copies.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's better than most games do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, there's a game that I may be more interested in purchasing new, and it's by this development house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, maybe I'm going to go buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But just this type of mind frame and stuff, to me it seems like the next step is, oh, I'm going to try to find a way to prevent the second-hand sales, and then that's where we get into the whole other problems.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's not going to go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, let's move on to a story about a game that maybe some folks would have bought new.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of people bought it new over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or put out more DLC because then those people who bought it used it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to ruin my transition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can buy the DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there is DLC for Heavy Rain, isn't there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, put more.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's talk about Rock Band in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know this, that Harmonix was teaming up with Q Entertainment back in 2008 to actually put Rock Band out in Japan, but it didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Q Entertainment actually walked away from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, apparently, Harmonix didn't end up ever putting the game out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there's been questions that have come up at Tokyo Game Show this week and so forth, because they did put out Dance Central, which is also coming out in Japan, Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: and in an interview this week they were saying that they were very much interested in bringing the experience to the Japanese market but there were just some challenges a lot of it had to do with the fact that you know trying to get all those plastic peripherals to an island country I guess proved difficult just the fact that people have smaller homes and all that stuff of course I kind of go well what about like Guitar Hero and excuse me Guitar Freaks and Drum Freaks and all that um
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix I guess at one point was looking at arcades as a way to do it but they said that arcades are very very noisy and if you're trying to make something that's really a musical experience and you've got 37 other arcade machines all turned up to full volume it kind of impairs the musicality of the experience um
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku in chat says, bullshit, Konami was trying to sue their ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't the lawsuit, the lawsuit was never about Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't it about Activision?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was Activision.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was Activision.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all been so long ago now.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2008, that was like three years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good lord.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just something about Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_10]: The European Oblivion 5th Anniversary Edition release date, in fact, if anyone's interested.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will be on September 23rd, and it will be £20 on PS3 and Xbox 360 and £18 on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be the Game of the Year edition of Oblivion which has the download content, add-ons, Shivering Isles and Knights of the Nine and in the box are the Making of Oblivion DVD and a color map of the world and the Shivering Isles.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we've had the regular Oblivion, then we had Oblivion Game of the Year Edition, now we're having Oblivion 5 years of Oblivion Edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also a Skyrim video thrown in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's not going to have the Steelbook casing in Europe, but it will in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if it's that same walkthrough video that hit YouTube this past week for Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a pretty good video.
[SPEAKER_10]: No idea, but people like Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't know that was in a steelbook case in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was just re-released with $10.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is the anniversary edition coming out in the steelbook case?
[SPEAKER_03]: In the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_10]: In the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's already come out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out back in July.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, the end of June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this is a new new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fifth anniversary edition?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the fifth anniversary edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it said it had the steelbook case in the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought the game like five years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to buy it again just because they threw in some extra shit that I already got.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you get ten bucks off Skyrim if you buy the game too.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you haven't played it, you know, it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, you can punch sheep in the face.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'll say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or let Loki say for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can join guilds and rob them blind.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the fun stuff you can do in Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks in chat are like, wow, Oblivion's that old?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's the same reaction I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, shit, I remember when that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was delayed from the original Xbox launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to be a launch title.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto is a lot...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big game series.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fourth expansion, Grand Theft Auto 4, surpassed 22 million units shipped, which brings the total for the entire franchise to 114 million units shipped since 1997.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently surpassed San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_03]: San Andreas sold 21.5 million units, and this, of course, 500,000 over that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto V
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically, you know, obviously it kind of came up with the whole sandbox gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, people buy the gameplay because you can do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can drive around, be a criminal, and do all sorts of crazy stuff with cars, shooting people, and then just, you know, recently with the PSP and then the, you know, Grand Theft Auto 4 and the episodes from Liberty City and stuff, you know, the multiplayer has been pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: San Andreas especially that was a great game and then of course the new one 5 is supposed to be kind of like at least taking place in San Andreas again so that'll be freaking awesome
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well I got one more news story for you guys and then we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or of course our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio but this is a very important story because I've been waiting like a year and a half, maybe two years to report on this story and it's not that I'm like particularly the biggest fan of this game but...
[SPEAKER_04]: This just takes me back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thanks to the Australian Classification Board listing, apparently an HD remake has been spotted of a certain racing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what racing game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Derby Owners Club.
That's right!
Daytona, USA!
Daytona!
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it doesn't have this song in it, fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolute fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do not purchase.
[SPEAKER_04]: Demand that this song be included.
[SPEAKER_10]: We know that the lyrics are taken out for the Sega Racing Classic.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still the music, but... Do you at least get the do-do-do-do-do-do part?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's the most important part right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, so we don't know when the release date is, but clearly it looks like something that's probably going to come out for Xbox Live Arcade or PlayStation Network, something downloadable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there already was like a Sega racing game earlier this year, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and I know that there are no announcements, and as far as I'm aware, no plans whatsoever to bring this game to consoles or portable systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you do a Carmen Sandiego game, it's got to have the theme song from the game show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, one more time before I open up the skyline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just please, one more bit of Daytona, at least until a couple weeks when it gets confirmed to have a release date.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I can play the song again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
Come on, put up the horns.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I may make people sing the Daytona theme song tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may need our listeners to call in and give us at least a do-do-do-do-do-do a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It depends who you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're someone that calls the show every week, I'm going to make you sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a call and we will...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you'll love this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: A mother of five met her online lover who was 16 in New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: They met on the game World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was a 35-year-old mother of five, and she allegedly lured a minor for sex after meeting him in an online video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my favorite passage of the whole story, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this part.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jenkins, who's the suspect, Angie Jenkins, allegedly made contact with the 15-year-old boy with the World of Warcraft video game, where players can talk with each other, according to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: attorney.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an online game where you're shitting me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They talk to each other now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, in inter...
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's be real, no one uses voice chat on WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: They built that whole feature in and ain't no one using it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's on Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The boy's parents took away his cell phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: She bought him a new one and then drove to New York to have sex with him in a parking lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Classy!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: footage of the cancelled Avengers game apparently made its way to the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is in a tweet that Tigerclaw sent us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not seen this at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn these fucking sponsor messages.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta get through these messages.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's come back to this after we take a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanna feel the force.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do not wanna feel the force.
[SPEAKER_04]: You wanna feel this phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: C.D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thunder
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say about Dead Island?
[SPEAKER_13]: and then it's almost like an RPG because you can upgrade things but it's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like you might have a gun in Dead Island and heaven forbid you actually run out of bullets and you can't use that gun anymore?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you mean when you say artsy?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how, like, that trailer that they put out had that sad little song and it was all in slow motion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very artsy, like, the way they did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, like, the game at the end of the day is a zombie first-person shooter, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is it, like, did they try to class it up a bit?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I didn't see the trailer, but it's very colorful.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's set like a jungle setting where you have all these different apartment and condo things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, how does it compare to other zombie games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it as good or does it suck or what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I haven't actually played it, but it looks really good, but I think I might want to play it if I could.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just assumed that he'd played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, what do you want to say about Driver San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you played Driver San Francisco or is this just like you want to?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like another want to thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you want to play Driver San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually heard a lot of good things about Driver San Francisco, especially the multiplayer, which is interesting because the last Driver game I remember playing was Driver 3, which was lol.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lol.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say about Driver San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_13]: One of the things I really like about it is there's parts where your body is floating above the city and you go into other vehicles and you take over another person's body pretty much.
[SPEAKER_13]: And when you talk, it's actually the person talking, but you're making them say whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that the whole thing about Driver?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to possess people?
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of float from car to car and you could possess a cop car and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Off a cliff!
[SPEAKER_13]: That's how you want to play, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a mission where you have to take possession of this guy and scare his driving instructor.
[SPEAKER_13]: So he had to make his heartbeat go up to this number of beats per second.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he says stuff like, oh, if you stop doing this now, take 20% off your next driving lessons, which there will be a lot of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kevin68 in our chat says, Driver San Francisco is actually good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then why did they call it Driver?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, because you're a guy who's a cop who drives around doing these different things, different missions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I think that's why it's called Driver.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, because it's that same concept that's been around since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can't get out of the car you're driving.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're stuck in the car forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until you drive it off cliff and then... Well, CD Thunder, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other games you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: There's one I'm really looking forward to, that Rise of Nightmares.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why Rise of Nightmares?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I like creepy games like House of the Dead and all that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking you're kind of a zombie fan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not completely.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And...
[SPEAKER_13]: So I've only seen parts of it, but it's not actually that scary.
[SPEAKER_13]: It might scare other people, but it's got very creepy atmospheres.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's also incredibly gory.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, before we let you go, CD Thunder, I've got to let you go so we can get more calls, but we have folks in chat requesting, could we get a few bars of the Daytona theme song?
[SPEAKER_13]: Day, Daytona, let's go racing, Daytona.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beautiful, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He had a little bit of vibrato in his voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Suddenly I'm Simon Cowell.
[SPEAKER_03]: You reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: There were some previews, people talking about Silent Hill Downpour and how terrible it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got delayed to next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Won't make it for Halloween, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if that's what they got to do to make it really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They got to polish it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why it's going next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably a good thing then.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what I've heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't seen the official move yet, but yeah, it's next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let me get to this Avengers preview.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been making DarkSakura wait here for so long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take a look at this here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is some of the Avengers game that was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if this game looks cool to you, like this whole flying around as Iron Man, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're never going to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to give us a call, by the way, 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all first person.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it'd probably make me throw up, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might be fun to watch someone else play for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, Sega's probably going to have a license for the Avengers game and it'll be a crappy brawler beat-em-up like the other games have been.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I would really like for them to do an Avengers game like they did Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be really fun because I love Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do kind of like the way that they've done this where it's like you really become the superhero.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you fight Super Skrulls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to see if there's any other clips other than just the Iron Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's Hulk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's clear that's Hulk.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: With Captain America, you see the shield on one arm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for sharing that with us, TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to one more tweet from TigerClaw at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think this is sadly the last tweet we got tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is about a... Oh, you guys will love this.
[SPEAKER_04]: An Unreal Tournament 3 mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they've modded on this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nyan Cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, they've modded Nyan Cat in Unreal Tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, because we're getting another call, but we'll come back to Nyan Cat in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, me.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would the listeners rather know you as?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miklatov, Shane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Miklatov, Shane, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about Shane Latov?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shane Latov.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you call in to talk about tonight, Shane Latov?
[SPEAKER_02]: I called in to talk about how awesome NeoWiz is and they released Tapsonic this week on the iPhone or iOS and it's really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I forgot to talk about that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I downloaded that on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: NeoWiz, what else do they make?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you said they're awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't realize it's the same company.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're partially responsible for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why you see a lot of DJ Max songs when you're actually playing Tapsonic.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the free songs is
[SPEAKER_04]: I just thought it was because they were both Korean games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell the listeners about this game a little bit for those that have no idea what TapSonic is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is free to check out, sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's microtransactions at the butt in the game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to play for real, you have to use those microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, as I was unaware, when you spend... If you were one of the first 1,000 people that downloaded it, you got 300 million points.
[SPEAKER_02]: and use those music points to purchase songs or so I thought you actually use those music points to play songs and you do not get to keep those songs once you spend the money on them so every time you play a song you're spending points so it's awesome I go back later I can just get a preview because I'm out of points wow that's kind of shitty though I gotta say I don't like that but I noticed the free songs rotate what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be okay with it if it was cheaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess the Korean version, our rates for song purchases are four times what they are in Korea.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're really getting screwed here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't recommend it past the free songs for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's worth to check out the free version for the free songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The free songs rotate.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one thing I noticed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a song show up the first day that I wanted to play again, and now it was a pay song.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a different song had showed up instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think they rotate a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't noticed that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've only seen the same free songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll probably do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of looks like a sound Voltex if you're following Konami games, in a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's got that Guitar Hero Hallway-style notes falling at you, and, well, I guess that's really about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's musical.
[SPEAKER_02]: so would you recommend people check out Tapsonic or no it's too damn expensive even though it's free to at least play the Mozart songs awesome I would say download the free thing and if you like it and you want to spend money on it go ahead it's not like you're paying 30 bucks to play three songs or something like that if you buy the points you know you'd probably get a good week's worth of play time if you don't play it like for hours and hours and hours on end so it's not so bad alright well any other games you want to mention
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I only called to talk about that since you failed to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I'm sorry, so just shame on me forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should be, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we let you go, Miklatov, can we get a few bars of Daytona?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, do-do-do-do-do-do?
[SPEAKER_04]: How hard is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: How hard is do-do-do-do-do-do?
[SPEAKER_10]: You're my hero for not playing along.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to make that big a fool out of myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll let other people that call in do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So since you refused to play along with the Daytona, you're going to get a failure noise.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you a golden wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd rather do that than make noise.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch how he dies though
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Nancat survival not guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_04]: High quality rainbow trail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just watch this when they actually nail him.
[SPEAKER_10]: He explodes in color.
[SPEAKER_04]: He explodes in a barf of color.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got more calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's... You're breaking up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you another shot there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your name?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's CinderWolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, CinderWolf, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just, you know, thought I'd call in first night I'm listening to the podcast and really loving it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great job so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of the stories we've been talking about tonight?
[SPEAKER_12]: The stories today have been great.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's awesome watching and listening to the conversation moving from side to side, top to top, going all over the place.
[SPEAKER_12]: I find it's really laid back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really impressed with the setup you guys have going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost like he called just to inflate our egos tonight, and I really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I already have a headache because my skull's not big enough to hold all of my ego.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no, it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hopefully it's not going to get too much larger than the studio.
[SPEAKER_10]: This isn't a very big room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's important to note, if folks have only ever listened to the podcast feed and never joined us for a live show, the chatroom is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even on a night like tonight where it's kind of a smaller turnout in chat than it usually is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid Emmys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, stupid Emmys.
[SPEAKER_04]: The topic will sometimes be about the show, but then it kind of goes into these related topics and lots of links and fun things to look at.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost like its own little stumble upon.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of like a domino effect of just sheer awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, right now, somebody is asking for the Nyan Cat video, so I said I would link that to me, Rob, and I'll put it on the Tumblr because we're putting stuff on the Tumblr now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that people will visit our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what do you think about 3DS versus Vita, Cinderwolf, since that's one of the big topics we got into tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a 3DS owner by chance?
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I'm not an owner of the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've had the pleasure of playing with it a few times through colleagues, coworkers down at the office.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really liking it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do love the option of adjusting the intensity of the 3D feature just because it's accommodating to everybody.
[SPEAKER_12]: The people that typically suffer from things like headaches or migraines with the 3D technology
[SPEAKER_12]: So Nintendo definitely made a great choice in adding that intensity feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go from like super gigantic headache to just minor headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: To like slurpy headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, going from migraine headaches to I drank a slurpy too fast headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what about the Vita, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Vita's coming out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you're a PSP owner or if you're into Sony stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about what Sony's doing over there?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I do like Sony's hardware and even Sony's gaming repertoire, but I'm not particularly a fan of their marketing mode.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, they tend to wait for the competition to see what they can improve on, and that's always a great strategy.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I find that because they're not trying to stay ahead
[SPEAKER_12]: in the push everything out first mode, I think they're losing a lot of the possible potential fan base.
[SPEAKER_12]: What I mentioned earlier in the chat room was that Sony waited for Microsoft to launch their 360 console and now worldwide there have been more 360 consoles sold than the Sony PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_12]: Xbox seems to have that much wider game repertoire to kind of cater to
[SPEAKER_12]: Except in Japan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yeah, I suppose that is kind of true.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I find that, you know, comparing the 360 repertoire to the PlayStation, you know, there really are maybe only five or six games so far, say for the PS3, for example, I'm really interested in that I haven't had a chance to play yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, it seems like Microsoft is hawking, you know, a new game every week that seems to be catching my and Eric's attention too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: so I'm feeling it'll be similar with the Vita
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask you one other quick question since you are a first time caller of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I always ask this of listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: This kind of helps me understand what kind of a gamer our listeners are.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say is your favorite video game of all time or if you're having trouble picking just one, one of your favorite video games of all time?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, favorite game of all time right now, it's an old game, I think it was released back in 1990 on the TurboGrafx-16 console by NEC, it was called Newtopia 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was sort of NEC and Hudson Soft's attempt at a Zelda killer.
[SPEAKER_12]: The TurboGrafx released a year before the Super Nintendo console.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it really has a lot of the traditional RPG elements in it, like the old Zelda games.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, great soundtrack too, even more so than, say, the old Zelda games.
[SPEAKER_12]: and I don't know, I find it a fun run right from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can do it in a handful of hours, five, six hours, but it's just very addicting I find.
[SPEAKER_04]: I absolutely remember the Nootopia series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you covered that on the show before, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have indeed covered Nootopia.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, it's good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: So one of the highlights of the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you brought up TurboGrafx in chat earlier, so you must have been a big fan many years ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, growing up, my family, you know, we didn't have the standard Nintendo or Super Nintendo console.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dad had the old ColecoVision and Ataris, and then we jumped right into the TurboGrafx mode sort of deal.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I kind of grew up playing a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And actually had the pleasure of finding one in a flea market about three years ago, so it's soaked up to the HDTV.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you had a duo before?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I haven't, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've wanted to find one, but other costs and other bills are kind of trumping that right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I can tell you right now, if you're looking to play any of the imports, that it actually is going to... We had some converter, but the converters hardly ever work.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you can get the core graphics really cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that is true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and I mean, although I do like the idea of the duo, it's kind of funny, my little brother back home actually hooked me up with a lot of the old ROMs and emulators, actually, that I can just, you know, I play on my own time here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the Magic Engine?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I use the Magic Engine actually for all the TurboGrafx games that are out there so far, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you have a fan in chat because GameGuru says Newtopia is awesome!
[SPEAKER_10]: Newtopia is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a good series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played it once, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's just a number, if you're really into TurboGrafx, there's a number of duo games that you've got to check out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm pretty sure there were two.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, my younger brother back home, a bit more of a classic-slash-hardcore old school gamer than myself...
[SPEAKER_12]: He's constantly telling me about the older titles that he's finding.
[SPEAKER_12]: But just one of the funniest things that might actually throw you guys off, that the one game on Utopia 2, the actual copy on eBay, $256.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're kidding me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that like just the HuCard?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that just the HuCard or like with everything?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the original CD case that came in on the HuCard itself, the little game booklet, everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's used, obviously, but yeah, $256.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, I think we got ours in a stack of games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, well, I'm sure my dad's going to kick himself in the ass when he finds out what it's going for, because I think we paid five bucks for it back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I let this call go on a little long, but that's okay, because he's a first-time caller, so those of you that call every week can just deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But before I let you go, can we get a few bars at Daytona?
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can only do the beginning because, again, I never decided to play the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Never really peaked my interest back in the day.
[SPEAKER_12]: But from what I heard, it's Daytona!
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of the jazzy version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Daytona!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a little bit jazzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A+.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thank you so much for your call and thanks for enjoying the show and tuning in live and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, thanks so much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll be around for the foreseeable future, guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: So thanks for letting me stay on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take it easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love Canadians, and we love... Clearly, I mentioned he was from Canada earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's in the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Cinderwolf?
[SPEAKER_04]: His accent was Canadian, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we love TurboGrafx fans, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So very, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: So what the heck?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a mod that he sent us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Super Pixel Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a playable Super Mario Brothers, but it's only 64 pixels?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's an 8x8 LED board that does Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can't imagine this at all looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's gotta be terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see what this looks like here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm trying to load up the video in chat, but it's... Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get points for hitting blocks, and under certain blocks, and I've actually made it random, you get 5 points, whereas just normal blocks you get 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now another feature I've added is Firepower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Different colored blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's literally the Nintendo ROM, but it looks like somebody made their own version of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine one of those old school LED games where there's only so many places you can have a cutout.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically these colored lights and the little Mario is like an orange square that kind of goes around and you can break blocks and jump on top of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, this is much more impressive than what I was thinking it was going to look like.
[SPEAKER_04]: And these levels are... It's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recognize these levels based off of the real game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been translated really well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's... I gotta say, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess, DarkSakura, I got one more link for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why don't you go post that on the Tumblrs.
[SPEAKER_04]: People who are watching Tumblr are going to say, it blew up tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that does it for the Twitter tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And before we wrap up the show, I always like to check in with Loki and DarkSakura and see if they have any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there is an Overclocked Remix album I think someone made for Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all guitar and metal versions of the song, so I believe that's free to download on the Overclocked Remix site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Overclock puts out some good stuff, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that is going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for downloading our show and supporting it and telling friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we really appreciate.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have a big budget behind this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have commercials and what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask, if you enjoyed Orange Launch Radio, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're like, but I have no friends to tell about the show, then tell an enemy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can leave us a nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help us spread the word around the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That whole nomination for podcast award thing I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll get more listeners next week, just like we had Cinderwolf tonight, who seemed to enjoy this program very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we wrap it up, though, for good, I need to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, we'll start with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know why my scroll lock button keeps turning on when I don't press anything to turn on my scroll lock
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those great mysteries of space.
[SPEAKER_10]: The world may never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm in space.
[SPEAKER_04]: That does it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for downloading us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will see you in like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God, that's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry guys, but I'll be having fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But DarkSakura and Loki will be back here next week with Tiara to bring you more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tune in and we'll do it all again in one more week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_05]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!