On this, the second week of thematically expected intros, Sonic 3 and Michael Jackson's involvement has, in my opinion, been officially confirmed.
Uh, I mean, the not-E3 delusion of news has begun, or I suppose continued, since there is lesser importance of announcements around the principal event week. Maybe next year?
Maybe next year? This is the intro you expected, kind of. Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers and Loki to tell you about the continued avalanche of gaming news, starting right now in the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello, my friends out there on the internet. Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio and we are live once again with episode number 918 of our show for tonight, June the 12th of 2022.
My name is Rob Roberts and joining me here, as always, welcome back this week from a week off last week. Say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers. Hi, um, who's muted somewhere that's not Discord?
No, I'm not.
Oh, the audio didn't come through. That's weird. Hi. How are you?
I'm alright.
How was your trip? Because you were, I know you were helping a friend move and you, did you drive there and fly back?
I was helping her move cats.
Ah, that's right.
On an airplane.
Oh boy.
I can say now that I have petted a cat at many, many feet in the air while drinking a mimosa.
You were literally herding cats.
Yes.
Okay.
By carrying them in a case and not actually herding.
Close enough. Close enough.
But, um, they were, they were well behaved on the flight, a little protesty in between flights, but, but it was, it was comfortable. I've decided that, I mean, first class and the Comfort Plus, I'm, I'm fine with either.
I'll stick with Comfort Plus.
Um, cause I get free booze, but it's cheaper.
Yeah.
Um, the house is really nice. It's a late Victorian built in 1913 brick, hardwood, big house.
And, and we walked to like a farmer's market and I bought myself something. Where did I put him?
Oh, I can't find him, but I got, um, I bought a 3d printed, uh, Falcor.
Oh, the luck dragon from, uh, the never ending story.
Yeah, yeah.
I put him somewhere and I don't remember where I put him anyway. I think he might be at work, but anyway.
Um, and it was just, it was just chill. I didn't really play much of anything until I got home except for my word scape game.
Well, we'll talk a little more about your gaming week in a little bit. I wanted to ask you, so Loki and I were holding down the fort ourselves last week talking about the weekend news.
And it was actually kind of curious because there was one story that came up last week and I was like, Oh, I wonder if Jamie's seen this and heard about it.
Um, did you hear about the Sega mega drive mini two that's coming out this year?
Yeah, it better be manufactured by someone better.
I think it is probably the same people to be honest. I don't think it's, uh, well, I mean, some of the components might come from better places. I'm not sure.
But I mean, it's, it's, it's cute. The, the, the make, I was looking at the, the mock up for it. It's pretty, it's pretty cute. I mean, and it's got some, some good games on it.
I mean, thunder force four and shining force and still feed and all of that. I mean, it seems pretty worthwhile to me as long as the emulation is decent.
Yeah, there were a lot of games on there where I was like, for somebody like me who kind of was a Nintendo loyal household through the years up until I don't know. So I was like, Nintendo, super Nintendo, and then finally hopped over to PlayStation.
But I think I also picked up a Nintendo 64. I kind of just missed the Sega boat. I didn't learn to appreciate Sega until later on when I got a Dreamcast for super cheap, you know, and then it kind of made me want to revisit some of their other games.
And so, like for me who missed a lot of the boat on that stuff, I'm kind of like, Oh, this would be a fun way to kind of revisit like things you missed along the way, you know, so I don't know, we'll see. We'll see how, how
probably grab one. We have the other one. Why not? Why not? Yeah, it's kind of how I feel about like the mini turbo graphics and the C 64. And so I was like, Well, why not? They're fun. They're fun. C 64 window would totally be you. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Well, I there I do have that original mini but now and then they did a normal full size one. I think there's another one coming now that they're because somebody was sent me a link to it. I remember it was Brad from Pod Culture Rama or somebody had sent me a link to a, like a full probably both a full size like C 64 where they're putting like PC parts inside of it. Like it sounds like it sounds like that Atari VCS in a way but like cooler because it's Commodore. So there's that.
All right. Also say hello. As he's here every week. Say hello to Loki.
Hello. Hi, how are you? I'm good.
So as we do tape live every Sunday night at the voice of geeks network twitch.tv slash v o g network, nine o'clock Eastern six o'clock Pacific, you get to see us. You know, as we're doing this show, I know it's a radio show, we try to keep a lot of the visuals minimal for that reason. However, sometimes we have some fun things going on behind us on cam like Jamie might be showing off a little trinkets or fortune cookie messages. And Loki is always has some game playing behind him. And usually I'm like, what's this game? What's this game? But this one I'm like,
okay, it's, it's Megaman two, but it's not because it's Mario. So is this that is this that crossover eight bit game? Now? I can't remember the name of it. Super Mario crossover or whatever it was called. What?
No, it's Rockman CX. It's just some fan game.
Okay. Oh, it's just some fan game. I see. What what did you do that this week?
I found it like a video of it earlier this week. And it looked funny because it's Megaman versus a bunch of other video game characters. Yeah. And common writer for some reason.
Why? Why not?
I don't know why.
Well, I like in the video right now. Megaman is fighting Mario fire Mario to be specific. So that's kind of interesting. So okay. Well, I like what the, you know, homebrew scene has done to a lot of those types of classics. I randomly started getting into like randomizers and that type of stuff. And there's a Zelda Metroid randomizer that I
Yeah, those are cool.
Z one m one. And I think that's really like fun. And so and I know I've complained about this on the show before. I'm sorry, I'm being the old man who's going to complain about it again. I really wish Nintendo themselves would see this and like capitalize on it. But for whatever reason, I guess they feel it's I think they feel it's too niche that like gamers wide wouldn't wouldn't care.
You're right. It's it's it's too niche to mix video games together or a video games together. Oh, wait, look at these games we released on the Wii U and 3ds.
Or yeah, well, any s remix? I'm assuming you're talking about? Yeah. Well, I'd love to see a new one of those. Like honestly, the last what they did to any s remix on Wii U, then they did a bundle pack retail. And then they did a 3ds one. I think that was
I think the 3ds was kind of like the same stuff in there. Yeah. And that was that was the last one, right? They haven't done one since I would love to see. And you know, everybody. Everybody was like, we want to s any s remix, right? Why not that for switch? Or hell, Nintendo's in bed with Sega now like time, times have changed. This isn't the 90s anymore. Nintendo and Sega have kissed and made up. They they they definitely hook up once in a while. And
they make this they make these they've gone from they've gone from the the hate fucking to friends with benefits. Exactly. It's exactly what it is. So so you know, why not a Genesis remix? You Do you think Sega would turn down somebody doing a Genesis remix? Absolutely not.
I mean, they might. Yeah, because they're dumb.
Bobby Blackwolf and chat says look, Rob, you can't mix two games together without crypto. All right. I forgot. crypto. Yeah, it's what allows you to take something for one game.
What do you think all those computations are for?
Exactly, exactly. Dogs and cats living together. It's only possible with crypto. I hope you all hear my tongue firmly planted inside my cheek. Zen monkey and chat says don't give them ideas. Nintendo is greedy as fuck. They'll probably charge you full price for all the games in the mix up game. Well, you know, we talked about Nintendo fun tickets, the the the NFTs that will make people pay
attention. Nintendo fun tickets. We talked about that on a previous episode, but I'm gonna leave that in a previous episode. I'm not going to go there again. All right. What I will go into again, some of the things that are going on in gaming this week. And some new stuff to talk about really new stuff. Because just today, we had the Xbox, Bethesda, and kind of surprising Activision Blizzard showcase happening today.
Loki, you want to walk us through some of the headlines out of the Xbox showcase? This is the only one by the way that I watched live all we all the others were while I was right. So this is the only one I got to watch.
I didn't watch it live. But like it was close to live because I was just getting back from the grocery store. But I saw I skipped through some of it. He's skinned it basically. So some of the thing. So yeah, so some of the notable things they showed off some gameplay. And they talked a little bit about, you know, speaking of Activision Blizzard, Diablo four. So that looked kind of neat with the character customization stuff that they have for that. And that's supposed to be
coming out next year that Diablo four thing they made was the best thing they've compiled on that game yet, at least for what is, to be fair, I haven't watched every deep dive on YouTube, because I've been a little about Diablo four. But this is the first thing that like, legit has me going, okay, okay, I think this game might actually deliver. And I think the secret sauce was, they had the game makers talking about the game, and not some
CEO president type hyping it up on a stage or whatever. I think what they did there was smart. I also want to talk about this, because obviously, you know, it's been I've been my brain's been in a really weird place with the Activision Blizzard stuff after everything that's come out, you know, within the last, you know, year and a half or so.
Um, and I realized that there's a lot of hard working people at Activision Blizzard that have nothing to do with Bobby Kotick. My point is, I think it was very smart of Microsoft to do this today, too, because you've seen a lot of like, good guy, Microsoft kind of things happening in just the past couple weeks with the whole, like, well, if Activision Blizzard were to make any unions, we'd recognize them after the, you know, transition. And, you know, well, we're looking, you know, you see a lot of
those types of maneuvers. And I think what Microsoft did by putting Diablo 4, and Overwatch, sorry, I'm jumping ahead a little bit Loki, but I have to, I think it was smart of them to do that, because they're trying to kind of be like, let's, let's move past Bobby Kotick, let's move, you know, let's, let's look at what the future looks like, with this being a Microsoft company, and not like all this fuckery that's happening under, you know, Bobby Kotick's
rule. I'm not saying we should forget it. I'm not saying we should overlook it. I'm not saying any of that by any means. But I think it's smart of Microsoft to be forward looking and show what Activision Blizzard can look like under their competent leadership. So I
appreciated that Diablo 4 and Overwatch 2, kind of surprisingly got such a focus today at the Microsoft thing when that deal hasn't closed yet. And that's, that's the thing to remember, they're not a Microsoft company yet. That deal still has to close. There are senators that believe that deal should not close, because of what Bobby Kotick is going to get out of it. And I do support that. I think it should be scrutinized, because I think Bobby Kotick shouldn't get a goddamn thing. But I'll, you know what, the
the fuss has been raised, the people that can do something about it have heard about it. We'll see how it all plays out. So yeah, that's my thought on the Diablo 4 stuff. Sorry.
And then Overwatch 2, they had a new trailer that showed off a new character, who I don't know has a name yet. But she's Junker Queen. She's been rumored for a long time. Okay. What else? So some of the Bethesda stuff, we had some more content coming for Elder Scrolls Online. So that looked pretty cool. And then also, more content coming for Fallout 76 with The Pit.
So that's gonna be a new area to check out and actually with Elder Scrolls Online, High Isle, which is apparently a new location that hasn't really been seen in a previous Elder Scrolls game. So that's kind of cool.
Question for both of you on the Fallout 76 The Pit. Are you surprised to see Bethesda even post Microsoft acquisition still investing as much as they are in Fallout 76? When that game got such a cold diarrhea reception?
I think they've kind of fixed it since then, but I still have no interest in it. But I think it's gone under like a lot of, well, just a lot of roadmap planning, fixing stuff. And I think it is a better game now.
There's been a lot of No Man's Skying to the game.
Yeah, let's not give them that much credit. But yeah, it has, it has no gone under much, much improvements, you know, since it launched, that's for sure. But yeah, I still have no interest in I'll play another single player Fallout game. But like, I really have no interest in Fallout 76. Because, because even though they've done all those, you know, cool expansions and stuff like that for the game, they also have
shoved so many microtransactions and stuff in the game as well. So no, thanks. I'll pass.
Um, and you know, um, I think what helps me kind of accept all of that and be like, you know, maybe I might try this out someday is that this whole thing we just saw this showcase was just one giant game pass commercial. Because I think Yeah, aside from those Activision Blizzard games, I think because I think those explicitly are not game pass yet. Anyway, I mean, we'll see. But everything else in there are like, either day one game pass or game pass or, you know, just
couple other watch to gonna be free to play.
It is but that's everywhere. That's PC and PlayStation all that as well. So yeah, and there's like, like Diablo four is cross platform, but they only talked about Xbox and PC. That game is still PlayStation five bound. But why would Microsoft mention that today? So you know, but it is cross platform. But anyway, my point was is that, you know, at least I'm a little more open to playing something like Fallout 76.
And even some of the other stuff that maybe, you know, doesn't necessarily look as interesting to me because it's all on game pass. And I'm paying for game pass to play other stuff I want to play anyway. So it's like, oh, just I'll just download this and try this as well. It's, you know, so maybe someday fallout 76. Who knows?
Yeah, maybe. Um, let's see. I mean, there's a lot of stuff. So we can kind of go through some of these not necessarily in particular order here.
Just to emphasize my point. Xbox game pass is how I finally started playing dead by daylight. After all these years, is because game pass allowed me to say all right, I can do this for free. We all know what I mean. I'm paying my subscription. I use for free and check it out. And then I kind of found out Oh, shit, I kind of like this. That I like this so much. I think I want to try to see if Jamie likes this too. Sorry about that.
Wait, you're now I know you're muted Jay because I see the icon.
Okay, I like him ended up by daylight on my own.
I feel like I helped. I think we got the receipts. We got the old episodes. I helped. But there's a lot of Twitch culture that certainly helped too.
All right. Uh, yeah, Bobby Blackwell says I can play this in my already allocated budget. Yeah, sure. All right. Now I'll sorry, Loki, I'll let you move on with the news.
That's all right. Okay, so obviously, the big thing kind of shown off at the end of the whole event was starfield. There was an extended look at that, which is pretty awesome. So it looks neat. It's definitely gonna be interesting to see how the game plays. They say there's like 1000 different planets to explore. And you can have all the ship customization.
player customization, you can build settlements, kind of like Fallout four. It looks interesting.
I'm so impressed with starfield. To be honest, like I'm, I really want to play it. The only thing that makes me a little bit cautious is that it does look like combat is a little bit shooty shooty bang bang, like Fallout games are I guess. And I guess even oblivion to some extent, except obviously, it's not guns, but you know, Elder Scrolls, you know, I mean, it's not guns so much, but y'all still get it.
Um, but then I think like Mass Effect kind of has gunplay too. And like, I don't like I don't mind it. And I can set the difficulty at a level where it's not particularly a blockade. And so I'm hoping as long as this game has like a Bobby Black Wolf mode, which is our slang term around here for an easy mode. As long as there's a Bobby Black Wolf mode in the game, I should be fine. And I think I'll really enjoy it. As long as it doesn't have like scaling difficulty or anything like silly life.
Like that, to be honest, you just have to set up your stealth Archer build, and then you're all good. Yeah, or the Mass Effect method is just if you play on the easiest difficulty, honestly, your squad mates will take care of almost all of it for you. So you just you're just telling them what to do, basically. So and that's fine. You know, it's it's how whatever works for you. Right. Right. Okay, so can I address the no man's sky comparisons? So yeah, I made those. Yeah. And a lot of people have been and that's fine.
You know, even in the chat when you know, because we were hosting it at VOG Network. And you know, I was riffing with Bobby Black Wolf on it. And I was like, wow, the space combat really looks a lot like no man's sky, like it really looks like no man's sky. But now some people have kind of taken those comparisons and taken them like so far as to like, IGN, of all places, put out this Twitter video, showing scenes from no man's sky and starfield side by side.
As to insinuate that starfield is a rip off of no man's sky. And that's the point where I'm like, hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up. That's, that's a little too far. Like, it's one thing for starfield to be inspired by no man's sky because yes, they are both space games, right. But to say that like starfield is like ripping every little thing or to insinuate, which is what that video is doing, that starfield is ripping off every little thing from no man's sky, I think is a bit ridiculous.
And I know I'm the biggest no man's sky stan on this show. And probably one of the bigger ones that you out there listening know, because I still actively play that game, have beat every seasonal expedition except the current one, which I'll finish up at some point, etc, etc. And I love that game. And I'll defend that game. And I think that game and starfield can both coexist. Why? Because art is always derivative of other art. Very rarely, very rarely.
Three is art, truly original, especially in games. And for IGN to put out that video, I'm like, and now but what happens is that fanboys latch on to that video and they go Oh, all no man's sky is just a rip or excuse me. starfield is just a rip off of no man's sky, Microsoft, Bethesda, unoriginal.
Duh, duh. Are you? Are you new here? Is this your first day in video gaming culture? Welcome. Welcome. And let me introduce you to this concept. All games are derivative of other games. And that video that you can't spell ignorant without IGN put out, you could easily make with Halo and destiny.
I Gran Turismo and Forza. It's members of Detroit and behalf the games that are out there now that hollow knight game they unveiled as well that looks amazing. And so on and so on. Street Fighter, and SNK fighting games, etc, etc. Like of course, it that everybody knows that. And the reason why they did that, though, is because it's
clickbaity. And this is how they pay their, you know, contract writers.
Yes, but I see, I see the the faction fanboys on Twitter people I know, buying into it cares what people think and this but this is your friend calling you out. Because when you have your tag sticking out of your shirt, what does a friend do? They say tuck that tag in. And I'm saying tuck that tweet in. You don't need it. It's it makes you look like you have never played a video game in your life.
Well, the game is like still like, you know, three quarters of a year away. So like, who cares? Like, I don't know what Yes, it looks similar. And there's the space game. I mean, whatever the compares. It's just dumb.
You know, and again, I am a huge No Man's Sky fan. Do you know what No Man's Sky is really missing? A meaty story. A story with really good substance to dive into. Yes, there is a story in No Man's Sky, which they patched in by the way, it wasn't the story in its current form was not there when the game originally launched. That's one of those things they had to fix was giving it a story. So if Bethesda RPG, the folks behind Skyrim and so forth are going to come in and give this a
real meaty story and bios on planets sitting in a library that I'll never read. I welcome it. I think it's going to be really cool. So you know, I do want to reserve my final judgment until I play it as most people ought to do. But I'm excited at the prospect of it. And to be honest, like when I heard that the
original vision for Mass Effect Andromeda was more like No Man's Sky, where there would be more planets to freely explore. So I thought that sounded really cool. To be honest, I kind of hope that's where the next Mass Effect games goes. But are we going to win Mass Effect, four, five, or whatever subtitle they give it when that new Mass Effect game finally comes out? Are we going to just compare that to No Man's Sky too?
Or are we going to compare it to Starfield?
Everything. We're going to compare it to all the things. Yeah.
You better boot up your Apple IIe's and Commodore 64's because mining for resources, and honestly pen and paper games before that.
Go play WoW.
Yeah. Go play D&D games from the 1980s because that concept goes way back. So that and that's the point I'm trying to make is that like Starfield and No Man's Sky being similar is not the end of the world. And you could put a lot of games side by side and find some very similar sequences in games where you have a
free roaming camera these days. Anyway, sorry, Loki. Again, I've interrupted your news with a big tangent, but it was warranted, dammit.
Okay. What else? Red Fall was a game that was shown off as well. It kind of looks like an action-oriented game similar to Dishonored, but with vampires. So that's supposed to be coming out the first half as well of 2023. So it looks kind of neat.
Uh, what else? Forza Motorsports got a trailer and that looks pretty. Lots of car porn, um, graphics porn. Exactly. You know, Ray Tracing, um,
You know what, this may not be the company that made that made Microsoft Flight Simulator, but it's the same console that brought us that beautiful piece game. So hey,
And then, uh, was it Forza Horizon 5 getting the Hot Wheels expansion again? Um, looks fantastic. Can't wait to see that again, but new. New, but old. New tracks, old idea.
They've done it before, but yeah. Yes. Uh, Flight Sim was just in. IGN has put out a video comparing Forza Horizon 5 Hot Wheels side by side with Forza Horizon 3 Hot Wheels, saying it's a ripoff. I can you believe that?
They're ripping themselves off? I know that's what we do now. Let's just, let's just go back to, remember, remember a time when we just didn't care what IGN thought? Like, it wasn't that long ago. Can we just go back to that time? I did make that up, by the way, for dramatic impact. But that's the problem is because that's too, too believable. It's too believable. Exactly. Anyway, anyway, can we just go back to that time?
Anyway, anyway, speaking of ripping our, our yourself off, that was just the FUs of the Week presented by Orange Lounge Radio. It's a brand new segment here on the show.
Uh, Flight Sim's getting the Pelican from Halo Infinite, so you can fly around the Pelican now. That's cool.
It's so fucking ridiculous that I love it. Like, you know, when a game crossed that point, it was like, this is, this is ridiculous. It's just, I love it.
I mean, yeah, it looks pretty. And I don't know, I haven't really played it yet, so I'll have to check it out and fly the Pelican as well.
God, there were so many, like, trailers. Okay, we're just gonna run a list. So Hollow Knight Silk Song, they showed that off.
That looked cool. Very artistic.
Follow up to Hollow Knight. What else? Naraka. Blade Point. It's a battle royale game coming out, like, a couple weeks here on the 23rd.
Uh, Pentemint, which is a detective game by Obsidian. So, neat.
There's a Grounded guest coming out of Early Access, so that'll be September when the full game has been released. And that'll look kinda cool.
You know, the sad part is there's no Rick Moranis in it, you know, that's really, I think, just a missed opportunity there, but maybe someday.
Uh, Persona coming to Xbox Game Pass.
That's a big deal.
That is a big thing, so you're gonna get quite a bit of Persona. Persona 3, Persona 4 Golden, Persona 5 Royale as well.
You know what, that's a really big deal. Persona 3 hasn't been on a console in a very long time, and the fact that it's now showing up on an Xbox console instead of Sony.
Oh, if you're one of those people that, like, likes to write tweets that are anti-Microsoft and you're just pro-Sony all the time, you are mad because...
And I think those people are ridiculous, and I think the opposite is ridiculous, too. I think if you write pro-Microsoft and anti-Sony, I think you're also ridiculous.
But I think this is just, I think this is a win for gamers, because it's bringing these games back, and who's to say they won't end up porting it to Steam and, you know, probably PlayStation down the line as well.
In fact, we know that the PlayStation 5 cloud library is coming out, what, like next week? Who's to say maybe Persona 2 doesn't, or excuse me, Persona 3 doesn't show up in that at some point?
Anyway.
Plague Tale Requiem. They showed off some more gameplay from that, and it looks pretty good.
Was it Flintlock the Siege of Dawn, a new third-person action game with guns and magic?
So that's supposed to be coming out later next year.
Scorn, I think. It wasn't that one that they showed off before. It is very creepy looking, and that's supposed to be coming out in October, aptly around Halloween.
What else? Aura History Untold, which I swear at first I thought was a Civilization or Anno game, but...
I thought it was Age of Empires.
Age of Empires.
I thought it was Saber Kings, whatever the Microsoft series is, yeah.
So, that looked interesting. Let's see, we talked about Elder Scrolls, Sea of Thieves, Season 7. They had a trailer for that. Can't believe they're on Season 7.
Lightyear Frontier, which people are calling Animal Crossing with mechs. It's interesting. It's like building your own little farmland or something like that, but you're walking around. It's like MechWarrior.
Oh yeah, it was Harvest Moon, but with mechs. Where was the audience for this game? Things I didn't know I needed until I saw it.
So, that looked interesting. Cocoon, which is a very artsy looking game that's being published by Annapura, and that's coming out also in 2023.
The Last Case of Benedict Fox, which is a side-scroller platformer.
Dad had a sexy voice, because it was evil.
Ravenlock, which is by the folks that made Echo Generation, which I didn't realize was out already and I need to go play it, because I really was looking forward to that.
Also looks great. Kind of fill in the void of my turn-based RPGs.
Ereban Shadow Legacy, a stealth action game about killing robots. Looked pretty cool.
Dusk Falls, they say, is a narrative-driven action adventure game about a family on the run from police. That's an interesting concept for sure.
What else did we get? Trail of Spore. Gunfire Reborn, which kind of looked like Borderlands to me, but there's a cat-like character with the guns instead.
Wulong Fallen Dynasty, which is a Tecmo Koei game. Lots of League of Legends coming to Game Pass.
League of Legends with all the champions unlocked, League of Legends Wild Rift, also getting that.
Legends of Runeterra, Team Fight Tactics, and Valorant.
That's a big deal.
A bunch of unlocks in there.
The Riot Game Pass partnership is a pretty big deal. It didn't confirm that those games were all going to be on Xbox. I think there was a follow-up or something.
No, there's a lot of PC and mobile on there. Actually, I think all those are PC and mobile.
Well, I think there might have been a follow-up that talked about they're looking at League of Legends for Xbox, but all that talk aside, PC Game Pass kind of needed something, I think, to maybe lift it up a little bit.
I mean, it's still fine, but I think that's going to definitely get people's attention versus Xbox Game Pass.
I think a lot of people kind of have both, and they may not even know it, that they're just paying for Game Pass Ultimate, which is both.
But I think just having that to kind of bolster the PC end of things is pretty neat.
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says there's going to be a League of Legends variation coming to Xbox. I thought there was a follow-up. It might have been like a follow-up. I don't think it was in the press conference, but you know how they put out press releases after the fact.
There was a game called High on Life, which is by the folks that...
It was Reckon Morty with talking guns.
Yeah, but if you've played Accounting, you know the kind of nonsense to expect with that, so that looked pretty great.
And what else? We had Ark 2 with Vin Diesel, Ryan and T-Rex. That's the thing.
And then a new Minecraft game, Minecraft Legends, which is kind of a...
It looks like an actor. I've heard it described kind of like the Mario and Rabbids game that they have.
It looked like Dragon Quest Builders, which cracked me the fuck up, because Dragon Quest Builders is just Dragon Quest with Minecraft.
No, it's not supposed to be like... Yeah, it's more of an... Almost either RTS or like...
I was getting Dragon Quest Builders from it, which is cracking me up.
Maybe, but yeah, it looks interesting, so I'll have to check it out when it comes out.
But yeah, I don't know what to think of it yet, but it looks neat. I used to like RTS games a lot, but we'll see.
Yeah, that was one of the... Because Minecraft Dungeons was a thing, and it turned out pretty good, so these Minecraft spin-off games are kind of neat.
Yeah.
So, you didn't mention the... Well, I guess we should talk about this, the Kojima horror...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We don't know what it is yet.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
So, at the end, Kojima... Towards the end, Kojima comes out and is like,
I'm partnering with Xbox to make my next game, because I want to use Xbox cloud technology, right?
Now, there's this whole rumor on the internet that was starting to gain traction, that the game that was to be unveiled, for whatever reason wasn't, is a horror game called Overdose.
And it had one of the actresses from Death Stranding in it, Margaret Qualley.
And it was this website that not a lot of people know about, called TryHardGuides, apparently got early footage from the game.
Here's the thing. Sometimes sites you don't know a lot about do come into big information. Been there, done that, right, Loki?
Yeah.
So, I'm not going to write it off just because people don't necessarily know about this site. Usually, I don't think it would have been something worth maybe reporting on.
However, apparently, Kojima asked for the information to be pulled, or Kojima Productions, rather, not Kojima himself.
But basically, I guess a Streisand effect type of thing, if you want to put it that way. And so it made a lot of people pay attention.
Now, the fact that the game didn't show up is a little weird.
Not necessarily.
And maybe makes this look like a little less credible. But it is very possible.
Well, because they were only showing off games that are coming out in the next 12 months.
Exactly.
And it could be later than that.
And maybe they were going to show something. And honestly, you know what, I stock enough Petty Crocker in my kitchen that they could have pulled the trailer to be like, you know what, we're gonna not show it right now to make it look like this is false, and then we'll reveal it later on.
But I think you're right on the this isn't the time because it's the next 12 months type of thing. But then there's also a part of me that I have to go, well, what the fuck is a horror game going to use the cloud for?
That's the part I'm not getting. But I mean, you know, desk stranding use the cloud and in a way, you know, we got we talked about this a little bit at the end of Bobby show.
But I think when I hear about the Xbox cloud, and what Xbox brings the table, I think of flight simulator. And the fact that you don't have to have gigabyte, honestly, probably terabytes of data on your PC, with all of the topography of the globe stored on it, because it processes that graphic information through the cloud as you play the game.
That's the kind of thing that I would think Kojima is talking about when he's going to Xbox specifically for something PlayStation can't offer. He didn't say that in so many words,
making multiple games, who knows?
Well, I think that's true, too. I think death stranding two is also a thing. But he's probably not as involved in that one, to be quite honest. Especially if it's in the same engine as the first game. I don't know. So anyway, I quest buster adding to the rumor mill, why not add this to the fire? It was rumored a while back that Sony wasn't keen on Kojima's proposed episodic approach for his new game.
It might be one of the reasons he was pushed to partner with Microsoft. That'd be interesting. I mean, you think like the Walking Dead games and that stuff came out on Sony platforms as well. Microsoft really embraced it with things like tell me why and some things they put out. But I don't know. I don't know. It just maybe.
Um, so that Okay, I think that's it for the Xbox show. Okay, we talked about that for a while. But um, yeah, there's there's a lot but it was good. I thought I thought there was something for everyone. Even if the whole thing wasn't for everyone, because there was definitely a lot where I was like, okay, guns, zombies. Yeah, yeehaw, whatever. But then there were things that really caught my attention. Well, I was like, oh, Diablo four. Oh, persona on Xbox. Really? Oh, they're Kojima is gonna do the Xbox thing. Huh? Okay.
There were definitely things that jumped out where I was like, Oh, that's interesting. So I think Microsoft did a good job in that regard. And I think they really cut a lot of the fluff. I think they, you know, there were some talking heads and executives, but it they didn't overdo it. So all right, um, let's move on talk about something a little more close to home our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we have been playing this week, whether they were in the cloud or not. And we talked about that.
And we'll start with dark Sakura, who I know does a bit of her gaming in the cloud. Thanks to stadia.
I do a lot of my gaming in the cloud. So yeah, um, I, I played a dead by daylight, I got the new expansion. The what roots of dread. Yeah, the garden of joy is not very joyful. No, it does not bring it does not spark joy.
But I, I played dredge new killer. I honestly I think that his default it's sorry, its default body is creepier than the doll body. So I use the doll body. And first game. Terrible. Second game. Okay. Third game adept. Nice.
And so I've actually found that I I kind of start off a little slow. The thing is, is that the the hands and everything, like it's normal hands are like super distracting to me because there's a lot on the screen.
And then I jumped out of my skin the first time I picked up a survivor.
Where all these little hands come out of his body.
And Maurice.
Maurice is an undead horse with three eyes y'all who don't know.
And he always hangs out at at Father Campbell's Chapel level, or as I call it scrotus pen.
That's just the other one he's at. Is he at that one too? He's at both of them. I think so he's in two maps, I think. Yeah.
But now he's not there anymore. And he falls out of the dredge his body like a big horse, horse poo. Oh, it's really weird. Yeah. If you stay on the, on the, on the lobby screen the end of the idle screen sorry.
Maurice plops out of his body. Interesting.
I bought the new content in the sense that I had 1000 orc cells on my account so I just bought the new killer about the new survivor, not the actual bundle or whatever but um, yeah, I, but I haven't played I've only played Hattie I haven't played as dredge yet.
So, dredge, very interesting just be ready to be distracted. Yeah, I bet, and teleport, a lot.
That's fine.
That's what I do with Sadako and that's why I really like her so yeah, but the, the thing I like with Sadako, is that judges teleports of boost the nightfall meter.
If Sadako teleports close to a survivor at boost their little insta kill meter so there is that is that too, although it shuts off TV it's obviously it's a different mechanic, but I think nightfall is a lot more useful though I, although people are already
really good at judging where you are but it's really nice having no terror radius and just sneaking up on somebody, or popping out of a locker and going, Hi, I love that. Yeah, like I can almost see people jump while they're playing it's hilarious.
Yeah, I've been watching twitch streamers play it it's a lot of fun.
But, um, I am at tear on been playing terror enigma, which I took off because when the new chapter came out instead of doing retro night I played terror enigma.
I mean, I played dead by daylight words.
Um, but, but I actually figured out what I was messing up on enter enigma was able to do like a bunch of the story. And now I have raised the, the doctor and found out that everybody was using poor arc as a pawn.
And then he's like screw you I'm going to make my own destiny.
And I still think that L is the reincarnation of the original L, but I'll find out for sure.
Alright, I'm enjoying it I actually am enjoying it a lot more than I did when I started the game. Yeah, I was gonna say you sound like you've really warmed up to it as you've invested more time in it so I was like, watching like the people, I'm glad I went ahead and got Neo
Tokyo out of the way because I was watching what happened to it.
And I was like, oh well they have nuclear annihilation in this game.
Great.
It was, it was pretty fun.
Right, I'm enjoying it but that's what I'm playing right now.
Um, although I own Evil Dead and I own VHS and I can't play either of them now thanks to that stupid launcher.
The, the anti cheat launcher doesn't run on our market texture.
I have written and I have complained and no one cares.
Maybe, maybe soon some, there's, there's some groups that are looking out for the Mac and or cloud side of things because I'm like Final Fantasy 14 they just said there is updating to run on the new OS, so let's eat well no that's something completely different.
Okay, so the arm architecture.
For Windows. Yeah, which is basically like the, the tablet OS, kinda, but it emulates it runs x86 and tries to emulate x64, but it can't run everything x64 that detects it's an ARM architecture.
So it's, it's really bizarre it just doesn't doesn't like it.
Okay. Um, but at least with Dead by Daylight I can you know update my game and rip rip the models from it to play with.
Alright, well let's go to Loki with your gaming week. How was your gaming week, Loki?
It was all Minecraft again. So I'm just been working on a build for a new episode and then start the new SMP on Saturday. Very excited about that. And then we participated in a world tour of their season one server so that was fun to see all that stuff.
So yeah, that's pretty much all I've been doing this week.
Okay, fun.
My gaming week, a lot of the similar stuff as well been continuing in Final Fantasy 14 I got my Reaper to level 90 so I've got another max level character in that game so that's pretty fun.
I also played a little bit of Dead by Daylight like Dark Sakura, but I've been, I just haven't played for like the last two or three weeks so I just kind of was like oh I guess I should check out this new DLC.
So I was trying to adapt the new survivor. I have not yet been successful I just have had some bad matches and I don't really have any good talents, because Hattie's base kit is not great.
And so she's just a little harder to adapt with, although generally survivor adapts I think are way easier than killer adapts because you can just get lucky and have a kill.
Well I mean I guess you could get lucky with a group of four survivors who don't give a crap, but you're way more likely to get a killer that doesn't give a crap, and you just get a free adapt, then get all four survivors not giving a crap.
So, but it's it's fun to go for those little challenges anyway so I will go on record saying that if I see someone, obviously trying to get their adapt.
Oh that's cute.
People have been that night, well, the way I got my nurse adapt, people realized I was, it was like my fifth time ever playing nurse.
And people realized I was a baby nurse, and they let me smack them and they let me get extra kicks on things and hook them and all of this business we memed around it was fun everyone had a good time and I thank them for their trouble.
Well that's cute.
My Blight one however I have no idea how I got it. I blame it on Midwich.
It's, it's nice to hear about a wholesome matching DBD once in a while. Once in a while.
Nice bugs me is when I try to have a boop match and no one wants to boop. Oh, yeah, I feel like I feel like people forgot about booping pigs they've moved on to like you know now dredge is the hot shit so anyway.
Um, let's see I just scary.
What else with my gaming week I thought there was one other thing I want to talk about but I can't remember so I guess I guess we'll just move on. I'll mention this. So, because this is a big exciting development I guess.
Alan and I, we've been trying to save a little money we got some nice.
Basically we were able to get time off cashed out at work, not all of it but a good chunk of time because we weren't going anywhere during the pandemic like a lot of people.
So we're going to use that money to buy ourselves new computers, and we bought them today.
And you might be like, Rob, why don't you build a computer well here's the thing.
Alan is the one that usually builds the computer, and he came to me and was like you know what I've built every computer I've ever owned since I was 19 or whatever and he's like, I, I don't want to build them.
I just want to buy and have somebody else build it at a company just make sure we can upgrade them later if we want, but I just, I just want to buy something that's like pre built by builders, and I was like, all right, cool, do it.
So we did we ordered new computers from.
And of course now I can't even remember the name of the site, but we're gonna have matching computers which I think is cute NZXT we got creator PCs from NZXT so we'll see how that goes.
So I'm excited.
All right. Um, I think that's it so that'll be really good for streaming too. So I'm hoping because I can actually stream games at 60 frames a second and not get the data loss and things like that so I'm really excited about that.
Bobby Black Wolf says he helped Alan that is true because I was like, I don't understand what the differences between all these parts they're just numbers that change. So Alan needed somebody who actually knew a little thing or two about computers so he reached out to Bobby and said, Here they are.
All right. Okay, that's it for gaming weeks. Let's move on. There's still a lot of news to get into. I will just mention two weeks from tonight is officially our 20th anniversary of orange launch radio if you can believe it. We've been doing this show for 20 years.
And you know what's kind of fun. One of my friends, Melody, I know Loki and Jamie both know melody has been sending me like, pictures she found tonight. And she sent me one I'll try to show it here on cam I'll see how this works.
This is an old old picture. And you can see that's DDR Angel in the back. And that's Loki. I don't know where Jamie was here. Maybe she wasn't at this show. But that is the old ass apartment that I lived in with Loki with no beard. And look at that giant honkin monitor back there.
Run an IRC, that giant CRT monitor back there. And that was an old because this had-
I remember Shane and I being very drunk and trying to type the word drunk in it coming out dunk.
Yes. So that there's that. And then don't ask me to explain this. I probably shouldn't show this picture. I probably shouldn't show this picture. But apparently we were visited by, you know, a group of DDR players. And you might recognize some of these DDR players. Why are we all trying to fit our fist in our mouth? I don't know. But we did it.
Anyway, that's what that's what the old OLR shenanigans look like. So there you go.
I still have some pictures from like a few attorneys and stuff.
It might be fun. You know, we should, you know, a dark tissue says do we need a new photo album? That might be like a cute thing to throw together for the 20th. You know, I know we've been sitting here going, we're kind of we don't have a lot of ideas for the 20th. Like we'd always talked about doing like an in person big celebration. But with the pandemic still being kind of like a weird thing. Like I think it just kind of kills sours the mood. I think it's good to really want to do something like that. So
I'll tell you what, I'll make a Dropbox.
That'd be fun.
And even more than that, I'll put together a book.
Yeah, I love that.
And I'll put it where someone where people can buy it.
Oh, that'd be fun.
It's just gonna be like a big photo album. You know, if people want to send in some of their photos, and, you know, maybe a couple of, you know, write up some memories about it, if they actually do it this time. I'll, I'll make a book. I'll lay it out myself.
It might be fun. Maybe fun to do like a little book. That'd be cool. Um, let's see.
And Alan has joined chat and wants to clarify about the computer build Alan is saying, I wanted it made by a gaming PC company but ready to ship as in they decided what the kit is with no changes.
And Alan also says if you use the customizer for every piece, the premium you pay is insane, then I would build it myself. So yeah, that's true. The whole graphic card situation is a little wild right now.
Um, the other thing is that the interesting thing about the way the timing is worked out, Bobby Black Wolf isn't going to be here the night we turn 20. He assures me he's not being a hater.
And it is it is a known fact that Bobby Black Wolf has been working with the games done quick marathon for some time now ever since the pandemic started, which was some time ago, believe it or not.
So he's actually going out to the Minneapolis area where the in person summer games done quick is because he's going to be doing the hosting again out there. He's talked about that on his show. I'll leave it to that.
But because of the way the timing works, the summer games are quick. He's not here that night. So we actually have the ability to take over the feed for the entire day. So I might take over and run some old from the vault programming during the day.
So we'll see. So we might be able to do some silly fun things with the
20th anniversary. So
we'll be here.
All right.
And people in chatter saying I'd love to fly out to sack I'd love to come out to sack. I think that would be wonderful but having everybody here at once is a bit much, and again it goes back to that whole in person, trying to plan your own in person stuff is a weird
thing right now just with, you know, I understand established conventions and things come back, we would have had to kind of build our own thing from the ground up and I just I think the whole COVID situation really just kind of.
It kills the motivation to want to do that. So, anyway, June 26 is the official show day for that. June 23 is technically the birthday but that is on a Thursday or something so it's not not anything that day.
So, all right. Um, okay, let's move on we got more gaming news to get into so other announcement fast right Loki.
Yes, so key three kicked off with the summer games fest opening ceremony live thing that they did, and showed off a bunch of trailers for a bunch of cool games so in no particular order here.
neon white was a game that they showed off look pretty cool kind of like a, they call it a speed run is like a FPS speed running.
I don't really know what to call it but like basically have like cards that can either you can use them for a speed boost or for like a weapon or something like that which is kind of cool.
And then there's also a dating sim mechanics in that as well. But very stylized very interesting game called high water which actually reminded me of a lot of was it like the sunken city and stuff like that that kind of a, I guess, survival game where there's, I guess, I assume the polar ice caps melted and all these cities are underwater now.
So that looks kind of cool. We got a trailer for the last of us remastered, which looks remastered I honestly like the comparisons between the original and this.
It's hard to kind of determine the differences of that the lighting is obviously better and stuff and they have a little bit more detail but I don't know.
They're remastering it. Was it that Marvel game or get is like that was an RTS I think it's an RTS Midnight Suns. They announced that that has Spider Man as well in it, and that's been delayed to the fall, which is October 7 when that's expected to be coming out.
There's a new scary aliens game called aliens, dark descent, and that's coming out in 2023. Lots of scary space horror games in this presentation. To go along with that there is Fort Solace, which was kind of a game starring Troy Baker and Roger Clark.
It looked interesting for sure. A game called Routine, which it reminded me almost like of a Dead Space meets Five Nights at Freddy's type of thing. At least the robots in that remind me of Five Nights at Freddy's, but also another space dark horror game.
What else? Let's see, we had Goat Simulator 3.
Where's Goat Simulator 2?
That's the joke.
The joke I made during Bobby show was Goat Simulator 2 is only playable on Windows 9.
Well, I like how they basically ripped off the whole trailer for Dead Island 2, which I think was funny.
Yeah, that was funny.
They mocked that, but I'm very, very much. This is like my most anticipated game.
Game of the show.
Game of the show, yes, for me. Absolutely. So yeah, Goat Simulator 3. Definitely want to see that.
What else do we have? So we've got the new Bloober Team game that is equal to Layers of Fear, or maybe it is. Is it just Layers of Fear?
I thought there already was a Layers of Fear game.
But anyways, it's Layers of Fear and it's coming out in Unreal 5. I don't know. Looks scary.
Starting with Bonds 006, still no Half-Life 3. I mean, let's be real, Loki. Wasn't Summer Game Fest kind of boring for all the hype that went into it and everything?
And even if Geoff Keighley said, you know, level those expectations, folks. Wasn't Summer Game Fest honestly kind of boring?
I didn't really have any expectations. The only thing I got excited about was Goat Simulator. That was it. That was the only thing I got really excited about.
The rest of it was like kind of. I mean, it's fine. I didn't have any expectation. And I know he said level your expectations. I wasn't expecting any really huge announcements, but like.
I wasn't expecting five space horror games. That was impressive.
Yeah. There's a new game called American Arcadia, which is a first person puzzle game, which looks interesting. It almost reminds me a little bit of. Oh, gosh, what was that?
I can't remember the name of it, but it's a very interesting premise where there's like this utopia and apparently it's part of like a reality show as well.
So it's like a little bit of Truman Show thrown in there. It's kind of interesting. A new trailer for TMNT Shredder's Revenge, which is going to be coming out later this week.
And they announced that Casey Jones is going to be playable. So that's cool. We've got a roster of six different playable characters now.
You can play six players online.
Yeah, and six players online. So or actually, no, it's seven players now. That's right, because April Neal and Splinter and Casey Jones are in there.
What else? Warhammer 40K Dark Tide had a trailer for that. That looked pretty awesome.
You know, definitely a like an FPS. I want to say we saw this a while back, but yeah, it's an FPS take on Warhammer 40K, which looks pretty cool.
Witchfire looked kind of neat. It was like almost like a reminds me of a Serious Sam meets like Dark Souls or something like that.
So that's really cool looking. Kind of this magical sci-fi FPS that looks pretty hard.
What else? Zenless Zone Zero, which is a new game by HoYoVerse. And they, of course, are behind Genshin Impact.
And then we had my favorite, aside from Goat Simulator, was the Rock cameo video segment where he sat there just spouting off nonsense for a good couple minutes,
plugging like as many things as possible within that time frame. I'm assuming it's one of these things that just pays the bills, I guess.
So that's the thing. We got a Street Fighter 6 trailer featuring Guile, which is less impactful now that the whole roster leaked, but still cool.
Well, it also confirms that whole roster leak because how did Guile look exactly like that roster leak?
Yep. One Piece Odyssey looks pretty neat. Brand new RPG based off of that anime series. Flashback 2 was unexpected.
So that was quite an interesting sequel out of nowhere. What we have, Midnight Fight Express looks like an isometric action game. Looked kind of neat.
Sounds like they're getting desperate for names.
Maybe. I don't know. We have a new trailer for Cuphead Delicious Last Course, which is coming out at the end of the month. Saints Row had a trailer for their character creator, which they've kind of done this in the past.
I think Saints Row the third or the fourth game had a character creator that they released ahead of time for the game. But yeah, apparently it's a really in-depth character creator.
You can make anything you want in that, which is pretty cool.
There is a trailer or gameplay for Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2, which I like the Call of Duty single player campaign, so it looks interesting, definitely. I'm interested in that.
Callisto Protocol, that was another one of the scary space games. This by the team that developed Dead Space before. So, I mean, you know what they kind of expected that.
And what else? Gotham Knights had a new gameplay trailer. I think that was everything. Oh, Stormgate was announced. It's getting a beta next year. Free-to-play RTS game from Frost Giant Studios. So those are the guys, the ex-Blizzard team.
I would say the thing that had most people talking after the Summer Game Fest was the whole Last of Us Part 1 and that reveal because Sony didn't do it at their own thing. They did it here and it had leaked that morning anyway.
But still people are saying, do we need the second remake of this game in 10 years? So this is going to be the third release of this game in 10 years.
I don't feel passionately one way or the other about it. I understand this is going to be one of Sony's all-time greatest games that they've made is this whole Last of Us series. I get it. So if they want to revisit it and do it again, I don't think it's a big...
I think it like especially looking at some of what the new one for PlayStation 5 looks like next to PlayStation 3. I'm like, you can tell it's come a long way. I don't know. I feel like the audience is there for it and people will buy it. I don't think it's quite the waste of time others are making it out to be. And Mike Defton says...
Well, the sales will say that.
I would have to say, okay, but are we being this critical of Sega and some of their classics? Because how many times has Sonic 2 been released or the original Sonic and Sonic 2? How many times have those games been released?
How many times is Skyrim being remastered?
Exactly.
Not enough times is the answer.
That's a compliment to both the Sonic games and the Elder Scrolls Skyrim is that people want to play those games again, and they want to, you know, there is an audience for them. So I think I think it's all right. I don't think it's as big of a deal as people are making it out to be as usual in gaming culture and gaming social media. Anyway.
All right. If we're done with Summer Game Fest, then I will quickly talk about the Devolver Digital Showcase, which had some games that they were showing including Cult of the Lamb, which is coming out on August 11, where you're playing as a possessed lamb who starts a cult. Sounds like fun. Resources, loyal followers and ridding the world of false prophets. Sounds good to me PCs and all the consoles on August 11.
Angerfoot was another game that they showed off. It's set in the caffeine fueled fever dream of Shit City. Who wants to take a trip to Shit City? Angerfoot does. So you kick down doors, you kill mobsters, and you go through sewers and skyscrapers. It's an FPS action game shooty bang bang. They said shit. It's all those types of games. Hooray.
Card shark was also shown even though this game is actually already out, but they showed it. So check it out on PC and switch. The game that everyone's talking about as they ought to be because it looked really neat when it came to the art in this game was the plucky squire. This looked really cool.
Great. Yeah, this was the one that was showing like a storybook that was in 2d. And then you were playing in the storybook. But then at some point, you jump right out of the book. And now you're in a 3d world where it looks like you're in Toy Story or something like that looks really cool. So it's on PlayStation five, Xbox series, surprisingly, Nintendo Switch, no tea, no shade, but maybe a little bit. And PC in 2023. And that's just that that's just a read on the graphics. That's all. So
maybe a cloud game, who knows. And then skate story was also a game where you that looks really good to you play a demon made of glass and pain. Well, you are scared. Oh, is it a glass pane? It's the house of glass and the house of pain on one. It's you're skating through an underworld and heard what you did there. You convinced the devil to strike a deal with you. If you if you skate to the moon, you're going to be in the
moon and swallow it. You get to leave hell. Well, that that sounds like a plot for me. I don't know about you all. But that sounds like fun. It looks really, really good. Yeah. So it's coming out on PC in 2023. A lot of people saying Devolver really like stole the like, stole the thunder right out of the summer game fest because they were like right after weren't they? No, there was a
they were they were after that. So as 200 mountain chat says plucky squire is my game of not E three week. Pod culture is suggesting that shit city is where pixel poops takes place. Perhaps but I think could be I think I thought it was given another name. Didn't you give that a name? Loki? No, I didn't. So it was it was the the magazine. The magazine that covered it thought it took place in New York because Central Park.
Yes. Okay. Despite the fact that there are multiple Central Parks in in the world, and not all of them are in New York City, whatever. I believe in the original yyr art piece that before you made a derivative work in the original yyr art piece, it was a big park you were pooping into. So because the background was green, therefore, because it was Atari 26 aspires. So therefore it was a park. So but it's it's any park, any town USA, right?
It's pooping is encouraged in all parks across the nation. Check out pixel poops to on itch IO and the original pixel poops on Steam free to play. All right. That was it I want to say for developer digital. So let's go to dark Sakura with other announcements from this week.
It's a Rick Richter Belmont Belmont one is Castlevania Nocturne. So I'm do hoping I do hope that it basically goes through the story for Dracula x. Maria Renard is in it. Of course, she was a little girl in that era, like looking at the outfit for for Richter. It looks more along the lines of what the Dracula x outfit was looks like younger. So as what I'm thinking it is. And I think I'm I think it's going to be
be really, really good. So this is going to be right around also with the French Revolution in the background around 1792. So I'd like to see how the history would be wrapped up into it, I think would be really neat. Yeah, that's Castlevania Nocturne. And then we have a Dragon Age one, but we don't really know much about the story. I mean, Bioware has been really quiet about that and about
Dragon Age, Dread Wolf, which is the new one coming out eventually. What we know about this one is that it's it's actually called Dragon Age Absolution. Is it this is going to be set in Tevinter, which has been talked about often and kind of shat talk upon, but it gave a story in so that's awesome. But we get to see a little bit more of that. They seem to be
expanding the lore and it's going to be coming out in December.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely hyped for more Castlevania. I think the thing is that original Castlevania anime series did really well for Netflix, like it got a lot of eyes on it. And I think it's led to a lot of subsequent stuff getting the dream green light such as this spin off the Dragon Age, etc, etc. So I'm really hoping that it's based off of Rondo but with the name Nocturne, as we know the the Japanese Symphony of the Night was called Nocturne in the Moonlight. Yeah, that'd be cool. But
I'm really hoping though, that it's Rondo because that gives us a little bit more origin story instead of just saying, Oh, by the way, here's Richter and this lady who says Richter.
Moving on other stuff going on in Hollywood, right? Logie? Yep. The more things that no one asks for, but apparently we are going to be getting a Duke Nukem movie. Only like, I'm sorry, I don't know. Is it 1998? Like what? Why now? I we've run out of ideas. But apparently this is going to be coming from it's a new project being produced by
the Cobra Kai creators, Josh Heald and John Hurtwitz and Hayden Schlossberg. So apparently also being worked on by Jean-Julien Baronet, who worked on the film adaptation of Assassin's Creed. So one positive, one negative. I don't know, like all I know is it's obviously they're gonna have to change it a bit.
To be, you know, fit the demographic of the, you know, the year 2022 or 23, I guess whenever the heck it's supposed to be coming out. Because it certain things that were in that game probably wouldn't be acceptable, you know, the just buckets full of misogyny in the game. But I mean, if they could probably remove that and just have it like, you know, big strong guy with guns taking on pig cops.
Bruce Campbell persona with a gun, I think will still perform very well. They can shooting strippers and things like that that, you know, just don't play well in this day and age. Or they'll just go full in and just be offensive as hell. I don't know. We'll see. Oh, like making the put? Well, we saw how well that that those type of movies worked out for Uwe Boll. So I would assume that they're not going to go that route. So that's see that right there. Like if it was Uwe Boll attached to making this movie.
I can believe I can believe that whatever happened to him. He was mentioned here in Sacramento before the pandemic. I just didn't make it out to Oh, I don't know. To ask this question. Like what the hell are you doing? I think he we asked this every once in a while. Yeah, he probably like, you know, he probably owns a subway franchise by now. Like he don't think I don't think movies work for him. Yeah, I don't know what he's up to. He runs me. I'm sure the donuts across from Central Park. You know,
it's movies work for him. All right. Yeah, Tiger con chat says Duke Nukem is like a parody of those 80s action heroes. You know, like a parody tongue in cheek thing of 80s action movies. That would be a good route for Duke Nukem to go because that's going to be the audience for it is dad jokes dads that grew up with that game. He is still making movies. Really? Because Bobby says he gave up on movies. He was too smart. No, he's well, he's the
producer of the decline. And there's a movie where he is directing, writing, producing and acting in called Hanau. I don't know what that is.
I'm gonna just venture a guess. There's a reason we've never heard of any of this shit. We're probably not going to so. Best of luck to you. All right. Moving on. Let's talk about another update fest that happened this week. This
one was all about Sonic. So Sonic had its own little it's not e3. But we're gonna put this out anyway, little event and there was actually quite a bit of news because they were talking about Sonic origins. It is still happening on June 23. They also are going to be doing new music for Sonic
origins. It's going to be basically adapted from Sonic three. An adapted soundtrack for Sonic three and knuckles will be faithfully recreated by June scenario. And people were kind of wondering what's going to happen with this because we all know even though it's never been confirmed Michael Jackson was supposedly involved with this. What's gonna so now yeah, during a special Sonic origin stream, they mentioned the social media manager mentioned that Sonic origins of Sonic three knuckles will have a recomposed version
of the original score, I guess to get rid of any of those types of rights and licensing. That's kind of interesting. Anyway, in other Sonic news, the Sonic speed simulator is coming to roblox. So maybe Loki's kids will be checking that out. I think that came out a while ago. We talked about that.
Oh, it's June 11. To is when that came out is what this is saying.
Well, they've already played it. So it's already out. Maybe they're doing an update to it or something.
Maybe there are Sonic mobile games that are getting movie collaborations, Sonic forces and Sonic dash. Sonic Prime, the TV show on Netflix coming soon. Ben Schwartz showed up to remind us that the Sonic two movie is now available on blu ray. Some other new merch like Sonic Pez dispensers. That's kind of rad. Actually, I do love me a Pez dispenser.
I saw the Sonic Lego set the other day. I didn't buy it though.
Good for you showing restraint. The Sonic symphony series is coming back. It's going to be in Brazil. So all the people that always tweet come to Brazil are getting what they want. It's going to be there in October. Fall guys will collaborate with Sonic on August 22. After it's free to play conversions. That's kind of neat. And then a knuckles animated prologue for Sonic frontiers was also glimpsed as well and more Sonic frontiers coverage to be coming later this month. And that was the big cliffhanger that they ended on.
But Sonic is everywhere. And with the success of the movie, it's not going anywhere. So there you go. Yeah, SSG 100 Mountain chat. Moisturizing, moisturizing, Sonic everything. Exactly. Tiger Claw, who I know loves the Sonic says so in order to get around the rights issue, they just recreate the original music with a different composer. We've seen this happen before
when they recreated music from the original because of rights issues. Yeah. So that's, that's basically how they're getting around the Sonic three Michael Jackson. Don't want to go have to get permission from his estate and that sort of stuff. So makes sense. I'm sure people I'm sure for the PC version, because this has to be releasing on PC, right? Somebody will create a mod within seconds to restore the original music seconds. So just wait for that. Yeah.
All right. Well, while we're on the subject of video game music, why do we go to dark soccer for our next story?
Why don't we? So, uh, well, there, you know, we always are like, we don't really care about the award shows, typically as a group. We're even live during award shows. They're usually on Sunday nights. Because IDGAF. But anyway, um, but we like when award shows recognize video game music.
And we like when it comes to gaming and video gaming culture and the things that go with it. So, um, basically, uh, the Grammys are getting a award for best score soundtrack for video games and other interactive media. And that's going to be starting, uh, next year, 2023. Uh, there's also a few other changes going through. There's another one that's like a special merit award for best song, uh, for social change and best spoken word poetry album.
Um, but the whole thing, and I'm going to just read the quote that this award will recognize quote, excellence in score soundtrack albums comprise predominantly of original scores and created specifically for, or as companion to a current video game or other interactive media released within the qualification period and quote.
Um, and I mean, there are plenty of, of Grammy winners who, who play games, right?
Sure.
Um, you know, uh, I, I was actually in the, the, the article I was reading, um, uh, Jon Batiste, who is a Grammy winner for, uh, for jazz and the band leader for the late show loves Final Fantasy VII's music.
Um, that's like kind of like his jam.
Um, there's a, there's just a bunch of, of different, you know, people out there who love their video games.
Um, so, uh, you know, and there's also people who, uh, I mean, now vinyl albums are being released for things.
And in fact, give me just a second, literally just a second.
One.
Well, I'll point out in chat, um, they're talking about that the Tonys happen to be on right now, ironically.
Uh, and the Tonys of course are, uh, Broadway. So like Patti LuPone wins a Tony.
So, um, yeah. Oh, Dead by Daylight vinyl. I didn't even know there was a vinyl of that. That's neat.
Oh yeah. This is actually a second printing.
Oh, cool.
That was like a random one. It had like some different artwork on it, but, um, but I got the shiny reflective one.
Um, but yeah, we're getting more and more albums actually being released for video game soundtracks.
And I think it's, it's awesome. And I think that I'm really glad that these, uh, that the, the music and the artistry that goes into it is being recognized.
Like I would still love to have, you know, uh, artists like that do concept art or, or modeling or whatever, you know, be recognized in a more, uh, formal setting.
If you know what I mean.
Um, SGA 100 Matt in our chat has a good point though. And I think he's right saying, I guess this will be done the night before during the tech awards, but yeah, it's cool. They're doing it.
Uh, I do believe with the Grammys, it's actually not the night before, but the actual Grammy ceremony starts like early in the day.
It actually starts at like noon because they give away like a hundred Grammy awards and they save all the big ones for the live televised part at like eight o'clock or whatever it is.
So they, they, this will probably just be one of the early awards that then they, they show during the show, like a montage.
Or they do make it something for the early evening to gather a larger viewership from people who would not normally watch the award show.
Not a bad call, honestly, or, or see if maybe, you know, um, because I believe one year PBS or somebody broadcast an early hour of it for what, for some reason, I don't remember what it was, but like somebody else broadcast like the hour before the prime time for some reason.
And that, why not partner up with an online network or something to show some of those more techie type of awards that would include video games. I think that's cool.
Yeah. SSG100 Matt in chat. Now Soken can win a Grammy. Look, I think the Grammys have a lot of issues, a lot of issues and I'll defer to what the weekends had to say about that as like, you know, um, a start, but, um, I, I can also acknowledge what Bobby Black Wolf is saying.
As much as we may not care about the Grammys for the musicians, winning a Grammy is amazing. And I can understand that having that acknowledgement of your peers can be a huge thing.
I would love nothing more than for Soken, the composer behind Final Fantasy XIV to win a Grammy for his work that I would love that. I realized he's got a lot of competition and I think we all have our composers that we're rooting for.
So it's going to make this this first year kind of interesting. So, we'll see.
There's a bit more to I like the mention of this they're talking about video games being indirectly recognized at the Oscars. There was that film called Colette.
That was based off of, well, it was featured in the Medal of Honor above and beyond VR game.
That's a story of a 92 year old French woman who was part of the World War Two resistance.
And that one, you know, that one Academy Award for Best Documentary. That's cool.
I think, I really think we're starting to see more and more and more mainstream acceptance. Yeah.
In fact, I think the only reason why we're only seeing it now is because of the stigma that had been around video games and gaming but gamers grew up.
If this feels long overdue, but maybe it took Baba Yetu winning a Grammy, the Kirby remix winning a Grammy, this last that was honestly that was probably really the catalyst was somebody looking at that going, I don't know why isn't there a category for this type of thing.
So, as she went out with a very, I think, realistic idea for how this might be seen live CBS has the rights to show the Grammys, watch them put that bonus stream up for these awards on Paramount Plus.
Honestly, you're joking, but like that's a very realistic outcome for how that might play out. So we'll see it's going to be, it's interesting because now we know everybody has a streaming service right.
And now we're starting to see which ones are able to stay afloat, like I would say Paramount Plus is staying afloat, which ones are dead on arrival like CNN plus right like not everybody's is able to make it with you know what they're doing.
Now I think we have to watch the streaming services kind of compete with each other and what they're going to pull out. So it's interesting. We have a story coming up later on how another streaming service is furthering their efforts and video games to try to get
more attention so we'll see. We'll see. Anyway. All right, E3VL in chat says never heard of CNN plus. Exactly. It launched and then it was gone in 30 days, because somebody out there thought people would want to pay for news.
In this day and age. So just didn't work out. All right, anyway, I'm moving on. Loki.
So I don't know where we are in this saga but now Bobby Kotick has announced that he will recognize Raven Software's union. So he promised that he will engage in good faith negotiations to enter a collective bargaining agreement with the communications workers of America.
And this was a letter they sent out to all Activision Blizzard employees. Now, in the past, they've tried to squash the union several times. I don't know why now the change of heart but we'll see what kind of good faith negotiations will actually occur because of this. I don't know, I'm not too confident.
Well, hopefully, and again, with today's, I keep wanting to say press conference but showcase in our rearview mirror. I think the move in to Microsoft is, is trying to move faster rather than slower and it won't really matter what the fuck Bobby Kotick thinks, and his, his goons that are on the board and so forth.
And in throughout other parts of the organization. I have, I have full faith that Phil Spencer is going to fire them all. And they're, they'll find a creative way to do it, but I have full faith a lot of these people not going to be around after this transition. So we'll see. I mean, you know, if it doesn't happen, that would be very disappointing. But I think there's going to be some housecleaning that happens.
I think the people that don't have to worry, the hard working, you know, staff that's actually making the at the actually touches the get actually makes the games and the associated things to keep them afloat people that have to worry management.
Good.
All right. Moving on. I mentioned this just a moment ago. Let's talk about Netflix, right? Because streaming services competing with each other. Netflix has optioned Spiritfarer for their Netflix service. So this is a game that it's already been released. It was something that was on I think it was on the switch before. And in this game, you play a fairy master who friends dead people and brings them to the afterlife.
You have to build a boat and then you craft Oh, yeah, that's right. I remember that. Yeah. So Spiritfarer, it's been out. But now Netflix is bringing it I think this would be the first time for mobile phones. So this is also debuting at the same time when desta, which I think is another Netflix game as well. So yeah, Netflix is starting to show those games off and try to put themselves in front as a games and movies and TV shows.
Again, I think Sony is missing a huge opportunity here. And I think they're going to regret not leveraging their large media presence in other areas to build something that can compete with this. But that's their problem, I guess. Microsoft doesn't really have the media. I think they were trying at one point, but it didn't go very far. So yeah, but interesting to see that coming in.
Netflix, especially one that you know, it's an award winning game. And it's, I think for me, the reason why it's especially relevant to point this one out is it's like, it's not a match three game, or a card game, or something that we've seen a million of them, right? This is something with a lot more depth to it. Mike Defton chat says the game about feels and furries in parentheses with Animal Crossing thrown in. Dr. Sia points out me she loves this one. Actually, I think a
lot of people do. I think it has been very well received and won awards. So yep. All right, let's move on and go to our next segment, which will go a long way back, well before streaming services got into games.
And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it. It's time for the classic game of the week.
And what did you pick for us tonight, Dark Sakura?
So you play a jet in the US by Senturi and Atari Ireland in Europe in the Middle East.
So basically you play a jet that flies across open airspace and has an infinite scrolling in all different directions. It's themed to each level is themed to a different time period, and there were ports and sequels and all kinds of things.
So basically you play as a fighter jet, a pilot in a fighter jet and trying to get fellow pilots that are trapped in different time periods.
Each of the levels you have enemy aircraft and then a stronger aircraft and your jet is always in the center of the screen.
You eventually will battle a mothership from the time period that people are in and then once defeated, you move on to the next time period. You can also rescue parachuting pilots if they appear on your screen.
So the levels are 1910, 1940, 1970, 1982 slash 83 and 2001.
After the fifth level is finished, the game repeats. You get extra lives at 10,000 and then per 50,000 then up to 960,000 you get extra lives and then the game goes to survival of the fittest mode.
Your fighters are destroyed if they get hit by a bullet, enemy ships, missiles and the game ends when you lose your last character.
So there's a little bit about development is that Okamoto proposed time pilot and Konami rejected it. His boss at Konami rejected it and said that he was supposed to be working on a driving game instead.
So he secretly gave instructions to a programmer to work on the idea while pretending to work on the driving game in front of his boss. Sneaky.
It was actually very well received when it came out in Japan. The annual game machine chart listed time pilot as the fifth highest grossing arcade game of 1982.
And then they listed time pilot as the 18th most popular arcade title of the month on June 1, 1983. In the US, it topped the play meter arcade earnings chart in February 1983.
The Amusement and Music Operators Association listed it among the 13th highest earning video games of 1983. And Magazine, Computer and Video Games gave the arcade game a very nice review.
There were re-releases, there were clones, there was all kinds of stuff. Home releases included the Atari 2600, the MSX and ColecoVision. I think I actually have it on ColecoVision.
It also had a sequel of Time Pilot 84 that didn't have the time travel in it but took place in the way future.
As far as other re-releases and whatnot, the Super Famicom or Super Nintendo had a Time Pilot 95 bonus game in Ganbare Goemon Kira Kira Douchuu Boku Ga Densa ni Nataake.
The PlayStation had a release in the Konami Arcade Classics in 1999. Game Boy Advance had it in part of the Konami Collector's arcade series Advanced in 2002. It had a hidden sixth era in it, 1 million BCE with pterodactyls.
PS2 had it as part of Oretachi Gaisen Zoku Sono in 2005. Xbox 360 had it as part of the Xbox Live Arcade in August 30, 2006. Nintendo DS had it as part of the Konami Classics arcade series.
I mode mobile phones in Japan in 2004 and Switch and PlayStation 4 had it as part of the arcade archives on May 27, 2021.
There are clones. There's one called Fury in 1983 which was a clone from Computershack for the TRS-80 color computer. There's also Space Pilot that was unrelated that came out in 1984 from Kingsoft for the Commodore 64 and Superior Software for BBC Micro.
And then there was Vector Pilot which was written just by a hobbyist for the Vetrex in 2011. And then that's it. That's Time Pilot.
Great pick. I love this game. I remember seeing it on Starcade back in the day. It was a very common game that showed up on Starcade, at least episodes I remember. And I played quite a bit of this actually on Xbox 360 because Time Pilot was one of the early releases for Xbox Live Arcade.
Like around the time they were putting things like Ms. Pac-Man, Joust and some of that, I really got into Time Pilot as one of the games. So I would actually love to have an arcade one up. I'm not sure if one exists.
Some of y'all, Bobby and some of you in chat might know more about Time Pilot, or excuse me, the arcade one ups than me. But I would love to see like a Konami cab with like Time Pilot, Scramble, Jairus, like some of the old school like Konami published classics from back in the day. I would really love that I'd be tempted to buy a machine like that.
I guess Time Pilot 84 would be in there too. I know like, at least 84 is in the arcade archives. I imagine this one has to be as well. The hamsters arcade archive collection. Oh, okay, Bobby Black. Oh, of course the Frogger machine. Okay, thank you, Bobby. Of course that would be Konami's biggest 80s arcade game was Time Pilot. Oh, I might have to look that up. I wouldn't mind that actually. Does it have Jairus as well?
Maybe I need to maybe I need to wait. If it doesn't have it yet, then I need to wait a little longer because now they're re releasing like old machines, but with more games. So I might need to wait a little bit. Oh, Bobby says no, it's out of stock anyway. So hopefully they get those rights renewed. We'll see. All right. Well, there it is your classic game of the week, Time Pilot. Love that game.
All right. Let's move on and talk about some other news happening in the game industry with some rapid fire news. Loki.
Yes, there is a a Capcom showcase coming tomorrow. It's going to be at 3pm Pacific time. They're going to be showing off some Capcom titles for 35 minutes.
Do you think they might announce a new Street Fighter six character?
Probably gonna announce another Street Fighter six character. Probably show some more of the Resident Evil stuff that they were showing off during the PlayStation thing.
Monster Hunter DLC on Switch or something. Yeah, maybe.
That's like a Capcom arcade collection too, I guess whatever.
Oh, yeah, the arcade stadium too. I forgot about that. That's a really good call that we'll probably get maybe even releasing tomorrow. We'll see.
Oh, and Capcom fighting collection as well.
Oh, yeah. So I guess there is a little bit for Capcom to just kind of like update folks on and stuff. So that's cool.
Yeah. Questbuster says I'm hoping for that tomorrow. Questbuster says I'm hoping for Dragons Dogma 2.
I don't know about that because I don't know if they're going to get to a lot a lot of new stuff you haven't heard about yet. But anything's possible, I guess.
I would think they'd save those type of reveals for their partnerships with Sony, Nintendo, you know, and so forth. But we'll see.
It's 200 Matt thinks maybe re for gameplay, maybe, maybe a deeper dive on that. We'll see. Maybe. But yeah, I think it'll just be more updates and deeper dives on things we already know about. I don't I wouldn't set for a lot of new stuff.
We'll find out the funny thing is, by the time most people hear this on the podcast feed, that Capcom event will have already happened. So we'll have to see. See next week. We'll recap it and take a look.
Yeah. Nickelodeon All Star Brawl finally got a patch to patch in the voice actors because it was sorely missing from the game. So now we have the original voice actors from most of the characters, I think in the game.
I don't think there's I don't know if they've got any different people like performing the characters in the originals. But yeah, it looks like most of the originals have come back to do the voices, which is pretty awesome. And then along with that, they're also adding items into the game. So now it's full, full blown Smash Brothers
items to annoy you just like they do in Smash Brothers. Yeah, and then balancing course. Okay. Oh, cool. All right. How about Dark Soccer? I think you have one for us. I do. Um, we have a well, we all know that teenage mutant interest turtles shredders revenge is coming out, but there will be a physical copy and the pre orders include a Pizza Hut deal, which is a classic the classic edition of the game.
The classic edition and ultimate collector's editions include this as well, or you can get a, a free personal pan pizza coupon you buy the game, you get the coupon, you get pizza, just like when the Manhattan Project came out, you get your your coupon for Pizza Hut in the box.
So I think that's pretty cool. They're doing that limited run games is certainly going above and beyond.
I think it's super cute. Somebody type slash pizza and chat for sure. So it's cute. Oh, that. All right. Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates. Loki will start in the US what's coming out this week, whether they have a lot, what do they have pizza coupons or not?
Uh, well, one of them is guaranteed to have pizza coupons. So we have frozen time coming out on PC. That's not the one the pizza coupon. Overlord escape from NARS. NARS Rick, that's on PC and Nintendo Switch also not that one. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles shredders revenge. That's the one that's coming out on PC Nintendo Switch PlayStation four and Xbox one.
Amari on Nintendo Switch and PlayStation four. And that's literally it.
All right. Well, going over to Japan, I think kind of echoes that it's a bit of a slower week on the Nintendo Switch this week, that same Overlord escape from Nazaric game is out. It's in English, but it is getting released in Japan in great Japan release style in a regular and a limited edition. I say that because a lot of games in Japan come out in regular limited edition.
We have some games on PlayStation five, including Sniper Elite five in a regular and Deluxe Edition. And oh, here it is. This is the game that that's the for the week. PlayStation five gets Disgaea six, Defiance of Destiny this week. And I know there's some people out there that love their Disgaea. So that's definitely the tentpole of the week there.
On the PlayStation four, a lot of the same stuff. The only kind of new thing I see here Road 96 is a game coming out in Japan on PlayStation four this week. Let's go to the UK Dark Sakura.
On the 16th, we have Windstorm, start of a great friendship, which apparently looks like a horse game on PlayStation and switch. Also on there, we also have the quest for Excalibur. On the 17th for PlayStation, we have Zengen, which I'm guessing is like Zen and Dungeon, portmanteau. On the 17th as well for Switch, we have White Knight. I love the typography on this one. It gives me some saw bass vibes.
On the 17th, we also have Final Vendetta. And that is for PlayStation and Switch. And then on PlayStation, we have Oxide Room 104. That's it.
That's it. Sorry, Alan came in here and recognize that it is very hot in this room and is helping me do something about it. So sorry.
It's getting hot in here. So turn on the AC.
I thought you were gonna say take off all your clothes. I'm like, No, no, no, not a cam, not a cam. But I did for the first time. And like, at least a decade yesterday, I did something that you're doing right now, Dark Sakura. And that is I think top I wore a tank top in public. So there was
good you can advertise mine.
Happy to happy to. Yeah, so it's it's pride season around the world. So I got together with some friends and I don't know if I'll do SF. Well, I can't really do SF pride this year because we got our 20th anniversary show and my birth my birthday is always the same frickin weekend as pride always.
I'm so I'm just used to it by now. So, whatever, but like I sometimes mine is almost always during Passover. Hmm. Yeah, yeah. Not having a birthday cake on your birthday was here here you and I are complaining and then Loki's birthday. Yeah, I think Loki I think Loki wins Star
Sakura between the three of us. Unfortunately, yeah, for those that don't know, Loki was born on September 11. So you know, yeah, it's just you can't pick the day you were born. It just happens. So well, it's, it's nice to have some good news on that day. We'll say that. All right. I'm moving on. Let's get to a few more headlines for you. And Loki, I just realized in the show, you know, I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to.
Moving on, we have a little bit of sad news, not the type of stuff we love to report on, right, DarkSakura?
Yeah. Billy Kametz, 35 years old, died. Death from colon cancer, which is a pretty nasty thing. That's what got my granddaddy.
At that age, it's so sad.
Yeah, and he was pretty, pretty big in video game and anime voice acting.
He was in The Rising of the Shield Hero in 2019. He also won Best Voice Actor Performance at the Crunchyroll Awards.
He also was Josuke in Jojo's Bizarre Adventure. He was in Attack on Titan, Boruto, Demon Slayer, Pokemon Journeys in Evangelion.
So, yeah, he also was offered the role of Aladdin in the Disneyland production that they had in the park.
Oh, God, you and I have probably seen that at least a dozen times.
Actually, I've only seen it once.
Really?
Yep. I only went once right before they got rid of it.
I thought you and I saw that together. Wow. Okay. Golly, I saw that at least a dozen times.
Yeah, I think it was just like a particularly hot day and I'd never gone and everyone's like, Oh, you should see it. I'm like, Okay, I'll go see it. Dan was with me, I think.
Huh? Interesting.
Yeah. But he also worked with Disney as part of the entertainment staff on a cruise line. This first break.
Oh, wow.
He took a break from doing everything after he got his diagnosis and he died on June 9th.
Bobby Blackwolf, our resident Persona fan, actually, there's a few of you in chat to be fair, is also pointing out he was an added character in Persona 5 Royal.
So, I mean, he just he has a long resume of performances.
You know, I've picked I've befriended a couple voice actors just thanks to all these conventions and panels I've hosted over the years, and they were definitely like I that's how I heard about this was just the peers and voice acting were really shook by this and really upset about this loss and understandably so.
It's at least nice to know that, because he did all these voices and because he contributed to all of these different art pieces, his family, his friends, his fans have things to go back and enjoy and hear, you know, I think that's, that's the great thing about being in an industry like that is that you leave a lasting impact that lives on in art, you know,
it's almost like kind of one of the things about this show, you know, this show this show will continue well you know this show will end someday but it will always be available once on the internet always on the internet right so it's something that's going to outlive us, you know, and maybe who knows maybe someday, there's going to be somebody that wants to go and maybe Loki's grandkids someday want to go back and listen to all the stupid shit he said on the internet.
No, I bet they will. I bet they will. Maybe not all of it. There's a lot. There's a lot of olr, but maybe some of it. All right, let's move on. Speaking of Loki, you have a clever headline here.
He's coming back, baby.
to be able to connect in person and see each other and talk about what makes games great. So they're talking about doing a in person event, as well as a virtual event. And, yeah, that's, that's nice that they think they're relevant still. But it's cute.
You know, it's cute. I mean, I guess there's probably investors and you know, people they kind of, you know, they can't the members on USA, they have to keep stringing them along to make them think that they're relevant again. But it's so adorable. But I think the reality is, if he three comes back, I do, you know, as much as I'm sitting here going, they're not going to be back in 2023. I think they will be back in 2023. It's not going to be what you expect, or what you remember.
Or what you want, I think they should stay gone. I think they should, too. I think the smart move, they're holding on to a relic. I 100% agree. They're holding on to a corpse that died in 2015 or so. Now hold on, hold on, it's in someone's closet somewhere in a bag of Bernie's at this point.
They could totally be relevant. All they have to do is they just have to, you know, embrace and incorporate cryptocurrency, NFTs, and the blockchain to make their vengeance next level lounge rate. It's what the gamers want. They have the radio is a product, they have their finger on the pulse of the gamers, and they know it's all about the NFTs.
I don't know if you saw dive headfirst. And I don't know if you saw that I rolled the credits on you.
Loki, on behalf of everyone listening to this show right now, shut up.
All right. I know that was good. It was good. Um, it's just E3 is not going to be what you remember. And that's, that's the thing that's gonna hurt the most.
Yeah, it hasn't been well, we remember it for like, at least 10 years, like, whatever. It's like, so.
Well, I mean, if you want to try to round everybody up and get them all to do their announcements in the same week again, sure, we'll see what happens there. But you have to remember, people were already leaving the party before COVID showed up. Sony was already not doing E3 before COVID showed up. EA checked out at E3 a long time ago before COVID showed up. So what makes the ESA so confident they're all going to come back?
They're not.
I mean, just sheer ignorance.
So what Jamie said a minute ago is exactly where I'm at. E3 is better left in the past. And if the ESA really wants to look forward, now is the time for E4. Oh, wait, I guess they tried that to E5 then.
We'll do the windows thing and skip a version go simulator. So E5 is where they need to go. No, but in all seriousness, what's the next show? What is what is the future show really look like? And stop hanging on to this corpse called the corpse three, which is how I'm going to refer to it in tweets from now on.
All right. Moving on, you know, a relic that I understand why a company holds on to it is Kirby and Nintendo and I understand why Nintendo wants to trot out Kirby every once in a while for a new ride. And in the latest Nintendo Switch Online update, I mean, this this is the Mike Deft update. I almost said Memorial update, but he's right there. So it's the Mike Deft tribute update will say with not one, not two, but three,
Kirby releases except they've already been released. These are SP versions, meaning they are ROM safe states being passed off as a new game. It's interesting that Nintendo endorses that but they won't do randomizers but go off I guess. But it does. I mean, it does bring neat things to these games because these are things that often would take you a long time to unlock. So there's
Kirby superstar, which will have some secret modes including Meta Knight Milky Way wishes and the arena. Kirby Dreamland three will have extra options like the play extra course and dance select. And then the miniature golf Kirby's dream course, you automatically have 100% completion. So you have access to all of the stages right out out the gate, you don't have
we have no reason to play the game, no reason to play the game, you can go straight to the hardest stuff. So there is that. So that's SP releases available on Super Nintendo. So all right. Orin Triton chat says, just in case you want to get to that bonus mode superstar immediately. And Artesia says, I mean, yeah, I get why these exist. Yeah, I mean, and I do too. Is it's one of those things where like, sometimes the attention span for retro games is not quite what it used to be. So
there is value in like, Oh, hey, I want to play Kid Icarus. But I just want to go straight to the last level that was like completely different from the rest of the game. Kid Icarus was such a good game. Sorry, but not sorry. I'm just old man's reminiscing at this point. Like damn, I miss Kid Icarus. That was such a good game. They don't make them like they used to. All right. And Mike Defton chat says Rob killed me when I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that too soon. All right. Let's get to the listener roundtable. So
we invite your chat comments at twitch.tv slash vog network, we invite your phone calls over at vog network.com slash discord. And of course, we invite your emails participate at orange lounge radio.com. I'm going to turn it over to dark soccer because I think we got at least one.
We did. Let's see if you're ready. Yep. Hello, Laura. I'm writing to express a dis of a bit of disappointment and also feedback. This is of course, relating not to any actual content presented on the show, but instead pertaining to Rama declining my DDR challenge. I'm disappointed, of course, but the reason is because I know he he can is because I know he can complete it even if he does not. Because especially at our age, it's not about raw power. It's about technique. DDR is not the same.
DDR is not the same game as it was 20 years ago when max 300 was first introduced at that. At the time, we all played more or less the same way stomping away on the arrows, picking our feet all the way up and then slamming them down on the centers of each panel. For the record, I don't do that.
Um, we, you may have heard of Chris, is it? I don't know how to pronounce his last name. He goes by the nickname I am Chris for life and he was most famous at one point in time for being the first player to hit 100% of the notes in legendary guitar hero song through the fire and flames. But now he is the best DDR player in the world bar none. Not only has he won the official Konami arcade championships twice.
He has more marvelous full combos at a higher level than anybody else in the world. MFC meaning only marvelous judgments, literally nothing else. And currently he is achieving one MFC after another on level 18 songs, which are many times more difficult than max 300 at level 15.
I invite you to watch any video of Chris doing his thing, achieving the absolute highest possible score on one of the game's most difficult charts. He has a foot cam in all of them and if you watch it, you'll notice something. His feet barely move. That's because he is not doing what we did 20 years ago.
If you stay near the center of the pad, hold the bar and focus on minimizing movement, yes, you can have the stamina to get through max 300 more easily dash. And if you have the chance to play every week, there's no question. Unless you stubbornly insist on playing 10s, 11s, and 12s your whole life, you could easily pass max 300 before the end of the year.
But don't take my word for it. I'll post one of these videos on Discord so you can see for yourself. It takes some practice, but if you give it a try, I think you'll be pleasantly surprised.
Also for those people who want a good pad to use at home, if you don't have the space or budget for a StepMania X arcade platform, I highly recommend Eltech. If you do a search for Eltech DDR, you will find them. They ship all the way from Poland, so the shipping isn't cheap, but they're the closest to arcade quality you can get without an actual machine or StepMania pad.
And they are thin and light enough to lean against a wall when you're not using them. There's even an optional bar you can order. I use one of their pro platforms, the Pottery Barn Ballet Bar. Not even kidding. Anyway, enjoy DDR. Thanks for the show and I look forward to hearing your thoughts. Keep on stepping, Aaron Yyr.
For the record, I cannot use a bar. I will not use a bar. My pride demands that I do not use a bar.
I am old school that way. I will not use the bar.
No, I get it. I get it.
That said, I've always tried to minimize my movements when playing. Rob, you remember when I play. I don't lift my feet very high. I'm also very short.
But there are people in this world, and I'm trying to say this as politely as I can, that saying that it's not power but technique is a little bit ableist.
There are people like me who have conditions that prevent them from being able to play a game that requires any degree of stamina like that. And it's gotten worse the older I've gotten. I do legitimately have a condition.
So there is power that needs to be had. One needs to be able to have the physical ability to keep up with the speed of it and not have their legs collapse from underneath them. And that would even be with using a bar.
I not very long ago tried to play, and stuff that was easy for me, I couldn't do it anymore. I had to sit down because my knees buckled underneath me. And that just has to do with my condition.
So I would be very, very cautious in how this is stated. Because there are people that the stamina and power is something that's going to play into it.
Two comments. And the first being, I do think, and I think you know this too, that YYR is coming from a well-intentioned place where I think he hears us saying we're all too old for DDR. And YYR is trying to say, no, you're not. And from that aspect, I get it.
Um, but Rama has just respectfully said, this isn't what I really want to invest my time in right now to get to that level. But I think and I think kind of the halfway point we did kind of get to at least on the last show when we were I don't remember it was a show before, is the idea of well, maybe we just need to pick up DDR again, we haven't played DDR.
And whether we're playing three footers, or 13 footers, you know, just get back into this game that we used to love a long time ago that you know, we just kind of lost the way because Konami lost the way. Let's be real. Why did we lose the way because Konami lost the way if Konami had had not abandoned ship for God, how long was it? How long was the gap between extreme and supernova? And then after that, like it was a long time. So yeah.
Yeah. Um, DJ romance has also I never said we're too old for DDR I did.
And we need re releases of the old stuff set up for for our modern time. Yeah. But But the thing is, is that, I mean,
I and I understand what you're saying. But I would my whole thing was just to caution be careful in the wording because there, there are legitimate reasons. I mean, and I will go ahead and add age in the body parts do not work the way that they used to. You know, I'll just be completely upfront with that. How many of us over 40 get up out of the bed and feel like we're about to fall the fuck apart.
And also on top of that, too, you know, when we're dealing with, you know, add in things like maybe being asthmatic or, you know, recovering from, you know, with COVID going on right now. I mean, for fuck's sake, people's lungs are not strong, especially after they've been sick like that.
You know, I think that we need to have something. I mean, there is something for everybody in in DDR, although I still hate freeze arrows with an unholy passion.
But, but it's like, you know, it's, I am old school. And the fact that I think that using the bar is cheating.
Well, that was I'll just say that that was the second thing I was going to mention is that I really think a lot of that is rooted in West Coast versus East Coast. I do I do. And that, you know, us being all West Coast based. Let's I'm and this is not going to be popular what I'm about to say. But the freestyle was always better on the West Coast.
Yeah, it was. I was always the fun thing too.
And I think and before you all I know we have a lot of East Coasters listen to this show that are about ready to smack me. Before you do that, I'm going to say and I think the perfect attack and the bar embracing and now thing got better on the East Coast.
And I think a lot of that is just because again, just the way the cultures of how folks play the game, you know, between the Zen monkey says don't start another East Coast West Coast where I'm tired. I'm not starting another war, because I'm not saying I don't believe there is a right or wrong way to play the game. I'm saying these perceptions, I think come from what grew out of the West Coast scene and the East Coast scene.
But for me, maybe now because of my age, I look back and I just go, just whatever, whatever makes you happy go off. I used to go back to old OLR. I used to say don't do the bar. Well, we used to say something very bad. We said something we would not say in 2022. But we used to say bar grapes, but a different word. And we used to say don't do that. And
it'd be a non consensual manipulation of the bar. Yeah. So you could that is probably just, again, the culture of the arcades, where we played on the West Coast, you don't do that. It's dance, dance revolution, you dance. But the culture and other arcades was, this is the way you get the perfect score. No, you hold it's a technical game. It's a technical issue. And it's it's just cultural differences in a weird way. DDR cultural differences.
On top of that, I, I look at if you're going to be in a competition, and it's supposed to be challenging, you do it the challenging way. You know, but I don't care how other people play, I give, I give zero shits, how other people play, and how they want to be perfect and everything. I, I don't play that way. I don't like to play that way. I don't like relying on on a crutch to help me get through
something, even if it's built into the game. You know, yes, I will cheat at RPGs, because that's how I want to play. I will play DDR the way that I want to play it. And if the way that I want to play it is not conducive to endurance, then so be it. But I will play it the way I want to.
And that's fair, the video games play them the way you want to play. And it's and again, there's there's a debate of sorts going on in chat right now talking about the style of play with a minimal movement. And is that really playing the game or not? And I think again, the biases that some of you have against it. And again, I don't know if I would have a lot of fun playing the game like that. But that's not for me to determine for somebody else.
Honestly, don't give a shit what this Chris guy is doing. I'll be perfectly honest. Good for him. I'm glad he's he's doing well. Yeah. So but it doesn't matter to me how he plays. What matters to me is how I play.
All right. On that note, again, I
I'm not trying to sound rude about it. It's just that I don't, it's a it's kind of a pet peeve for me, when someone says, This is how this person is doing it. And it's, you know, with saying that, if you do it the way that this person does it, you will have you will reach this goal that you don't care about.
Or it's not a priority. Well, like, like Rondo was saying, it's not a priority. Playing that way isn't a priority. Being perfect attacking everything or that long endurance isn't a priority. What's the priority is playing it to have fun.
I just want to blast erotic songs at the bowling alley and frighten everybody that's there. Yes. Those are the days I miss. That's all I want. Yes.
I want to put in the memory card with the edit that Loki made that has the first four bars of the song and then just completely absent the rest of the song so that we can run an entire lap around golf land and then back to the machine and finish off the song that ends with just a singular jump. Wasn't that like kick the can? Loki, didn't you have an edit to kick the can where it would start?
I don't think that was I don't I may have but like I don't think that was mine. I think that was Rick's actually he.
Oh, okay. Sorry. Oh, Rick, please.
There is one there was there was one that was I don't maybe it was Jamie. There was one that was big cans.
I didn't do big cans. I think I did. You didn't do big cans.
I did the one called another.
And which was
there was what I don't know if it was kick the camera what there was a song you would put on little the one that got rid of all the half beats. And there was a song November missing half the song when you put it on little and that was Oh, it was it was a say that you love me it love to me. Was that the song?
It was it was in like, in like trick mode, you would do it in little and so there would be like two steps in the beginning and then like 18 bars absent steps. And that's where you would run a lap around the arcade and then get it back on the machine. This is things that were funny and
and 20 November also had one of those to 20 November trick as well, I think.
Got it. Anyway.
All right. Let's see. Do you guys have any other questions or what have you in chat that you want us to address tonight? Otherwise, I would go to the green room but I don't see anybody there to call us tonight. That's all right as well.
DJ Rama S in chat says I had the entire erotic discography. A lot of it is on streaming now, at least on Spotify. And I just assume everything that Spotify has Apple Music has and whatever Pandora and whatever else is in that area. I assume if it's all one, it's on all of them. But a lot of the stuff is out there now. And the erotic specifically and for those who don't know what we're talking about, I'm not talking about like what that word usually means I'm talking about E dash erotic, the think they were German.
Euro trash pop band that had a lot of stuff in DDR back in the day. They actually came out with a new song not that long ago. So they're still there's just like everything else in the 90s. They're coming back all of a sudden. So see a Tiberi with a very interesting comparison to Pokemon, talking about, you know, this whole DDR how you play it saying, even like Pokemon, there are the completionists and the Nuzlocke players and the one type of Pokemon.
There's lots of ways to play a Pokemon, that's for sure. Some people say it's okay to keep resetting till you get a shiny. It's it just depends on how you want to do it. That's for sure. Anyway, I guess I guess that's all I got. So we'll go around and get everybody's final thoughts. Actually, before I do that, I should check in and see if Loki has any last minute stories.
Um, well, I did some a cool thing that apparently more dream stuff. So um, you know, there's all sorts of crazy games being made in dreams. So somebody's actually remade Motorstorm, at least the track from Motorstorm Pacific Rift, and then also someone who made a track from Ridge Racer Evolution, which is a really cool game.
So Sony's not gonna do it. They'll make it themselves, I guess. Awesome. Yeah, that's about it. All right. Well, I guess with that, it's time to wrap up the show and get everybody's final thoughts. Dark Sakura, I'm sure you're gonna head over to Dead by Daylight tonight, maybe show off some dredge dredgefulness some dredgeful gameplay.
I could do some dredge. I'll dredge up a few things. Sounds good. Um, so yeah, I'm full of Chinese food and I'm gonna be drinking some coffee and I yeah, I'm probably gonna play like a potato. But who gives a fuck? We're right before rank reset. It doesn't matter. Yeah, just have fun. Yeah, it's a video game. Later taters. All right. Bye. Have a good stream.
All right, and Loki will go to you your final thought tonight.
Oh, shoot. Good for you. Um, I was gonna say too, I don't. Can I talk about what you tweet? Well, you tweeted about it. So I'm assuming I talk about Oh, yeah, sure. Your kid did a video. And I watched it and it is embarrassed. But embarrassed by it. Like, it's, I think about what I was creating at that age. And I wasn't creating anything like that. Like, is it? Is it silly? Yes. But is it like, wow, like, this is it. I look at it. I can't do something like this. Like, I thought it was pretty cool. Like, I, your kid
get got the content creation stuff gene getting it from you. So I'm very curious to see what he does with it as he gets older. He does very interesting. Very interesting. Yeah. Oh, I've been trying to encourage him. But I don't know. We'll see. Yeah. You should I Well, I hope I don't know if he wants encouragement from other sources. But if he wants it, please let him know. He has all right. All right. And then my final thought, oh, gosh, I don't know, I want to I need to, I want to do some more
streaming this week. And it's, it's getting hot outside. So it's a good time for me to stay inside. I haven't really been streaming because I've been doing a lot of walking at a very specific time to try to dodge the heat. But yeah, it's just finding the balance between all that stuff. But I definitely want to go back to No Man's Sky now because I want to finish the latest expedition that I put on hold for about a week. And now it's been almost two weeks. So I want to go back to that. And, yeah, play some more fun stuff with you guys. So see, um, that's it. We'll be back in seven days to recap another week's
worth of news. We'll see whatever we find out at this Capcom event that's happening tomorrow and all these other not E3 shows. Who knows, maybe we'll get lucky and Nintendo will spring a direct on us. One can hope anyway. But until then, we'll see you in seven days. Have a great night, everybody. Bye bye.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio. Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios. To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
See you next week.
Thanks for watching.