Orange Lounge Radio
These are hosts, DarkSakura, Sky and Loco
Tonight, September 10th, 2006, Sony screws over Europe and then some, chips for the Wii have been in production for a while now, and we premiere new DDR songs in our DDR Sneak Peeks
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that independent video game podcast dedicated to video games that don't suck and video game culture and the gamer lifestyle
I'm here to help you through it, my name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky
Joining me as always, say hello to my lovely co-host in that corner, the one and only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Hello
How you doing Missy?
I'm doing ok
I love your new shirt, will you please share with the listeners what your new shirt is and where you got this
What was that place called Chris?
Oh God I forgot
It was some place on hate
Apparently it's called Oh God I Forgot, is the name of the store
But on the front it says, oh oh army, in the back it says DarkSakura with a zero like a team jersey and it's red and black
I want to get one and it's going to say Rob Roberts and the number 69
That would be awesome
Oh also over there, Loki what's your number going to be? Techmaster Loki
I guess 13 would be cool
Or 666 would be good for you
No we don't want to have too many 6's because you know the 6 and 9 both are kind of like 6's and then I'd have 666 that would just be too weird
That makes no sense at all but I like your shirt, you have a shirt that says Vader was framed
Yeah this I got as a gift from Eric and Melissa
Alright sounds good, happy early birthday
Matt's birthday is tomorrow September 11th, a day that is easy to remember
I mean I never forget Matt's birthday because it's easier to remember for some reason
Yeah because if you forget we'll drive another plane into a tower
Moving right along
My birthday was the Waco deal
Wow, you know what happened on my birthday? That's when the sodomy laws got overturned in Texas and Strom Thurmond died so hey we all got something special
Alright say hello to an OLR favorite even though she's only been here for one episode
Say hello to Chris
Hi
How you doing Chris?
I'm okay, I got here kind of late and I fucked up your intro
That's okay see
By bringing you crack
The podcast listeners don't know that because we edit the show when we fuck up
Oh okay
It's alright
The podcast listeners he fucked up
We had a faulty start this evening but that's alright
Say hello as well to a moldy favorite, Drunami
Yeah I mean you have to ask what my number is going to be
Oh you're Drunami
Yes I'm Drunami
Oh okay
That's chatters meeting for the first time how cute
Yeah your number would be 23 because of your old call sign
Alright enough of the pleasantries let's get down to business
We like to play a little game here at Orange Lawns Radio at the start of every show
It's called How Is Your Gaming Week? Dark Sakura answer that question
I played Tetris on Kristen's DS while having her hair done
I've never played DS while getting my hair done but that's a good thought
I was processing
Do you have to put your hair on one of those giant dryers where you can't hear anything?
No she did
Oh okay, oh you did?
But it was while the diet because he touched up my roots and I have actually a black streak now on either side but you can't tell because I have my hair pulled back
But I was sitting there playing Tetris and I couldn't see I had it right up in front of my face because I'm blind
And so I ended up just playing that and actually I played pinball
Did you guys get a new machine?
We got a new machine
Because you called last week and you told us you had a machine
We have Star Trek The Next Generation and Dan's apparently been working on it the whole time I've been gone
Right on
Yeah
Alright
Loki anything you've been playing this week?
I played Saints Row
I was bored during lunch one day so I tried climbing the mountain that's on the side of the map
Apparently there's an invisible wall so you can't do that
But I was really high in the air so I decided to shoot rockets down at cars because that's of course the only thing you want to do if you're really high up in the air
So I did that and that was fun
And what else did I do?
Oh I finished Blazing Angels finally have all 1000 achievement points now for it so I can sell it back
That game you hate that you talk about in this segment every single week for like the past 15 weeks
I hate it I really do hate it but you know what it's done so
The talk of a true achievement point for
Hey I have a question when it comes to achievement points
Like I was looking at one of those sites that has like the leaderboards and will show you everybody's gamer score I think it was like mygamercard.net
It's a big site that has that and like the person with the most points has like 53,000 gamers points
How does anyone on earth have the time to get that many points?
They all have a job and they live at home and they just play games all day all night
Wow that's kind of sad
Yeah it's ridiculous but whatever I mean if they want to spend the time to do that I'm not crazy like that
But I do like if I'm going to sell a game back I do want to make sure I have all the points out of it
Or in the case of like the outfit I just don't fucking care because the game is so awful that I'll just sell it back without even touching it
I mean so whatever
We have another guest that's always with us every week and that is our chat room available at orangehonoredtrader.com
Click on chat and VidPala has a comment to all this
Gamer points are like the new e-peen as in e-penis
How was that noise?
It was somebody's cell phone
Please silence all cell phones before entering the studio
I thought my laptop was like making noise I'm like that's a noise I haven't heard yet
Alright anything else you've been playing this week?
Grand Theft Auto of course I just played Grand Theft Auto on the PC too because I put it on my laptop
With the hot coffee mod because that's essential
And then what else have I been playing? I've played some live arcade stuff
I've actually been playing more like Galaga and stuff
And I actually tried well Nelly's been playing a lot Bejeweled 2
So I stole one of the games from her and I played that
And then yeah that was pretty much it though
I want to play more online for Saints Row but I'm waiting for the patch to come out
Because it's supposed to be soon
You know I saw you online this week on Xbox because you can see and I saw you were playing Bejeweled 2 and I was like loser
That's because it's Nelly she keeps playing Bejeweled 2
And then I went to Majornelson.com and he has the list of the top Xbox games and now he's doing the arcade games too
And Bejeweled 2 is like number 11, 13, somewhere around there and I'm like losers
So yeah
Bejeweled was cool like five years ago
It's the game she likes, the only game, she was playing Chloe and Clyde though earlier this week too
Which is impressive because that's like the game that you cannot get those gamer points ever
It's damn impossible
Bejeweled 2 has the hardest gamer points of any Xbox game I've played, period
I don't get it, I was looking at the leaderboards, there was someone that like did 250 levels of the main game
I'm like how do you even do that? That's one hell of a lucky game because
So yeah whatever
Alrighty, let's go over to Drewnami, Drewnami how was your gaming week?
I played Bejeweled
For real?
For real
Are you a loser? No I'm kidding, I don't wanna
Look people play casual games and that's okay, it's just you know
I was bored
If you own an Xbox 360 and the only thing you're playing on it is Bejeweled
You are a loser
Something's wrong, something's wrong
Aside from that I was kicking it semi old school, I was playing Space Channel 5 and Disgaea
And the usual WoW
Are you gonna be in the new Disgaea?
When I have the money
Yeah
I mean it's already out but I wanna finish the original Disgaea first
I hear, I haven't played the new Disgaea, I've just heard that it's almost just like the first one
Like you know it just kind of seamlessly picks up and moves on
Why change a good thing?
And there's still printies in it and apparently
Goodie
There is a cameo of Etna in it
Cool
So
Looks to be good
So anything else besides the WoW and the Bejeweled?
Like I said Space Channel 5
Oh hot, I love Space Channel 5
Reminds me how much my short term memory sucks
I'm sorry what were you talking about?
Your gaming week? Alright anyway
My gaming week, cause I forgot I haven't talked about mine yet
I haven't played anything new, there really wasn't a lot new this week I wanted to buy
So it's really most of the same stuff I don't have any new reviews for you guys this week
Just because you know people don't really send us stuff
And actually can we talk about the one game that we got sent the promo
Oh yeah okay we can talk about Rule of Rose now
So cause we got sent a review for Rule of Rose a while back and I think we can talk about that now
So I played Rule of Rose a few weeks ago and it's being promoted as this Silent Hill-esque kind of game
And for the most part that would be an accurate way to describe it
If you're into the Silent Hill games you'll probably like Rule of Rose
It's like historically based a little bit
So it kind of takes place in the 20's and I think it's supposed to be like actually based on this old story
Are there giant crabs?
There are no giant enemy crabs
There are screwed up children that mess with your mind
In fact this game is somewhat controversial right?
Cause there's subtle, very very subtle pedophilia themes in it
But not anything crazy
Very subtle
Don't take that to mean that it's like in your face
I didn't get to finish the game cause I had to loan my sister my Playstation 2 to use as a DVD player
Anyway so she's borrowing that right now
So I didn't get to finish it but I did play about three quarters away through the game
And yeah from what I understand it is based loosely on
I don't want to really
I guess the story that it's kind of based on is actually a real event about some zeppelin that crashed into an orphanage
Killed lots of people
So that gives you an idea of how it might be sort of like a Silent Hill type of game
Cause the whole game seems to take place pretty much on this blimp that you're on
And it's really creepy and strange
It's just unlike Silent Hill it's less
But to be fair the blimp is expansive
Just like Castlevania always takes place in the castle
But it's expansive you know what I mean?
Exactly it's huge so
It's an extra dimensional blimp
And you know what I thought of actually
You know how that Castlevania game on DS I said was one of the first games to take the game outside the castle
That's not true
Castlevania II Simon's Quest
I completely forgot about it
How dare I?
I lose five gamer points
To be technical you could also go outside the castle in Symphony of the Night
Not enough though you know what I mean?
Technically you were outside of the castle
You were above it as a bat
You could also say the very very first stage in Castlevania you're walking up to the castle
You could also say that Super Castlevania had the same thing too
What the fuck I didn't mean
In Castlevania III actually there's a lot of parts that weren't in the castle
And in Dracula X
Look shut your mouth
We're supposed to be talking about
Okay okay let's just play this way
The first Metroidvania where you can legitimately go outside the castle for an extended period of time
I like that Metroidvania
Weren't we talking about Rule of Rose?
How did this turn into bashrobsgamercred here somehow?
It's always bashrobsgamercred
Oh no only on message boards sorry
It was a pretty fun game I liked it
It's very strange and I think it's one of those games that you're not going to understand what's going on until the very end
What did you think of having the dog element?
Because that's where it really differs from Silent Hills
You have this partner about 30 minutes to an hour into the game
You get this partner that helps you
This dog that will seek out items
And kind of adds a real interesting element to the puzzle
It is an interesting element and to be honest I didn't realize how important it was
You can actually find a lot of hidden weapons and items that way by searching out different things
And you can get some really super powerful weapons if you actually spend the time to use the dog to find different items
That seem useless but you trade them in for better stuff
So the dog is pretty cool and it also kind of simplifies things because it makes it simple to find where you're supposed to go
You just have the dog sniff out stuff
But the creatures in it are very creepy though all these kind of golem or imp kind of characters
There's children that have like no faces basically and they're just kind of I don't know how to describe them really
Just creepy looking
So with the dog element we're talking like Silent Hill meets Secret of Evermore?
No it's more like Silent Hill meets...
Oh what was it?
Haunting Ground
You know the way I'll test if a game is scary or not is I'll make Christopher's sister play it, my roommate
I'll make his sister play it because like seriously this is the girl, and she's not here right now so I can talk a little shit
This is the girl who cried while fighting a Silent Hill 3 boss because she couldn't take it
Because the boss would run around her and then try to slash her so she started crying
Which one was it?
I don't remember the name
Was it Silent Hill 2?
No on 3, you find it on the rooftop
Oh yeah
Oh I got that
Like she cried a lot
So if I want to test if a game is scary or not I'll make her play it
So I made her play Rule of Rose and she did, she freaked out, she threw the controller on the ground in a few parts
She's like I'm not gonna play, I'm not gonna play
And then she picks it up again
So the scare factor is definitely there if you're a big girl
No no no no I got that beat
We were playing Fatal Frame, one of my friends and I, we were playing Fatal Frame
I could not even get her to walk the few feet in the fog because I was freaking out and nothing was happening and I was freaking out
I got that beat
You know Fatal Frame is the one scary series I could not get into for some reason
I don't know why
It freaked me out, I don't know why
How many of us that are playing the first Resident Evil freaked out when the dogs crashed through the window?
I freaked out at the horrible voiceovers
I hope that is not Chris's blood
Actually my first Resident Evil was 2 for some reason, I kind of missed the boat a little bit
But anyway, sorry, Rule of Rose, final thoughts on Rule of Rose
I really like it, it is probably one of the games I've actually played a lot of recently
At least almost all the way through and definitely one that I haven't really played that many games on the Playstation 2 lately
So I recommend picking it up, the only thing that sucks about it is it is full price, it's like $49.99
But if you're really into those kind of niche horror games, it's going to be pretty good for you
If you like adventure horror type games, Rule of Rose is going to be right up your alley
It's got a great soundtrack too, I forgot to say the soundtrack is phenomenal
The soundtrack is awesome, it's actually done by the people who did Panzer Dragoon
It's a phenomenal soundtrack, I'm very impressed
And what's even cool about the whole thing is once you're done with the game
If you do look up, if you read on message boards and stuff about the backstory to it
It's going to be even creepier just the whole thing because it's based on real life
Sort of, it's based on real events, how about that
The gameplay itself I wouldn't call super original
And it's a weird entry for sort of what's starting to, you know, we're wrapping down this generation of games
But overall I would recommend it to fans of the genre
And the animation in it is really good too
I would recommend it to fans of the genre, I think you guys will be pleased
Alright, shall we get into some gaming news tonight then?
Oh first, quick housekeeping before we get into gaming news
I just wanted to say if you missed the announcement on our website
We have relaunched the Dance Dance Revolution sneak peeks
And they start tonight and the good news is
Even though it was delayed a week, good things come to those who wait
It will be a part of the podcast, you don't have to just listen live to hear the songs
So this is amazing, we're really excited to be working with Konami of Hawaii
To play some new songs for you, we'll get to that shortly after some news
You know what else is amazing?
What?
Well actually what's not amazing?
In Karage
Why?
What did he do now?
In the news today, he got a new bicycle helmet
Because he chewed through his strap on his last one
And ended up throwing up crayons all over the place
Wow, and did he eat paste?
I'm sorry, we didn't do Chris's gaming week, I'm so sorry
Honey, how was your gaming week?
Oh it was okay, the only reason I wanted
I don't know how many Mac fans you guys have on there, probably not a lot
Actually, you'd be surprised how much hate mail Logan gets
Okay, I have a Mac PowerBook Pro or whatever it's called
The latest, whatever the most expensive thing is
Macbook Pro, whatever the most expensive thing is
And for those of you who like the Sims 2 games on the Mac
Go out and get open for business
Because in the last few games of the Sims 2
It slows, like the computer just lags it to death
Like anything, any animation, any huge thing that the game does
It's lagged and stuff like that
And out to lunch, they completely take care of that
It's lightning fast
Like I got all the animation, I got all the little fun nifty things that happen
When your character does something
So I just got that and I just played it
So that was my fun gaming week
That and I played The Da Vinci Code, which sucks
Why does it suck?
I'm not bright
Is it just your typical bad movie tie-in game?
Pretty much
They want you to do every little knick-knack thing
I thought it was going to be cool
Because it's like, oh, I like stories
And they make you do every little thing
And I'm not bright
So there's really no point to me playing that
So you're going to pick up Sims 2 pets when that comes out?
Hell yeah, I want to kill a dog
Alright
That's an excellent reason
I like killing puppies
Please, no hate mail for the pet lovers
No, no, no, no
If you kill the pets
Oh, it's a rumor actually
If you kill the pets, they get a little tombstone
And they walk around as ghosts
It's hilarious
Every time I hear about dead pets now, I can't help but think about
Madonna!
My precious Madonna!
Oh my god
I cheered when that lady got chewed on
Yeah, it's rumored that they did it again
And they have the dogs chase the cats
It's pretty funny
Before the hate mail from PETA comes in
Sorry, so sorry
It's because you're not standing on a chair
So you're down here on the ground
People eating tasty animals
I want to hear about people eating tasty paint chips
Back to a Sony
Ken Kuragi is licking wallpaper
But actually, this is proof that he has his head way up his ass
Sony has made an official statement saying that they are
To quote
The delay in mass production schedule of the blue laser diode within the Sony group
Thus affecting the timely procurement of key components to be utilized in PlayStation 3
So, in Europe, Russia, Middle East, Africa, and Australia
We'll have to wait until March to get a PS3
However, it is on track to launch in Japan on November 11th
And in North America on November 17th
So basically, by the time you all get it overseas, we're going to tell you how much it sucks already
So essentially, Sony just gave Europe the finger this week, essentially
Not just Europe, you know
That whole chunk of the world
Sorry, but yeah, everything on that side of the ocean pretty much got the shaft
Their plan, though, is to still ship 6 million PS3s globally by the end of the 2007 fiscal year
Is this a surprise, though, that this has been delayed? I think a lot of us saw this coming
The rumors were out before, you know
Actually, before they made the announcement that there was a shortage with their shipment
Hmm, that's kind of funny, you know, because when you don't, I don't know, start production on a console yet
Yeah, it's probably going to be delayed, but
And it's also, you know, not a surprise since the announcement of the delay that they're going to be limited on the quantities
That they're going to have for the other two territories that they're actually launching on time
And that would be both Japan and North America
What's interesting, though, is that the US is getting 400,000 units at launch
And Japan's only getting 100,000
Now, I don't know about you guys, but I figured that Sony, figured that Japan, you know, is pretty rabid Sony fans
And I figured they would give them more units than just 100,000, but I don't know
Is that because of the population difference or something?
I think what it is, I think what it is, maybe, population difference
Also the fact that they have probably a better, they want to have more ground on the US front instead of Japan
Because right now, Japan, the 360 isn't doing very well, so
Interesting, but, yeah
Is Sony screwed because of this? I mean, seriously guys, I was thinking this week
You know, I'm like, you know, I didn't buy a Playstation 2 until like it was already out for a year
You know, and the Playstation 1 I didn't even blink an eye at until they started getting some of the games I was really interested in on it
So, could the Playstation 3 simply repeat that or maybe we're all giving it a hard time
Because we're all focused on the launch right now
But in a year, could the Playstation 3 maybe be a good console?
To be honest, I mean, what, the 360 launched with almost the same amount of units
So, I don't see that being as big of a deal as the fact that it's $600
And, you know, right now, like they released their first commercial or kind of mini movies that they're going to be advertising it in the UK with
And their big advertisement is, yeah, the AI in games, guess what, it's not just, you know, it's better to spend $600 to buy our games
That's pretty much, you know, their first little thing, it's adaptive, it learns
Oh goody, learning AI, you know, because no other games out there have that
Or something
Interesting comments from chatroom here, Solarwing is in our chat and says
Of the 400,000, how many will work?
I mean, consoles are notorious at launch time for not working
Go back in the archives, when I got my Xbox 360 in like February
I got a freaking 3 rings of death after 24 hours and I was pissed
I think I went off on one show
Here's the other thing that you got to think about too that's really interesting
They allocated all their diodes that were being made to the Playstation 3
Because they were putting all their eggs in one basket
So their standalone Blu-ray player is probably going to be delayed because there's no diodes for it obviously
Since they can't even make enough for the Playstation 3
What's that going to do for Blu-ray?
That's the big thing, because if they get enough of those HD DVD players out there
Then, you know, that might be a problem
But then again, I don't know, I think they use even the same diodes on the HD DVD players
Who knows
Comment from Jeremy Todd 1 in chat, with such an extreme shortage I wonder how high prices for the PS3 will get on eBay
And here's the other thing too
Remember back in spring when it was supposedly that Playstation 3 was going to launch
And, you know, oh yeah we're on track, we're on track
Do we really trust that they're really on track seeing as they haven't even started building these things yet
I mean, I wouldn't be surprised if we get to November and oh, guess what, we're delayed until 2007
So, well let's just, it's kind of a wait and see
Don't you think, maybe that wouldn't be such a bad thing for them at this point
I mean honestly, should Sony delay the console worldwide until 2007
I asked this to everybody on the panel
Yes or no and why
No, because they're going to miss out on their Christmas and I think that'd be death for them
They need to have their console out there even if it's going to be limited in numbers
Because if anything it'll sell out, people will want it because it's sold out
And there you go
Dark Sakura
That's pretty much my assessment on the same thing
I mean, people want what they can't have basically
Okay
Drunami
Ditto, the shortage is just going to create more demand
So, you know, why mess up a good marketing strategy
Even though the commercials are much akin to polishing a turd
Okay, Chris, should Sony delay, yes or no
No, they at least need to get the Christmas stuff out there
I mean, that whole market and stuff like that, so pretty much what everyone else said
Okay, I'm going to be brave, I'm going to say yes
I think Sony ought to delay at this point
Because the games, the lineup games could get stronger for launch
Because you've seen all these games getting shuffled around the launch window
They would still get the console out by the end of their fiscal year
And they could have a stronger launch
I think people are going to buy these systems Christmas or not
I think the same people are going to buy the system no matter what time of year you launch
I realize there's this huge thing to want to get the spoiled kids around Christmas
But those spoiled kids will find an excuse to get their systems in April or March if they want to release them
Oh, hold on a sec
What I think is, why would developers be so brave as to dev new games after the launch titles
If the system hasn't been sold yet and the launch titles haven't caught on
And so the PS3 hasn't caught on
Who's going to be brave enough to dev games for that?
Alright
Interesting thoughts from Chad as well
Jeremy Tom 1 says, the huge problem with this though is that a few people will get a PS3
And then their friends will see it and they might decide that the graphics aren't much different from the 360
And they'll go buy a 360 instead
You know, it's kind of weird
And I'm having this weird thing going on
The more I haven't been actually seeing some of these games again
You know, like Resistance and Lair and stuff like that
I'm actually starting to think, hey you know what, these are actually kind of looking better than the 360
But then again, it makes the games look interesting but I want to see how they play
I don't give a crap if the graphics are slightly higher resolution than this
That does not make the console any better than its predecessor
Or its competition for that matter
It's just why some DS games are simpler looking but they're more fun to play
I don't know, they're really trying to say better graphics equal better games and that's just not the case
The system is only as good as the games that are on it
True, and Psycoon has an interesting follow up to that
Psycoon says, I will get a PS3 on the day Kingdom Hearts 3 comes out
So is it just going to take, and even Chris agrees with that comment
Is it just going to take that game to sell the system?
You know what, I'm sorry, I don't have a lot of money to drop on a game system
If there's not going to be a game that I want
I'm a very big Disney fan so I bought a PS2 for the sole purpose of playing Kingdom Hearts
And I've discovered other games that I like about it
But unless they make a game that I want, I'm not going to drop that much money on it
The Wii does look interesting though
Megzy's in chat and says there's no reason to get a PS3 at launch
The only exclusive games worth getting will be out in 2007-2008
Metal Gear Solid 4, Final Fantasy 13 and so on
That's kind of how I felt about the Playstation 2
To be honest, what was I going to buy at launch, Fantavision?
There is some good games, there are some
Fantavision was sort of fun
Was it Lair, is it Miklotov or Jamie in here? I'm not sure
It was sort of fun
I would say there are some good exclusive games, Lair and Resistance Fall of Man look pretty good
But then again, I haven't seen them
I think after Tokyo Game Show we'll get a better gauge of how good the games are going to be
And they're going to have to start marketing this thing pretty soon
Because convincing someone why they need to buy a $600 console is going to be pretty difficult
So, we'll have to wait and see
Alright, well moving on, one thing that will be available around the PS3 launch
If you can't afford a Playstation 3, which most of us can't
And by the way, you know what Europe, I'll do you a favor
I am not going to buy a Playstation 3 until you guys are able to buy a Playstation 3
Which is easy because I wasn't going to get one anyway
But we can call this a protest now, it makes it really easy
Honestly Europe, I don't think you guys are missing much
I mean that's kind of how I feel, I don't want one of these at launch
I guess maybe I feel bad for the person who really really does in Europe that can't have one now
Well, you know what, couldn't they just import?
Because the games are supposed to be region free
We haven't really had super final confirmation on that though, that could have changed
However, unless Sony is just going to say give a big F you to format
Because you still have the difference between NTSC and PAL
Oh, that's a good point
Unless they are just going to say screw all you, it's high definition or NTSC only
But I don't think that's right, that would really put aside a large market of business
I meant to say that something that will be available when the Playstation 3 launches in November
Is the PSP download service
Original Playstation games will be downloadable and the PSP has no problem running them via an emulator
This is all coming from Sony's head of platform development in Japan, Izumi Kawanishi
Kawanishi is also saying that the PSP download service will have movies as well as full original Playstation games
And it will launch at the same time as the Playstation 3
And that's about it, that's all they said
Well, you can't download retail movies yet, you can get like vodcasts and things using little hacks
But Sony has yet to really support full blown movies
And obviously they are going to be releasing the digital rights management and all this stuff
And I guess trying to salvage some of what they have lost on UMD, I don't know
Well, I think they were rumored to be trying to relaunch UMD at a lower price point or something like that
I remember seeing an article on some site that talked about how they really, really sliced the cost of UMDs in Japan
To about 8 bucks a disk, our price, and they are on fire, they are selling like crazy
So that's the secret Sony, just put out the UMDs and sell them a little cheaper than what you are doing
Make them cheaper than DVDs, and I think they will be a lot more appealing to a lot of people very quick
And you will sell PSPs, but what do I know, I'm just some schmo on the internet
Exactly, well I didn't want to say exactly
But anyways, some other things that are possibly in the works right now would be a Sony Playstation phone
And I kind of, when I saw this I was thinking, oh god, please not another N-Gage, because that's just horrible
But apparently, according to Sony Ericsson's Senior Vice President of Product and Application Planning, Rico Sakaguchi
The company is working on something related to the Playstation phone
And it says the surprise must be kept for the future, so maybe something that will be announced at the Tokyo Game Show
I don't know, it sounds interesting, I'm not sure, maybe something to do with the download service
And they are going to do something with the phones, you can download Playstation 1 games or something
Voice over IP
That would be a huge perk, I think, to voice over IP
The phone station
I think what I like about the PSP a lot is that it really is kind of this all in one system
It kind of is the leg up that it has on the DS, it seems like the DS, well it has a lot of solid games that are innovative
It's kind of having to catch up in the department of having a web browser, playing MP3s and all this other stuff that a PSP does
You know what I mean?
But wouldn't you rather have a system that you know is going to play a good game, that you know they put effort into
Well, what if I'm more of the casual gamer, who maybe that's not my biggest focus on the system
DS sales are still kicking PSP
Yeah, but don't get me wrong, it's interesting all these things that kind of distinguish the PSP a little bit
I think they're all cool, but the market is showing people aren't interested in all that as much as they are in just having good games
Okay
Well, speaking of good games, there is something coming on to PSP that I will definitely be all over
Parappa the Rapper is coming on to PSP
In the rain or in the snow?
Got the funky, funky flow
Crack butter!
No, don't even get me started on too many levels
Check and turn and signal to the left, sorry, love Parappa, love it
There's not really an official announcement yet, but the game was recently featured in Famitsu
So the talk is that we are pretty much going to be getting a Parappa
And actually that makes sense because they did Guitar Man
And they're starting to put out a bit more music and slash quirky games on the PSP
So my hope is that this does come to pass
And so this isn't just a port of the PS1 thing on the download service, this is like a whole new frickin' thing
That's the rumor
Wow, that would be hot, because Parappa kind of disappeared for a while
Granted, Parappa the Rapper 2 wasn't quite as good as one, at least commercially
We need to own Jameralami
Yeah, I know, we need to bring the series back, that would be awesome
Well, Parappa is not the only thing rumored to be coming back for the PSP
Electronic Arts has confirmed that they are doing an EA Replay collection
And this will be a budget series of adventures for those folks that would be interested in this
Get this, the types of games that are going to be in the EA Replay
Syndicate, Ultima 7 The Black Gate, Road Rash 1-3, Wing Commander
And some other interesting titles such as Desert Strike, Jungle Strike, Virtual Pinball, Mutant League Football
That would be very interesting
But they haven't said anything about that they're going to upgrade the graphics
These may just be straight up ports, but still there's something oddly appealing about being able to play Wing Commander
I think they were supposed to be ports of the Super Nintendo and Genesis versions
Oh, that would be a crap, if it's just a port of the Genesis, oh forget it
It's all about the PC one, but Ultima 7 wasn't on PC
I mean, whoops, Ultima 7 was only on PC, wasn't it?
They ported 6 to Super Nintendo, they didn't do 7
Yeah, they ported 6, they didn't port 7
Yeah, they didn't port 7, so there must be some PC things involved
Who knows?
Anyways, it's kind of interesting though that at least that is coming out
One game that is not coming out on time, Armored Core 4
It's missing the Playstation 3 launch and it's rumored to have been canceled for the 360
Which is very disappointing because I love me my Armored Core a bit more than ChromeHounds, that's for sure
But anyways, yeah, the From Software game
You know, I just have a really hard time believing that it's canceled on 360
Seeing as, you know, they've already kind of worked on, you know, ChromeHounds
But anyways, it's supposed to be coming out in spring of next year
So, you know, yet another reason why waiting to march maybe isn't such a bad idea for the Playstation 3
Well, in regards to other games and the Playstation 3
Enchanted Arms is actually going to be out on the Playstation 3
I don't know how I feel about that, I mean, I picked up Enchanted Arms, I haven't played it yet
I think you're going to enjoy it, I think you'll enjoy it
You know, it took me a while to get into the game, but it's really good
I mean, it's not the best RPG I've ever played, but it's a very good first next-gen experience for RPGs
I was just thinking it was good to have such a solid, you know, apparently a solid game
On the 360 and just that it's coming out on the Playstation 3, just sort of like, no
It seems like it's a little late, you know, by the time it comes out for the Playstation 3
It'll be like, oh well, next-gen RPGs are going to be old news
I guess it depends when it comes out, I mean, if Enchanted Arms is coming out at launch
Well, that might not be a bad thing, that could be pretty good for Sony
But it doesn't seem like it would be out in time for launch if it's just now being announced
I don't know
Nah, probably not
I mean, they already have Oblivion coming out, so that's pretty good
That's true, maybe if they could redo all the voiceovers then it wouldn't be so bad
I don't think they would
It would be just a port
I don't think they would either
Well, one other thing you're going to be missing out on on the Playstation 3
Rumors now is that 1080p is actually not really going to be used in games as much as you think
According to Sony, the official US Playstation 3 site says that the HDMI connection is required for 1080p signals in Blu-ray movies
Sony has made an issue of pointing out that 1080p, which the Xbox 360 is incapable of, is the holy grail of full HD
The only game that's running in 1080p, though, is Gran Turismo HD
This was just a tech demo that was created, not really a full game that's running yet
Well, actually, it is going to be a full game, unfortunately
Well, but it should be said also that even with final hardware in mind, reaching a good frame rate at 1080p with next-gen graphics is almost impossible
Most folks are just aiming for 720p
So it sounds like, okay, your movies will be at 1080p, which will be nice, but your games, not a lot are going to be at 1080p
Now, to Sony's benefit, or to Sony's credit, though, here
Maybe this is something that would be more at the Playstation 3's end of cycle, that you'd start seeing more 1080p games
Like how on Xbox, the first Xbox, before the 360
You started seeing, in the end, some games start to come out in high def towards the end
And then widescreen, especially, you started seeing a lot more widescreen games on Xbox
And then you started to see, like, burnout, wasn't one of the burnouts towards the end in 720p?
Yeah, I think so
So maybe 1080p is just something that will be more utilized later down the road
But wait, are you guys seeing that Sony was lying when they said that they can do 1080p at 120 frames per second?
Well, in one game
Fucking retarded, I don't know why we trust them with any comments anymore
But, whatever, so, okay, so your games are not going to be 1080p
You know, 1080i is pretty good anyways
Although, one thing that's kind of being debated right now is load times
And as anyone remembers on the Playstation stuff, the load times can be quite long
And they're actually saying that because of the blu-ray drive being a first generation drive
It is going to be slower than the actual DVD drive in the Xbox 360
Now, the blu-ray drive is actually going to be a 1.5 speed drive
And transfers at about 54 megabits a second
And they said that their Playstation 3 is actually a 2-speed blu-ray drive
Which is actually 72 megabits per second or 9 megabytes per second
Now, the 360 is a 12-speed DVD drive which gives you 16 megabytes per second
So that is a bit faster
Now, the thing that, when I was reading this, is since all the Playstation 3s are going to have a hard drive in them though
The developers are going to be able to develop, you know, with a hard drive in mind
So you're going to be able to cache a lot of stuff to your hard drive, I would think
Because whereas, you know, the one big thing with the 360, I remember, because of the core and premium bundles
Is they weren't sure if the hard drive was going to be there
And so they couldn't really, you know, take that into account and cache the information to it
But I guess now more of the games are using the hard drive
But that might be something that might speed it up
And, whatever, it's load times
If you want your 1080p games at 120 frames per second, you're going to have to wait
Well, yeah, I think you said it with load times
I mean, I don't care what the speed is of the thing inside the system
It's all about, you know, the load time and how good the system is at, you know, caching and all that stuff
Though, you know, I get it, logic dictates that you have a slow drive in the thing, you're going to have longer load times
I get it, but if there's some other way Sony can get around that and the developers
Then I don't think it will be the end of the world
Yeah, exactly
Alright, well let's go over to a realm that we don't get into often enough here on this program, that's PC gaming
And we have a few PC gaming stories for you guys tonight
And I want to start off with something on Second Life
Which is this thing I keep hearing about, but honestly I've never really had a chance to get into and play
Drew Nami, you play Second Life, tell me a little bit about what Second Life is all about
It's kind of like a virtual community, if you've ever played
Actually, it is a virtual community
If you've ever played like, say, Sims Online or There or anything like that
It's this virtual world, you have your avatar, you can customize the avatar
It's got a lot of communities in there, it's fairly technical if you want to code your own stuff
Okay, I get that, it's a virtual world, why should I get into Second Life?
Basically anything you can't do in real life, you can do in Second Life
You can build stuff all on your own, have your own zone's own virtual land in there
I can be a stripper
Have sex in different rooms
I can't, as Chris said, wait you gotta say that Chris
Have sex in weird positions
Yeah, things that may not be physically possible in real life
Number one, it is possible, number two, unfortunately I've seen it done
Or in the case of this picture I'm looking at here, I'm not sure if this is from Second Life or what
But it looks like you have furries banding together there in Second Life
There's actually a pretty active furry community within Second Life
Okay, whatever you're into, don't touch me with your paws
But anyway, the reason why I bring this up, I got in the news this week that hackers broke into Second Life on Thursday
And it was noted on the blog of the parent company to Second Life, Linden Labs
The intruders got access to the account names, real life names, contact information, encrypted account passwords and encrypted payment information
Now, these types of violations of security sadly aren't that uncommon when you think about it happens in the Amazon type market
I'm not saying that site specifically, but those type of markets online all the time
But this is really the first, or at least one of the most notable cases where it's happening in a video game
Or it's happening in a place where people spend a lot of time as opposed to check in, check out
So the possibility that folks are going to feel more violated over it is I think a lot higher in my opinion
I mean we still get pissed off in MMOs over gold sellers
True, so what do you think about this? Being a Second Life player, what do you think about the fact that your information may have been compromised?
Well, for me personally, I don't put anything up on there that I wouldn't be embarrassed to have public
But the net result what pissed me off is I had to reset my damn password, they invalidated everyone's passwords
Oh interesting, well at least they were pretty quick to get in there and try to fix things, that's good
Yeah, I think they got it done in like a matter of hours
Alright, well, pretty quick on Linden Labs
Good for them for being right on it and you know, remedying the situation
Well, guess what is not being remedied
What's that?
Well not really, but you know, you remember how everyone was all like, yeah Spore's gonna be all over the place, right?
Right, like DS and PSP and all that stuff?
No
No? Like no console versions at all?
It's PC only for now
Oh, okay
Basically, and this is the quote from EA
Although we're investigating the possibilities of bringing this franchise to other platforms in the future
Any announcements or confirmations for the Wii or any other platform would be premature
Oh, this might be because I think I remember reading another story earlier this week about how
I think they were saying something about Spore on the Wii was gonna be able to download to the DS
And you could edit your creatures on the go
Well, they're saying right now they're 100% focused on finishing Spore for PC and PC only
Okay
As that's the official word
That makes sense, but we all know it's gonna go like The Sims
Where The Sims was on PC first and then you had 5 gazillion different versions on all the consoles just later on
It'll spread
Yeah
But for now, I think it's actually good that they are focusing only on PC
That way they can bring out a quality product to get the buzz going and then from their work on the other versions
Now, OLarmyEddie in our chat room says EA lies, lies
They all lie
Interesting
By the way, also following up on the Second Life information, Tigerclaw in our chat says
Also note that the credit card information was on another server and that wasn't compromised
Okay
That's good
Anyways, if you're really into Sims stuff, you might be interested in this
No, this doesn't have to do with The Sims
Some other gaming series, Sid Meier's is actually being
They're releasing a wonderful collection, which is going to be coming to the stores pretty soon here
It will be including quite a few different games, including Civilization I, Civ II, Civ II Fantastic Worlds, Civ II Conflicts in Civilization
Civ II Tests of Time, Civ III, Civ III Play the World, and Civ III Conquest, and finally Civ IV
So a whole bunch of Civilization for you
But to be honest, if you're a Civilization fan, you probably have all that shit already
I mean, is there anything special that doesn't, you know
Well, you get a Civilization card game, a 96-page book of artwork
Ooh, artwork
And a DVD featuring lead designer Soren Johnson and artist Dorian Newcomb and talking about the creation of Civ IV
Now, I really can't bash this too much because I've said it on this show before, Civilization, the original
The first one that ever came out on the PC is hands down my favorite PC game ever, ever
I love the original Civilization
Don't ask me, I can't get into Civ II, III the same
I haven't tried IV yet, I really want to
I can't get into II and III the same way I can the original
What were you doing this for? Are you saying I'm too stupid to get II and III?
No, I'm saying the entirety of Civ goes right over my head
Seriously, I don't know if...
There's got to be a way you can get Civilization I really cheap now
I highly urge you guys to check it out
Civ II is not bad either, really, I mean, it's not bad
I just didn't enjoy it as much as I
So, seriously, check these games out
It's a great, great landmark game in PC history
I absolutely love Civ I
I used to play Civ Net back in the day
But, you know, I have to admit
Actually, something like this, to me, who hasn't followed the Civ series for a long time
This almost sounds appealing
But I don't know, I don't know if I have that much time
Civilization is one of those things
When I was playing Civilization on the PC, I literally was not playing anything else, ever
So, I don't know
Nerd
Yeah, I am, a little bit
Speaking of nerds, many of you out there on the internet like to email us every week
And we're here to read your emails on air
Don't roll your eyes at me, Dark Sakura
I wasn't rolling my eyes
And the queen nerd, Dark Sakura, is here to read those emails for you every week
I'm the queen nerd, you're the king dork
So, suit up the rubber gloves in this besto suit
And tell us who's emailed us at Mailbag at OrangeOnTrader.com this week
I do want to go ahead and actually repeat the ages-old disclaimer
If you send us hate mail, all we're going to do is laugh at you
Yeah, so we had a couple ha-has this week, which was great
Thank you for the hate mail
It was the most ridiculous thing I've ever read
Anyway, so back
Actually, we need more, because I didn't laugh enough this week
So please send us more hate mail, actually
And hate mail means you were listening
So thank you for downloading our podcast
Seriously
You know what's funny about that hate mail that I read?
It's obvious that the people were listening to the show regularly
So hey, cool, new listener
I didn't see the one that was towards you
Doesn't matter
Anyway, we got one that is not crap
From Renee
I guess it's Renee? Yeah
Hello Jamie Skye and Loki, but mostly Jamie as you're the only one who mostly reads these emails
I was looking through the PEGI, Pan-European Game Information website
Which is a video game rating board
Reported that video games are actually good for you
Here is a link, it's an old article, July 12th, 2006
But at least we know that Europe loves video games
It's sort of a long URL, but I'll just go over some highlights
It was about a meeting that was in Brussels on July 6th, 2006
That had the consumers, publishers, developers of video games
In the European Union involved in this
They were including parent representatives
Panels of expert psychologists, media specialists
Who were just discussing the whole thing from what I was reading in this article
And there's actually a quote on here that I liked
In light of such a thorough analysis of current issues and such a lively dialogue
We should not let this intellectual stimulation die out
ISFE will see to building upon this exchange and make it happen on a permanent and regular basis
But as they were going through they were saying
They were just reviewing the different perceptions based on all sides of the issue
And that it was coming through that basically that games have innovative effects
You can use them for education, treatment of behavior problems, attention deficit disorder
They're even going into manned space exploration
There's all kinds of different applications that video games themselves apply to
If our army is using them then there's got to be something there
Where the hell was that kind of information when my parents wouldn't let me get a game system when I was in high school?
I'm posting in the chatroom right now
Video games do not rot your brain
The television does and then the aliens suck your face off just like in that episode of Doctor Who
I play video games on the television
Moving on
Wow this is a long one too
I guess I'm going to go over this I'm not sure
Wow this is a very long email
Sorry
I'm just going to say this is from Kenji
Congratulations on your upcoming 200 episodes
I've been watching OLR since the late 80 episodes
And while I've been unable to watch you guys on a consistent basis
That's amazing seeing we're a radio program
I applaud your perseverance against the Mackinac dominant big wig video game journalist
I have a feeling this is going to be a long email please brace yourselves
I went into the email box and actually read the email
Was this the one that was about the really in depth analysis about Sony?
I think I could be crossing my wires here
E3 and Mardi Gras
Oh yeah there's a Sony Microsoft deal gameplay
It's fairly long there's a lot of good bits in this
I read over it in the time that I had available to me
Maybe we should post it in the forums
I'm going to
Pick one paragraph from the letter to read so at least we have something to respond to here
It's long okay
No it's okay I'll go with the gameplay
Since the handheld love the adoration for everyone's favorite innocently yet so vulgarly named Wii
Games with the ability to simply pick up and play and of all things retro gaming
CD and television lives
Sorry I guess television lives console and target the mock up 2600s that are announced
That now store pretty much every good Atari game within its tape deck like cabinet
The TV games that were on everyone's Christmas wish list a year ago or so
Because there is a growing community that realizes that maybe the forefathers of video gaming had something going
On graphically sucked balls great description but it still has the staying power due to its at the time imaginative gameplay
Super Mario Brothers was beautiful in the fact that it only took at most two lives for even the most dimwitted of people
To get the hang of what you had to do and the list goes on and on
I'm going to keep going a little bit
In fact what do the majority of people who game on their PS
PS use NES SNES Neo Geo and Genesis emulators nonetheless
That's a good point
Gunpei who let's see Mr. Yokoi's magnum opus for the Wonderswan is now being remade for the current generations
And touch generations are catering to a whole new type of game
Our Xbox Live Arcade is an ingenious Microsoft strategy that I applaud even if I do load their very being
Yeah it's a really long email and actually if you don't mind I would like to actually put this letter up on our forums
Alright
So if you're listening which we hope if you're listening to the podcast right now
Just shoot me an email at jamieatorangegeldradio.com and let me know if you're fine with that
Sweet
You know just to respond to that about the retro gaming I think the person's got a good point there
I love Xbox Live Arcade as well that practically sold the system for me
Because the launch titles didn't you know rock my world but I knew that arcade was like this great thing
And there were a couple launch titles I wanted
But I think even if a game is old and has basic graphics doesn't mean it's going to be a bad game
And I think people do have a lot of respect for the retro graphics
And you know of course a little game called Geometry Wars I think woke everybody up to that fact really in this next gen battle
So I think you are going to see the retro factor really start to kind of crank up a little bit in this next gen
There's actually a very good comparison to one of Tezuka's comics
And I guess the current industry I really want to put this up on the site
It's very long and I'm not going to do it just reading it over the air
So I'd really like permission to post it up on the site just let me know please
Alright any more emails?
Oh yeah
Alright
No I have no more email
One week you weren't here I went into the mail bag and there was like nothing there
They knew Jamie was gone so I was like ok no need to email
Hey watch that ego
Hey my email is great
Ok this is from I guess Stickaxe I don't have a signature on here so I'm just going to go
Oh Eric sorry
You guys are absolutely the greatest audio only entertainment out there no questions asked
My name is Eric and I write to you from Indiana
Loki you are amazing, awesome, superior, great, mighty, sweet, strong, marvelous, almighty, godlike, admirable, excellent
Satisfying, pleasing, respectable, gnarly, stupendous, and honorable
Who is that?
What?
No I
Who was that?
That they were talking about?
I missed
They were talking about Loki
Oh ok
Apparently
Oh is this the one that
Yeah that was the one I mentioned
Oh that's not hardly you
No I know it's funny
Ok so Jamie you are just absolutely amazing
Oh thank you
This guy I'm sorry man but you honestly have to try and shut up for more than 10 seconds at a time
As he drinks his ginger beer
Not talking
Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob
Nope sorry can't talk listeners don't like me talking
Rob
I talk too damn much
I like you talking
Nope I make this show too gay I can't talk anymore
This Rob is, this Rob, our show is
This Rob is gay, this Rob is very gay
What is wrong with this Rob?
He's so gay he gays up Orange Line Radio
Rob is our facilitator
Look maybe I do talk too much it's fine
You know what it's just
Keep in mind kids what I do for a living
I talk all day to people and they are paid to listen to me
I'm a trainer basically
So you know I just I can't shut up it's my nature I'm sorry
Mhmm
Hugs and kisses
With all of that out of the way I was seriously wondering something
You probably, by the way the one I got was crap
But okay
But um probably mentioned it on one of your earlier shows so I apologize
I'm a big fanboy of the show Stargate SG-1 Oh I Love You
And last year I heard there was going to be a Stargate SG-1 video game coming out later that year
I was really excited about it at first and sort of forgot about it as time went on
It's now late 2006 and I haven't heard anything about it
Was it cancelled or was it out?
Or am I just not seeing it do you guys know?
I do know
I freaking played it in E3
I was like oh my god Stargate because I am a big Stargate fangirl
Okay I have all eight box sets and I'm eagerly awaiting the ninth
And I was like they made a life sized Stargate thing up here
And I like wanted to stand in it and see if if I if the big you know if the event horizon was splashed out at me and everything
Except that that would have vaporized me so I would have stayed out of the way
Do you mean?
I know the answer I know the answer to the guys question but I can't talk
It was cancelled they did cancel it
If you want however I did take pictures of their area I took pictures of the game
I can get all that up actually it's I should our gallery from that E3 should still be up
I think it is
So a lot of my pictures are there you can check them out on in our picture gallery on orangeoutradio.com
Everyone remembers why did they cancel that because Stargate really does have a nerd-tastic following to it
That's not a bad thing it's a good show
It's a first person shooter and I think it was really great
I wish they had kept going with it because I mean I would have bought that day one
Solarwing in the chat room read my mind Battlestar Galactica the video game
That's just a matter of time yes?
One would hope I want a Doctor Who video game because I'm into my Doctor Who fandom
But as for the very end I'm also becoming a bit confused
Would it be possible for you guys to list every gaming console you have ever owned in your long lifespan please?
We do not have a show long enough because I still currently own them
Unless you've got time for me to list off about 47 video game systems sorry
You know I was just thinking if they made video games out of TV shows I watch
Video game industry would die
Big Brother the video game
For anyone that reads my live journal I never talk about games I just talk about the TV show Big Brother
Can you imagine Big Brother the video game
Three people in my car me who does not watch TV I just buy box sets talking about Big Brother
Press the A button to continue
But first a live eviction never mind
If you watch Big Brother you get it
Anyway Eric thanks for writing in and yeah no more Stargate that pisses me off too
I am such a Stargate fangirl because it's all about Michael Shanks
Even though you hate me I'm mad about the Stargate news too
He doesn't hate you
DMN hates me there it is in chat
What?
I love you
DMN you bastard
He doesn't really hate me and look
Solarwing says Big Brother could be an MMO vidpower admits to watching Big Brother
I know we have UK listeners and I know it's a completely different show here than it is over there
But I know it's crazy over there
Anyway sorry video games yes
Okay this one comes from Distinct
Hey all the store I run sells games and we've got release dates for Wii games coming November 1
I know these usually change a lot
But I think if Nintendo was going to do an October launch then the games would be listed for October
So it looks like to me the Wii is going to drop a week or two before the PS3
Which we have dates for games as well and they're all around the same time as the PS3 launch
Here are some release dates for other titles
Loki probably is on top of this already
But in case something is different from what you've heard
Lost Planet Xbox 360 January 31
Soprano Xbox 360 November 14
Darkness Xbox 360 March 31
Superman Xbox 360 December 1
Rainbow Six Vegas on Xbox 360 November 15
And a lot of other titles dropping the same time as the PS3 launch
Oddly enough we have no confirmed date for Gears of War
Which actually had a date announced to the press
Anyway great show I thought I'd try and give some info but like I said you probably noticed this already
Did you post some of that? I don't know I don't remember
Well I mean it's different sources though because this person says they work on the retail end
So sometimes it's interesting to see where the distribution end and where you are in the retail end
Where this listener is you know
That's pretty accurate we've got dates that are in November and we've got dates that are
We have a lot that are in November 1st and a lot that are on the 15th
I think those are all placeholder dates right now
But it is supposed to be like we mentioned last week
No it wasn't last week it was the week before last I think
I can't remember I get my weeks old script
As we mentioned it is going to be probably a November launch
And that was a big you know to do thing
Also what was I going to say? I thought the Supranus game was cancelled
I think it was I thought it was
Yeah I thought it was
But yeah our purchasing people haven't taken it out of our system either
But I know
Maybe it wasn't
You know I was cleaning up my Xbox hard drive this week
And I was deleting the Superman Returns trailer for the game
And I watched it one more time and I think I might want to pick up that game
I really might
Sometimes it's not as awful as the one that was on the Nintendo 64
Oh yeah no no no
At E3 it was awesome
Imagine Grand Theft Auto but you're Superman
Hey I'd be all over that
It'll be as badass as Superman on the Atari 2600 was
Or maybe what was it?
Death and Return of Superman one of the few beat-em-ups Blizzard ever made
Okay well anyways
While we're on the subject here I thought I would you know clear up a few things
Let's see as far as release dates go
I think that was about right
Remember I know Lost Planet is coming out in January
Because they were saying that no other games are coming out in January
And you'll pretty much own January
Now I know there have been a lot of
I'm sure that you saw this too
In our wonderful Under the Radar thread that we have in our forums
There have been a lot of the stories that we've been talking about
Have appeared and reported by other news sources
As well as you know current topics and people have been sourcing them
Like for example I think when we talked about winning the 11th revolution in 2007
Bobby we mentioned this and freaking goes to IGN you know
Who reported the exact same thing
Bobby bad Bobby Black Wolf
I know he doesn't listen to the show very much but
Bad Bobby no cookie for you
Well to go ahead and gear this back towards the email
You've got a story coming up that addresses something we brought up last week
You're trying to make a preemptive strike here
Let her finish the damn email
Warrior Bob writes in and says
Hey there OLR crew it's been like a year or something since I've written in
But you're still awesome and I'm still listening
Thanks for all the great podcasts
Comments for each of you
Sky I was just listening to your last podcast and you were asking about
Disconnects in Street Fighter 2 HF on Xbox Live
Well I can assure you that a disconnect counts as a win for the person who didn't disconnect
Oh
Because I got my achievement for 20 wins online when the other guy timed out
Hot okay good
Good to know thank you
Loki
So a friend of mine runs a college radio show about video games at Cal Poly San Luis Obispo
And called me on frequently as a co-host
Like any person I've got influence in how I approach something
And after a few months of broadcasting I realized that even if I don't agree with you all the time
Even most of the time
Your style on air is basically my biggest influence and I wanted to write and say so
So that you can have the ego boost you rightfully deserve
Aww
My style on air
That was the equivalent of a man hug I think
That was very nice
One to me by right is a false icon
Yes
Damn them to hell
Wow my ears are ringing
Sorry
I held the microphone away
Oh I know
Didn't help me in studio
You guys all rule and I look forward to this week's show just like I do every week take care
Aww so nice
Aww I love the ego boost email
Maybe we should run down to Cal Poly and do a show
I think so
Was that the same person that wanted us to go there to do some type of panel thingy
That was about a year ago
We couldn't make it at that time
It didn't work out unfortunately but
We need to go on the road
We need to go on a college tour across America
Make sure that you have kegs with good beer
Just bring Guinness kegs
Bring Guinness bring bass
Dronami will be our roadie
Bring me some fat tire
Chris can be our tour manager
Uhh sure
She can bring us coffee and donuts
Oh yes and lesbian
There will be massive lesbian pillow fights at every after party
Huh Loki? Huh? Huh?
I guess
Me I'm old I go to bed early
Alright next
I like pillow fights
Next email
Hey O.L.R. this is from DMN oh my god
Hi DMN and this is the one that I said I would read
I was wondering what your opinion on Guitar Hero 2 retailing for $49.99
This being for the game only
Do you guys think that with this being the first music game being priced for over $40
That the sales of this game will be hampered
Or will this encourage the sale of the bundle to people who already own the game
Also your thoughts on Dance Factory thanks
I haven't played Dance Factory yet so I can't give a fair opinion on it
Same here
Maybe I'll check it out but it honestly
I've seen these dance games that use your own music before
And haven't been very impressed so I don't see where this one's gonna win me over
It thinks it's accurate but it's not
It can't make accurate steps the same way that a step artist
To borrow a term from Roxor can
So it can't be as good as DDR in the groove even
I can't imagine
As far as Guitar Hero 2 going for $49.99 I do think that's a bit excessive for price
I think that for those of us who already have it
The game should retail around I'd say between $30 and $40
And make a really good deal for the guitar bundle
It's like $60 for the guitar bundle or something like that
That's how I think it should be $50 for the game only is excessive I believe
Alright
Given that I spent that on the guitar and game bundle last time
Well you know everybody's gonna pay it anyway
Yeah
Is that it for email?
By the way Addict
Oh shit
Who played last week's show for her?
She's not supposed to
No
My informant in the chatroom right now told me
And I was gonna say something last week and I took mercy on you
But DEAR GOD IN HEAVEN WHY
Rob is back on Final Fantasy XI
You traitor
You are a traitor and a liar
And you need to be spanked
Chris spank him for me
A little harder please
You
Quit World of Warcraft
I can't quit World of Warcraft
My account is still active
You sit down and you sit down in your goddamn chair and drink your goddamn tea
Orange Lounge Radio is quite possibly the only podcast
Video game podcast on the entire internet
That has lesbian spanking gay men
Over MMOs
And to correct myself is sit your ass down in that chair and drink your goddamn tea
Lesbians are always relevant
I um
You have a hot ass Rob
Thank you
Um
Mikotov
Gave me cookies
I don't know what else to say
Oh my god
GS68 said that I was using a level 4 limit break
And DJ Janae wants me to hit him with the yaoi paddle stick
I need to make one
Okay
What's this we're going to yaoi con?
I heard that coming out of your mouth
I heard this we're going to
No, we as in me and Chris and Megzia and another one of our friends
Is going to yaoi con this year
So we need to make yaoi behave paddles
Alright look we gotta wrap this up
Cause we still have DDR
We saw the DDR previous to get to this segment
And whoever that little rat informant is in chat
I'm gonna find you I'm gonna get you
I know it's DMN I know it's him
No it's not DMN
Don't worry I'm going to own DMN anyway
I'm going to figure out who you are I'm going to beat you up
Uh send an email
Mailbag at orange times radio
Sorry orange time I love you
I'm coming to New York too
And I'm bringing my yaoi paddle
By the way
DMN says fuck you Rob
Check
You name the time and the place I'll be there no pants
Tape it
New year
I'm turning this car around
And we are going back to on topic road
Right now
Check the orange times radio forums
Because Sky is coming to New York City
In October and we'll be doing a meet up
I think at the Nintendo store
Uh possibly somewhere else
I'm not sure yet
But check the forums for more information if you're in New York City
Cause I want to meet some fans
And maybe tape a live segment or something
I'll just have a part on the show
Alright back to games
Super Paper Mario a game I'm very very much looking forward to
That was going to be coming out for the GameCube
Um is now not going to be coming out for the GameCube
Rumor
Well it's a rumor but this seems like a pretty good one to me
Rumored until Thursday when they announced it officially
I don't understand why they would continue to build all these GameCube games
Well I mean I guess the Wii can play them
Yeah
You know what I think
This obviously is going to be coming out for the Wii
This is coming off some IGN dude's blog
That says hmm how should I write this
Have to be vague you know
Let me just say that yes Paper Mario will be headed to Wii and not GameCube
Now read between the lines damn you wait
That was a terrible hint
Alright that's it for today time to beat Bozone
And that was coming from Matt Casamassina from IGN
Who apparently gets more insider knowledge than we do
Whatever
Look I would bet anything maybe it's one of those games where
There's more features on the Wii than there are on the GameCube
Not like Zelda where there's two separate versions
But I think about those games like the Zelda games that were on the Color Game Boy
When you put them in the advance you got the advance store
Like what was it Oracle of Ages Seasons whatever that was
You had like extra stuff if you played it in the advance
That would seem logical to me and a very Nintendo thing to do
That's pretty interesting
That Matt Casamassina or whatever guy really has the inside scoop
Oh wait no he doesn't
That's right because he just did an interview with Ubisoft about GT
And well he just found out guess what that they're coming out with
I know that I'm sure it's the first that you've ever heard of it
They're coming out with the steering wheel attachment
That's going to come out for the Wii game GT
Wait a second didn't some podcast talk about that last week?
Okay to this credit though I'm actually going to give the doubt
If they went to Ubisoft and talked about it directly they probably didn't get it from the show
But doesn't that validate what you were saying last week at least part of it?
What I'm saying I don't say that it's not legit and they stole the story or whatever the case may be
I didn't say that at all but I'm just saying that I'm not just spouting off crap here
That this stuff is actually real
Maybe you should fucking listen people
Seriously
If anybody's wrong it's the sales people
All you're doing is you're saying things the sales people told you
But yeah it's very interesting I've been reading forums this week
Because we've been getting a lot of hits on that story
And of course we can see where the hits are coming from
It's very interesting to read people's opinions on our credibility
For example other things that kind of go along with that
1UP ran a story this week talking about the PS2 Slim coming out in a silver color
As we reported on episode 196
Kotaku reported on a brand new PSP Entertainment bundle that's going to be coming out
This story of course we talked about came out last week we talked about that
IGN also ran a story about the grim adventures of Billy and Mandy coming out for the Wii
As reported on episode 195
And then
Yeah so
It's not a big surprise here
You know what our t-shirts should have that big
Should have that picture of the alien spaceship that you see on it
And it says I believe and then in parenthesis OLR
That could be our shirts
I want to believe OLR
And as I was mentioning earlier when I was yelling at Bobby
The thing was he was talking about a story today on his podcast
About how Provolution Soccer 2007 is not going to be exclusive to the 360 as Microsoft stated
Well we also mentioned that I think it was on 198
That that was not the case
That it was actually still in development and that kind of stuff
Okay big deal
We're just giving Bobby a hard time
I know we love Bobby
Bobby is awesome but I always have to give him
Allgames.com Sunday night it's 5 o'clock
Bobby Black Wolf Show it's rad
So alright
Are we ready for the next story?
Next story
I don't know I think I'm going to like Boycott
Why?
Because I don't like this game
Well read it anyway
Anyway there is going to be a progressive scan in 16 to 9 widescreen mode
For Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam
On what system does it say?
Well it's only for the Wii
Oh the Wii?
You know what that's neat that's great but not too surprising
Because when we saw Elibits at the Konami thing it was running widescreen
Yeah and I think they were supposed to be doing 480p and widescreen on the games anyways
Weren't all the games we saw at E3 on widescreen?
I think so
It's kind of weird
I mean not to belittle your story but I'm just saying because somebody else picked up that story
I'm just kind of like well weren't they all kind of showing in widescreen anyway?
I don't know
Maybe because people are ragging on the graphics of the Wii saying it's not going to be as good as the other systems
I think it looks fine
Here's something to show that hey at least they still support widescreen
It's a little something
And also they showed the first screenshots of GT on IGN
And it actually looks pretty cool it's all cel-shaded
So it kind of reminds me a little bit of like Crazy Taxi but a racing game
So I don't know I like it
Alright cool
I just wanted to point out as well I saw part of the reason that Final Fantasy 12 has taken an incredible amount of time to come out here in the US
Is that they actually added in the American version widescreen support
So that's going to be pretty cool
So you can have like in Dragon Quest 8 you know supported widescreen as well
Thank you Squeenix for supporting widescreen on the current gen consoles
That's very nice of you
I can't wait to check that out
Some interesting stuff that's going to be coming out also with the Wii
And this is rumor for now
A list of the launch titles for the virtual console
And I think most of this is speculation but
You know as I mentioned with the Wii date stories and anything like that that's going on
We're going to know September 14th it's going to be the big news
All this stuff so
For now if you want to speculate on it in a couple days here you go
The list some of the notables on there Box Adventure, Castlevania, Duck Hunt
Excitebike, F-Zero, Kid Icarus, The Legend of Zelda
The Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, Mario Kart 64
The original Metroid, Mortal Kombat, New Adventure Island, Ninja Gaiden
Outrun, Pac-Man, Prince of Persia
I imagine the original
Punch Out, R-Type, Rayman 2, Sonic the Hedgehog
Star Fox, Super Mario 64, Super Mario Brothers, Super Mario Kart
Super Mario World, and Tecmo Bowl
It's so weird, a rat, the best football game ever made
None of us need Blades of Steel
But isn't it weird to hear R-Type and Outrun alongside Legend of Zelda and Kid Icarus
By the way, thank you to somebody at Nintendo for showing Kid Icarus a little bit of love
R-Type
I want to know, I've only known two people who can beat R-Type on one credit
I want to know who else of our listeners can do it, send me an email
I want to know where some of the more Genesis games are
Because in the mail they'll probably just slowly roll out, don't you think?
I don't know, I'm kind of a wait and see, I want to see how this thing's going to look
Because to be honest, the virtual console is awesome and stuff
But it's not why I'm buying the system
Alright, well now we're going to get into a part of the show that I think a lot of you guys have been waiting for
We're going to play some new tracks from the brand new DDR games, UltraMix 4 and DDR Universe
Of course, Dance Dance Revolution UltraMix 4 is coming out later this year for the Xbox
You guys know the UltraMix series by now, it's brought a lot of great music to us
Synth-pop style music from a different drum label, as well as a lot of brand new mixes
And the last game especially was really diverse in the selection
Even some folks criticized it for how diverse it was
But it's going to be interesting, I think you're going to find that UltraMix 4
The song list was previously announced and posted to our website
There's a lot of very interesting and diverse tracks in this game as well
A lot of new originals, and we're going to be playing for the next few weeks on our show
So not just tonight guys, but over the next few weeks
Every week we're going to be doing some previews of new tracks from DDR UltraMix 4 and DDR Universe
DDR Universe being the game that's coming out for the Xbox 360
Either later this year or early, early next year
It's still a little bit unknown, I think they're still aiming for this year on the Xbox 360
And that's of course DDR's first, well your system is saying December still, right?
Yeah
Sounds good, that'll be good
American Idol, Karaoke Revolution got pushed to January
Oh, that's a bummer
Well maybe it's to actually get Paula in
I think so
That would be nice, that would be nice
Well that makes sense though, because American Idol would come out when the show comes out, right?
I thought December was a bit early for American Idol, because the show doesn't start until January
Alright, well anyway, let's get into the DDR
So, tonight we're going to debut two songs from DDR Universe and two songs from DDR UltraMix 4
And that's pretty much going to be the same rhythm we're going to do throughout the promotion
As two songs from each game each week
And I guess we should just get it started, shouldn't we?
So here's tonight's first song, tonight's first song is from DDR Universe
And this first one is going to be a long version, because we have some long versions sprinkled out throughout the promotion
This is a brand new original song, and it's by an artist called Drew Campbell
And the song is called 8-Bit
And I think what you're going to dig about this song is that the title describes the sound of the song
So I think you guys are going to really dig this track
So here it is, to kick off our series of DDR Sneak Peaks here on Orange Lounge Radio
This is Drew Campbell with 8-Bit from DDR Universe, the long version
So here it is, to kick off our series of DDR Sneak Peaks
Coming soon to DDR Universe, that was Drew Campbell with 8-Bit here on Orange Lounge Radio
The DDR Sneak previews
And speaking of 8-Bit, we've been running a contest here on the program recently
It's called Beat the Host, and it had to do with guessing the songs that we were playing from 8-Bit video games of the past
And we have one of the winners on the line with us tonight
Say hello to DMN everybody, how are you doing DMN?
I'm doing pretty good, Rob
Alright, well as part of the prize, you and Raven's Dolphin get to introduce new songs
Are you a big DDR fan?
Absolutely
Alright, well get to it, you're going to introduce one of the new songs here from Dance Dance Revolution Ultra Mix 4
What are they hearing tonight?
You're going to be listening to Edge of Control by Jondi and Spesh
Here it is, Edge of Control by Jondi and Spesh here on Orange Lounge Radio
Yeah!
Edge of Control by Jondi and Spesh here on the DDR Sneak Peaks
Alright, we're going to get into another song here, another track tonight from DDR Universe
And I'm very excited about this song we're going to play for you guys
Because it involves a long time favorite DDR artist here at Orange Lounge Radio
It's a remix of a song from the Echoing Green, so this is coming to us I believe from the A Different Drum License
And it's remixed by Echo Image
So here it is from DDR Universe, this is Echoing Green
Remixed by Echo Image, Heart With a View here on Orange Lounge Radio, DDR Sneak Peaks
Do you find that you're haunted by reflections in your eyes?
Do you mind that you're haunted?
Look into the sky, feel the wind blow
Look into my eyes, there's a place to go but I can't sense the sun
There's a pain that won't stop the sun
There's a place to go but I can't sense the sun
Echoing Green, remixed by Echo Image here on Orange Lounge Radio, that is Heart With a View
Coming up to DDR Universe
Alright, one more song for the previews tonight
This is another song coming to you on DDR UltraMix 4
It's by a group called Funk Police
This is the problem here on Orange Lounge Radio
Government is a cool problem
Government is not the solution to our problem