[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 198 for this September the 3rd, 2006.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're listening to us on the podcast feed, remember that Orange Lounge Radio is distributed in two parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Part A rolls out Monday morning, and Part B rolls out somewhere between Tuesday and Wednesday, whenever we feel like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you have to go back and listen to Part A to really get the full experience of what's going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what is going on tonight is that Loki and I have been partaking in a little bit of...
[SPEAKER_09]: Alcohol, because this is a three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: But please, drink responsibly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do not follow our example unless you are responsible, like we are.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Mikl Tov here, who's completely sober.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our special guest tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Babysitting us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go back to Part A and catch up on your Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for now, we'll get back into the gaming news on this Part B. Loki, start it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, to start things off...
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I said in part A, I've been playing some Saints Row and got some good news.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's new download content coming soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, this content, I'm not sure if it's going to be downloadable through live or through kiosks, because if you remember correctly, and this really hasn't been advertised too much, but
[SPEAKER_07]: The demo kiosks that are in your Best Buys and GameStops and whatnot, they actually do have content you can download off of there onto a memory card.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you do happen to have one of the memory units for the 360, you might be able to get some good stuff, including some brand new outfits and clothing for your Saints Row characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: including such wacky things like a samurai helmet, a leather eye patch, a fake tuxedo t-shirt, which is awesome, some tropical shirt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you get a Moo Moo like you can in Dead Rising?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that is the best costume ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Possibly, but not yet at least.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get a spike leather jacket.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who made Saints Row?
[SPEAKER_07]: THQ?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear THQ,
[SPEAKER_07]: MooMoo, please, thanks, LoveSky, OrangeLounge Anywho, you've also got leopard slash tiger skin boxers, leather chaps, crazy bunny slippers, a skull ring, a Saints Row medallion, and Saints Row wristband, as well as some tattoos.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a large and small panther, rattlesnake, biohazard sign, an ankh, and a spider.
[SPEAKER_07]: So,
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, you can get it pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've already got some screenshots of these things, including someone who's wearing all of them at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: He looks like a freak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, of course, some folks are noticing the Saints Row has a few problems with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, Volition, one of the developers of the game there, they are aware of the problems and they are working on a patch right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And these are things that are supposed to be in the patch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Improvements to the way the game handles packet loss and bandwidth management between players.
[SPEAKER_09]: This will address lag and general synchronization problems between the players' clients and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: The system for rating a player's quality of service has been improved and made less conservative.
[SPEAKER_09]: This means you'll see many more matches with 10-12 player limits.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fixed for the closed stealing exploit in multiplayer, fixed for widescreen formatting issues in certain resolutions, and changes to the matchmaking phase to get players in the game faster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like that first Halo 2 patch did a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's good, because I know the multiplayer as it is right now, at least the game I played, was pretty unplayable.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, on my friends list on Xbox Live, Saints Row is easily the most popular game right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody ever plays Final Fantasy XI on my friends list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen maybe one other person playing Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: And we do have a gang on Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_07]: The OLL Army is there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And all you need to do, it's pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me know if you've got the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send an invite if you're not a friend of Loki OLR already.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically what I'll do is I'll send an invite to join the gang.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've done that already.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a thread in our forums, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there is a thread.
[SPEAKER_07]: But even people, like I see them playing Saints Row, I'll send them an invite.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll jump in the game real quick and send an invite.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, try that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'm just trying to get some people to join up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, we're not really going all hardcore at this, but I think later on down the line it would be fun to do a multiplayer game, maybe Deathmatch versus everyone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fun game, though, multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm curious to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I notice other podcasters on my friends list are playing the hell out of this game, like GamerAndy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think I've seen playing anything else but this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Godfrey from Gamertag has been playing a crap load of Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think we need to form a gang and take some of those guys on in a multi-podcast tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully it will work this time, unlike a certain Chrome House tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is my only stipulation.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't have Saints Row yet, there might be some other games you can get soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are some other games for the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of stuff actually coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week, of course, if you're a NASCAR fan, you can look forward to it on the PlayStation 2, Xbox, and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on those systems, well, not the PSP, but you're going to be getting Spy Hunter Nowhere to Run, which is kind of a classic remake of the old
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcade Shooter Series, also which is supposed to be coming out as a movie later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: For your 360 fans, Test Drive Unlimited is coming out as well as Xbox Live Arcade Unplugged Volume 1 will be also hitting the streets.
[SPEAKER_07]: LocoRoco is coming out on the PSP this week and Yakuza on the PlayStation 2 is going to be coming out this week and those are going to be the big ones for this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: and also of course next week the big thing is probably going to be LEGO Star Wars 2 as well as Rulerose which I hopefully look forward to talking to or about soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you have news about price drops too?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of fun stuff getting price drops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, D3 announced this week that Naruto the
[SPEAKER_07]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Game Boy Advance game, Ninja Council, is going to be added to the player choice lineup as well as... And they will pay you $5 to play their game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, that game wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just teasing, I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, sheesh.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, they were getting added.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come to the Dark Side Bismarck Server
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you really can't wait for some FIFA action, FIFA World Cup 06 for the 360 has dropped down to $39.99 as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: FIFA 07, of course, coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, not too far off, but... I still gotta wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it was worth the wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, probably not.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing I don't like about the box art, no representation for the ServBot head.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the game is pretty hot, so you guys in Europe have been waiting long enough for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you finally get it on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Enchanted Arms is also coming out for you guys on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also coming out for you guys, Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot that was also coming out this week here.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're a PC gamer, you have two games coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Secret Files, Tunguska, and Warfront Turning Point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looking ahead to the week of the 15th on the PC, Call of Juarez, Faces of War, GTR 2, Broken Sword, The Angel of Death.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're a little bit more of a console gamer, you do have Yakuza and NASCAR 07 to look forward to on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, should be pointed out, calendared right now for September 16th, Miku Tavio like this, UK finally getting Suikoden V.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care about them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, you're polite.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you like Suikoden V?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it a good game in the series?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so, but I helped write it, so... Which means we have to make double fun of it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Gosh, I wish we could get the original Japanese version instead, because the English version sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody heard you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of things that suck and happen to be from Konami...
[SPEAKER_07]: FunnyFungi, Stuntmant, and Daredevil
[SPEAKER_07]: or Stuntman Daredevil.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't heard those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, it's got a 2-inch backlit TFT LCD display screen as well as some fun little white shell for it that's also lime green, magenta, and orange.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll be able to be hooked up to your TV, kind of like a plug-and-play type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to retail... Oh, and by the way, it does not come with the plug-and-play...
[SPEAKER_07]: I really love you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, Castlevania, DDR, Contra, Silent Hill, Gods Among Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even Suikoden's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gods Among Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But seriously, Konami...
[SPEAKER_09]: Get over, Frogger.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let the damn frog drown and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way... Put those resources towards something else, I beg of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is what the device looks like, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: That looks like poop.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a cheap knockoff of the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks kind of like a WonderSwan in a weird way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it's just the button layout kind of reminds me of WonderSwan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perhaps I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know who you can really blame for this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pelican, because they're the one putting it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray, hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, look, moving on to other games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to see if there's any feedback in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya says, every effing Frogger game, he can't swim.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a frog for crying out loud.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, let the frog get run over by a semi already.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's our chat room, www.orangeonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am so excited about this port to the DS, or at least I was when I first read about it, and then I was a little bit disappointed.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the most underlooked Super Nintendo games of all time that was so great was SimCity on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yes, I know it was a PC game to begin with, and the PC game was awesome too, but the Super Nintendo version kind of added the cuteness factor to it that made the game very cool, although my favorite version of this game will always be the one that was on CD-ROM.
[SPEAKER_09]: SimCity on the DS except then I read this
[SPEAKER_09]: It's based on SimCity 3000.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I went, NO!
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I hate SimCity 3000.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, nothing will never be as good as the original.
[SPEAKER_09]: For me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like SimCity 4, it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like SimCity 3000, then maybe you'll get a kick out of this SimCity DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's got three main modes of play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Build the City, Save the City, and Sister City.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sister City Mode lets you chat with other players and trade landmarks.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something to look forward to for you DS fans.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, one good thing for Nintendo is Tecmo is supporting the Wii's Virtual Console aggressively.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what does this mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it probably means that you're going to be able to play such wonderful games like Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_07]: and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have not said exactly which games are going to be supported on there, but it is going to be coming with lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like to see that they're supporting it and maybe we'll get some Ninja Gaiden stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I'd like to go to a story about the Wii, talking about the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically what's going on, there could be some production issues going on right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: GoNintendo picked up a story that was going on about the Nintendo Wii, and there's a quote here on what's going on with the Wii production.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quote, the factory has received Wii controllers purchasing order in its sample, but is still stuck in testing phase.
[SPEAKER_09]: From feedbacks of testers, currently the Wiimote and Nunchuck still have a lot of small issues, such as the buttons not being sensitive, it's hard to press two buttons together, and no response occasionally.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-oh, could this be a bad sign for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, the thing felt fine to me at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what this thing's talking about, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, I mean, come on, they've already produced some already.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see why, you know, it didn't seem that hard to play with at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: They should be able to get it right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we are going to go to the Skype line right now because I noticed we're getting a call in right now on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: I definitely want to take this call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio, are you there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I am, sort of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, is that Jamie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a very busy day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: What kinds of stuff have you been doing to celebrate your anniversary?
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy anniversary, by the way, from all of us at Orange Lounge Radio and our chat room and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Friday, I came home, there were roses waiting for me, which made me all happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, I am a girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like girl things sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we went out to eat at this place called Fats, which was me actually after we ate.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, it's this place in Roseville that's like an expensive Chinese place.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, one of the people I met at Disneyland, who is also somebody I've been watching on DeviantArt, she worked at Disneyland until just recently and was going around putting those plushy snakes on different characters' heads.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's in a journal.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: She did, like, Snakes on a Hatter.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's movie files of the Mad Hatter and Alice playing with snakes.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's been about, what, two weeks since you've been to Disneyland and you still haven't stopped talking about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: What kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I just got done playing a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The newest addition to the pinball collection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: What'd you guys get?
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Trek The Next Generation Pinball.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a great pinball table.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the thing about it, Dan got it for pretty much a steal, given that the machines go for, what, $3,000, $4,000?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, don't take the phone to the bathroom, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but we got it for a pretty good price, and it needs a lot of work to it, but it came with a bunch of extra ramps and stuff, and Dan's going to put some work into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually went ahead and played it, but we had the glass off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God, 10-mile issues are loud when they have no glass on them, so we were cheating and hitting the targets.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is a little bit of cheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were, like, throwing the ball at the Delta Quadrant ramp and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you play any console games at all?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I have Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't actually played it yet because I've been sort of busy with the whole anniversary thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played some Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to play it before the next show because I want to know what you think of Makoto.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I will play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a gay guy in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, that makes my inner hag happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, you've been playing Super Mario Brothers?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like the new Super Mario Brothers or the old one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I got one for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been giving it some play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you have any news you wanted to share with the listeners tonight since you're not here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I did release dates for you and we did mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually, I've been conversing with a few of our listeners being, I've been sort of, I looked into the box, I'll be honest, I thought that since you would check it for me, I was like, oh, I'll handle that tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have fun with your weekend off and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will be there next weekend with a vengeance.
$199.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_09]: We're almost at episode 200.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's next week, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: $199 is next week and then $200.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: $199 is next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Craziness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to share with the listeners, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put it in the DarkSakura's next anniversary fund.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can send those dollars to mailbag at OrangeScienceRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_10]: Virtual dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can draw pictures of dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: New Photoshop contest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best dollar wins.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I think they're doing a Photoshop contest right now on OrangeScienceRadio.com of best Orange Science Radio fake news.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been looking at that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all done like the old Death Cake logo.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's it for now, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, definitely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other people will hear me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that works.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, oh, I have to say, wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've been drinking tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you condone this action?
[SPEAKER_10]: I fully do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was drinking the other night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be drinking tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have fun, but not too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, I need to talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know where to find me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like those, you know, totally personal messages in the middle of the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nellie was talking about how she wanted to bring you Long Island iced tea because she remembered that one time that you were at the old apartment and you were trying to run up the wall because you had Long Island iced tea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a little bit crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some interesting stuff I'm speaking about, kind of running and flailing and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're looking for testers for the Wii, and you're going to be doing a lot of flailing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, there's some article posted on MTV News, and I'm sure they're the great source of gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, saying that they're going into more of the process of creating and testing the games, and some of the testers, for example, for Marvel Ultimate Alliance, that they...
[SPEAKER_07]: You're actually doing a lot of flailing in order to perform some of the moves, because only the buttons are using for A to jump and stuff like that, but still, you've got to do a lot of gestures in order to actually be doing attacks and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that includes a lot of arm flailing and stuff like that, which should be interesting, because I can't imagine playing that four-player, staying next to your buddy or whatever, and swinging your arms around.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii is all the rage right now and folks can't wait to get their hands on that and I'm sure a lot of folks will be wanting to playtest it just to be able to say they played it early.
[SPEAKER_09]: But one thing nobody seems to want to play is the Game Boy Micro, at least in the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: GAME, I'm not sure if it's an acronym for something, but I guess you could just call it GAME for short.
[SPEAKER_09]: A UK retailer has sent the Game Boy Micros to the bargain bin.
[SPEAKER_09]: They used to be 69 pounds, now they're running for just 39 pounds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that there's new colors coming to Japan, actually pretty much all the regions here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that we're getting here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: the black and pink DS lights, which are going to be coming out I think on the 20th.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then I know in the UK they're getting the pink one as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, should be interesting with lots of different colors.
[SPEAKER_07]: People seem to eat up that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just another color.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand why people are going nuts over this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, then again, I'm going to get the pink one, I think, and let's have a change of heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's just because I knew if I bought a white one, they would come out with new colors.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I waited.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, that's not what you're supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're supposed to go to EB or GameStop and
[SPEAKER_05]: buy the system when it comes out in the color you don't want get the replacement plan then when the color does come out that you want put down the money for the reservation take your old system that you didn't like back say it didn't work then get your new color and then you still got money for your next replacement plan for the next color you want like I have
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to get a blue one when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if those colors don't come out?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to be screwed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll have black.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's better than the white one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or just pick a color and stick with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go to another segment now, and it's a segment that's returning because it was so popular a couple weeks ago that we're bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just picked up a call there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, are you there on the phone?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, my microphone decided to die.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am doing fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just splurged on a bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have Beatmania US.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a brand spanking new DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am in a great mood.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, you're set.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we're bringing back an old segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, it's not that old.
[SPEAKER_09]: We just did this for the first time a couple shows ago, and it was so friggin' popular.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're bringing it back tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Beat the Host.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, DMN, you fucking always seem to get in on our Skype line, but we're okay with letting you play tonight because I know you didn't get to play last time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this will be the first time that you get to play this game, correct?
[SPEAKER_09]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the prize we were going to give away tonight was another space on our MySpace Top 8, but gee, you already seem to have that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll have to come up with something more creative for you, DMN, if you win tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're talking about Game Boy Micros.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the host beats me, I'll give him mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, snap!
[SPEAKER_09]: Something on the line tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that really a prize, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's a Game Boy Micro.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you lose.
[SPEAKER_09]: The gauntlet has been thrown, then.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is going to be interesting tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so some actual stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, DMN, this is what we'll do.
[SPEAKER_09]: We will give you the same prize we gave the last guy, and you will get to help us with our Power Preview debuts, meaning you'll be the first in the world to know about some of these new tracks whenever we get to do them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which hopefully should be soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so anyway, who do you want to challenge tonight and beat the host?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, first off...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even know if I need to ask because you work for Nintendo, but how would you say your knowledge of 8-bit video game music is?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty decent?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: He works for Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, he does.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't know that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I came in late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who do I have to choose from?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here's what you do.
[SPEAKER_09]: First, I have to boot you from the chat room because you cannot have their help tonight in this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can challenge either, and don't rejoin yet, you can challenge either Miklatov or Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, let's do it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's do it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a plan.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can write him down as you go, whatever you want to do, but you only get 30 seconds to name him back, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, now, chat room, you guys can play along.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amiglatov, are you hurt that nobody ever picks you for this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're stupid for not picking me because I'm really bad at this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like an automatic win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, but you basically shat on the prize that DMN was going to give you, so I wouldn't have picked you either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I could have given him, I don't know, toenail clippings, and it would have been just as good.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If they came with a certificate of authenticity, I'll take them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of gross, but you're on.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might be able to get something like that from DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready, DMN?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here is the clip.
... ... ...
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, 30 seconds to name them back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Warrior, Excitebike, Adventure Solo, Gradient, Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2, Tetris, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not Turtles 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is somebody helping you?
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_09]: Five seconds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, um, OLR, the 8-bit game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't fucking know anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, time's up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: He would have beat me because I only got 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you don't know what the answers are yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I got 3 that he got, so that means they're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got 6, which is not a bad score.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think you will beat Loki with this, but let's see, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Miklatov, if you'd be so kind, could you go get Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate to take you away from the Final Fantasy XI Alakazam websites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a lot of people calling in, but now DMN is saying he didn't get any.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you should be in good shape.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's all right, because I probably won't get any either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Loki's intoxicated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I'm going to write him down this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Loki, you know how it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: Pen and paper, the works?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting in the typing mode here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: 30 seconds to name him back once it's played.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here are your 10 songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beat the host.
Oh God!
Hey shut up, we can hear you!
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Loki, you have 30 seconds to name them back.
[SPEAKER_09]: On your mark, get set, go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Friday the 13th, Tetris.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excitebike.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bionic Commando.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, I want to say Super C. No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_07]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got 15 seconds to just randomly name games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_07]: DMN got 6, The Host has been beaten!
[SPEAKER_09]: DMN, congratulations on your fabulous prize.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'll be helping us with power previews whenever they actually happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, while I'm here, I should also say the Around the Horn thing has been completely scrapped.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I will be coming in when we get the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will be coming to the studio and giving it away live.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's going to give away a Wii live on air.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to bring a bat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or he's just going to beat up DMN because you don't like him.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't hate him at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want a free Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: DMN, I have to know, did you have outside help?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I heard you talking to somebody there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had somebody remembering my guesses, but in all honesty, he did not give me any single answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, all right, fine, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, I'm sure you guys want to know what the correct answers were.
[SPEAKER_09]: Charum did a really good job, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they got them all, but here they are for you guys listening on the podcast that we're playing along.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you beat the host tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's find out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Adventures of Lolo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Friday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of my favorite sleeper hits.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care if that game got negative reviews, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tetris!
[SPEAKER_09]: That was an easy one.
[SPEAKER_09]: River City Ransom.
[SPEAKER_09]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the one I thought was Contra.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I would have thought it was the one coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was some sort of freaking Konami game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excitebike!
[SPEAKER_09]: Excitebike!
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's like the only music in all of Excitebike is right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bionic Commando.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played this game so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the one that I completely forgot to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would have thought you'd know that one, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, sorry, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gradius, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dragon Warrior.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think either of you guys got this one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Double Dragons.
[SPEAKER_09]: And lastly, you guys both got Super Mario Bros. 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm turning in my resignation to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pitiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no, you did fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't do that before you give me the free Wii that I'm going to beat you up for.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually, I'm thinking later on at some point during the show, we're going to have like a take-home, beat-the-host type thing that you guys will have like a week to send in the correct answers and we'll give away something big like around Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're going to be really fucking hard, like really fucking obscure games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, DMN, are you proud of beating the host tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am, seeing as I jumped in the show about 20 minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: Listening live any time, it ends up working out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners before I hang up on you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy anniversary, Jamie, and I'll see whoever's challenging me to Tetris in about 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, have fun with the chatroom in Tetris.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Later.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will honor the chat room's request.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next time we do Beat the Host, we will do something maybe Sega games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know some folks want to challenge their Sega knowledge, especially against Jamie because that girl is scary with her Sega knowledge.
[SPEAKER_09]: And maybe some other more current titles.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that will probably be the last time we do 8-bit Nintendo for a little while.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to do an all Mega Man one because there's so many different robot bosses and they all sound the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: That might be one for the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you saying that you would be willing to... Yeah, but if you can just name out guesses, you can just go through all the Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe you'd have to actually only guess one per song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a list that you have to fill out.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Some new songs were announced for Guitar Hero 2 Nirvana with Heart Shaped Box Primus with John the Fisherman Stone Temple Pilots with Trippin' on a Hole in a Paper Heart That's an amazing song Anthrax with Mouth House Motley Crue with Shout at the Devil The Police with Message in a Bottle I think that's awesome The Pretenders with Tattooed Love Boys and get this Spinal Tap with Tonight I'm Gonna Rock You Tonight That is so awesome that they got Spinal Tap in the game
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's Queen and Black Hole Sun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Black Hole Sun would be great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rumor is Black Hole Sun is there.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some really weird rumor going around on the official Guitar Hero forums that involves
[SPEAKER_09]: Like PlayStation 3 versions of the game and all this crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to have to like this stupid game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you hate Guitar Hero so much?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a good time with it every time I've tried it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm with you, Shane.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like about this close to selling back my Guitar Hero and Guitar Hero controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: but I'm almost like seeing okay maybe I should wait until this comes out I don't know because I figure I'm going to have to buy another one anyways for the 360 if it comes out so I might as well I don't know it's just now they're getting what Rush is pretty cool and getting Stone Temple Pilots makes me happy and we're running low on liquor so I'm running out boys and girls okie dokie goodbye hey
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about mashed potatoes again.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can't talk about mashed potatoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dang it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to talk about Best Buy and talk about Bully and talk about stupid people having too much time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyways, there are some oddly named protest group called the Pizzaholics that have staged a protest at a Best Buy outside of New York City.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently they're just protesting the game, saying that Rockstar is worse than terrorists.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really tired of people protesting a game that they don't even know what the premise of the game is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or just how you actually play the game and whether it actually rewards bullying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because to be honest, from what I've seen in the game, it doesn't look like you are the bully.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like you're being bullied.
[SPEAKER_05]: you know, that type of thing I think it was something like you start out being bullied and then you become the bully later on but it doesn't matter because all they're protesting is that little image in the corner with the R and the star there for Rockstar I'm just tired of people protesting crap protest something else how about high gas prices or something I don't know but whatever they're protesting bully for now until the next Grand Theft Auto game comes out high gas prices doesn't corrupt your kids though okay
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Should be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I was getting more drinks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I brought you back more watermelon stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, but fuck, you didn't want more watermelon stuff, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to drink it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to go to waste.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's starving children throughout the world who might want that drink.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm not sure how much more I really want to drink this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want a straight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want the screwdriver?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I do not want the screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will drink the watermelon stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that cup that you have it in was, I think, originally a candy dish, and it is like an over... It's been washed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it's been washed, but it's an oversized mug.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like fucking huge is what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Drink gets you a big wimp.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it my turn for a story?
[SPEAKER_09]: It is your turn.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it the bully name change?
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys didn't do that yet?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we haven't.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then bully is getting a name change, but only in other countries.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you just talked about bully, yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the protests.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you see the YouTube thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: but maybe because Rockstar is a little bit afraid of all the controversy?
[SPEAKER_09]: That might be a really good thing to do here is just kind of swap the name around and then people will go, I had no idea what you were talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, Rockstar is kind of pussying out, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think they will change it here in America and I don't think that may be the reason they changed it in Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe, you know, they do name changes all the time with games in Europe for weird reasons.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a pretty dumb name for the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like that game either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, there's some interesting news about Resident Evil for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually coming from Tara Platt, who is the voice actress for Jill Valentine.
[SPEAKER_07]: She confirmed that the game will feature zombies, or zombie-like enemies, and plant creatures, as well as a wide variety of weaponry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The fact that Mrs. Platt was aware of the weapons in the game infers that she's voicing a playable character and not just doing
[SPEAKER_07]: A cameo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says Jill being the main character increases likelihood of seeing Carlos and Barry turn up as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they're remaking the first one or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully it's not a gun survivor game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because those kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you looking forward to Resident Evil on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I found something else funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: She sent them an email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is coming from Kotaku here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I sent them an email about saying that she's not allowed to verify information about Biohazard 5 or Resident Evil 5 in Japan or in the Wii game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, oops, I slipped and then I take it all back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a quick story for you guys here regarding, also on the Wii, The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in a little, tiny little blip that IGN wrote earlier this week, they dropped an interesting little tidbit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twilight Princess will not only be bigger, a horse ride from one side of Hyrule to the next is rumored to take 45 real minutes to get from one side of the world to the other on a horse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, that's nothing compared to a chocobo ride around Final Fantasy XI, but
[SPEAKER_09]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_09]: MMOs are supposed to be big, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's still pretty impressive, you've got to admit.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got to imagine how long it's going to take you to walk, then, from the other side.
[SPEAKER_05]: Horse will significantly increase the speed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking, obviously, at some point you'll be able to play an ocarina and be able to warp around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you think you have an ocarina?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you have to, it's Zelda.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they don't always have ocarinas.
[SPEAKER_09]: They could have something else, a flute, something.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know there's going to be a tornado that will wish you away, because they're not going to expect people to actually use 45 minutes to run from one side unless they're exploring.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or do they?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they'd be stupid if they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: They made you do that crap in... What's that game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had to go and find the Triforce pieces and that was hours upon hours of pain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wind Waker was a little bit lame compared to the other Zeldas and that other god-awful 64 one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Majora's Mask.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't even get me started.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be honest, I kind of liked Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have rather seen that kind of
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess, not Link's Awakening, but I don't know, one of the older Zelda's done kind of the same style as Wind Waker, but actually be for the GameCube in fully 3D and not for the DS with Wind Waker graphics type of crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, speaking of stuff that's kind of crappy, live ads coming to video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: EA has signed a deal with two ad companies that will stream live advertisement into the brand new Need for Speed Carbon and, of course, the upcoming PC and probably next-gen game, Battlefield 2142.
[SPEAKER_07]: Quite interesting that they're doing this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, they've also kind of run into a lot of controversy with, you know, gathering information about their users and whatnot for God knows what reasons.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe now they're going to be gathering information about their users to advertise to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think if I pay for a game, then why the fuck do I got to see advertisements in the game as well?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's going to be kind of stupid when I'm playing around Battlefield 21, you know, 42, and all of a sudden there's a Toyota Yaris...
[SPEAKER_07]: Funnydale says Orange Launch Radio needs to have ads in Saints Row
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: You think this is the end of video games as we know it, or what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's not the end, because, you know, I can ignore them just as easily as I ignore everything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least they're not having, like, the Bird King King coming out and fucking, you know, walking around.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still think, though, they should have made him a playable character in Fight Night Round 3, because that would have been fucking... I would have bought the game for... I would have bought Fight Night Round 3 just for that, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just put the Muppets into the Fight Night engine, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I gotta say, Rumble Roses, okay, true, that game was kind of shitty, but it was hilarious watching, I mean, getting to play the women beating up on each other was so funny, because, like, you know, I was able to give running commentary on the game, and I was just going like, ow, you just got kicked in the vagina, ow, you just got kicked in the vagina, and it was really funny, wasn't it, Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because I had to work on that game and I don't find anything about that game funny anymore because it's obnoxious and annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell us what you did on the game or is that secret?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you rather play Bomberman Act Zero or Rumble Roses XX?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd rather have my hands cut off.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I just worked on text.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would you rather play Rumble Roses XX or not have a new sweet coding game ever again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um... If it ended on 5, that wouldn't be terrible, but... Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else you want to say on this topic, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I gotta play through that damn game to get the achievements.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't want to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our Skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so sorry for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our Skype line is open, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can give us a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's area code 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: But remember, a toll charge may apply if you're using that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you can call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just go to OrangeLoungeRadio.com, click on Interact With Us for all the details.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you can call username OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_09]: For now, let's go to the phones and take a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_12]: The PSP thing and the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_12]: You speak on it very briefly and you said, what is wrong with porn?
[SPEAKER_12]: I enjoy porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_12]: I enjoy Super Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, so there's no need for a PSP versus DS war.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty much what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone should just get along.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, what do you think the PSP's strengths are and what do you think the DS's strengths are?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I think the PSP's strengths are it's in the video games and video.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's where the strength is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it really does well with that, and the DS is, you know, DS is good for, like, porting games, right, with the touchscreen, and that's what the Wii is gonna be like, it's gonna be like touchscreen, I mean, not touchscreen, I mean with... A different way of interacting with the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, who knows, there are rumors that the DS could be used as a controller on the Wii, much like you could use a Game Boy Advance on the GameCube with that special little hookup.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe there will be touchscreen Wii games in the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas the PSP, you can only use as your rear-view mirror on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was funny, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, in all seriousness, that is a pretty cool feature.
[SPEAKER_09]: Expensive, but good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think of PSP a lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wouldn't you think if the PSP didn't come along that they'll be like ports of Nintendo 64 games a lot more expensive?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, run that by me again, because you're kind of cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, if the PSP didn't come along, the Nintendo 64, of course, would be on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, that's kind of what the Nintendo DS feels like to me, is the Nintendo 64 with touchscreen graphics.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but if the PSP didn't come along, that would be like... Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: and I thank PSP for that and for its innovation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_12]: My internet sucks tonight, Sky.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's why I'm calling on my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: That answers the lie because it's a little bit fuzzy but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: We appreciate the phone call nevertheless.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good week, my friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: You too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Until next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on Interact With Us, or 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoa, shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, my friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, why is everyone getting their panties in a bunch about Bully, especially groups that think they know a lot about the game, yet they're protesting misinformation?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's teaching the youth of America how to smoke, crack, and worship Satan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, Billy's teaching him about the right thing to do, fighting back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's debatable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, every family can choose.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you get pumped around, you fight back.
[SPEAKER_09]: My parents didn't choose to raise me that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: They didn't choose to raise me to fight back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did they raise you to use your words?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they raised me to go run and tell the principal and then sue him.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: But something along those lines.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't fight violence with violence.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not in my household.
[SPEAKER_00]: I sort of suspect that the pieces of comics are being manipulated by, you know, he who cannot be named.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well, needless to say, it's up to a parent how they want to raise their kids or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it should also be up to a parent how they want or what games they want their kids... Sorry, I've been drinking a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's also up to a parent... That's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you're slurring too a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's up to a parent... Shut up!
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm trying to think!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's also up to a parent how... God damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's up to a parent what games they want their kids to play, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was my point.
[SPEAKER_00]: They ultimately control what the kid actually plays, and that's where all the responsibility falls, not the government, not the right of the government to tell us how to live our lives to an extent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Obviously, murder, stealing, and all that other stuff has to be regulated, but... Okay, well, now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, here's another question for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about freedom of speech?
[SPEAKER_09]: These guys have a right... These guys have a right... Well, I'm defending these guys a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just be a devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_09]: These guys have a right to protest just as we have the right to get on internet radio and call them stupid heads.
[SPEAKER_00]: I respect that right, but I also have the right to criticize.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm trying to be very constructive in that I'm pointing out their fallacies.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like the fact that they're saying that the FCC regulates the whole content rating, which actually the ESRB does.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the fact that they're saying that Rockstar is a bunch of terrorists, that's just blown out of proportion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I can agree with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What could these guys do better if they wouldn't get their point across?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, they need to play the game and then criticize.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't criticize something that you don't know or haven't seen or haven't experienced.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's what people, you know, it's been done already in the past.
[SPEAKER_00]: People have jumped the gun too quickly without knowing the whole side of the story and they just made up their mind already.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you know what, guys?
[SPEAKER_09]: Halo 3 fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate to tell you, but it's going to be the biggest letdown of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a horrible game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Live is so buggy, you guys, you wouldn't even believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, it's just, you know, those people make up their mind without hearing the other side of the story.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're fools.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just literally fools.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're not that smart to actually, you know, they don't have the guts to actually experience the other side of the story and then make up their mind and what they want to stand for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, any other words you have for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: That was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And just, you know, don't drink in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I won't.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't drink in 2DX, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: The chatroom's yelling at me over that Halo 3 comment.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kidding, you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a joke, in a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a bad joke, but it was a joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: If that makes any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll take one more call if anybody actually wants to call us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Area code 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, kids, that may be a toll call.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are too cheap to get an 800 number, or at least Skype doesn't offer them yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you can Skype us, username OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm noticing the phones are a little dead tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little weird for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: We usually have, like, tons of people calling in, but not tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone is kind of on vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Out drinking at their local Labor Day barbecues.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know what was going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know what...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know what was going on in town here locally tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm here at this show instead of being at this event.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a big gay pride fest going on downtown.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have Riken from The Amazing Race.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you love him.
[SPEAKER_09]: And probably his boyfriend Lance Bass is there too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tiffany and Debbie Gibson on the same stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds terrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but you're a homophobic gay man.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true, but still terrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how I describe you to all my friends, Shane.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a homophobic gay man.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's better, Tiffany or Debbie Gibson?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, who's me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, me is Drunami.
[SPEAKER_08]: Drunami, you didn't sing Electric Youth, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't drink anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we have to respect his right to be sober.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but we don't have to like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody has to drive you to life after the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying it to piss you off.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't even fucking played Sucor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, this is just like last time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you call in to say anything intelligent?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or did you just come on to fuck up the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm calling in to fuck up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I'm hanging up on you, bitch!
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you have something intelligent to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, uh, next time we do Beat the Hosts, I am so in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, this is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Nintendo Maniac 64, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um... I just berated the last caller, so I'm in an angry mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you better have something good to say, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is just a simple question, and I sent in... Okay, I can do questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: ...but nobody read it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might have read it, we just ignored it for now.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might get into it next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess we'll do your question, since you have a question.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is your question?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I remember something about last year, where you mentioned something about an Ogvorbis stream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did that ever exist?
[SPEAKER_02]: A what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like an Ogvorbis stream?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, um, you know, okay, that would involve us getting off of Live 365, which right now, um, we have other options we're pursuing is all I can say right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, oh, the OGG stream is a little bit on hold.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was something we were exploring previously.
[SPEAKER_09]: We do know it would give a little bit of a better sound than MP3 Pro, but, uh, um, we're just not going to do it at this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there something you want to say about OGG?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's just that I thought of it, and I'm like, wait, I know he said something about Augs Vorbis.
[SPEAKER_02]: but I had no idea what.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, okay, so it was supposed to be like a future idea or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, yes, but we have another future idea that's taking precedence and that's all I can say at this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any comments on tonight's stories otherwise?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh... Okay, I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's go...
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to drink more often because I get mean angry jokes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do love the callers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is what every iTunes reviewer has always wanted us to do to the calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, this is Jaded.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Jaded.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind I'm in a bad mood, so make it good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just reading all these DS reviews, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like what DS reviews?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pardon me?
[SPEAKER_09]: You say DS reviews?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, DS reviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, what's on your mind with the DS reviews?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, all these new products, or actually all these full products that I saw for the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, who's writing the DS reviews?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I want to know if I value their opinion or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, they're not reviews.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're just products that I think are pretty cool for the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, what are they?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I found the DS Rumble Pack.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also found the DS TV Tuner.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also found the DS Memory Expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this a website or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I just have a friend that's looking up random DS things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: What, are you going to buy these, or what?
[SPEAKER_11]: He's thinking about it, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: On top of that, about your game, Beat the Host.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beat the Host.
[SPEAKER_09]: We love Beat the Host.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: You want to get into some really odd boss stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: How about you do stuff from the Atari era?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you say it though, then everybody's prepared for it so it's not so offbeat.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: True.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I do like the idea of Atari 2600 stuff, but here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of the folks that listen to our program are like 17 and weren't even a sperm yet when Atari 2600 was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I guess we could, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would you do an Atari 2600 beat the host?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would probably get less right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's the thing is a lot of Atari 2600 games didn't have music.
[SPEAKER_09]: We will take it under consideration for the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: How does that sound?
[SPEAKER_09]: Pardon?
[SPEAKER_09]: We will take it under consideration for the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: How does that sound?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that would sound pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Atari 2600 games did have music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, also you're forgetting the Atari 7800.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Atari 800, the Atari 400 Wait, okay, now you're just getting crazy Because not that many people played those systems I mean, we could, I guess But then why don't I throw in VIC-20 games while we're at it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on Okay, that would be a pretty good idea You need to throw in those Tiger Electronics Okay, but that's assuming that the host would be able to get any points at all We don't want to embarrass ourselves through this game
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to cover all genres of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're taking all your suggestions under consideration.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for your feedback.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to share with the listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, then that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're so mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jaded's a good guy, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: He really supports us.
[SPEAKER_09]: I shouldn't have hung up on him, but I'm just feeling a little feisty tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Should we do one more call?
[SPEAKER_09]: PS3
[SPEAKER_07]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You pay $600 for it, you get no HDMI cable.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it sucks to be you hooking it up to a high-end media center or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, some other things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking, since you were talking about, well, they were talking about accessories for the DS, Europe is supposed to be seeing a DS MP3 player this October.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: and supposedly it's going to be using the flash... What was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just collect those SD memory cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're getting another call on the skyline, so I'm going to go to that right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okie dokie.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: No one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a crank call!
[SPEAKER_07]: Crank call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the last one I had, which was really cool, there's five games that...
[SPEAKER_07]: are coming to Xbox Live Arcade from NVIDIA.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you might know NVIDIA who happen to be...
[SPEAKER_07]: They own the rights to the Sierra games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to be getting wonderful games like Megaforce, which I never played, 3D Ultra Mini Golf, which was fucking awesome on the PC, and I used to play this online all the time, Red Baron, and two other games, one based on The Incredible Machine, and one based on the popular TV series Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am incredibly excited about The Incredible Machine game.
[SPEAKER_07]: XBOX Live Arcade King's Quest, Space Quest, Leisure Suit Larry
[SPEAKER_09]: bring me these games on a console yes I know I can get most to that stuff through GameTap and that's cool but you know I played those games on a computer before I want to do something on a console I want
[SPEAKER_09]: Achievement Points for King's Quest 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that too much to ask?
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to know something funny?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is just purely observational.
[SPEAKER_07]: GamersReports.com You know how they have banner ads on websites and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: This one has a banner ad for a London escort service.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they have escorts on a gaming news site.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm easily amused tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, and there's rumors about Rez coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't know if that's really anything, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if they've actually got info to back that up, but it's probably one of those, yeah, that would be cool to, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm seriously considering it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was the quote here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm currently seriously considering it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's always been there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm always thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Space Channel 5 is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Space Channel 5 on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you'd have to do the motions for the different dances and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Chew!
[SPEAKER_07]: So you'd be doing the dances too?
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to bring our show to a close then for this evening.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys, by the way, for tuning in and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know we were a little crazy tonight and, you know, we appreciate you guys sticking by us no matter what.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miklatov, thank you for being here even though you barely ever talked at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm reading.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you reading?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's more important?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're chatting on Instant Messenger, at least be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm also reading about Blue Maze.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who are you chatting with on Instant Messenger?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jazz and, god, I don't remember his name on DDR Freak and that
[SPEAKER_05]: Makes me angry, but the guy that sent us, or that sent the cookies for Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: I only know him by his real name now, I don't remember his... I know his name on Xbox Live, but I can't... El Mullet!
[SPEAKER_05]: El Mullet, yes, I'm talking to El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's he doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't heard from him in a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does he still listen to the show?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea, because I didn't ask him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ask him if he's listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll maybe do that later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're talking about Dance Factory right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that game came out last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and it's pretty stupid from what I understand, but it's getting good scores.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is getting good scores.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what the scores are?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, because then you can put any song in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but all those dance steps are probably crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and off-sync apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's eye-toily mode doesn't work, I guess, which makes it equally cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they have a bundle with a really crappy dance pad coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's something I'll be skipping.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what game they should put out over here that's coming out in the UK?
[SPEAKER_07]: B-Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I vaguely remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a breakdancing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like a Bust the Move.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love that, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a great thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what they need?
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: X-Tango
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: If you guys can see this right now, it's the stupidest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't go out in public if you're like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I can.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to go meet your boyfriend at Taco Bell that we were talking about during the live bonus segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's totally not working now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we really have to end the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final thought, Miklotop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm really hungry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to play more Saints Row tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is I'm really sorry for making a mess of myself tonight, and...
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I'm sorry to the callers I hung up on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm really not that mean usually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stock salt here and I'll be able to get more drunk next time because I can drink faster that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next week on the program it is episode number 199.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're hoping to have a good interview for you next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, we'll be saving all the good stuff for episode number 200, which is just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully, I don't know for sure yet, but it looks like the Power Previews may be back next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: so it's definitely incentive for you guys to listen live if you're not already so we'll see you next week thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening have a great week and don't drink and drive, it's bad have a good night
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_04]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!