[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: Sunday, September 17th, 2006 for episode 200.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you can't join us live, there's always a podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what we'll be talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be talking about the Wii because the official announcement is going to be happening, what, this Thursday?
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet Nintendo planned it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They knew.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did it just for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Reggie to come out on stage with his 40 and go, this one's for OLR!
[SPEAKER_03]: My bitches!
[SPEAKER_09]: I am nobody's bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will, however, whore myself out for... Yeah, but who needs a Nintendo press conference to have Wii News?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, you don't need Wii News.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do what some sites did and tell people, hey, guess what, we got big freaking news coming!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 12.01 in the morning and then you find out, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something that we pretty much already knew, that the Wii chips were well under production.
[SPEAKER_02]: But IBM came out and confirmed that, that it's been in production since the beginning of this quarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for those of you who are not savvy in the calendar, that means July.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so that the actual first shipments of the chips are in Nintendo's hands, and that the Wii is well underway for launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whenever that is, of course, we'll know that in a few days.
[SPEAKER_02]: November, though, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: We know that for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, it's November, but you know, I'm still not whole... You never know, they could just come and say, You've been punked!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fucking... It's coming out tomorrow!
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as we're not juiced, I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and to the site's credit, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: I know the hype machine got way out of control, but they didn't know that people were going to run in on Dig and all this crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, people went wild with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be news soon, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heck, we already told you guys, the Wii is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, definitely one thing that will be coming to the Wii that is a little bit of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not usually the type of game you think about when you think about Nintendo, at least I don't, but Splinter Cell Double Agent does appear that it's going to be a launch title, at least that's what IGN reported earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii version, Splinter Cell Double Agent, was based on the PlayStation 2 and GameCube builds, and it will fully utilize the unique control system that the Wii has.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, nothing specific has been given on the control system yet, but I'm sure we will know more as time moves on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Examples that have been given as possible ideas that the Wiimote could be used to pick locks and cute little things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that should be fun for those of you guys that are into the Splinter Cell series.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do have a Wii and you just don't want that new finicky controls and stuff from the Wii version, you can just get the GameCube version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, speaking of...
[SPEAKER_09]: I have an announcement to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: I am really fond of burritos.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're burrito-sexual, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm burrito-sexual.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, really, I, uh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe one day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, release dates.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 11th in the UK, we have LEGO Star Wars 2, the opening, the original trilogy, coming up for everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm not kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming up for everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except for PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, even PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming up for everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking at that and it's all...
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope you're a Star Wars fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually a bunch of stuff on the 15th too.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have 50 Cent Bulletproof on PSP, Ace Combat Zero, The Belkan War, Broken Sword, The Angel of Death, Call of Juarez, Faces of War, GTR2, Joint Task Force, NASCAR 07, yay, Nightwatch, Passport 2, dot dot dot, Pro Stroke Golf, I love that name, Pro Stroke, Golf World Tour 2007,
[SPEAKER_09]: Rome, Total War, Alexander, Secret Files, Tunguska, Steambot Chronicles, Super Bike Racing Challenge, Tekken Dark Resurrection, which I have and it's freaking rad, and Yakuza.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 16th, I'll be getting Suikoden V. Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pretty good lineup there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to share this real quick from chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100Matt says, the Wii rumors are like the US terror threat.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know when it will happen, but it will happen soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good analogy.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to join our chat room and get funny little gems like that, it's orangelawntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bravo to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anywho, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: is getting quite a slate of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, they are also getting LEGO Star Wars 2, the original trilogy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some stuff also coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got, of course, the good Bomberman on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Hoops 3-on-1 for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cookie Mama, also for the DS, Godfather on the 360, and then Godfather Mob Wars on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: King of Fires 2006 is coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mega Man ZX on the DS, NHL 07 on PS2, Xbox, 360, PSP, NHL 2K7 on PS2, Xbox, 360 Rengoku 2 on PSP, One Piece Pirates Carnival on PS2, Gamecube
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Robot Taisen
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Slug 6, Mina no Tennis
[SPEAKER_03]: Cluster Edge, G.I.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jockey 3 and 4 Simple 2000 Series Volume 106, 107, and 108
[SPEAKER_03]: Winning Post 6 coming out also from Koei and Neon Genesis Evangelion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Evangelion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said it, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kotsetsu no Girlfriend Special Edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another Eva dating sim?
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out September 15th.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one of the Evangelion dating sims.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one of the ones on Saturn.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, those are so hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're dating sims with combat sequences.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did, however, get to end the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I got for you guys this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I need to borrow for the Saturn?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to borrow a stall.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a stall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, speaking of good games, because a stall was freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this will interest Chris.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kingdom Hearts 2 is eventually coming out in the U.K.,
[SPEAKER_09]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, dear, the wee is not out yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: That suddenly made me think of Mitch Hedberg.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's like, wee!
[SPEAKER_09]: When you're having fun, you mention yourself and other people!
Wee!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, Kingdom Hearts 2 is on its way to Europe very soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: You will like it!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's cute!
[SPEAKER_09]: It really is!
[SPEAKER_09]: Axel!
[SPEAKER_06]: Axel!
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we've got it memorized by now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't get that yet unless they imported it.
[SPEAKER_15]: They will, believe me, they will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, back to the news before I'm so rudely interrupted by Mr. Junami in the corner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go eat a donut.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, but there's a difference between your helping and Junami helping.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because I always forgive you because you're cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, she just watched the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm not?
[SPEAKER_09]: Back to the news, hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you're a boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't count.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: To our friends in the UK, it will actually be coming out on September 29th.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came out last December in Japan, and we got it this year a few months ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: But honestly, get the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: When it is out, get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of great gameplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: But make sure that you do Agrabah and the Pride Lands.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make sure that you do them, because Jamie decided she was going to skip those two places, and now can't get back to them.
A.K.A.
[SPEAKER_09]: you fucked yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did, so I have to start over from Dan's game, because he's right where I am, only he did those two parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who the hell skips areas?
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that I was going the right way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It gave me a choice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I chose the one I wanted to do pirates, and I wanted to do... You chose wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I wanted to do pirates in Halloween Town, so you shut up, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: Barbossa Barbossa
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that came from when we were riding Pirates of the Caribbean the second time through when we were singing with the whole ride, annoying the people in front of us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Barbossa's up on the Wicked Wench, so we decided to call him Dreamboat Barbie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, guys, get the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: September 29th, you will not be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Rob...
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, and as far as also other stuff... Okay, these people are giggling and driving me nuts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vice City Stories...
[SPEAKER_09]: and Grand Theft Auto by City Stories will not be going out until November in the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was supposed to be out October 20th and now it's been pushed back to November 3rd.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's also another good game if you're into the GTA series.
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually is a really good addition to PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: My man's been pretty happy with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's also delayed in the United States too, November 1st.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I was referring to Liberty City Stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, was the story about Liberty City?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it's anything like Liberty City... You were about to say Liberty Shitty, I think you were.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's my game, bitch!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm saying if it was anything like Liberty City Stories, because Dan was playing that game all the time, keeping me awake.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hear...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not a big fan of Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand why it's so freaking amazingly popular, but I think I might actually get suckered into playing Saints Row, because as we've all found out, I easily succumb to peer pressure, hence why I'm playing Final Fantasy XI again.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll probably go to Saints Row, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a fun, casual game, where you casually beat up workers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like casual.
I like beating up workers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, delayed in the United States until November 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks because I was really looking forward to play that in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just play some more Liberty City stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of delays, Forza 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been rumored to be delayed to 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is coming straight from the development team.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their quote is, I think we've always said that it will appear in our...
[SPEAKER_02]: Day of Forza
[SPEAKER_02]: It's rumored, let me put it this way, it's not coming out when it was supposed to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because this is straight, you know, I actually, when I saw this story, I, you know, called my Microsoft rep and asked him when the fuck this game's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's to be announced right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was in November, I think the 15th, and now it's being pushed back even further.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we're supposed to know the official date in a couple weeks, so that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the other game I was going to mention?
[SPEAKER_02]: Crackdown was another game that was slated for the end of, or actually middle of October, and that's been delayed to be announced now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now the only Microsoft game coming out in October, Fusion Frenzy 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of delays on the Xbox, if you were the one person that was looking forward to Scramble coming onto Xbox Live Arcade this week, sorry, but you have to wait one more week because there were some last-minute things that had to be cleaned up with Scramble, and it's now going to be released this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably by the time you hear this podcast, it's already on the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those of you folks listening live, it'll be out this Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, Microsoft has this big Xbox Live Arcade promotion thing going on where they're trying to release new stuff every Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they had to put something out this Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what did we get instead of Scramble?
[SPEAKER_03]: We got a brand new Uno deck featuring cards from Project Gotham Racing 3 for 100 points.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet less people will be buying this than Scramble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, there's a lot of Uno horse out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people are pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're Unos.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not a big Scramble fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of things coming out for the 360, Japan is actually getting lucky.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might remember when the console launched over Japan, they didn't get a core unit.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically just had the premium unit and that was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now the 360 core is making its way over to Japan and they're getting a few additions to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: The price point is going to be less than what it is in the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only going to be 29,800 yen, which is around about $255, which is about 40 bucks less than what we're paying for it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, what's kind of neat about it is the core pack will include two games, 99 Nights and Project Gotham Racing 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the hard drives are supposed to be sold around $85 there, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, overall, they're getting a pretty good discount.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish we'd get some bundles over here, but that's not going to be the case.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all that's going to be available November 2nd.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, speaking of...
[SPEAKER_09]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll be in euros.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's 293 euros, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it will come with two HD DVD movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, there's a rumor that the premium console bundle with the movie player will be coming out around 400 pounds.
[SPEAKER_09]: and the speculations could even be as low as $3.75.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are we hearing more about this in Europe than we are in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the news has been very quiet on the HD DVD expansion here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Microsoft waiting for something?
[SPEAKER_03]: X06?
[SPEAKER_03]: When is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because this we speculated last week with the whole, you know, Halo 3 is coming out earlier in the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it seem like Microsoft's going to be holding a press conference soon where they start announcing a lot of this stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the other rumor, which we'll get into later, was another racing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft isn't really commenting on it as much yet and I guess it's for the same reason that we're not seeing much on it over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's really looking like they're actually trying to now really take advantage of the UK market is what it seems like.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to point this out in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat is on this big kick right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never understand when the chat room gets on this thing and they
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: This just in.
[SPEAKER_03]: When people buy the Oblivion Horse Armor, they will buy the PGR deck in Uno.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody's going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody will buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uno's cool and all, but I don't need 100 points for new cards that are basically a commercial for another Microsoft game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need an Uno deck that's the Horse Armor.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's showing off the Horse Armor to get people to buy the Horse Armor.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were right, by the way, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Nazgul Slayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some stuff that Japan is also going to be seeing a price drop in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's actually pretty interesting because I don't think any... Well, everybody else has been dropping the price of the PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the PS2 is going to be dropping to 19,980 yen, which is about $170.
[SPEAKER_02]: So not too big of a drop, but still an okay drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I remember correctly, the... What was that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the old price.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay, people make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I should do my research.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not allowed to make mistakes!
[SPEAKER_03]: Just so you know, the dozens and dozens of people that listen to this show are going to be very upset at you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's okay, you can just give them the raspberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, the new suggested retail price for the PS2 in the...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that might be their way of stealing the Wii announcement thunder, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, that's going to be happening soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: In case you know, you might be one of those people in Japan that hasn't bought a PlayStation 2 yet, which is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what is the website of the week?
[SPEAKER_09]: The website of the week is Gamer.org.
[SPEAKER_09]: G-A-Y-M-E-R.org.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I... Stop doing that face!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking to Junami, being a dork, as usual.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it's actually, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I ran across this, um, just looking randomly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a site basically for gay and gay-friendly gaming, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, to go ahead and read a little blurb off of the website, it says, you know, why do you need a gay gamer site?
[SPEAKER_09]: The truth is, in the gaming community, there are some pretty staunchly homophobic players, and Gamer.org is about having... Yeah, Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who makes faces.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's about having fun without hearing the bashing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that, you know, I like what it says here, so I give this site to you as a safe haven where gaming is the focus, not hate.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually a World of Warcraft guild on here that's on the Blackwing server, their alliance, called Alternatives with an alter-native.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I've looked at the site.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got some core views, gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a pretty well put together site.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd say not overly a lot to look at, but the information is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love just reading over the community there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I only have one complaint about this site, and that's when you go over the drop-down menus, I don't like the little tinkle noise.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what else to call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fairy dust spreading all over your computer as you visit the site.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this high-pitched little noise, and I'm like, are you ganging my computer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, I don't need... I'm in your computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: and your computer gating you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to give a shout out to a couple other, although that is a good site, I have visited that site.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to give a shout out to a couple other gay friendly gaming sites because, you know, a couple years ago there weren't any.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's really nice to see these, you know, gay gamer sites that are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one of them I've been visiting a lot recently because they have a hilarious blog.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gaygamer.net and they have a hilarious blog there.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been photoshopping Nintendudes is their latest thing going on and they have like
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo's Twink Edition, and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's silly, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they got some forums there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also have to mention Gamer Experimentations is another forum I've posted on before.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have a semi-active community over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when that whole World of Warcraft guild thing was going down a couple months ago,
[SPEAKER_03]: Very, very active discussion going on over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of gay and World of Warcraft, some of the sound clips have come out for the, they've leaked to the internet somehow from the beta or I don't know what.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the sound clips of some of the new races, including Blood Elves and Draanes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, now, I'm not saying that the Blood Elves are gay, but here's a clip of what one of the things the Blood Elves says, and you be the judge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't you wish your girlfriend was hot like me?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: You must now take back that homophobic joke, because I am making one of those.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright?
[SPEAKER_15]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's some great sound clips as well, and that's just to the iceberg.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The female blood elf seems to be a little bit of a valley girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You tell me on this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to Undercity to get a facial.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you seen these people?
[SPEAKER_11]: I said, you don't have a lower jaw and you're going to give me a facial?
[SPEAKER_11]: She got mad.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least I think she did.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ever heard someone talk without a lower jaw?
[SPEAKER_11]: She sounded like a murloc.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or getting her hair done.
[SPEAKER_15]: at a troll shop and winding up with a mohawk and a frickin' bone in her nose.
[SPEAKER_15]: Getting her hair did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Killed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Killed it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Although the female Draenei voices are also funny, asking if gnomes come with vibrate functions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I haven't gotten there yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't gotten there yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stinkin' jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the Draenei female.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do gnomes have a vibrate setting?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not call that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We couldn't hear that over your bitching.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do gnomes have a vibrate setting?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did not mean to call that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love this planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I come here, I see cow and chicken and ride little horses.
[SPEAKER_03]: This planet has everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it's balky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that show?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on Perfect Strangers.
[SPEAKER_07]: In old country, boobs did not fly free.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were disciplined, structured.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why we have Uta's brassieres.
[SPEAKER_07]: They hold boobies in place.
[SPEAKER_15]: In Soviet Russia now.
[SPEAKER_15]: In the world of Warcraft, Dronne drink you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cultural influence confusion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Male Draenei, their dance animation is the internet phenomenon Tunak Tunak Tunak dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Blood Elf Males do have the Napoleon Dynamite dance going for them.
Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just to add to their sexual ambiguity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though Napoleon Dynamite is kind of last year's news, that's kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate Napoleon Dynamite.
[SPEAKER_03]: You hate Napoleon Dynamite?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like the one person in the world that thought that movie was the best thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually I know a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's anti-human.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is that the movie got so hyped up, by the time a lot of people saw it, they were like, that's it?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there's only one thing in the world that needs to live up to the hype, and that's Snakes on a Plane.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Snakes on a Plane was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lord help us all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, give me my microphone, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I fucking hated that movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: That movie was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of really stupid things... In World of Warcraft, Planes on Snakes!
[SPEAKER_15]: Give me my joke book back!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of really dumb, dumb, dumb speculation, there was a, I guess, a story posted about how some cryptologists have figured out the Wii date.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's how they did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Roman numerals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you see, a W is actually, looks like two Vs, which would equal 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the two I's would be two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Therefore, October 2nd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Therefore, they are stupid is my opinion on the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look, with all due respect to the sites that ran this story, why is this news?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is this news?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me coming over there to strangle you for running stories like this that perpetuate these stinking rumors, that would be news.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is great video game journalism when I come strangle you for writing these stories around the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: That just broke my ear.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got you back for earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no, I guess that was Jamie who did it earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Traitor!
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to say this, because in the chat room here, I'm not sure if this is Cage or Kage.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably Kage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snakes, or, I'm sorry, whoops, that's not what I was, that's not the comment I wanted to read.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kage said this, World of Warcraft is YTMND with a level cap.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of a good way to sum it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about what made the movie irated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Traitor.
[SPEAKER_09]: So is it my turn now?
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to report this on your blogs?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll give you a worldwide exclusive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sky leaves Orange Lounge Radio right before episode 200.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no one cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one will run it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we replace them with a flask of coffee.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to understand, no one...
[SPEAKER_02]: No one's going to believe that you left the show until IGN reports it anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, next week I'm going to be... That person has to circulate a one-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the big news for next week's show, is that I'm replaced with a blood elf male, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't you wish your girlfriend was hot like me?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway... Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Back to the news.
[SPEAKER_09]: My God, you people are random.
[SPEAKER_09]: I blame Drew Nami's presence.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, as he bowels, bowels?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, I just cleaned the carpet, Drew!
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't you paper trained?
[SPEAKER_09]: Please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our dear friends at Squeenix are being sued by Softworld International for 3.78 million dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_09]: D.M.N.
[SPEAKER_09]: has a new nickname for Drew.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poonami
[SPEAKER_03]: How old are we?
[SPEAKER_07]: He said poo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does this mean I have to team up with Poo Eater?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Drew, are these... Then we won't have to worry about a mess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poo Maker and Poo Eater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are these poo jokes making you angry?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very angry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you know what time it is.
Sigh.
[SPEAKER_03]: FUs of the week time.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU of the week goes towards the really... No, no, no, no, no, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually do not quite recall what it was I was so angry about because I was really freaking angry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it when you called me from downtown earlier?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it... Well, okay, this is my... And I hate to resort to traffic.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is what it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fucking person who almost ran into me while I was on the 80.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you on your car?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to go back to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it was some dumbass was swerving to avoid another dumbass and nearly ran into me and I swerved.
[SPEAKER_09]: I managed to stay in my lane, but like five people behind me had to pull into the side because they were all swerving.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then all the traffic on the Bay Bridge, since they did all the work on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't they done with the work, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're supposed to be, but it was still stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I personally dislike you now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm also lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to all those
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU of the week goes to the amazing off-topicness of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we're going to have a lot of new listeners tonight thanks to the DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I would also say FU to just how crazy my work has been.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next week is going to suck and it makes me want to cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pays the rent.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU goes to whoever invented the United States.
[SPEAKER_08]: He sucks and needs to get resurrected and die again because, as most of you know, my girlfriend lives in Wisconsin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I live in Northern California.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't walk there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I miss her a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes me sad that she's not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened to the pedestrians?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck pedestrians!
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck America!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want her right here!
[SPEAKER_06]: I have this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was going to be a political rant, and then it was just a F you to the distance, my heart aches, gush, gush, gush, cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should have heard me trying to get rid of her on the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, not get rid of her, but when I was talking to her on the phone during the break, I was going, I miss you, I love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, I miss you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I gotta go, I miss you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not that sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just threw up in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up, I'm a girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Drew, any F yous?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, F you to...
[SPEAKER_15]: I have friends of mine who call in on their 21st and ask me to roll a DC-15 check against their fortitude to see if they're drunk.
[SPEAKER_15]: I shit you not.
[SPEAKER_15]: He had me roll to see if he was drunk on 4 Rubber Coats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Roll the dice to see if I'm getting drunk!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, you are!
[SPEAKER_06]: Are there any girls there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: If there's any girls there, I wanna do them!
[SPEAKER_16]: God, kill me now.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there were, and I did, but I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was playing Ogres.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not there, you're getting drunk!
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, a big F you to Guild Drama on my server.
[SPEAKER_15]: It really sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silverwing wanted to know if he failed, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: He did fail his check.
[SPEAKER_15]: His DC 15, he rolled an 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, shows like this drive me to drink.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games like this might drive me to drink, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it might be okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game coming out from Ubisoft, and it's called Alive.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposedly going to be coming out in 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was first talked about in March 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: What makes this interesting is that this game has been referred to as an Action Plus title.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a genre that...
[SPEAKER_03]: The International Herald Tribune writer Doreen Carvajal has spun into Ubisoft's attempt to focus on what the writer says is the feminine side of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, the reason is because Alive is more oriented toward drama, more life in characters, more depth.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about surviving, but you can't resolve things by shooting only.
[SPEAKER_03]: You see, Alive features characters who rely on their instincts and each other to endure after an earthquake.
[SPEAKER_03]: So in other words, boring!
[SPEAKER_03]: So apparently girls like boring games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck that noise!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was not nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like killing things as much as a nice person.
[SPEAKER_03]: In all seriousness, if Ubisoft wants to make the ultimate girl game, what should they be making?
[SPEAKER_09]: A Lorena Bob at the MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next topic!
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to make fucking Barbie, like, Horse Adventures 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Barbie with a vengeance or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Barbie fucks you up.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it was a really good girl game, I thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was for the computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alice.
[SPEAKER_08]: American McGee's Alice.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a fucking great game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that.
Drugs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe if you're a girl smoking crack.
[SPEAKER_09]: IGN ripping off OLR said Megzy and Chris is pro-lesbian too.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is that from?
[SPEAKER_09]: For a game suggestion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of games for girls, Dead Rising is supposed to be getting some download content here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they did get some download content, but there's going to be some coming to in-store kiosks as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you actually check online, they do have on the marketplace a brand new costume, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cold-Hearted Snake is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: No idea what that looks like because I haven't actually played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like Paula Abdul.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's a snake outfit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like Solid Snake, but it looks like snake skin is your suit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a snakeskin suit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then in the in-store kiosks, they're supposed to be getting Accountant, Burgundy Wine, Pure White Suit, and Stripe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those are going to be available in keys in the brand new September kiosk disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So look for that pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Project Gotham Racing 4
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's through this contest, or it's through the site that's talking about having a contest for designing the car And the winning design will be on Project Gotham Racing 4 Just like Test Drive Unlimited Well, and actually, neat news Sorry You know, Project Gotham 4, it's going to be in my house And it's going to annoy the crap out of me Just like its predecessors did
[SPEAKER_09]: But there is some news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who of our listeners reads Vibe Magazine?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, not usually the best known thing for gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, they had $150 under a description for the Wii in their last issue.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, I'm looking at the image now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has down at the bottom just a little description about all the stuff that's going to be on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says $150 www.nintendo.com So we're not sure if that's actually going to be just based off of rumors or if it's going to be more in the close to $300 range like we were hearing before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a rumor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that they've posted unsubstantiated information.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was just a placeholder that accidentally went to print that shouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it means anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: But of course, wasn't there those rumors saying that the Europe site said it was going to be 150 pounds?
[SPEAKER_03]: 150 pounds would be a lot more here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yes, but usually if it's $2.99 here, like look at the PlayStation 3, it's going to be $5.99 here, $5.99 pounds over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think converting that would bring it up to at least the $200.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's not possible, but can you imagine if they released that for $99?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would fly off the shelves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone would own a Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But even $199 is going to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, you're going to know in a couple days anyway, so who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well this is the part of the show where we open it up to you guys to call us and interact with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you'd like to give us a call, you can always head on over to OrangeLoungeRadio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you can pick up the phone and dial 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_03]: But kids, please keep in mind that that is not a toll-free number, so if you're not paying the phone bill, don't call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Download Skype and use that for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And looky look, the calls are already coming in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Once again, I am number one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you just had to trigger a finger there.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma, hey, I hear you're a snitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone pays my bills.
[SPEAKER_03]: My finger is floating over the hang-up button, so you better have some... Hey, don't hang up on him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I veto hanging up on him.
[SPEAKER_03]: You better have something good to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I have a lot of good stuff to say, because, you know, if you was going to do that, I wasn't going to treat you to Dunkin' Donuts when you came to New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, then maybe I won't hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, a few things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to say hi to everybody in the studio, and a special hello to the angel of death, Loki.
Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had screenshots from Africa get posted this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Africa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we figure out what the game's about yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just pictures of animals.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's about animal poo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
Africa.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, really, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I play DDR Supernova, and I'm in love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you love about DDR Supernova?
[SPEAKER_13]: I just love the eye candy to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, the new videos, all the new characters dancing, especially Emmy's new costume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Emmy's new costume.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would you say is your favorite song in DDR Supernova?
[SPEAKER_13]: I only got to play one song, and right now, I was floored by Centerfold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the Captain Jack song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So are you going to be picking up the home version when it comes out for PS2?
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I hear you can make your own steps at home and then take them to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be awesome, but... It's like the old days.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but the machines around here don't have memory cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to get them.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're working on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else on your mind, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_13]: I beat New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: and Nintendo threw old schoolers a bone in the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait until you get to the final level in the castle.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright Ranma, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to get more callers, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Two more things, Ranma, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number one, I picked up Beatmania for $40 at Version Megastore and I'm calling out Drunami and Nintendo Maniac 64 for bad phone calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm raising the bar here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come on, you can do better than me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drunami, response?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we're going to go to another call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to answer it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Africa, Africa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zebra Buzz.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go to another call here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, you're calling Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, this is Solar Wing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Solar Wing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've never called the show before, have you?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm a first-time actually live listener.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we're popping someone's Skype cherry tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're happy to have some new blood on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, a few things.
[SPEAKER_14]: First, the PS3 thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: How many do you actually think will actually make it to Canada?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it says 400,000 to North America.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, good point.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does that necessarily mean anything about it just going to States or Canada or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a damn good point that I don't know if anyone's really thought of about how many of those machines are going to Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone assumed North America is just the United States.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like, you know, Europe doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Mexico, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Mexico is getting 350,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to know what's sad, my friend, is that probably Canada is getting about 10,000 of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you a Sony fan?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I actually owe someone a PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You owe someone a PS3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, you must have done something big.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you do?
[SPEAKER_14]: It is a Christmas present, wedding present, birthday present from two years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wow, so this is like a get out of presents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you having to make up for presents you forgot?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, he had a choice.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was either Xbox 360 or PS3.
[SPEAKER_14]: He chose the PS3 because he hates me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is going to be a get-out-of-presence free pass for the next two years, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a pretty big one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even so, I think that with the shipment coming out, it would be similar to what the other systems are.
[SPEAKER_09]: There shouldn't be any type of region coding or any type of specification between.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, not for Canada.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I wouldn't see why you can't order one off of GameStop's site or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you might be able to just order, you know, it might cost a little extra for shipping, but if Push came to shove, you could order one from a U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: website and just have it shipped to Canada.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I could probably do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just $700 as it is, plus how much are the games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're talking $600 American, which is a little bit more in Canadian, although not much lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: The dollars are equating pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_03]: What part of Canada are you from?
[SPEAKER_14]: West Coast, near Toronto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Near Toronto?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, Toronto's not... Wait, they consider Toronto the West Coast?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can always, you know, dip in... I don't know how far of a drive you are from the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: border, but, you know, you can always dip into the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: and try some of the big Best Buys, you know, around the border.
[SPEAKER_03]: Could be a thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you think so?
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of...
[SPEAKER_09]: The distributors, you know, the national distributors are in California.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, if you order from any of the distribution sites or any of the other, maybe even the importers, you're still probably going to get a system fairly quickly.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as shipping is concerned.
[SPEAKER_14]: My other question was about the new NTSs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, what about them?
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you think about them?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting a pink one.
[SPEAKER_03]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of dirty because it's been in my purse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, you have the white one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you have the virginal white one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you think they'll actually fix that crack issue?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the whole, the cracking of the hinges?
[SPEAKER_03]: I imagine because it was such a big deal on the blogs that they'll do something about it, but I don't know, what can you really do about the hinges without redesigning the whole setup of the system?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know mine hasn't yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't think they all have, but I hear the fats are cracking now too.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the blogs I was reading ran a story that their fat was cracking.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know, it takes one person with an internet site to have that happen and then, you know, it's all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know exactly how rampant the cracks are.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that issue is less widespread than people are thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get the black one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You won't be able to see the crack.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: My last thing, I've played DDR once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was looking at getting a PS2.
[SPEAKER_14]: What should I get for DDR?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get an ignition pad, first of all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, make sure you get a good dance pad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, well, if he's warming up to DDR, I'd say a $20 dance pad can hold him over to see if he likes the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially because you can play the basic songs on the cheapo pads.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once you get into the harder stuff, though, it will start moving under your feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say by far the best home release for PS2 is Extreme 2, the most recent one, and that'll be the easiest one to find.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you could probably get some of the oldies for like $20 American easily, like Max 2 and DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're not bad, but DDR Extreme 2 is by far the best one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably right after Supernova comes out, that will drop in price.
[SPEAKER_03]: And who knows, maybe actually Supernova's going to be the best one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't tell you until after I've played it, but it sounds like it's going to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: but Extreme 2 has a lot of radio friendly songs and things you might have heard of before and not a bunch of crazy stuff that sometimes turns people off to DDR alright, well thanks not a problem, thank you so much for calling in have a good one buddy good luck with the Playstation 3 hunting that's gotta be a pain in the ass oh my god, oh you're a friend of Playstation 3 like Jamie, if I bought you a Playstation 3 you don't get anything else the rest of your life
[SPEAKER_09]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I gave you a PlayStation 3, you'd give it back.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, if you gave me a PlayStation 3, honestly, I'd sell it on eBay for three times what it's worth and then I'd take us all to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, you want to answer the next call, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I decided not to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Africa, they rendered zebra genitalia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to throw up my mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Jamie, answer the next call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you've called Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Feel special.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they hung up.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't feel so special.
Bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: They got you and decided to run the other way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, you want to try this one instead?
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you've called Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: This guy's got a feminine voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I talk too much, so... Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so we're letting Jamie answer the calls.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't think you talk enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways... What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, something you guys have completely overlooked.
[SPEAKER_17]: Next Saturday morning is the season premiere of Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think we overlooked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just don't care, my friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will subject myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the ultimate in video game journalism right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Self-sacrifice for the better of the community.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm sure that the entirety of our radio listeners can hear you pointing at Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, I sacrificed myself to watch Viva Pinata, and that show sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: I watched the Viva Pinata clips on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, what else is on your mind, DMN?
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't remember what else.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know I was going to bug you guys with Dance Revolution, and the other thing slipped my mind, so I think we'll cut this one short and let you hang up on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I think we have time for about one more call here.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to give us a call, you can call our username is Orange Lounge Radio, or you can call our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_05]: Megzy, call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Megzy's supposed to call us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't she the one that hung up?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Megzy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's try.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, are you going to answer this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You better be Megzy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, this is Megzy.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: This must be Megzi.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Megzi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, Megzi?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, first, anyone in the chat room who is listening, do not go to my genius site.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not look at my bad art.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Megzi, you're kind of breaking up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be careful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, better?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, better, much better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at all of her art.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was during the bonus segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Podcasters didn't hear it anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The majority of them won't go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other thing is about the conference.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Nintendo conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have been waiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am counting the hours until the press conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you a Reggie fangirl?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am so totally a Reggie fangirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really hope he gets up there and holds up his 40 and goes, This one's for my homies at OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you looking forward to seeing at the Wii press conference?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it just the date and the price to get the anticipation building so you can start taking pre-orders?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you hoping to see some new games or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to know when I can get it and how much it is and I want to be able to run my GameStop and throw my $50 down and say, how's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I really, really hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ken Cooter, Huggie, and he's the doctor off of Crams.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's the doctor from all the Crams.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you, sweetheart.
I'm really happy now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get to see her often, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm allowed to be sentimental.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for letting me be sad about it on video.
[SPEAKER_03]: That radio show is so gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can see the iTunes review now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gay video game radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck iTunes.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I love iTunes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's where we get a lot of downloads from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like burritos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, please help.
[SPEAKER_15]: GameTap is actually putting Sam and Max Hit the Road on its list of games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually have a question for the chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: But gay can mean happy, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So just, you know, there's something for everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you have, Chris?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just had a question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's played Xena Saga 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: And how good is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that's a question.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to take a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to take a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Change of mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, do you have anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: For my birthday, people chipped in and got me surround sound.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I have 5.1 surround sound in my living room with my widescreen TV and the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it pretty?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: It plays Saints Row and I can hear the prostitutes yelling behind me so then I turn around and go beat their ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it awesome like a hot dog?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo Maniac 64 says my friend has played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funnydale said I heard that game has a six-hour cutscene.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that would work.
[SPEAKER_03]: DMN says it blows ass.
Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, he may not be talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: He may just be talking, responding to somebody else again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody may have asked him, you know, what do you think about, you know, colonoscopies?
[SPEAKER_03]: He might have been responding to that question.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma said if Reggie comes out with a 40, he better have cornrows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sephiroth 1215 says Xenosaga is $30 at Circuit City this week for those of you guys that like deals I already bought it I just haven't played it yet I actually was a moron and didn't get Xenosaga 2 when it came out so I have to order that and wait to play that or I can actually play Xenosaga 3 DMN is saying Xenosaga 3 is garbage is what?
[SPEAKER_08]: garbage fuck you, it's blue hair I gotta have blue hair
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it possible that the game might suck, even though the first two were good?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, again, I haven't played the first two.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't played two.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really like the first one, mainly because I like playing stuff with a storyline.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't care if the storyline is bad, kind of, because I really like the art in three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you like five-hour miniseries for cutscenes?
[SPEAKER_03]: If so, it sounds like you'll love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like a game that plays itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a movie that you interact with.
[SPEAKER_03]: You press the A button once in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, with actual game news, Exo 6 is taking place in Barcelona on the 27th and 28th of September.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet there's going to be big news out of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're expected to announce new franchises from Bungie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some stuff for Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one last little tidbit here that's being sent to private message in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a rumor going around that a Wii tech demo of sorts is going to come with a Wii remote purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just a rumor, but that might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of that stuff you saw at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I collect tech demos.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually have like five of the old PlayStation tech demos.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to see something crazy, go back and look at the old tech demos on the PlayStation, and they look pretty damn good, even by today's standards.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, DarkSakura can't say something nice about Sony once in a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop hating.
[SPEAKER_09]: And remember, the PlayStation was born from the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: In a way, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, boys and girls, that's going to bring this edition of Orange Lounge Radio to a close.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really appreciate the fact that you guys tune in to us and support independent radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're going to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll start off with Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew Nami, thank you for being here tonight, as always.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's your final thought for tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: No poo, thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, your final thought for tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm sorry for making this place so random.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we love you too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Random is fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Old school listeners especially love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to take tomorrow off.
[SPEAKER_02]: and hopefully we'll play some more games this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to take tomorrow off.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to take tomorrow off.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've had the best weekend ever and I owe it all to my bestest buddy right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aww, I think I threw up in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I want potato chips.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are there any left?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are starting a campaign to call them crisps and to call French fries chips.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Freedom fries?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they're chips.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to mention, and this is not that important, but it is news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire and Mortar 2.81 came out for the PSP, which allows you to use memory sticks that are larger than 4 gigs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have one more final thought for you all.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Owned!
[SPEAKER_09]: That is not pwnage.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is homage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pure ownage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Imitation is the finest form of flattery, my dear.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you thought tonight was crazy, next week, boys and girls, episode 200.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brace yourselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until then, I'm a very scared Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: For DarkSakura, Loki, and myself, goodnight.
[SPEAKER_14]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_14]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!