[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio here on this lovely Sunday evening, September the 17th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is our 200th episode tonight, so it's a little bit crazy, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else can we do here to celebrate our 200th episode?
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a little cake during the break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Chris, for bringing the chocolate cake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm filled with chocolatey goodness now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we're going to get back into what we do well here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, and as we talked about in Part A about the Wii being region-free or not being region-free, we still don't know, there is rumors that the PlayStation 3 may be region-free, and there might be confirmation on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: According to a Resistance Fall of Man video interview posted on Game Videos, the PlayStation 3 may indeed be region-free, and basically the kind of proof for that is that they're talking about multiple versions of the game
[SPEAKER_01]: All the videos being, you know, put in there in both the high def formats including PAL on one disc.
[SPEAKER_01]: So people are, you know, kind of assuming, okay, so there's going to be one run of the game that's going to be, you know, throughout the world.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, maybe kind of some proof that there might be some region free games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think, if anything, it's going to be like, you know, the 360 whereas some games are region free if the developers want them, some games aren't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's probably what you're going to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forget the imports.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll just have to live without it.
[SPEAKER_03]: X-Fire X-Fire X-Fire
[SPEAKER_03]: I would be very excited to see something like this come to PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was a quote this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe it was a one-up reporting from a transcript of Viacom's report.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quote, importantly, Xfire just signed a deal with Sony to create a version of their platform for the new PlayStation 3, which will now enable Xfire to extend its reach further into the huge console gaming market.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're saying that Untold Legends Dark Kingdom, which was a PS3 launch exclusive, was in Xfire's PC initialization file.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, after this story sat on the internet for a couple days before you folks in the chatroom start yelling at us and telling us, you know, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we do know little news came out a little later that says, actually, Sony doesn't plan to be fully integrating X-Fire right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was just for this one game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I still find this partnership to be very interesting nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Loki, you know a lot about X-Fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you use it at all?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what do you think about teaming up with a PC-based...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, might as well since Sony doesn't seem to know what they're asked from their foot as far as online services go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, how do you know they don't have something already and they just haven't said anything yet?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because their whole answer is like, yes, our services will be exactly what Xbox Live is.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, since they can't really innovate on that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, they haven't really said anything about it, and the fact that there's a lack of information about what they're providing on their online service makes me think, hmm, they don't know what they're providing on their online service yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't have a plan whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I'm sure, you know, we're going to hear more about their online service and about their games at Tokyo Game Show in a few weeks, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: Until then, I don't think they know shit about their online service right now, and I think it's just kind of pieced together.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think you just said what exactly is going to prove your statement wrong, Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're going to get the answers to our questions there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, until then, I still think that their online service is very pieced together, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't sound very good so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, any thoughts from you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you don't really do a lot of PC gaming, but... I have AIM.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, X-Files kind of like it in a way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have AIM.
[SPEAKER_03]: What if PlayStation 3 had AIM on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Would that be cool?
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably wouldn't use it on there because I'd be too busy playing a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good thought, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: PS3, PS4, PS5, PS6, PS7, PS8, PS9, PS10
[SPEAKER_01]: So you're going to be seeing most of these coming out in the more expensive bundle, but I think a lot of people are going to be getting the more expensive one anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of like how with the Xbox 360, sure they had the core one available, but people only bought it because the premium was sold out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I guess that's their way of making more money off of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or losing less money, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was kind of bitter when the only Xbox 360 I could get was a core, because they were making it seem like half and half.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think they know that more people want the premiums because the cores are kind of a joke, just like they were with 360 in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's going to be shortages because they're only going to have, what, 400,000 units to launch with North America.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I ain't buying one until at least 2007, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's one more free on the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least with the Wii, they're promising 4 million units by the end of the year, most of which are coming to the United States.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I hope they make good on that or else it better not be the 360 all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, in other news, this actually has to do with the Xbox 360 and some UK news.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is going to be a free week of Xbox Live for our friends overseas.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's stating that you'll actually be able to use the services starting on...
[SPEAKER_06]: 20th November I'm sorry, 20th September, my apologies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a different song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll ferret you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not my fault you can't tell your September from your November, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to throw my hat at you.
[SPEAKER_01]: If only Nintendo would make that mistake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the 20th of September, Xbox Live will be free to our friends in Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free access.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it ends on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it will be at 11.59pm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's UK time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So get in all that laggy, scramble Xbox Live action while you can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I played it online and it's laggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the games available right now, just to give a list, is Project Gotham Racing 3, Top Spin 2, Table Tennis, Saints Row, World Cup Soccer, Dark Zero, I'm sorry, Perfect Dark Zero, Street Fighter 2, Hyper Fighting Edition, Texas Hold'em.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Log on, play Uno with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we could do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a good way for us to meet some UK listeners, except one of us is going to have to be awake at a god-awful hour for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Rare, of course, was responsible for a lot of the launch titles, or a couple of launch titles, I should say, for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were only one title.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, they had a launch title for the 360, Perfect Dark Zero, and now, of course, I'm going to be announcing some more titles at X06, which is later this month, including, well, some thoughts at least, Banjo-3, or Killer Instinct, or some of the...
[SPEAKER_01]: BlackWolf is saying, skip four, you tit!
[SPEAKER_03]: and he also said, draw for you, bloody bloke!
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, that was my worst British accent ever, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sorry, I won't do that again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, UK folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: I apologize to the entire United Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I knew it was a couple, and I have to go and correct myself again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to another story, Final Fantasy XII, something about the current gen systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we've had a lot of next gen news, but something about the current gen systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're actually going to be having a whole day to celebrate Final Fantasy XII in New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's going on is that on October 12th through October 15th at the Digital Life Expo, Final Fantasy XII will be appearing at the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know we have a lot of fans there at New York City that want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, here's the other part you should check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: October 11th is Final Fantasy XII Day, and that has been declared by New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be a special commemoration in Times Square.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cosplayers will be abounding, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't see why people are making such a big deal out of something that's such a crap game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't even played it yet, have you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's incredible.
[SPEAKER_06]: The demo?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be incredible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to play my game by myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll just see when the full version comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still going to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you see, fangirl.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm using Megzi's excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal box.
[SPEAKER_03]: Special edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, special stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, one thing that I think a lot of us will be happy about, especially a certain somebody sitting by my foot,
[SPEAKER_06]: is Kingdom Hearts 2 is getting an international version in Japan we're getting Kingdom Hearts 2 Final Mix which a couple of us who pay attention to our live journals have seen pictures of because somebody posted a scan from a magazine of a certain somebody who was in a mask in the bonus clip for Kingdom Hearts 2 oh so this game will actually have an ending that makes sense?
[SPEAKER_06]: It made sense!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just messing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But from what that picture indicated, it's going to give us more of that little clip.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care if I'm spoiling now, but if you get the perfect ending for Kingdom Hearts 2, you get a little clip of three armored figures picking up Keyblades.
[SPEAKER_07]: YouTube is amazing!
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's a bajillion other Keyblades, like a graveyard, around them.
[SPEAKER_06]: and apparently they're going to have more of that in the ending you know how there was the deep dive in the last Kingdom Hearts but they're also saying that they're going to be incorporating the card battle the card battle system from Chain of Memories it didn't give a lot of detail again I saw the ad for this I've seen the article they showed it like they actually showed I think the Sephiroth battle on this picture and I'll have to find out who it was on my friends list that posted the article
[SPEAKER_06]: but it had the little card icons in the side and you draw your cards and play them out like Chain of Memories but it looked really neat another point is that they are getting all the English voices so hey importers be happy you too can own this game and play it in an understandable language unless you are fluent in Japanese and then you won't have a problem anyway
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay, Japanese!
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of stuff coming out in Japan, well, this is more, of course, for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have some release dates for you, including the stuff that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And lots of good stuff, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: My favorites being on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okami is going to be finally making its way out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, very anticipated game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about fucking time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will talk with my mouth full whenever I want.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am one of the hosts of this podcast, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okie dokie, anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I was yelling at Chris for trying to be my mommy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, um, no, we're going to be getting some other stuff, including, uh, well,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: OpenSeasons, pretty much on every single console, including 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why you would buy that one, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dragon Quest Heroes Rocket Slime is going to be making its way to the DS, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're a fan of Sierra games, there's going to be some PC compilations coming out for you, including the King's Quest compilation, Leisure Suit Larry compilation, Police Quest, Space Quest, and yeah, those will be the compilations for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hot!
[SPEAKER_01]: Samurai Warriors 2 on the 360 and PlayStation 2 are going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you have some stuff for the 360, you're looking to pick up some games, well, The Godfather is going to be coming out for you, as well as, well, not really a game, but the Xbox Live Vision Camera, as we mentioned earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: World Series of Poker Tournament of Champions, which is also on PSP and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually, I might pick this up because it looks funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kabbalah's Alaskan Adventure, you know, all that ice fishing and hunting polar bears on HD there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, no Africa on ice, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then finally, on the Game Boy Advance, Capcom Classics, Minimix will be making its way out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you really buy everything for the Game Boy Advance, Fashion Dogs, where you can dress up dogs on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are people who do that for real though, that's sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you're one of those people, never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please stop listening to OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, King of Fighters 2006, I'm sorry, was also making its way in Godfather Mob Wars.
[SPEAKER_01]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, as for our friends overseas in Europe, by the way, Suikoden V came out yesterday, so get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But on the 21st, Jaws Unleashed, yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then on the 22nd, FIFA 07 is coming out for everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is coming out for damn near everything, including, you know, Nintendo Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: How can you still play your Virtual Boy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that just the biggest migraine maker ever?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still play Teleroboxer, damn it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Freak.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out is Guilty Gear Dust Strikers for the DS, Jaws Unleashed on the Xbox, which I don't know why it's not coming out on the 21st with the other versions, Just Cause on Xbox 360, NHL Eastside Hockey Manager 2007 on PC, Pyroworld on PC, and Saint Seiya The Hades on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad you get it as Saint Seiya, not as like Warriors of the Zodiac, which is stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Harukanaru Jikunokare Maiichiya
[SPEAKER_03]: NHL 06, Rugby 06, Midway Arcade Treasures
[SPEAKER_03]: Translated in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess it's a way for them to play some of the games that were really big here in America years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of neat to see a four-year-old game getting translated for a Japanese audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think a lot of them were already out in Japan, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, especially in arcade format.
[SPEAKER_03]: But some of the games, I kind of see because not all the games that were popular here were popular there and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I imagine Mortal Kombat was probably bigger here than it was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't in Japan in the mid-90s, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's what you have to look forward to this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait a minute, though!
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember when they tried the 64...
[SPEAKER_03]: When have you ever seen an SNK machine at an arcade?
[SPEAKER_03]: I always see these SNK machines at frickin' pizza parlors, and I saw one at the supermarket and one at Jim Boy's Tacos, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a six-slot MBS at my arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those SNK machines show up in the craziest fuckin' places.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we had one of the big-screen TV ones for Summer Showdown 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw one in a 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Summer Showdown 4 has a signal that resets those TVs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It turns them off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, anywho...
[SPEAKER_01]: and Regulation A is actually based on the 3D home console fighting series by the same name and at least includes one new character, Ash Crimson.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, Ash Crimson is such a generic sounding name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, he's from King of Fires 03 and King of Fires 11.
[SPEAKER_01]: Samurai Spirit Sen also play as a 3D game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This will be the second time the sword fighting series has made its way in the arcade in 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other one that remembers King of Fighters 64 The only good thing about that game was bringing in, what's your name that had the two swords?
[SPEAKER_03]: Psycho Girl This is also, they announced that they're going to be releasing King of Fighters 12 on the new hardware too
[SPEAKER_03]: Goddamn, make a new game, SNK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make a new fucking game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Give us Godot Mark of the Wolves 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Give us Last Blade 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a new series game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give us Last Blade 3, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, my God, I love Last Blade 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob, aren't you looking forward to the Metal Slug anthology that's going to be on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait to play Metal Slug 413, which is like the same graphics for Metal Slug 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could play Metal Slug all day because it's all about... Okay, and King of Fighters 2007.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: That wasn't SNK.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was on all the freaking machines, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Play more SNK now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: But why are they porting a shitty game like Maximum Impact?
[SPEAKER_00]: We didn't like it here in America.
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't like it there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: The voiceovers suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: Port a decent game to arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, as far as hopefully, and I would hope with 573 titles, something good will have to be among them.
[SPEAKER_03]: E3 probably has more.
[SPEAKER_01]: Konami will own Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm wondering, when are we going to get WTF?
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't they change the name of that?
[SPEAKER_01]: They did.
[SPEAKER_01]: They changed it and they changed it back.
[SPEAKER_01]: WTF is coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: Work time fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: but there are actually a lot of games for PC, mobile phone games they're actually saying for PC and mobile phone they had 252 titles for portables DS will be bringing 52 PSP will have 33 18 Playstation 3 games are going to show and they'll probably all still suck and play on rack mounted servers and 20 games coming out for Xbox 360 but they're only showing 5 for the Wii Wii is holding out
[SPEAKER_06]: The ones that they are actually going to be putting on is the Bleach game, Shiraha Kirameku Rinbu Kyoku, Marvelous Interactives, Bokujo Monogatari Wi, which is still a working title, and Elebits.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't say if it's going to be playable or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, they do list a lot of the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: T for Teen
[SPEAKER_03]: T for Teen Crude Humor, Violence, Sexual Themes, Language, and Use of Alcohol and Tobacco
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been delayed forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, some of the other Rockstar games, not Grand Theft Auto, have been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Warriors was pretty fun for a while, and then I got bored with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Bully looks pretty fun, and they've got a really good system for all the classes and stuff that you have to take.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of minigames and stuff involved with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I think it'll be pretty good if you give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just have to wait until it comes out, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: ActDeft in our chatroom says, Jack Thompson will sue.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack Thompson's stupid, and it doesn't have anything to do with, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Great, so he's going to complain about this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Play the damn game, you'll see that there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even think it has much to do with bullying people, to be honest, if you actually play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLArmyEddy says, sexual themes, usually that's an automatic M. Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could just be a chick dancing in her bra or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That might not be M, but it might be a little bit, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not to bring this up again, but they have sexual themes in The Sims 2, and that's rated T.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it has woohoo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if you get the special furniture with the sex animations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, woohoo in, I think, on the couch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo in the bed, woohoo in the hot tub, and then something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: Woohoo indeed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo should have come out with a system called the woohoo.
[SPEAKER_06]: The old Sims, the first Sims game actually had someone programmed a countertop that you could... Woohoo on.
[SPEAKER_06]: With full animations.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, woohoo indeed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, online content may change.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking about, you know, some stuff that people think that games like Bully Cause, well, there was a shooter in Montreal that went and killed a bunch of people in his school, and guess what they found as one of his favorite games?
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently this guy plays a lot of games, including one that happens to be Super Columbine Massacre RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, not the sequel to Super Mario RPG, just to clear that up for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks, I wasn't sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see the videos of him on CNN?
[SPEAKER_06]: A real gamer would have been that crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's all the game's fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did the game do to him?
[SPEAKER_06]: I blame his psychosis and his parents for not being more observant.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think it was his favorite game, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: When you see that, of course, if you're going to be trying to spin this in the news, that's going to get the most attention.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's, of course, blame it on the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Naturally, lots of feedback from our viewers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat room over at orangeentrainer.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: OL Army Eddie says, Super Columbine RPG does not glorify school shootings at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always butcher this name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, help me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nazgul Slayer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nazgul?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nazgul.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one fucks me up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nazgul Slayer says, he used RPG Maker 2000 to make Super Columbine Massacre.
[SPEAKER_03]: I read an article about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not really Super Columbine Massacre that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's RPG Maker, the devil's game.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm attacking the darkness.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm using magic missiles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any Mountain Dew?
[SPEAKER_03]: Socorino would like to point out, also, his gun was legal, but his clips weren't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is, it just further illustrates that society is more ready to look for a scapegoat than actually treat the true root of the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do these kind of stories make you angry, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: They make me furious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Livid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ludicrously livid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they make you want to rant a little bit?
[SPEAKER_06]: They make me want to go to a school and shoot people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it wouldn't be episode... It wouldn't be episode 200 of a podcast without... The Fuse of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: FU of the week I can't believe I completely blamed I had what my FU was going to be and it wasn't related to traffic at all wow my FU of the week goes toward the Japantown Anime Festival oh my god crappiest convention ever well to you know in their defense they were pretty small I mean but still hey that's not nice talking about the Japanese being small okay
[SPEAKER_04]: This was my... You're Pokemon!
[SPEAKER_04]: You connect all to Pokemon!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: My problem with it being is that... No, this is in San Francisco, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: My problem with it was that it suffered the same problem that AX started to suffer as in being spread across different areas.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had to do... You had to go from one mall to the other, into the hotel, into the courtyard downstairs under Kinozumiya at Kintetsu Mall.
[SPEAKER_06]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a pretty good band that we were there for listening to the warm-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually sounded pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the dealer's room, it was a dealer's closet.
[SPEAKER_06]: The closet!
[SPEAKER_04]: And they had some interesting stuff, some nice stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, overall it was pretty much what you could find online pretty easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what I was most disappointed with was the cosplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I expected to go and see people taking advantage of the opportunity to cosplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a pretty big Naruto group.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a pretty big Bleach group.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been done, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could go see that at any other convention.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did meet lots of nice people.
[SPEAKER_06]: We met some people on DA, on DeviantArt, who were really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But overall, I think I had a higher expectation for it just because of how it was played up there, having all this different stuff go on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it really was just blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only advantage of it is that our badges gave us discounts at the stores.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I could buy porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought some Yelly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mine don't have to do with porn.
[SPEAKER_01]: FU to Wicker Man.
[SPEAKER_01]: That movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why did they have to kill Nicolas Cage's character off?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it was getting good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, the whole movie was kind of like, eh, okay, this whole island with... Wow, thanks for saving me ten bucks!
[SPEAKER_06]: And isn't that how the original ended?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, but I'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why did they have to kill his character off?
[SPEAKER_01]: It started getting good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, he punched a woman in the face.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, god damn, this movie's gonna be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then, fucking, oh god, I can't remember her name.
[SPEAKER_01]: The chick from...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Burning Man?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, this whole, the whole movie reminded me of Burning Man, like, in Seattle or something, you know, it's like, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, my FU of the week goes to my iPod, which upon boot up today gave me a frowny face of death.
[SPEAKER_03]: I blame iTunes 7, because ever since I installed iTunes 7, that thing started acting weird, like, iTunes did not want to talk to my old-ass, you know, fourth-gen iPod or whatever it is, the black and white before they were color iPods, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: FU iTunes 7 for ruining my iPod and now I can't listen to podcasts in my car.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, no Bobby, no All Games, no other podcasts I listen to or OLR in my car for a while until I can afford the video iPod.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, FU frowny face of death.
[SPEAKER_03]: I blame Apple.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, just bite your tongue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, how about... I blame the lack of Rockbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about your... Oh, okay, Drew Nami, your FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, first off, FU to Missing Class for an entire week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for the thought, but tried it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, for lack of anything better, my FU of the week is to my bed at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: It, for some reason, thinks that I need to be molested in the middle of the night.
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of bed is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to buy one.
[SPEAKER_04]: IKEA, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there is only one bed... God, I love Sweden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I never let any of my friends... Abba and molesting beds.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't get much better than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to hear my story or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there's only one other bed that's available in my house when my friends come over, and that's the one my dad and his girlfriend use, so they have to sleep in my bed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And twice I've woken up to my friends trying to molest me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie slept in there last night, and she was all trying to pet my chest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I was having a dream.
[SPEAKER_03]: This show just got a lot hotter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was having a dream about a couple of characters, and they were just sleeping in the bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a cat there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is what Shermie does.
[SPEAKER_06]: She'll crawl in the bed between me and Dan, and I'll reach over and pet her.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in the dream, I guess the character there in my dream was reaching over to pet the cat, and I opened my eyes to see my hand hovering over Kristen's chest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, oh, you're not a cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Marissa's reaction, except she said, oh, you don't have a penis.
[SPEAKER_04]: She thought my friend Marissa came down a few weekends ago and she thought I was her boyfriend, Christopher, and was all rubbing my back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she's like, oh, wait, you don't have a penis, and turned over and fell asleep.
[SPEAKER_04]: So people want to molest me in my bed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to respond to Jeremy Todd, I have had a hot lesbian dream about Angelina Jolie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I've had a hot lesbian dream about Angelina Jolie, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who hasn't had a hot lesbian dream about her?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not kidding either, and I also had one about Billy Piper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one who played Rose in Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's pretty!
[SPEAKER_03]: We've lost control here on episode 200.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we had a story earlier in the program about Final Fantasy XII and Final Fantasy XII Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe there'll be two Final Fantasy XII Days, because guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XII Revenant Wings Final Fantasy XII Revenant Wings Final Fantasy XII Revenant Wings
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: This one is a very special one, especially for episode 200.
[SPEAKER_06]: The website of the week is OrangeLoungeRadio.com You must go to our site every day, hang out on our forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you find news stories, link them up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we don't think it's utter crap, then we'll put it up on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you get to talk to us!
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's special.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know, I figured it's about damn time that I plug our own damn site.
[SPEAKER_06]: So OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the site of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to forget... Shameless self-promotion!
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn right!
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to forget OLR PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: OLR PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can go to E3 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, E3 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, very, very, very... It's about as updated as the OLR on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to see something that hasn't been updated in like five years, there's DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, haven't updated it in five years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_06]: And we have our blogs at stuff.orangenounsradio.com Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those blogs haven't been updated in like a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to update mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: We better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's my Jack Thompson is a bully rant on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some good reads on there if you haven't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's kind of interesting and very disappointing to me is that it was announced this week that the PS3 controller will not be named Poos.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be named Sixaxis or Syaxis or whatever it's
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically comes from the fact that the controller has six different axes of motion sensing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yeah, since it doesn't rumble, I guess they can't really call it DualShock now, can they?
[SPEAKER_01]: So six axes is the name of the controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also a palindrome.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do we find this out for sure?
[SPEAKER_03]: How do we know for sure that this is the name of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, this was from a patent.
[SPEAKER_01]: or I should say a trademark that was registered and it's been pulled up and it's owned by Sony, so hurrah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What if they're just trying a couple things out?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's true, you know, I don't know if it's for sure, but you know what, they've been, it's also been, you know, mentioned 6-axis and a few different PR things, not as, you know, it might be like the system, you know, the name for the system of the motion sensing, like for example, it says the
[SPEAKER_01]: The controller for the PS3 employs breakthrough technology of high precision, highly sensitive 6-axis sensing system that does not require any devices other than the controller itself for seamless interactive operation.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that might be just the technology they're calling it 6-axis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, every week you guys write us letters, and we read them right here on Orange Lounge Radio's podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to send us an email, it's mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, and when you send your email, DarkSakura suits up in her biohazard suit and puts on her rubber gloves.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a hazmat suit and asbestos gloves.
[SPEAKER_06]: All you guys suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob is not sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie is a mean bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your show is full of lesbians and 30-year-old children who live in their parents' cellar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Die!
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that good enough hate mail?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you know I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy 200.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, isn't your online name DisneyButtPunk10?
[SPEAKER_06]: DisneyButt?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm going to start calling you after that email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why, yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: As a matter of fact, DisneyPunk10 is my handle.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's an awful coincidence!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thanks for the hate mail.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love getting hate mail at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, she brings me cake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_06]: And donuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: And crowns.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go parade in the living room right now while Jamie reads the next email and listen for the laughter.
[SPEAKER_06]: You look like such a lovely princess, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: And anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: Our next email comes from Robert M. Now that Apple has announced that you can purchase games for the iPod, what do you see becoming of this form of mobile gaming?
[SPEAKER_06]: I may pick up Bejeweled just to see, but later it'll be interesting to see how the Units Limited controller, basically like an Atari 2600 paddle controller...
[SPEAKER_06]: I really wonder even seeing the preview of how Pac-Man is controlled is used.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can imagine a great version of Gyruss, for instance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, how does this open up the possibility of homebrewed games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's easy to make your own music and movies and play them on the iPod without ever starting an account to buy them, but what about those with skill and patience to program full games?
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought they already had homebrewed games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like they had Doom on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: For what reason, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said hail to the queen when I walked out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think since they've already got it, then... Sorry, I missed the reading of the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was this about the iPod games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, because I dug in there earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought I saw some gay in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem with gaming on the iPod is that frickin' wheel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's not the best controller in the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what would be great, though, is that, you know that little thing that you plug your USB thing into in the bottom?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be an awesome place to just jam a controller into, and then there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what Apple should do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apple will make more money.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would be a smart idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Apple wanted to get into gaming on the iPod, that would be a great addition.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just some show on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, our next email says, Dear OLR crew, I would like to say thank you for the past 1.5 years of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went into the gigantic list of gaming podcasts and my first random pick happened to be this wonderful podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been listening ever since and it's been fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: The hosts and guest hosts are great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, this podcast introduced some of the coolest bands, Gorillaz, Freeze Pop, Games, Guitar Hero, Katamari, Websites, Gorillaz, and Official DeviantArt, and Survival Tips.
[SPEAKER_06]: I now know how to stop a camel.
[SPEAKER_06]: So thanks for being a part of all your listeners' life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reject false icons, Ion671.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come to the East Coast sometime.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm coming to New York City end of October.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm going to be going to the Nintendo World Store to meet fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know what day that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to go, but I'm going to YaoiCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a sweet email, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone who remembers me reading the... For anyone who wants to know where I got my survival tips from, it's the Worst Case Scenario Survival Handbook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoa, sorry, we had a snafu there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neverending stories started playing in the background there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: The neverending soda.
[SPEAKER_03]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next up is Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's such a cool name.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never!
[SPEAKER_06]: But it may be a good way to get some exposure to the non-podcast audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reading that again to myself, I suppose lesbian pillow fights may have a similar effect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I didn't mean to bring that in.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was an accident.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Regardless, were it feasible, I'd definitely attend a traveling OLR show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to miss the Fanime panel last spring, so I'd love to have that sort of thing happen again.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will, by the way, be at Fanime next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fanime next year, and it looks like SakuraCon is also for Seattle people.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And possibly, at least myself, will be at one East Coast con.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to be doing anime cons up the butt next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to try to get to OdaCon next year, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But more on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to ASUN next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Megzi, so we can try something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flyer, girls!
[SPEAKER_04]: We can walk around with a shirt or something stupid like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Afterwards, we'll drink Guinness and play old games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be a party.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Guinness.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is my idea of a party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking forward to your show hitting the podcast stream, so I'll hear you then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_06]: And relatedly, fuck Pyrite.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_01]: That is a card-carrying OL Army member.
[SPEAKER_01]: For a second there, I thought you said pyrite.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, damn that fool's gold.
[SPEAKER_01]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pyrite is cool because it crystallizes in cube form.
[SPEAKER_06]: I took chemistry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: Science and technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Science.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should ban dihydrogen monoxide.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you know that dihydrogen monoxide is just water.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that on an episode?
[SPEAKER_03]: Penn and Teller's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, one of my friends was just telling me about that episode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wanted to congratulate you on your 200th episode since I won't be listening live tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's from Mike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next one up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, long one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not long, long, but.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually from Kenji, who I posted his email as my email of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this is our essay writer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to start doing an email of the month, by the way, so make sure you start sending in very thoughtful and well-written things that don't have hate in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy 200th episode, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations on making it this far, and here's hoping for your continued successes and good fortune.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheers.
[SPEAKER_06]: This won't be long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I figure that everything I'll mention in this letter will already be mentioned before you even touch this week's mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: They blew it, blew it, blew it, blew it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo couldn't have been set up any better.
[SPEAKER_06]: $600 PS3 on November 17th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can Kutaragi stick up his ass?
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft with a dollar sign.
[SPEAKER_06]: Problem with selling 360s in every other market in the US.
[SPEAKER_06]: The cars were all laid out in Nintendo's favor.
[SPEAKER_06]: All Reggie had to say was $199, October something or the other, and get off the stage.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, does anyone else see the Pictochat-like qualities in the Wii channels?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, it might just be the system alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just as Pictochat sold DS systems in Japan without selling any accompanying software, Photo Channel and the Mii Channel especially seem to be those quirky things that'll keep non-gamers entertained for hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then they have the Wii Forums, where you can post stuff with your caricature as your little avatar.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but that's specific to your Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not Internet Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was your own Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like for family members to leave messages to each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Mom, you suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dad's a whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: For a good time, call Mom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last night, ooh!
[SPEAKER_06]: And it said, Mad, just my opinions from a slightly educated gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you haven't answered this already, will the higher, near next-gen price point keep you guys from getting a Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks and congrats again, Kenji.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, didn't he say, I mean, I think this guy's great and all because he has a lot to say, but didn't he just say, you know, Nintendo fucked up, and then he said, but it sounds kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think what the intention was is that Nintendo could have gotten a whole lot more in the terms of new people buying the system had it just been dropped a little bit more, had a few more pack-ins.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not doom and gloom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still the cheapest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still the cheapest one on the shelf.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Sunshine and Rainbows.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not only the cheapest one on the shelf, but it's the cheapest one on the shelf with the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can buy that in a 360 and still not pay as much as you would for... Wii 60.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pre-ordering one in both GameStop and my work, so I may have two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not allowed to talk about how I'm getting a Wii, but I am getting a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I will have it on release day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll have ours on release day.
[SPEAKER_03]: We all will because we're special.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, the last email tonight comes from Alessa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, like Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I'm excited about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a link to an article about a father that killed his child over a video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's he playing World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_06]: Reading further in the article, apparently just being a cute little kid, she was pulling on the controller cord, playing with it, and the system fell, and he apparently was so upset he punched her in the face twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: When the mother came in to ask, because she was taking a nap, she didn't know anything was happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: When she got up to check on her daughter, she asked why she's not breathing, and he said she's breathing, she's just asleep or something like that, but
[SPEAKER_06]: She called the ambulance and she was pronounced dead at the scene.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently this guy was supposed to be, they said that he was a fairly non-violent person, but I think, first of all, I think the game has nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if he had been building a house of cards and she knocked it over?
[SPEAKER_06]: If he's given to punch somebody over something, especially a child, over something so trivial, he would have done it over anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some type of violent gene there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That definitely has nothing to do with a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is one seriously mentally fucked up person.
[SPEAKER_00]: On a completely unrelated note, five bucks says it was Madden.
[SPEAKER_00]: I kid, I kid, I kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was Baby Tossing 2000, you know, on the Xbox 360 arcade, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually doesn't say what game it was from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendog Sniper 2006 The sad thing is that the lady was pregnant with another baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: The good news is he'll be the hell away from that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he is locked up.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually charging him with murder, endangering the welfare of a child, and possession of an instrument of crime.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the thing that struck me is that the lady was saying that her daughter is never going to meet her big sister.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was what got me on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 in our chatroom says I'll say it now shut up Jack seriously you know he's gonna hop on that shit but again I don't think it was what he was doing so much you know if she had toppled over something else he might have been working on if he was that mentally unstable to strike a child you know then he would have done it over anything
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm not sure how to transition to this story.
[SPEAKER_03]: I suppose I could say something about at least he didn't throw the Guitar Hero controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is a story on Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: New songs announced for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega Death with Hanger 18 is supposedly going to be like the last final boss song in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aerosmith with Last Child.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this song I think is pretty cool coming to Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cheap Trick with Surrender.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've already announced the one song I was most interested in, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, the Spinal Tap?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, YYZ.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't you a big fan of the Spinal Tap?
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Rush.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rush is cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, I'm glad to see that Guitar Hero 2 seems to be on its way to being finished.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's another game which supposedly is going to be finished pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Duke Nukem Forever is apparently in the polished stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what the fuck does that mean.
[SPEAKER_01]: The polish stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: It means that the physics and animation systems are virtually finished and shippable.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's simply maintenance and polish from here on out.
[SPEAKER_01]: We haven't needed to make substantial changes to those systems in months.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they mean polish as in polishing a turd.
[SPEAKER_03]: The changes have been made... Sorry the game's delayed.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've all been too busy polishing our poles.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says... And then he goes on to say...
[SPEAKER_01]: I worked for Prey Drew said it worked for Prey
[SPEAKER_01]: Pray, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: It wasn't that great of a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pray's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was kind of fun, but kind of fun isn't like, wow, ten years in the making.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll see how the free expansion pack is that's supposedly coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know how we're always bringing up some of our more quirky games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Majesco is bringing Cake Mania to the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll bring in the touchscreen part so you can bake your cakes with extra touch power, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it will be the full game plus the Back to the Bakery expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if anyone's into the weirdo quirk stuff, it will be coming out for $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: Developed by Digital Embryo, which I think is a cool name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another series that Majesco is going to be bringing out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have two titles in development for the Wii series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bust-a-Move
[SPEAKER_03]: I was wondering if it was maybe the Cake Mania thing came out later or something, but I guess not.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's ones for the DS and ones for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we should have more information pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, that's going to bring to an end this Part B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you guys are thinking, wait a minute, you haven't taken calls yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't done last minute stories yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, tonight, guys, for our very special episode number 200, we're going to be doing a Part C.
[SPEAKER_03]: Part C of Episode 200 hits our podcast feed