[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, September 3rd, 2006, Loki brings us new exclusives from the inside, PlayStation 3 gets a new slogan, and an old computer classic makes its way to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio Hello everybody and welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that video game independent podcast dedicated...
[SPEAKER_02]: to what gamers really want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video game news, gamer culture, the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all right here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm here to help you through that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also here to help us out, say hello to Loki, Techmaster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is celebrating her anniversary this weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: They got married on September 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a big congratulations and happy first wedding anniversary wishes to DarkSakura and Dan the Man, her husband.
[SPEAKER_02]: Filling in tonight, say hello to an old Orange Lounge Radio favorite, Miklatov!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's not waste a moment here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get right into How Is Your Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to start it off with Loki tonight to tell us about his gaming week, when the games he's been playing and what he likes, what he hates.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing, well, lots of Saints Row because that game's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried a little bit of the online and I think it's, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: The games that I played were very laggy to the point where they were pretty much unplayable.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be fun, though, when they get whatever that, you know, what's wrong with it worked out.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in the meantime...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did discover that there are cheat codes in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Granted, cheat codes you can't get achievements for, but it's fun during lunch hours, you know, and having infinite rockets.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I've been keeping myself very occupied with that, and it's pretty cool driving around in a big rig and stuff and killing cops and people and just general mayhem.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then other than that, I did try a little bit more of Rumble Roses XX, and I really don't like the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: 3 waves of 12 planes and you have to do that for each plane that's in your collection which is there's 32 of them and it takes a very long time it's just it's not that it's impossible it's just so fucking boring and to be honest I don't know why they put that even in there because arcade mode is almost the same as this like mini campaign mode that they have it's just dumb it's a really really dumb game I'm sorry but it is and I do not recommend it for the PlayStation 3 or the Wii when it comes out no matter how you know
[SPEAKER_01]: The Tooth Control
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a cool mission, and I wish there was more of it in the game, but there's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's only that one level, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, oh well, but it's a crappy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I have to introduce our always present fourth guest, and that is the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're listening live on this Sunday night, head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's see, it was JeremyTodd1 in chat said, Wait, he was complaining about it being boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's boring, why would you do god mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: It would make it even more boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I want to get the game over as quick as possible because it is so boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, basically the whole game requires you to chase after these planes and you have to end up looping around shooting them, looping around shooting them again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Imagine that for like, oh, trust me, the missions are long enough as it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do not want to make them any longer.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I'm almost done with the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is my last achievement.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just need to get it done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I'll be done with this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can sell it back.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then play more Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a fun game and I really wish Ridge Racer 7 was coming out on the 360 but it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sadly enough, I saw the screenshots for Ridge Racer 7 and it makes me want to get a PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck you, Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_02]: No wonder there's a lot of Ridge Racer love from Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could sell some systems there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about that next time you tell some Ridge Racer jokes.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really does sell systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really sad because seeing some of these screenshots of
[SPEAKER_01]: Not necessarily the first party stuff that they showed at E3, but like Ridge Racer 7 and Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd have to see it actually being played, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's pretty much... Oh, and of course, as usual, the Grand Theft Auto Liberty City stories.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've been playing... We actually did some races.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually have racing and stuff, and that was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which I should point out, you always have something new to complain about that game, yet you can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and... Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have thought that it would have been like the reason why that game sells as well as it's doing is because of multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it weren't really boring, I'm sure it would be a really good multiplayer game but it kind of sucks a lot and maybe if you had more than three people like we had playing, you can play up to six.
[SPEAKER_03]: That can make it fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Enchanted Arms is really cool and I enjoy playing that and I've been playing Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Leveling Blue Mage Even Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes Specifically?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like there are any other ones The rest of them are stupid Well there's a new one called Final Fantasy XII that a lot of people are really excited about You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care Alright That's not a real Final Fantasy game
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, technically, yes, it is actually a real Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not in my world!
[SPEAKER_01]: Some would complain that it's actually more of a Final Fantasy game than XI was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there's chocobos, and red mages, and blue mages, and black mages, and white mages, and whatever else.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's way more fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And red hearts, and green clovers, and purple horseshoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And blue moons.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They taste good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky charms.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want some lucky charms now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't do anything else besides work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, you can't talk about what you're playing at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I can tell you what I'm playing at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm playing at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was by Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's on my TV a lot, so I guess I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard a really funny name for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Noobisoft was what I heard somebody call them this week, and I thought that was really funny for some reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except, didn't they do...
[SPEAKER_02]: That DDR urban game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Flow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Flow was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was not a great game, but it's way better than, like, I don't know, In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except for a couple songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sephiroth1215, what do you think of this comment in our chatroom?
[SPEAKER_03]: I ignored it, is what I thought about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have to read it here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI should have been called Final Fantasy Online and not by a number.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually said that when the game first came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I love Final Fantasy XI, I actually agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Quest VIII Dragon Quest VIII Dragon Quest VIII
[SPEAKER_02]: In response to Jeremy Todd's comment about how it's ironic that a couple weeks ago I said I wasn't a gamer, I'm still not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just, you know, I've got a bad addiction.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, you know, I need help.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: JeremyTal1 in chat is also pointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy, you'd think he's the only one in chat with how much we're quoting him tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's saying that Ubisoft is also making Assassin's Creed, which was some news this week because, you know, it's coming out to the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_02]: We all knew that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that was, like, totally unexpected.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: MyGamingWeek.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I am an enabler.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really, really good at that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you not see my cute little chocobo?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is why you guys buy Macs, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one of our Link Shell buddies today put it best, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said something about,
[SPEAKER_02]: We were all looking at the total time spent in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, Jazz, he's up to 198 days in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, he's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he says probably a quarter of that has been spent looking for party.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is the downside to Final Fantasy XI, big time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to have a good link shell so that you have a chat room to keep you busy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, honestly, I missed a lot of the people in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat room, the link shell on Final Fantasy XI, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's a good reason to come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the fact that I was playing the game is a good reason to come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know that doing all that crap last night to get you those quests was really fun, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we did all the new job quests.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Blue Mage, Corsair, and Puppeteer all in one night, and it was actually kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say this about the game, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They upped the graphics on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: They upped the resolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a slight change.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may not even notice it, but I did, and I think it did make the game look a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still kind of hard to read the text.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still takes forever to get logged into the game, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm having a good time
[SPEAKER_02]: A. I will still be going to Phantasy Star Universe when that comes out, so Final Fantasy XI can kiss my butt while I go play Phantasy Star Universe for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: B. Did you hear me complain the 40 times she went back to Ragnarok Online?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: She quit and went back to WoW as well, so you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We all have our things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, suck it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care what you people think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will game however I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another game that I bought that a lot of people have been going, why would you buy that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Time Pilot on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now look, this was one of my favorite 80s games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it was kind of like my cultish game that I really liked.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and Gyruss.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they're both Konami games, just by coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are like the shooters that I absolutely love.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was really excited to see Time Pilot was coming out to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool you can play with original graphics as well as enhanced.
[SPEAKER_02]: The enhanced graphics aren't exactly going to, you know, rock your world by any means.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably Super Nintendo-level graphics, but I mean, I guess it's kind of nice to have them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, the game has super easy achievements.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably got about eight achievements the first time I played through the game, but maybe that's just because I played it before, so I kind of, you know, was already decent at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't think there's going to be a lot here that's going to win a person over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's $5.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say check out the demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like those Geometry Wars-ish shooting games and you want another easy-to-pick-up shooter, or you're an achievement points whore, I think Time Pilot's pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's worth a look.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the game that they're putting out next week, though, Scramble, I think I'm going to totally pass on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was not a Konami game, I remember, by any means.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Gradius should have been the one we're getting instead, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're waiting on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the other game I played this week was Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't like the game at first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not that I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was just like a real average RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was kind of like, okay, am I only liking this because...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's as good as it could be, but I think a lot of the cutscenes are really, really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of the battle, though, looks like PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some of the graphic stuff annoys me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if you use big characters in your party, sometimes it blocks other characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't even see them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some very basic camera controls could have been put into battle to make it a lot easier to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: English Voice Acting English Voice Acting
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: basically you move around a 12 square grid and put in your attacks and you kind of have to think about where your characters are positioned might make it easier for the enemy to attack you so it's somewhat tactical but still old fashioned style as well there's a lot of customization ability kind of has a Pokemon-ish element in it because there's a hundred different golem creatures you can use the story started off very cliche and it's still a little bit cliche as far as Japanese RPGs go but it's getting better I find that if you stay with the game
[SPEAKER_02]: Up until about, there's a major event that happens about two hours into the game that has a really gorgeous cutscene with it, and I think the game gets a lot better after that point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to ask this, though, because I am a gay gamer, and Miklatov, I know you are too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's getting a lot of talk because it has a gay character in it named Makoto, and Makoto is very, let's say, flamboyant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Carson, the blonde guy from Queer Eye, who's like a bard character.
[SPEAKER_02]: He plays sax or something, and
[SPEAKER_02]: He talks like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: He talks like James from Pokemon, if you've ever watched that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he doesn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he does.
[SPEAKER_02]: He totally has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: If anything, he talks more like Xander from Drawn Together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, what do you think of this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it's a good thing for gay gamers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think it sets us back two years?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't like him, but I like how they're...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think it's very interesting and a very risky thing to do in an Xbox 360 game, because you think of the typical, stereotypical Xbox audience, Madden 07 and all that stuff, and I think it would be very shocking, and I can imagine a lot of people going, ew, ew, ew, gross, but I think they need that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they need that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a step in the right direction, even if the character was done a little over the top, to put it lightly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a good thing, overall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I do a spoiler?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blaze in our chatroom says, that's how the world should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, maybe it's a utopia view of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, those are the games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do kind of recommend Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if you're into Japanese RPGs and you own an Xbox 360, you really should take a look at this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you haven't really played these types of games before, I don't think this is the one that's going to win you over.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think this is a good one to appease fans of Japanese RPGs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get into some housekeeping news tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know some of you folks might be listening tonight for the DDR Power Previews, which we were promoting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you've noticed on OrangeLawnTrader.com, we were requested earlier this week by Konami to suspend that for the time being.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some things are going on behind the scenes where they just weren't ready for us to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're hoping that, and I don't know why, there's a million reasons we can theorize, but long story short, it's just not happening tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: The good news is it does look like we will be getting to debut some type of new tracks from Ultramix 4 and Universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami of Hawaii has been really good in working with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we will have something possibly as soon as next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So keep your eyes peeled on the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do think it's going to happen in one form or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you will hear new songs that you have not heard yet here on Orange Launch Radio and over on allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: So stay tuned to the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: I apologize for anyone that was tuning in ready to hear it tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: These things happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other housekeeping news.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a 3 day weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: and uh... if you've been in our chat room tonight you'll know that Loki and myself have started the drinking tonight
[SPEAKER_02]: A few things I want to say about drunk shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: A, we do this because we can, because people out there say, oh, professionals shouldn't drink while we're on the job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're not professionals, and we're perfectly fine with that, so shove it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other thing is that people say, wait a minute, Rob, aren't you being a little bit of a hypocrite?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because last week you were saying you were criticizing those folks that had gone to the press event and were drinking at the press event.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's a big difference here, you see.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because they were drinking in someone else's house.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we were guests on, let's say, Scott's show, Bobby's show, whatever podcast we want to have us on, Loki, do you think we'd go on their show drunk?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, unless they were doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, unless they asked us to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But really, we would probably not do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would have the respect to be our professional self.
[SPEAKER_02]: But while we're in our own house, we can do whatever we want.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's the difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to call us a hypocrite after hearing that, whatever, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: All I drink, for those who don't know, is screwdrivers, except tonight I've actually switched with Rob, he's drinking screwdrivers and I'm drinking some watermelon thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even that is pretty tough for me to drink, and it's just all mental right now, so I'm not trying to overdo it at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, I'm pretty sure I'm probably not going to get too drunk tonight, so whatever, I mean.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I've just known people who've had a problem in my past, and it's not an easy thing to deal with.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the other thing I was thinking about bringing over, but I didn't, I was going to get drunk off a kosher wine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which would have been funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would have been funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's get into some gaming news, shall we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we shall.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we have some exclusives tonight, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_01]: How did you land so many exclusives this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, once a year, and actually we started this last year, we have the game publishers out to basically give us their rundown of the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: So, starting things off here, which is actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: This year, for the first time, we had Nintendo come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, obviously, the question on everyone's mind, when the hell is Wii coming out?
[SPEAKER_01]: When is this coming out?
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, the guy was very tight-lipped about it, except for a few things.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is most definitely going to be announced on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said it's actually going to be announced in Japan as well at the same time, which is kind of funny because the news story came out afterwards about that same.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say it lines up with a story that came out later this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said they're going to have multi-regional press events, so that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has confirmed, though, it is going to be a November launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said 100% a November launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is based on his knowledge, what he knows so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, the October 18th date that we were so certain of just got shot down this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: What went wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why were we wrong on October 18th?
[SPEAKER_01]: We were wrong because the launch right now, he doesn't know exactly when it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's November, but they're trying to time it either two weeks before the PS3 launch or a week after.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they don't want their thunder being stolen by Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're telling me Nintendo themselves doesn't even know when they're launching this system as of yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he hasn't been told the final date yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: The reason why is they're waiting on the amount of units that they have in production.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're making sure that they have enough to launch because they're doing a worldwide launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it will not delay the launch past Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it will be before...
[SPEAKER_01]: That gives you a pretty good range there of when it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if Nintendo themselves doesn't even know the launch date, or at least maybe a very, very few select people know it at this point inside Nintendo, would it be safe to say that any story you've read on the internet about launch date today is bullshit?
[SPEAKER_02]: Including the one we ran.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And remember, mine was just purely speculation because of the anniversary and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that would make sense because if Nintendo themselves has kind of not really known the date they wanted to do...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, I would think that they're not launching in November.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes sense because you want to make sure you have the most units so you can sell as much as possible so you don't run into the shortages.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some interesting stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are spending $30 million in marketing this thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's twice as much as the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's definitely going to be out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not going to have in-store kiosks because the reason why they're not is because of the setup issues with this thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it has that sensor bar, it would make it very difficult for them to be able to set up and they want to make sure that they have
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: There is one interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going the Xbox route with the DVD player in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be an add-on and not included in the box.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you've got to get this extra dongle or whatever to put on it to be able to play DVDs.
[SPEAKER_01]: But his thought on it was, who doesn't own a DVD player by now?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, seriously, everybody owns a DVD player.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Moving on from Nintendo a little bit...
[SPEAKER_01]: to Midway.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has that DVD player rumor been announced anywhere?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's something interesting from Midway.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I asked him twice when I heard this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Blitz the League for the Wii is not coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely not at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is cancelled as far as they're concerned.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, not happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are basically concerned with launching Rampage.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rampage, I guess, is going to be their big...
[SPEAKER_01]: ActaVision
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Hero 2 will be coming with a red guitar controller
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, and I have asked him twice about this, because this didn't make sense, and I don't know, Shane, if you know anything about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said that for Universe, all the songpacks from the Ultramix series will be transferable to Universe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never heard that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that was interesting because I asked, I'm like, are you sure?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, how would that be possible?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: That didn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm thinking this guy might have been confusing Ultramix 4 because that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, like maybe Ultramix 4 and Universe have the same songpacks or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe they're going to have the same soundpacks later on.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I asked him again, I'm like, are you sure?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, that seemed a little weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said, yes, Universe will be able to play the songpacks from Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so take that with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, DarkSakura brings up a good point in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultramix 1 through 4 aren't on the backward compatibility list, so how would that work?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless they're planning on re-releasing the songpacks or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: According to Sega...
[SPEAKER_01]: Fantasy Star Universe, on the 360 there will be no charge for the online service, which is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: There will be a charge, a monthly fee for PlayStation 2 and PC users.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would almost be worth it for me to get a 360 again just to get PSU with no monthly charge.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Secret of the Rings, or you might remember Sonic Wildfire, not a launch title for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Coming March 2007, so look for that then.
[SPEAKER_01]: There will not be Full Auto 2 on the Xbox 360 at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not later, not ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the first one didn't sell very well, so they're not bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder why they think that it'll sell on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're just trying a different audience.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's really what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really weird because, I mean, in the scope of about five minutes, you've contradicted about seven different news stories that have ran out there previously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you're right or we're going to look stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, these are from the... Okay, so marketing people could be wrong and therefore you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: LucasArts
[SPEAKER_01]: The Wii Star Wars game is in development.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will not be done until late 2007 or early 2008.
[SPEAKER_01]: They want to make sure they get it right because they have a rabid fan base of Star Wars fans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously, they mix it with rabid Wii fans.
[SPEAKER_01]: They want to make sure they don't fuck this up, so that's mainly the case.
[SPEAKER_01]: The next-gen Star Wars game is going to be coming in the fall of 2007.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, Indiana Jones, the next-gen game, will be released at the same time as the new movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: which is confirmed in pre-production from them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had Vimvedi, they were talking about the Scarface game and one of the funny bits of trivia from it is that the voice actor that they picked for Tony Montana is actually Al Pacino's driver.
[SPEAKER_01]: And apparently because Al Pacino can't do Tony's voice anymore due to his age,
[SPEAKER_01]: Say hello to my little friend!
[SPEAKER_01]: GT, that racing game that they announced, it's going to come with a steering wheel add-on for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is going to be something that you plug... Like you put the Wii controller in the middle of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: You do not need it to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could I use the A button for the horn?
[SPEAKER_01]: Beep, beep.
[SPEAKER_01]: You do not need it to play the game, but it will be just something that you can slap the controller into to play it, which I thought that was very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone actually thinking about how to use the system.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Prince of Persia New Chariot Races
[SPEAKER_01]: And right now the working title is just Prince of Persia, so they haven't really made an announcement yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now for once, that lines up with something I did read on the rest of the internet a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was actually the DS one that you were reading about, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Far Cry and the Wii looks pretty awesome from what I've seen so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: The pictures look pretty cool, the screenshots, so that was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Koei.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bladestorm, The Hundred Years War, not coming out at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be quarter one of 2007, and I guess it is in the launch window, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar-O-Man Lives is going to have online play and new songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't that already come out?
[SPEAKER_01]: In Europe?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe in Europe, I don't know, but it's coming out October here.
[SPEAKER_01]: New Romance of the Three Kingdoms game coming out on the PlayStation 2, quarter one or quarter two of 2007, which should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now the big one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_01]: No price drops, no bundles whatsoever for the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not worried because their competition is $200 more expensive than them.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, they were unaware that Canada, because Canada kind of operates a little bit independent than the U.S., Microsoft was doing a bundle until after it had been announced.
[SPEAKER_01]: And much hate mail was exchanged, according to our rep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gears of War is coming out November 7th, not November 12th.
[SPEAKER_01]: November 12th is actually Emergency, which is their big marketing push.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, that makes absolutely no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would they have all this huge hype over emergency, emergency, and then you're telling me the game's coming out five days earlier?
[SPEAKER_01]: The game is coming out on the 7th because you can't really launch a game on a Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's when everybody's getting in the game is on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, stores, you know, some stores are waiting until the 12th because they're confused on this emergency thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the emergency is when they're going to be doing all the big ad pushes, you know, their campaigns.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're playing with fame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because didn't Halo launch on a Friday?
[SPEAKER_01]: So could it be like that where maybe the stores are getting it that day, but they're not supposed to sell it until the 12th?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, according to him, they can sell it when they get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this was also kind of ties in with another story that we had earlier about the same thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I can confirm that it's always been the 7th, but I thought it was weird that they were selling it on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the best one right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, everybody thinks it's coming out in the fall of 2007.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be March or April of 2007.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not going to be the fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I was a betting man, I'd say it's the end of spring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't sound like he knew for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he says, if I was a betting man, I would da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you launch a game in April, especially before E3 or whatever?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's my thought on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though E3 is the same thing next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: This makes perfect sense when you think about it this way.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm Not Sure About Microsoft
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Atari, Alone in the Dark Test Drive Unlimited
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is coming out actually next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll be getting download packs each month.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're planned up until June of next year so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first two packs will be Lexus cars.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says no word off these cars.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to be free.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Lexus paid a quarter million dollars to get the cars in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it says all the download packs will range from free to $7.99 or the Microsoft equivalent in points.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all the big news from our wonderful...
[SPEAKER_02]: Meetings.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Nintendo Maniac 64 has a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP came out in March.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the end of their fiscal year.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I would think that they would wait until the fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, maybe they want to make sure that people... Think about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Microsoft is doing something big around the PlayStation 3 launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just some sort of announcement or event.
[SPEAKER_01]: What if that announcement is that Halo is coming out in March?
[SPEAKER_01]: Then people that were going to buy PlayStation 3, they're going to wait until this game comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's... That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, maybe that's just the liquor talking, but that makes a lot of sense now that you've put it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, okay, would you say if November goes by and we still haven't heard anything that maybe something's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think if they're going to announce anything, it's going to be a big... It's going to be... A Halo 3 announcement, I mean, is going to be huge, but... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you would... Because people are like, well, there's... You know, Gears of War is awesome, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I really want Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might be getting a PlayStation 3 because Resistance looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, by the way, Halo's coming out in a few months.
[SPEAKER_01]: People are like, okay, I can wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or I'll buy a 360 now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be just downright evil, but kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, didn't they say that they were going to... Well, they always were saying that they were going to release Halo 3 on the... Yeah, but I think then everybody realized realistically that can't happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: If Halo 3 is going to be really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, but... Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take it with a grain of salt, but that's straight from the mouths of people that are working for these companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know... Turbopunk in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pure evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd expect no less from Macroshaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were very excited.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried to get more out of the Microsoft guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: He kind of wanted to talk about stuff that had already come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of juicy tidbits there.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will post all this stuff in that thread that we have going, the Under the Radar thread.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you'll have that for reference in case this stuff actually... Or he's wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or he's downright wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, this is coming from salespeople.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sales?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sales people, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, one thing we do know about Xbox Live Arcade is that we have this new game that's going to be coming out, and it's called Space Giraffe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, usually I'd laugh at a game called Space Giraffe, but what looks pretty awesome about it is that it looks a lot like Tempest, but a lot trippy, kind of like how Geometry Wars was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I remember seeing a screenshot for this game that had a lot of really dirty words on it, but I can't seem to find that anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember that one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that was photoshopped or what, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope... Because there were some words in there that actually offended me, and that's hard to do, so hopefully those aren't actually in the game, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there were some pictures posted on LiveJournal or something like that, so that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's one of the, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Biggest Sleeper Hits that people don't appreciate and was like the reason to own a Jaguar was that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be very happy if a game like this came to Xbox Live Arcade more as it develops.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also a story this week talking about the Xbox 360 soccer exclusive deals that they have going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Talking about how the Xbox 360 is going to be the only place that you're going to be able to get next-gen soccer games or all next-gen soccer games I should say because FIFA is going to be on both systems and
[SPEAKER_01]: Pro Evolution Soccer 6 Winning 11 Pro Evolution Soccer 2007
[SPEAKER_01]: According to Konami, who was also at our event this week, spoke to the rep there.
[SPEAKER_01]: The reason why Pro Evolution Soccer, or Winning Eleven, whatever, Pro Evolution Soccer 2007, the reason it's not coming out on the PlayStation 3 at launch is because they haven't got the final dev kits yet, and because the game's not getting done until March.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or actually, as late as May, according to him.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's only exclusive because it's not finished.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, take it as you will, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one... I don't remember them saying anything at the barbecue about it being exclusive or anything, and I would have thought if it was going to be exclusive, they would have said something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it seemed like they were... I mean, the game was being ported to DS... What else was there?
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it seemed like they were porting it to other systems anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, sure, for the handhelds, they'd be downgraded versions, but... Well...
[SPEAKER_01]: Think about it, if they didn't really assign an exclusive deal, and I'm not sure FIFA's coming out on the PlayStation 3, I would figure it is, but maybe not this year, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's the case, then there is no soccer game on the... Now, wait, okay, hold on a minute here, because the guy from Microsoft at the Germany convention went out there and said, we have both franchises exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're saying, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, according to my rep, but then again, you know, he may be,
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just taking Konami's word for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's one game we know is not going to be exclusive to either system and shouldn't be a shock at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a Burnout 5 coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, really?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's coming to the 360 and the PlayStation 3, who would have thought, sometime in 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Burnout is going to be getting a little bit of a makeover.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just going to be rehash of the old same old Burnout.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this time Burnout will be more of an open-world-ish environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Players will be able to go in and out of menus at every intersection, possibly a crash course by going through any type of intersection.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be taking place in a town called Paradise City.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take me down to the Paradise City.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I just can't help but think of that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why isn't it coming out for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: No ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also say, though, EA says, the most explosive pileups in the series history.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're always going to say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is kind of the first true next-gen burnout.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the other one was just a souped-up old burnout.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's not a big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, what's interesting, though, Microsoft Japan is talking about bringing Tokyo Game Show and Exo 6 home.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, kind of like, it sounds like what they're doing, or what they did with E3, how they had, you know, a bunch of exclusive, like, video and demos and stuff, and I really hope they do that, because, you know, with the region-free, uh, you know, those logins that we have, you can download some pretty cool demos.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um, yeah, so there'll be, um, more of that stuff coming, um, around Tokyo Game Show, which is actually only in a few weeks, I mean, uh, 23rd to 24th of September, so, um, should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: On This Day or Days because of the, you know, dateline and all that stuff, messing everything up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, it kind of goes on into the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what should be noted, Nintendo usually doesn't attend Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this might be their way of kind of doing it on their own terms of publicity.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not not a huge surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was a pretty big surprise, though, was Microsoft released another backwards compatibility update.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there was quite a few titles this time, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: They even had some pretty good stuff, like Burnout 3 and Dead the Rights.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right after I sold back Burnout 3, thank you, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fetal Frame 2, Freaky Flyers, if you were into that game, Gauntlet Seven Sorrows, Sid Meier's Pirates.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Barbie fits the same scheme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to old Nintendo emulators.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once you make a certain mapper work, most of the other games that run on that mapper work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's something interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was talking actually with Midway about, hey, did you guys know that this game has got to add to the compatibility list today?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're like, no, I didn't hear that, but I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're like, well, we actually know what engine it's built on.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's built on the LA Rush engine, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they're talking about maybe...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not, but I don't think he'd mind me sharing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He linked me to a story on GoNintendo.com which talks about the demo unit, which we talked about a little bit ago for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently, according to GoNintendo, the picture has turned out to be true due to numerous sources who have informed me.
[SPEAKER_02]: The same image shows up in a packet sent out to EB GameStop employees to get them ready for the unit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad to hear that it turned out to be real.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really like the look of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the whole...
[SPEAKER_01]: To be honest, the guys said Street Cruise were the way they were going to demo it, not the units.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Could that mean a reduction in the units?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was going to be harder to do maybe the retail units just because of the setup that's needed for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe he was talking about the promotional marketing stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not doing demo units like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know that EBs and GameStop have the in-store units that they always have.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, you guys,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Psychonauts
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: F you at these drinks taking like ass no offense I mean it's kind of like you know watermelon thing don't make it too strong um I don't know mainly my F you this week goes to people that do not pay attention on the road and who cannot park and I swear to god every time I see someone on a cell phone I know that they're gonna be driving like shit and you can always tell you know these people they're you know veering in and out of lanes going slow
[SPEAKER_01]: you know can't seem to follow the road at all and then you drive past them you see they're yapping away on the cell phone well fuck them also these people that fucking do not take the time to park their cars correctly you know you get into a parking complex that doesn't have a lot of parking and then all of a sudden you see oh Jackass is over the line he's taken up two spaces because his fucking Yukon or whatever is too big for a compact space well fuck them for trying to park in these goddamn small spaces
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, to you Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to busyness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been like crazy busy with all this stuff going on and I've had like zero free time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when it comes to my work life is mostly what I'm talking about here.
[SPEAKER_02]: My work life has just been nuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And FU to having this feeling because this is how I felt.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of a work story.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to...
[SPEAKER_02]: Folks that like to leave carrots on the ground, and then you kind of hop up to that carrot to take a little bite, and then BAM!
[SPEAKER_02]: The net comes out and grabs you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of work do you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hunting wabbits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you a furry?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miklatov, your turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well then F you to Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to me for not having an FU of this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about F you to Miklatov for fucking suckering me back into Final Fantasy XI and it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome, because the day that you started, you're like, you're not going to get me to play this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I didn't even have to coerce you that much, and you're just like, you wanted to check out how the graphics were on the 360 update, and we couldn't get mine to log in, so you had to log in, you had to pay for it, and then you just started playing, and it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thanks to Final Fantasy XI, here's a game I haven't been playing a lot of on Xbox Live this week, but I did get it patched.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: It discourages people from backing out at all if someone's going to get a loss.
[SPEAKER_02]: So no backing out of the game early.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think they also address some of those timeout issues and connection things with this patch.
[SPEAKER_01]: And reset the leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why can't they just have a counter for disconnects?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Will I get achievement points for playing it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well then I think I'd be okay with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, speculation abounds here on the internet about Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_02]: And usually we don't talk about a lot of non-gaming news, but this is kind of relevant because folks do their gamings on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know we don't talk enough about...
[SPEAKER_01]: And you also have DirectX 10, which is going to be fucking awesome for gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, and I'm just saying, we don't talk a lot about PC games on this show, and I apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just we're so busy with consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do try to talk about big things in the computer gaming world, and this would certainly be one of them, even if it is about an operating system, and it's about Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, apparently Microsoft Canada actually spilled the beans on their website about how much
[SPEAKER_02]: Vista Home Basic
[SPEAKER_02]: and 26993.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be noted that Microsoft Canada has since removed the listing and they said, quote, a number of pricing models are undergoing consideration internally.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, nothing has been finalized.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft is currently finalizing its pricing model and will have more to share at a later date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, I'm starting to get the impression that Microsoft Canada is kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because of the whole, you know, they did the bundle thing when they weren't supposed to and all that other stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of makes them cool that they're doing stuff when they're not supposed to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that makes them retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it makes them great.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe it's just because I'm still having those residual I'm going to move to Canada someday feelings because I just, I love Vancouver so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we love you guys who choose to email us every week so much and we like to read your emails and even though DarkSakura is not here this week, that's not going to prevent me from borrowing her gear and jumping into the mailbag at mailbag at orange launch radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Email numero uno comes to us tonight from somebody from Vancouver, Canada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Vancouver Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see the island is out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This comes to us from Wyatt.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura's butt-kicking-ness
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a lot for what you do for us loyal listeners, and here's for years more of the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sky, you should come to Canada more often.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think that the maple syrup cookies sold on Granville Island are good, you should try the... I don't know what they're called, but basically they are maple syrup thrown into snow and then eaten like a piece of maple syrup thrown in the snow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a lot, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe if I come in the winter, I'll have to try that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like a winter treat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if I try to eat that in the summer, that might be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But thank you very much for the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I might know which podcast you're talking about, because I keep tabs on a few that are going on, and you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things change.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our personal lives change.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes, you know, it just affects what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as much as I would love to do Orange Lounge Radio forever, you know, there might come a time where I have to move for work.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura has to move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's got to go somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and we would like to think that we would keep the show going.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I applaud the other shows that try to keep on going despite the other little setbacks that go on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I want to continue to support independent radio forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: My advice, if it's new people that have been thrown into it, give them a couple weeks to warm up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'll tell you what, this shit ain't easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I realize it seems like it's easy because you hear all these shows and you form opinions on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the difference between doing and listening is really, really, really different.
[SPEAKER_02]: And trust me, it raises my...
[SPEAKER_02]: Perception of Independent Podcasts just so much more by doing one of my own.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, give them a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet you that same thing that you liked before will come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if, you know, not, we appreciate the fact that you check us out and support us.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the fact that you're supporting independent radio at all is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I hope things go good for you and the shows that you're listening to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to a new email.
[SPEAKER_02]: This person did not sign their email.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I will, let's see, I'll just call them Tolu because I think that's what...
[SPEAKER_02]: The subject in support of the PSP because of the uninformed bashing and ninty fanboys
[SPEAKER_02]: We asked for emails like this, so here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over the last couple months, the Sony bashing in the news has become almost unbearable.
[SPEAKER_02]: They bash the PSP saying that it has no good games or just ports, while the DS has just as many.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, Animal Crossing, New Super Mario Bros., Castlevania, wait, you can go outside the castle, Innovative, Metroid, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a deeper experience instead of minigames or games from 15 years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Syphon Filter, Daxter, Tekken, Metal Gear Solid, LocoRoco, Wipeout, and GTA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Mario again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninty fans don't care, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's that email.
[SPEAKER_02]: I appreciate your perspective, because I think this guy does bring up a point, is that a lot of people say the PSP is the same shit over again, and then run off to play the newest Mario game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, he brought up another point, though, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have to say, okay, wait a minute, though, because the games that you mentioned at the end there, Tekken, Metal Gear Solid, Wipeout, Grand Theft, those are all franchises, too, that get a new game every year, so I don't know if that's the best perspective.
[SPEAKER_01]: I agree, there's not a lot on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, I do own a PSP, and to be honest, I play more on my PSP than I do on my DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he's right in most aspects, but he's also wrong in some stuff too.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's right in the fact that there are a lot of games that are just ports.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Super Mario 64 for the DS, Animal Crossing...
[SPEAKER_01]: Not quite a port, more of like kind of an upgrade to the current game, but still not very different to where it's like a different game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_01]: You are getting some exclusive games like, you know, you've got the Tony Hawk American Skate Land and the new Downhill Jam is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are getting like some exclusive new games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Castlevania, yeah, Castlevania is pretty much Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is a new game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a port of like, say, Castlevania 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's new.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for longtime fans of the series, getting to go outside the castle is something new, but I get your point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now for the PSP though, you have the same thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, PSP Tekken 5 Dark Resurrection, it's a port of the arcade game, it's also a port of Tekken 5, but still it's good to have a fighting game on, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: The PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, you've got all these collections that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got the Capcom Puzzle Collection, which is ports of old games.
[SPEAKER_01]: My biggest gripe with Sony, we'll get Twisted Metal head-on.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a port of Twisted Metal 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is a blatant port of the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't change really anything other than adding online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in the same aspect, I think both...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: I was hoping for a little bit better of a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, Twisted Metal head on, you know, I wanted it to be a new game, and it was just the old game all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68 brings up an interesting counterpoint in our chatroom right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the Oil Army ports render the original obsolete.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not on portables, because that way I can play my favorite games on the go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't need a TV or a system.
[SPEAKER_03]: in the car or on the train.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, but it renders the original obsolete.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what about the game on the TV?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a completely different experience playing the same game on a TV and on the portable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to point this out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yuri Lover says, Objection, because there are other games that are original on the Nintendo DS and cites the following.
[SPEAKER_02]: WarioWare, Phoenix Wright, Trauma Center, Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: WarioWare is not really, because I came out on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but you get the point, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a really original game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Japanese, but okay, whatever, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'll help them out then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Electroplankton, Elite Beat Agents, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, well, if you want PSP games, let me try to think here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luminous, I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: But look, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've always said this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PSP is a great system if you want to do more with a handheld than just game.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to do the web, music, movies, all that crap is great on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's really the reason to own a PSP, because you want something that's a multimedia thing on the go.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's kind of where Sony's going.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3, I think it's going to be a lot of that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're going to see in the long run from PlayStation 3, it doesn't want to be just a game system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony's biggest problem is that Xbox 360 doesn't want to be just a game system either.
[SPEAKER_02]: But never mind, that's another day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo, on the other hand, is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting to catch up with some of that with the Opera browser coming out and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for now, it's really just about the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games, games, games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you want some fun, short attention span, most of the time, types of games, you know, for the casual gamer, Nintendo DS is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, if you're a real hardcore gamer, you ought to own both.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can afford it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can't afford it, get a job.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, I mean, what are people complaining about ports anyways?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if you don't like them, don't buy them.
[SPEAKER_01]: or Don'tPlayThem.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's a lot coming out for both systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: Granted, when I look at it, I think most of it's crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, I only play one game on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't really have a valid opinion on most of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there is a lot of games that come out that I'm just not impressed with.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The chat room is bringing up from various folks there that the DS has had their share of misfires.
[SPEAKER_02]: Such as Ping Pals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sprung, anyone?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sprung was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sprung was the worst video game I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you play as the guy, the game is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more email.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to do one more email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one is from DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Jamie, Rob, and Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope all is well with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally have caught back up with the show now that I have moved and have cable internet at the place I'm currently living.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like the show is doing great, like always, and is very informative and actually helps me out at my work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I work at EB Games, FYI.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually quite a compliment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually heard of stores that have been playing our show over the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that is crazy, but awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's better than Ian Kessler.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gotta be better than the EB Games Television or whatever that crap is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ian Kessler and Courtney Friel, they both suck and I want to beat them up.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you work at EB Games, get our show played in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will send you versions that have the S words and F words bleeped out if we will get played in store.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, the point of this email was to encourage the OL Army to get involved in the Beatmania US Internet Ranking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would be a great way to show Konami interest in the game and that people did actually buy the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Currently, I've only seen Drew Nami and myself in the internet ranking so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry if I missed anyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you could mention this on the show, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so if you're a music game fan, go show your love in the Beatmania internet ranking.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the record, they did see that game as a success, and it sold as many units, or it outsold as many units as they thought it would, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds like a good sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I am really looking forward to the music previews for DDR Ultramix 4 and DDR Universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry about the delay there.
[SPEAKER_02]: When are you going to get some music previews for In the Groove 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: With a little face on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have Rockstar give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're open.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the great work and I can't wait to hear your next show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe sometime in the future I will see you guys again at a con or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: as it was a disappointment to see you, OnlyRob, I believe, for an extremely short time by the Konami booth at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, stay healthy and well, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad your show is doing so great.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much for the email.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as other previews for other games go, we're not exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: We branched out of the music game thing a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get us wrong, but we love all video games as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if any company wants to do some type of premiere thing, we're down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just have them give us a call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use that for your comments as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk about your game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would love to get you on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely, yes, we've given In the Groove somewhat of a hard time on the show in the past, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm willing to give it a try.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually don't hate In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an alternative.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people like Coke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people like Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people like pee.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some people like RC Cola for some god-awful reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: RC Cola is okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, scratch one other loss for Sony, unfortunately, in their battle against Homebrew.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Firmware 2.8 has been hacked, and now Homebrew is able... So far, they have found an exploit in 2.8, and they have Homebrew running now in every single firmware that's available from 2.0 and up, and of course, 1.5 and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, so that's kind of interesting, and the best part about it, you don't need Grand Theft Auto for it to work, because unfortunately with some of the other ones, that's how you had to do it, is with Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now, they do have a Hello World proof of concept homebrew program that is available out there, and, um, yeah, it's quite interesting actually, because, um, there's also, was a story that I read, um, this week, that they're
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: GPS comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing with the liquor?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I hear you starting to slur a little bit and I'm doing the same thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like halfway through that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The chat room pointed out to me that you can call our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something I said earlier, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever, I'm not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't know me!
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't know my life.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just like, I'm starting to get sick of the watermelon thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want something new?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want some pineapple?
[SPEAKER_01]: I do want... No, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want some of the... You want to try this again?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, I don't want that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially if you don't want the orange juice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pussy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't like orange juice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, I've got this thing stuck in my head now where orange juice equals vomiting, and so it's not good drinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the first times I ever threw up, I threw up SpaghettiOs, and for some reason, I've never been able to really eat SpaghettiOs the same way ever since then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know what's interesting, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: The first time I threw up here from over-drinking was...
[SPEAKER_01]: Minestrone Blue Raspberry Jell-O
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was actually not that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good going down and coming up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was kind of like, wow, kind of sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should put that on the box.
[SPEAKER_01]: Raspberry Jell-O.
[SPEAKER_01]: Great going down, pretty good coming up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck those Pudding Pops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shane, you might have to do the rest of the stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm just going to complain.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how's that Suikoden doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck Suikoden.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will kill you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suikoden's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just not that great either.
[SPEAKER_02]: When are they putting out Suikoden on PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's this movement on an official Konami site.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like konamigamestars.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an RPG site that Konami opened for the US fans of the Konami RPGs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they want the fans to show how much they want this port of 1 and 2 that came out for PSP in Japan to come out over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm sure I just made up the website URL I just sent with the KonamiGameStars.com, but if you go there and show your support, I mean, we're really trying to get it to come out here, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Show that it will sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't you talk to someone at work and make it happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: We've been talking for a long time about this game coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's like, come on, put it out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I come to your work and berate people?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because obviously Kami doesn't mind if people drink.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even have a freaking office at my job.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I have to share my office with two other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do too, but just one other person and he's leaving soon, so I'm going to get the office office myself again.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a funny thing, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: Since our sales staff is down to two people now for the games, at least they're in our building, my co-worker is like, yeah, at the end of September I'm thinking about leaving.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, sweet!
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be just me!
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd fucking own everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, uh, Eddie would like to point out his Konami RPG stars, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I said something... You're not even drunk!
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your excuse?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm stupid!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much my excuse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to get through this segment in under two hours, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, you know, because we don't want to get any more.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need any angry iTunes reviews this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: This show is too fucking long.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to download this show because it's too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like my news short.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn on G4.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll get about two minutes of game news in an entire 24-hour period.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know...
[SPEAKER_02]: This month's PlayStation Magazine has a scoop on the new PSP model.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the unit features 8GB of flash memory built in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, there's a video camera still being planned, but no hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seem to recall there was something I read later in the week where Sony said, Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lies.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all lies.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that the official PlayStation Magazine or PSM?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was the official PlayStation Magazine.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell's wrong with these official... Let's just make up news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll give the PSP more attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck, chatroom pointed out I said something that was banned last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: G4.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not banned, I say whatever I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, but you're not drunk, I can use that as an excuse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad run.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I made fun of him, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I still think, it's Borderlands, let it happen again.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way though, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do gotta mention, they are remaking the original Star Trek series.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're redoing all the CG effects in it, so you know that'll be playing on a certain channel soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways... Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways... A little quieter.
[SPEAKER_01]: The PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's news, actually from the Enquirer, which I'm sure is a great source of game news, that the RSX chip in the PlayStation 3, which it originally was set to run at 550, 700 core memory,
[SPEAKER_01]: has been realigned with the expectations that the value will be dropped to $506.50.
[SPEAKER_01]: In other words, being throttled down.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what's that supposed to mean to you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably nothing because...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The slogan for the PlayStation 3 ad campaign has been revealed and it's called This Is Living.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the new catchphrase you're going to hear, at least in Europe, I believe, but I think they're going to use that in the rest of the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's hope not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you take that last story into account, I think the tagline should have been, this is burning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think, I think they already have a catchphrase here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called, we used the Spider-Man logo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Play Beyond?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Play Beyond, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I don't know, somewhere else they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is living.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is living in poverty because they spent all my money on a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Welfare!
[SPEAKER_01]: This is crappy.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: This joke needs to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rayman, of course, is coming to the Wii in the form of Rayman Raving Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_02]: And somehow the rumor got started that this game was going to be Wii exclusive, although I never heard that in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: But needless to say, it was picked up earlier this week that Rayman is not going to be Wii exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I don't know, there's all this confusion going on at Ubisoft because, you know, is Assassin's Creed exclusive and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Supposedly, it's supposed to hit more next-gen systems next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Assassin's Creed, though, is definitely multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, PC, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why the hell shouldn't Rayman be multi-platform?
[SPEAKER_01]: Corey, Ubisoft, I even asked them this.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not exclusive, and it will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, the Wii version is going to be exclusive to the Wii, obviously, because it has a different control system.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: GameLock, Unconstitutional, Mike Hatch
[SPEAKER_01]: His reason for appealing it says, What the act really does is make sure the parents are involved in the decisions of whether their children should play violent or sexually explicit video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I agree with him in that statement because, yeah, parents should be involved with what their kids play.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, I don't think the law should really do much as restricting people because I think it should really be up to the parents.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, the law simply prohibits children 16 years old and younger from buying those types of games.
[SPEAKER_01]: If the parents aren't troubled by their kids playing these games, they can buy them for their children.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that still doesn't make any sense because what if these, say for example, little billies at a, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's illegal to sell alcohol to a minor, but if your mom buys it for you, it's okay if you drink it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of the way that they're phrasing this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which makes this law even more retarded, which there's no reason for the law anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drunami in our chatroom says, enough is enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure if he's talking about what you're saying or all the incessant snakes on a plane jokes that are still going on in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so annoying.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know how I watched that movie this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Macman says, here's the pop culture reference of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Insert animal here on a insert form of transportation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Mad Libs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chainsaw on a dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, if you want to join in the craziness that is our chat room, just head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I guess that's going to do it for Part A of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a little bit of a break and we're going to come right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio to come in Part B. Tonight in Part B of our program.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could beat three right now
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.