All the time we'll be together Cause it's yours and mine Forever we're in this love thing Tomorrow never knows Wise men can tell me so
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be your everything
SYNCHRONIZED LOVE IS WHAT WE GOT TO DO ALL THE TIME WE'LL BE TOGETHER CAUSE IT'S YOURS AND MINE FOREVER WE'RE IN THIS RUNNING I WON'T BE A MAN SO TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA MESS THE NIGHT AWAY ONE AND ONE IS TWO DON'T YOU BE SO CRUEL SYNCHRONIZED LOVE IS WHAT WE GOT TO DO ALL THE
[SPEAKER_25]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_19]: And this is episode number 129 for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_19]: January the 30th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're tuned in to the Bee Money Scene's most repaired radio station of all things, Bee Money.
[SPEAKER_19]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_19]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_19]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate my nose.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate allergies.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you allergic to me?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been like this all day.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is it that you're allergic to?
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not gay people, is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Rob, it's gay people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Also joining us, say hello to TechMassaLoki.
[SPEAKER_19]: I found my knife.
[SPEAKER_19]: Please, don't run around the house with it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Promise me you will not chase DDR Angel around with your knife again this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, I'll have to see about that, but sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: Speaking of DDR Angels, say hello to our special guest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're always here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, now what are you going to call me?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to call you Al.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know, I just was thinking of the old... forget it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_19]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel's the only special guest here tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's not really that special anymore either, because she's always here.
[SPEAKER_19]: So she's just your standard guest.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's more of a standard guest than a special guest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just your pest.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: You wouldn't be a pest, because then when I sprayed the raid on you, it would have gotten rid of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raid?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it's just us.
[SPEAKER_19]: Feeling the love here in the Orange Lounge Radio Studio, especially after a chaotic week last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish I felt the love for my allergy medicine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, this should be a lovely night.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie's extra sassy because of her allergies.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki's got a knife.
[SPEAKER_19]: This should be an interesting show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm just trying to turn this into a round cable, but I think I just broke it.
[SPEAKER_19]: So basically you've got a square cable over there and you're trying to turn it into a round cable.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a ribbon cable.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought, at least in theory, that I could split these down here.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, they're a little thinner than I thought, so when I poked this knife through, instead of actually splitting it, it stripped all the covering on this one wire here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_19]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, well...
[SPEAKER_17]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not really, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can see the action because Loki has decided to go sit in front of the webcam because people say that the webcam is never that exciting.
[SPEAKER_19]: So Loki is cutting things.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just happened to find my knife over here.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's why I sat down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki's cutting things on cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: www.orgsloungeradio.com And if somebody in studio pisses him off enough, they might get cut tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Gotta expect.
[SPEAKER_19]: They can't hear that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't fucking care.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tonight is definitely one of those nights.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want the world to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything good in this world needs to wither and die and stop spreading your goddamn pollen.
[SPEAKER_17]: Please.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the person in the chatroom named Come As You Are.
[SPEAKER_17]: No script.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go ahead and boot their ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_19]: That calls for Instaban.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, we'll handle that.
[SPEAKER_19]: As soon as we come back after these lovely songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: In this break, random 2DX songs from Yonder Pass.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're old 2DX songs that we don't play that often.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because, you know, last week we had people bitching, You guys play the same songs all the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Every week we have to hear Skull.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why don't you play something new?
[SPEAKER_19]: So fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: You get some random stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: We should play Girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let that die already.
[SPEAKER_19]: No!
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, we'll be back after this with more Orange Launch Radio, maybe some Bomani news, some random video game stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie wants to take this show tonight in a really random video game direction, but I don't care, we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: So stay tuned, we'll be back after this with Don't Stop!
I'll take you up, oh sweet baby As years go by
I win!
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: I love that promo because it's the only one we have.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the only promo we have where I get to hear Jamie click like a chicken.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't do any imitations right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except one.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_26]: It's the Grudge Show!
[SPEAKER_19]: Who's soul will Tobio take today?
[SPEAKER_19]: Starring... and... Oh, wow, we're dumb.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, here we are.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another week is upon us here at the Orange Lounge Radio Headquarters.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I don't know, but they're cool, I like them, and I wanted to go see them play live.
[SPEAKER_19]: Me and the boys were gonna go catch the Scissor Sister, like me and, you know, some of my friends, but we... I kind of made a mistake, because when I tried to go in and get tickets, the only tickets that were available were in, like, the back, back, back row.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, it was row, like, double Y in the second balcony, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: It was that far back.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I was like...
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck that, I'm not going to get tickets if I have to sit that far back So I'm going to wait, because usually with concerts, this is a trick a lot of people don't know They'll open up better tickets like a week before Or, you know, sometimes you can get general admission So we were trying to get floor seats, but it never opened up I kept checking every day and I was not able to get better tickets So therefore I'm here tonight, where somewhere in the city, by the bay Scissor Sisters is taking the stage right now, and I'm not there
[SPEAKER_19]: Therefore, I'm a little bit bitter tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I sound a little bit bitter, it's because I could be somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to start off tonight's show as we do every week, playing a little bit of How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been sneezing all fucking day.
[SPEAKER_11]: I made it to level 10 in a week on fucking game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Also known as Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_11]: Been going to school.
[SPEAKER_11]: My teacher's an asshole.
[SPEAKER_11]: More like an elitist snob, but eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just stuff, really.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went bowling yesterday with Iguana Girl and Islander.
[SPEAKER_19]: You went bowling?
[SPEAKER_11]: I went bowling.
[SPEAKER_11]: I scored five strikes my second game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do you do the strike dance?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Drake!
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you do that?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then we went to Mikuni.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: We should start an Orange Lounge Bowling League.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_19]: We could all have orange bowling balls.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'd be cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we could all have this... Rob.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey Rob, once I had a really good idea just like that, you know, it was to put a Russian space station around, you know, orbit, around Earth.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that didn't turn out very well.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let Jamie finish her week.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've been sneezing all day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woke up with a cat on my head.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I just, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not very often that Jamie wakes up with pussy in her face.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: That wasn't funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought it was funny and I didn't even hear the... I was laughing before the joke.
[SPEAKER_19]: The reaction we got in studio when I said that, just Jamie, she's got this very dead look on her face.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, you know, kind of like... You know, she's got that look on her face right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's kind of leaning back.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's staring off into space, staring at the ceiling, going, you know, I don't want to be here, type thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then when I said that, you know... And she doesn't often get pussy on her face.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's just kind of...
[SPEAKER_19]: Reaches over and grabs the mic and goes, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, my cat didn't poop.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's sick.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sometimes I wish we were a TV show.
[SPEAKER_19]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've taken two doses of Advil cold sinus, a dose of Benadryl, and two doses of Tylenol allergy sinus.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm drugged, upset, I ate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Three Lindered Chocolate Balls on the way here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Were they salty chocolate balls?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, hush.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were dark chocolate.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I go look at my friends list to see freaking sluts on my friends list on my live journal.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got sluts on my friends list too, but that's just how they... But I need pictures of sluts.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I'm like, these are actual people.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just have to accept them.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the way they are.
[SPEAKER_17]: I never get sluts on my friends list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my life is miserable.
[SPEAKER_19]: Join a couple gay live journal communities.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can get tons of sluts on your friends' page.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need... Wow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_19]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, my week was okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Didn't really do too much.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Friday, Christopher brought over the parts for his PC, so I built that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that was fun, until I couldn't figure out why I wasn't booting.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's because... Now...
[SPEAKER_17]: The motherboard I bought has actually two different chipsets on it, you know, so you can run the older Athlon processors, and you can run the new 64-bit ones, the ones beside, you know, above 3.2 gigahertz or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, anyways, I had the processor in the right one, but I had the RAM in the wrong set of slots there, so it wasn't booting up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Finally figured that out after about six hours, and then...
[SPEAKER_17]: Loaded that all up.
[SPEAKER_17]: It looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then on my computer, which is sitting in the middle of the room right now, I installed the motherboard in that and cut the rest of the case.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I'm pretty much ready to go with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I probably should set it up to install everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I was messing around with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then played lots of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_17]: And...
[SPEAKER_17]: They didn't do too much else other than that.
[SPEAKER_17]: The first night when Christopher brought his computer over on Friday, I stayed up until 6 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then last night I stayed up until 6 in the morning playing Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I'm kind of like my whole schedule is messed up right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've been staying up way too late.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you have to work tomorrow, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's going to be great though because my co-worker's quitting.
[SPEAKER_17]: So now they're going to be panicking.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's great because I'm just an observer in their panic.
[SPEAKER_17]: So it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then this week I have to go see the Kings in floor seats.
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate the Kings, but I'm taking my mom because whatever, I couldn't really do much of these tickets, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, DT says I should invest in a Mac Mini.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I'm sorry, I already have a toaster.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't need a piece of shit computer that's small.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why do you hate Apple computers so much?
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, I remember the day I brought home my iPod, you were like... Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll tell you why.
[SPEAKER_17]: Back in the day when I had to do fucking school assignments at the Mac Lab at our school, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll tell you what, those things are a piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: You put the disc in, the whole thing explodes.
[SPEAKER_17]: That is pretty much how reliable Macintosh computers are.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're computers for idiots!
[SPEAKER_19]: But I remember in the computer school lab, the Macs, when you turn them on, you'd see the little picture of the computer and it had the little happy face.
[SPEAKER_17]: You don't buy computers because they're cute!
[SPEAKER_17]: You buy them because they work and they're functional.
[SPEAKER_17]: You don't buy fucking cute computers.
[SPEAKER_17]: You shouldn't choose a computer because, oh, it'll match my curtains.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, but it'll still get on the internet, and the fact that it matches the curtains is a plus.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, you know, an old 386 computer will get on the internet too, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not going to be using that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're good if you're a graphic artist.
[SPEAKER_11]: A-ha, a-ha, good graphics.
[SPEAKER_11]: And actually, you can link, for every Mac you have linked up, it will increase the entire processing power of the entire unit because of the dual processing system.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can actually get more power out of a Mac than you can out of a PC.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can do that with anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they do the video editing really easy, really easy.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can film the kitty.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can film your kitty cat and then really easily put it on your Mac and you can make little videos like my kitty and string it all together and then you put music in the background.
[SPEAKER_19]: So cute and so easy on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can do that with Windows too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but everything crashes in Windows.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, not everything crashes in Windows.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everything crashes in Windows.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_17]: I love Windows.
[SPEAKER_17]: Look at all those fucking games for the Macs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh wait, no there isn't!
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right, because they suck!
[SPEAKER_19]: Now wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I'll tell you what's cool about Macs, are the laptops, the little iBooks.
[SPEAKER_19]: The little apple, when you use it on the back, it glows.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, let's say you ever have to be in the dark.
[SPEAKER_19]: The apple will glow, and it gives you... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_19]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it's cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have you ever been to the Apple Store at the mall?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's blinding!
[SPEAKER_19]: Here at the local mall, yeah, they have an Apple Store.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I don't know how they light that thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think they actually took a little chunk of the sun and put it inside the Apple Store because it is so freaking bright in there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's like, you know... No, no, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am... I will never, ever, ever... I'm going down the record stands.
[SPEAKER_17]: I will never own...
[SPEAKER_17]: Anything that's made by Apple.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not buying an iPod.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not buying a computer.
[SPEAKER_17]: I will not buy a laptop made by them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, Apple is a fully unsubsidiary of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Did I say Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_17]: I said Apple.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: You should hold your tongue and say Apple.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Apple.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, I think I graduated from elementary school a while ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, this is coming from someone who said that the chair was not green.
[SPEAKER_19]: The chair's green.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think the chair's green.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's mostly black.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's green!
[SPEAKER_17]: If you take green, or black, and add a little bit of green to that, that is mainly black.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a night green.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's black, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: I will take a piece of that chair into a paint match store and we will settle this debate.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's fucking black.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just like my trench coat.
[SPEAKER_17]: My trench coat's blue, but it's fucking black.
[SPEAKER_17]: It looks black, therefore it's black, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care if it has a hint of green in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's still black.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on, hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually is more green.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on, hold on, I'm working.
[SPEAKER_19]: No way, I want you to rant a little more here.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just, you know, finding some music here.
[SPEAKER_19]: The chair is green.
[SPEAKER_17]: Black.
[SPEAKER_17]: Green.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a goddamn chair!
[SPEAKER_17]: If Justin Timberlake can be black, that chair can be black, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you finished?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_19]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob made my tongue numb.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even want to know how that happened.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry, I won't bite so hard next time.
[SPEAKER_19]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_10]: Stupid Altoids.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that was your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, when I was on, you guys weren't, because you guys had to work.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again, I had school, so... Not much happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm supposed to say hi to Mikey, so hi Mikey!
[SPEAKER_10]: otherwise known as BRPOhiovaMoney That's quick.
[SPEAKER_19]: My week and my day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really, not a whole lot going on.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did play a little bit of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had days off, actually, this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: I took Monday and Tuesday off of work, and oh my god, I had this big list of things I was going to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was going to go to the mall, and I was going to go shopping, and there was all this stuff I wanted to buy, like new socks and underwear and things.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was going to buy all this stuff at the mall, and then, let's see, I was going to go to Ikea one day, and then I was going to clean my room from top to bottom.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had this big project where I was going to totally redo my room and clean it,
[SPEAKER_19]: and I didn't get any of that done because I was leveling in Final Fantasy all day both days.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think I'm just going to uninstall it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then I won't be tempted to play it anymore.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm seriously wondering how much would I get done if Final Fantasy XI wasn't installed.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what though, seriously, if it wasn't that, it would be some other game.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'd go right back to playing Final Fantasy X or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki says, at least I'd finish the damn game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: And now they're yelling at me, I can't uninstall the game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_19]: What else is going on in Rob's world?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yesterday we went out to sushi, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: We went to wasabi, which is cool, because when you walk in the door, they all yell at you from behind the bar, WASABI!
[SPEAKER_19]: When you walk in, WASABI!
[SPEAKER_07]: WASABI!
[SPEAKER_19]: And it always scares me.
[SPEAKER_19]: It always scares me when I walk in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like, you know, I walk in.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to walk into a nice little sushi restaurant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you sure they're not saying it ashamase?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It always sounds like wasabi.
[SPEAKER_19]: I always thought they were saying the name of the restaurant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, because I know Mikuni does it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like any time you go into an establishment, they're supposed to go ashamase, which is like welcome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else?
[SPEAKER_19]: I had this whole list of things I was going to talk about, but I can't think of any, so I guess we'll just have to move on.
[SPEAKER_19]: I wish I had some exciting DDR story to tell, but I really don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't been to the arcade in a while.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm still waiting for them to set up 2DX.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're supposed to be getting 2DX here locally.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was supposed to happen, what, four weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess they're waiting on a part, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki has a comment.
[SPEAKER_17]: It'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_17]: They'll just keep talking and hinting at it.
[SPEAKER_17]: The monitor will constantly be in trend to us.
[SPEAKER_17]: It'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I took fucking pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But there's no monitor.
[SPEAKER_19]: The monitor's gone.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: They should, like, ghetto rig it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Pimp my 2DX machine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, what was that idea for a TV show you were talking about earlier this week?
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Pimp my rig...
[SPEAKER_17]: And what would happen on this show?
[SPEAKER_17]: They would take someone's piece of shit computer and they'd make it pretty.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they'd case mod it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kind of what you did to Christopher's computer this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's just building a computer.
[SPEAKER_17]: But yeah, more or less.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just, um, I could see G4 doing this because they're retarded and want to rip off ideas from people, so why not?
[SPEAKER_19]: Our show's come to a halt because I'm trying to give Jamie chocolate right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Gotta get your priorities in straight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chocolate first.
[SPEAKER_19]: Legend of Zaku says he needs someone to pimp his PA skills.
[SPEAKER_19]: Practice, practice.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what it takes.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want to join our chatroom and make random comments that we might read on air, join our chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on chat, and it's lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: El Mullet made it funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: He says once they pimp it, they could call it an apple.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're not removing all functionality out of it or replacing the innards with a toaster.
[SPEAKER_17]: I remember the old GeForce, the transparent toasters.
[SPEAKER_17]: Those are great.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_19]: When we come back from this break, I guess we'll talk about some DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's some stuff going on in the Babani scene this week, and I suppose we can talk about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Might as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: In this break, what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah, and Jamie has this really random Castlevania thing she wants to share with you guys, so we'll hook that up for later.
[SPEAKER_19]: In this break, we're going to play some PlayStation 2DX songs, because I want to hear Cracker.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
Lens Flasher and Destroyer
and Torture and Destroy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and Jamie...
[SPEAKER_19]: wants to do something for you guys here.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is a little bit random.
[SPEAKER_19]: It doesn't really have to do with Bomani per se, but turn on the satanic music we've got there in the background.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not satanic.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's churchy.
[SPEAKER_19]: It sounds satanic to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually feeling better now that I stand up.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, we've always made fun of Castlevania Symphony of the Night before the bad voice acting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Right, and this has to do with the podcast from last week.
[SPEAKER_19]: This kind of relates into the podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you listen to it, you'd know what we were talking about.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the plug I was going to make.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you haven't checked out the podcast yet...
[SPEAKER_19]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_19]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on Orange Lounge Radio to go.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a whole extra 20-minute show that we do, and we talk about random shit like this, such as the voice acting in Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_19]: And a lot of you guys have played this game.
[SPEAKER_19]: God, this song scares the shit out of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: A lot of you... Listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is holy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I didn't know it was going through.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's already going through.
[SPEAKER_19]: They can hear it.
[SPEAKER_19]: The holiest of internet radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to go ahead and get started playing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, you know the bad voice acting in Symphony of the Night is like, Die, monster.
[SPEAKER_19]: You don't belong in this world.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's really lame.
[SPEAKER_19]: So anyway, Jamie said she wanted to play for you all how much better the Japanese voice acting is.
[SPEAKER_19]: So she's going to do that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, this is the cool thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you're listening live on Sunday night, which I know obviously right now you are, but some of you guys hear this show on the rebroadcast over on DDR Freak Radio and all that stuff, you can actually see it on our webcam, www.orangehornsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would appreciate it, however, though, if people save copies of them, I will put this up somewhere for people to see the images.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, Misty is our usual webcam whore, and she's not here tonight, so hopefully somebody else is saving pictures.
[SPEAKER_11]: Save the pictures, and after the show, I'll give you my email address.
[SPEAKER_27]: One gay man.
[SPEAKER_27]: One angsty woman and one angry man.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Coming to a theater near you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see the story on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know how they give you the whole story?
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually is different, but it's still written in English.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they say it as your... Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, you actually have to play the game for a little bit to get to the opening.
[SPEAKER_19]: You just wanted to play games on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't this an Akira Yamaoka track?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't this great?
[SPEAKER_19]: You guys are tuned into an internet radio station, and you're not even watching somebody play games.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Destroy!
[SPEAKER_13]: This is not the world you live in!
[SPEAKER_13]: I will not be revived by my own power.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will be revived by greedy humans.
[SPEAKER_13]: Power is the only justice.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's your own way of saying it.
[SPEAKER_14]: People seek each other under the same belief, unite, and walk.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, humans have developed by desire, and have been defeated by faith.
[SPEAKER_13]: Humans cannot be defeated by power alone.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uyamae,
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, that was very scary.
[SPEAKER_14]: And now you're doing the little battle in the beginning, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: I recognize one part.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's when the little glass breaks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I remember that in the English version.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is a man?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_19]: How cool he says what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Hydro Storm.
That was very hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: Symphony of the Night is like the sex... I mean, I know this isn't Symphony of the Night, but I'm used to Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_19]: It has the sexiest music.
[SPEAKER_19]: God, the music is so good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Translation, because they changed it.
[SPEAKER_11]: After a series of epic battles, Richter Velma finally succeeded in destroying Count Dracula, the ancient vampire who had been the most recently resurrected by the Dark Priest Shaft.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, one night, four years later, under the bright glare of the moon, Richter mysteriously vanished.
[SPEAKER_11]: With no idea of where to begin her search, Maria Renard set out to look for him.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was then that fate intervened.
[SPEAKER_11]: Castlevania, The Castle of Dracula, which is rumored to appear only once every century, suddenly and mysteriously materialized.
[SPEAKER_11]: More text.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, powerful forces were at work in the life of a man named Alucard.
[SPEAKER_11]: The very same Alucard who had previously teamed up with Ralph C. Belmont
[SPEAKER_11]: to destroy his immortal father, Vlad Tepesov, aka Count Dracula.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alucard, in order to rid the world of his own first bloodline, sealed off his powers and entered into what was supposed to be an eternal slumber.
[SPEAKER_11]: At the end of this is the line that they pissed off that they changed.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now that sleep had been disturbed, Alucard is aware of the evil that has once again arisen in his homeland.
[SPEAKER_11]: The time has come once more for the forces of good and evil to engage in their ancient battle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dracula's castle beckons for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: and perhaps none but that bright and glaring moon can say who will triumph.
[SPEAKER_11]: They changed that line.
[SPEAKER_11]: That pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is just like watching Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_20]: And the secret ingredient?
[SPEAKER_19]: Potato!
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me bite this pepper.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it says Dracula X. That's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is actually supposed to be on the 32X.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, all I gotta say is, uh... Who's the man?
[SPEAKER_20]: The resurrected Dracula?
[SPEAKER_20]: Shit!
[SPEAKER_20]: Can you dig it?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're a dumbass.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Gave me just one excuse to play video games during the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'd actually never heard that, the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think maybe you sent me bits and pieces, like on Wave.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had a file of Alucard, though, because I figured we wouldn't be getting to the part with Alucard, so I brought a file with him.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you want me to play that little Wave sample?
[SPEAKER_11]: In just a sec.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: A little bit there.
Ugh.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be talking about Bomani News at some point this evening, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: But let's face it, you know, there hasn't been a new game lately.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, actually, there was a big new game this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: We don't really have an excuse to not be talking Bomani.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll get to it, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: We will, we will.
[SPEAKER_19]: Of course, Castlevania, I mean, a lot of you guys that play DDR, I know a lot of you guys are into Castlevania, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you're not, you should be.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because the music's good, the gameplay's good.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: The file of Alucard?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: You want it now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But see, isn't the voice acting better?
[SPEAKER_19]: But see, there's something about the American voice acting that's very charming.
[SPEAKER_11]: Die, monster!
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't belong in this world!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, excuse me, Richter.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, boy, oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki's going to hook the webcam back up so you can stare at the couch again.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to check on my laundry.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Meanwhile, we're going to talk a little bit about some Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_19]: There actually was a little bit of news this week, and we can talk about that.
[SPEAKER_19]: This isn't Bomani.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I'll talk about the Castlevania thing real fast.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you know that Konami was making this big announcement on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_19]: They were going to make a big announcement on January 27th, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well...
[SPEAKER_19]: It turned out that the big announcement was just their 2005 lineup.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, you know, you can see all the new Konami games that are coming out in 2005.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, of course, as suspected, and if you were paying attention to OrangeLawnRadio.com throughout the week, you already knew this, but one of the games they announced was Castlevania Curse of Darkness, which is going to be a brand new PlayStation 2 title.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's in addition to the DS Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_19]: So it's going to be a big year for Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then they announced some other games.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ninja Turtles game is in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else was there?
[SPEAKER_19]: There was a new Frogger game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and of course, Metal Gear Acid for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_19]: We all knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_19]: So they announced all these games.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then what was weird is that the same day, the exact same day,
[SPEAKER_19]: in unrelated news, but they put out a press release on this.
[SPEAKER_19]: They did not announce any new DDR titles.
[SPEAKER_19]: They did not announce any Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: They did not announce Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_19]: They didn't announce DDR with Mario for the US.
[SPEAKER_19]: They didn't announce any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: But what they did do is that they published this press release saying, Hey, guess what, kids?
[SPEAKER_19]: Dance Dance Revolution sold 1.2 million copies in North America in 2004.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, that's across all titles, so we're talking Extreme and Ultramix 2 combined, along with Ultramix 1 and Max 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: All those combined, all those sales totaled 1.2 million, but really, for a game that requires an additional peripheral to play, not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_19]: Certainly higher sales than any Power Pad game ever got, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: So that was 1.2 million copies in 2004.
[SPEAKER_19]: since DDR debuted in 2001 all the way back on Dance Dance Revolution on the Playstation 2.5 million copies of DDR games for the home consoles in the US sold not too shabby right?
[SPEAKER_19]: But then they didn't announce a new DDR game to go along with that.
[SPEAKER_19]: They just said, gee, isn't DDR great?
[SPEAKER_19]: But honestly, think about it, people.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are they going to submit this press release and then say, oh, and by the way, because of DDR's great success, no more DDR games in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're pulling the plug on DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going out on the top.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're like a TV sitcom like Friends or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to go out while we're still on top.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think so, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not quite how it works.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can bet your sweet ass that we will see new games on PlayStation and Xbox this year, and we will probably see that GameCube game as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it's just a foregone conclusion.
[SPEAKER_19]: We just have to sit here and twiddle our thumbs until the details are announced, which probably won't be until E3.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anything you want to add to that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: What's a GameCube?
[SPEAKER_19]: Smartass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie, anything you want to add to that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Aren't you excited about new DDRM consoles?
[SPEAKER_15]: I am, if I... Yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, this is what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_19]: How many copies of a video game do you think it would take to sell to call it a success?
[SPEAKER_19]: A success... How many copies does a successful video game sell?
[SPEAKER_19]: Two.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like 100,000?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's decent.
[SPEAKER_11]: 100,000 would be really decent, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Now...
[SPEAKER_19]: If one out of every ten people that bought DDR 2004 were to support a, I don't know, another music game that Konami would put out, say, Beatmania 2DX, if you could convince one out of every ten people that bought DDR that Beatmania 2DX is a good idea, one out of every ten, you'd have a successful game on your hands.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you could say, convince those same one out of ten people to, I don't know, say support an online,
[SPEAKER_17]: Music game related radio show, we would be rich.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Man can dream.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whereas the figure is actually more like one out of every million actually support that internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because that would make it what, two?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, that's about how many listeners we have, two.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: And everyone else is expecting to hear Tomosuke and the rest of the Orange Lounge Radio band because they think that this shows... You know, there's been so many people out there that have actually thought that Orange Lounge Radio is related to Orange Lounge that we finally put a disclaimer on the website at the very, very bottom in little text.
[SPEAKER_19]: Note.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio is not affiliated with Orange Lounge the band from DDR and 2DX and all that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tomosuke does have his own site.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's out there.
[SPEAKER_19]: We had a link to it once.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just put Orange Lounge into Google and it's the site that comes up before Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Before I let my pet peeve bug me anymore, it's Tomosuke.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm white.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know a lot of people have this fear that if they bring out 2DX in America, it's going to be fucked up.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I kind of don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just really want them to do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even if it isn't as good as 2DX 7th, 8th, 9th style that's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even if it's not that good, give us some new songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Give us something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Something to make it US.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'd be happy.
[SPEAKER_19]: A lot of people would be very, very happy if you do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's my plea.
[SPEAKER_19]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Any other comments on Beatmania 2DX USA and the hopes and dreams of seeing it happen?
[SPEAKER_19]: We wish, we wish.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not gonna happen, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: See, now Jamie... Listen up, pessimist.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie, you usually prefer the Japanese mixes to American mixes, usually.
[SPEAKER_19]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you still would want to see a 2DX US mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just to have it out here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another 2DX game to waste my money on, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still have to find a copy of Fourth Style somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I understand what they're saying in the chatroom there.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're saying, if you were to bring 2DX to the US, it would have to appeal to the US gamers.
[SPEAKER_19]: You only have to appeal to one out of every ten people that bought DDR last year to make this game a success.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_19]: One out of every ten should not be that hard.
[SPEAKER_19]: If Donkey Konga can be a success, 2DX can be a success.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know this in my heart.
[SPEAKER_19]: A lot of 2DX elitists I'm not saying everybody that plays 2DX is a 2DX elitist but a lot of 2DX elitists out there would have you believe that the masses don't want to eat up a game like 2DX.
[SPEAKER_19]: But whenever I play 2DX in the arcades there's always these people that stand around kind of watching going ooh ah just like with DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's got a lot of that same appeal to it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be back
[SPEAKER_19]: Allie Japan
[SPEAKER_19]: And we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
You gotta move it, move it now
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Whoops, forgot to queue up a promo there that says we're coming back.
[SPEAKER_19]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me put something up there.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_19]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now we can come back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know the DDR Freak was down earlier this evening, but it's back up now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess they were having some server problems.
[SPEAKER_19]: DDR Freak was down, and then didn't you try to get on Bomani Style, and they were down too?
[SPEAKER_19]: Everybody's broken!
[SPEAKER_19]: They all broke!
[SPEAKER_19]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_19]: But now the DDR Freak is back up.
[SPEAKER_19]: I went over to the Mod of the Month thread, and I voted for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: I voted for you for Mod of the Month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not going to win.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know you're not because a bunch of people went in there and flooded for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_19]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: You should still vote for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, I was asked to pass along our buddy Explicit, who's usually here at the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, he has a lot of FUs.
[SPEAKER_19]: He sent along a little private message to me over on Orange Lounge Radio, and he wanted me to share some stuff with you guys about the upcoming tournament that's happening on, what, Saturday?
[SPEAKER_19]: This Saturday, Saturday, February 5th.
[SPEAKER_19]: Piss is happening this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_19]: Paradise Island, SmackDown Sackdown...
[SPEAKER_17]: If I have a lot to drink tonight, piss might happen even earlier.
[SPEAKER_19]: The Paradise Island Sacktown Smackdown is happening this Saturday, February 5th.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they're going to have the P.A.
[SPEAKER_19]: and Demonium, like Pan-Demonium, get it?
[SPEAKER_19]: P.A.
[SPEAKER_19]: and Demonium?
[SPEAKER_19]: Pan-Demonium?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's their version of Perfect Attack.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they're going to have a Showstopper Freestyle Contest, that should be fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, get your rice rockets ready, an initial D Grand Prix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Joy and joy, that should be fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Golden showers for all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Explicit asked me to pass along some updates to the tournament.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've actually lowered some of the prices, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if you were thinking about it, they've actually lowered the price to get into freestyle and try to pull up the latest update.
[SPEAKER_19]: And let's see, freestyle price has been reduced to $10, only $8 if you're pre-registered.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if you want to pre-register, go to DDR Freak, now that it's back up, go to DDR Tournament Chat, or whatever that forum's called, and look for the Paradise Island thread.
[SPEAKER_19]: And yes, I know that's a local tournament, so those of you guys on the East Coast probably are not feasibly going to be going to this, but I did promise we would put that little local plug.
[SPEAKER_19]: And at some point during the tournament, I do plan on making a cameo.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm gonna dabble in the piss for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you gonna get your hands wet?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm gonna get my hands wet at piss.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, we'll stop.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_19]: Looking forward to piss.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: But don't call it that in front of him because he'll get really mad.
[SPEAKER_19]: He was a really good sport here at the show the other week.
[SPEAKER_19]: DDR scene this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, they announced their new Dancing Stage game, which I remember had a really dumb name to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not Dancing Stage Fusion, it's like Dancing Stage Happy Fun Time.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know what the hell it's called, but it's like something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, and it's got all the crap that was in... It's Dancing Stage Fusion.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it's not Dancing Stage Fusion.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's called something else.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on, I'm going to look at these pictures here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, Dancing Stage Dayglo Mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Dayglo Mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was what somebody said they should call it.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's not what they really call it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because if you go and you look at the pictures of the cabinet... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's Dancing Stage Fusion.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what somebody on Freak said it should be called because of the way it looked.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dancing Stage Fusion
[SPEAKER_19]: 321 Stars, A, A Stupid Barber, Across the Nightmare, AM3P, Be Lovin', Believe, Can't Stop Falling in Love, Speed Mix, Candy Star, Colors for Extreme, Destiny Lovers, Dive, Dynamite Rave, Soda Mix, Firefly, Familiar Feeling, whatever that is, Healing Vision, Angelic Mix, Heaven and Earth, which I think is a licensed song, It's Rain and Men, you know that one, Kakumei,
[SPEAKER_19]: Keep on moving.
[SPEAKER_19]: Kids in America, Ladies Night, La Senorita and La Senorita Virtual.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Ladies Night, we do want to mention is Atomic Kitten.
[SPEAKER_19]: Make It Better, Make It Better So Real Mix, Mickey, Orion 7-8 Civ Mix, Paranoia Max Dirty Mix, Rapper's Delight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, that was in Dancing Stage Fusion.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know, how cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Still in My Heart, Sync, Tomorrow Perfume, Tough Enough, Trip Machine.
[SPEAKER_17]: try to love you une, deux, trois waiting for tonight you're not here and your reign the rage mix and that's not all of them that's just what was on the demo cabinet that they had that's not everything that's going to be on the mix there's a lot more stuff so it looks pretty good so far but I mean granted it's just exactly like Dancing Stage Fusion or DDR Extreme you know the home versions
[SPEAKER_17]: But hey, it's something new, so, yay!
[SPEAKER_17]: I wonder if they're going to bring anything over here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_17]: Who knows, you might get lucky, someone might import it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, people import stuff from, you know, Korea and, you know, China and Japan and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why not from Europe?
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, that's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, um, no real, I don't think they really announced when, um...
[SPEAKER_17]: They're going to be releasing that, but we're thinking probably the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I think it'll be sooner than that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know they were showing In The Groove at this show, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that was right.
[SPEAKER_17]: The In The Groove was being shown by, I forget what company it was, they had boasted that their, what was it, they have, at the show they had gotten 200 orders for In The Groove
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't want to have another In The Groove debate on this show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe they'll fix some of the problems with 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: The longer and longer this goes on, the more and more I'm buying into the theory of Konami, that's what you get for not putting out any more arcade mixes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, they deserve in the groove to be out there at this point.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I still think if they try to release in the groove on a home console, there's going to be issues.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still say that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you can argue all you want, but I'm welcome to my opinion.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't wait for them to try.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hope they do try to release on a home console so we can have this debate and get it over with.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_17]: If anything, to watch a show like X-Play rip it apart.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if they would.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, the casual gamer doesn't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Right?
[SPEAKER_19]: True.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's how pieces of crap like Britney's Dance Beat get out there and get played.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, people call Pump It Up that dance game and don't realize the differences between that... You know, whatever happened to fucking Pump It Up coming to the Japanese PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a game that should be, you know, fucking brought over here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, it's doing well in, like, all these other countries, but, you know, no one wants to bring it over here, obviously, because of the lawsuits and shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: But yet, stuff like, you know, fucking...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't understand how one can be okay and the other one can't.
[SPEAKER_17]: You see what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, I don't get it, but nothing's going on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, I promised that we would open up the Skype line, so that's exactly what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want to call into the show, head on over to www.orangelonsradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_19]: I do request, Skype actually upgraded to version 1.1 earlier this week, or no, I'm sorry, actually it was earlier this month, it was a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they have some new features in it, so make sure you upgrade the latest version.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Agent Izaku here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello, Izaku, how are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I'm just looking over, you know, now that DDR Freak went back up again.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was looking over the Dancing States thread, and apparently, to my surprise, during the... For some reason, during the whole event, I looked at, you know, I saw two pictures.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of a person, you know, one of the, you know, Konami's area where they had fusion...
[SPEAKER_12]: It's one of the most recent posts on the thread, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, and I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought we were supposed to be behind something like this 100%.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, from the looks of it, it looks like there was some type of event going on at the Pump It Up booth.
[SPEAKER_19]: And so all those people were there.
[SPEAKER_19]: And whereas Dancing Stage just kind of had the machine out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess, I don't know if I should accept that as an excuse.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, now that we have, now that DDR itself already hit at least 1.3 billion last year.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what, Zach, I just want to say, for all you know, I mean, we don't know because we weren't there, but for all we know, there was a topless girl playing Pump It Up at that moment.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really?
[SPEAKER_19]: For all you know.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you don't know why all those people were there, but that's one possible reason.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you look at the picture, they all kind of have that, ooh, boobies look on their face.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, now that DDR has already sold 1.2 million last year, totaling up to 2.5 million, which, if I'm not mistaken, should almost count for a quarter of all DDR sales worldwide.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't have the latest figures, but sure
[SPEAKER_12]: And so, I don't know, there has to be something done, some sort of action.
[SPEAKER_12]: We already know people, you know, who can make it happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just gotta, you know, push, you know, we gotta basically, you know, we just gotta stay on top of this 110%.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_19]: I hear what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, you're preaching to the choir here.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're preaching to the choir here.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not gonna disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_19]: You are absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that we need to be doing a new USA Mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have just...
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that the people who have made it happen previously are trying to make it happen again.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know this for a fact, but I would assume.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know that there's people that love DDR trying to make it happen.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't doubt that they're trying again, but sometimes it's a matter of it's just got to be the right time.
[SPEAKER_19]: You've got to get the people to say the right thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what it's going to take.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you don't see Silent Scope websites out there with 50,000 dedicated members.
[SPEAKER_19]: To my knowledge, there is no internet radio station dedicated to the game Silent Scope.
[SPEAKER_19]: And there's two for DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can definitely start.
[SPEAKER_19]: We could start one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly, but this is a cult following.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have a game here that...
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the thing, you have a cult following.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have people who love this game to the point that it consumes their lives to an extent.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they basically have purpose to make something happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: And in this case, we could go after a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically.
[SPEAKER_12]: I doubt I would see something that perfect, but you know, it's worth a shot.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think the most we can do as fans right now, continue to support the games.
[SPEAKER_19]: When the home mixes come out, buy the new home mixes as they come out, support the arcade mixes that are already out there, and just keep showing that there's...
[SPEAKER_19]: Demand out there for dance games.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I hate to say it, but maybe supporting In The Groove, God, I can't believe I just said that, would show folks that there's still a demand out there for dance games.
[SPEAKER_19]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, I still have mixed feelings on In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I'm going to let you go, buddy, because we've got connection issues.
[SPEAKER_19]: I understand what you're saying, and I hope we can all band together in one happy Bamani Rainbow family.
[SPEAKER_19]: Take care, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think he was behind.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think he, like, it was weird.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think he was hearing us about five seconds after we said something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe that's a weird Skype thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anything you guys want to add to that?
[SPEAKER_19]: No?
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, Skype line's open again if somebody else wants to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_19]: We certainly would love to hear what you have to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: Otherwise, I guess we're going to go ahead and get into the Orange Launch Radio cage match next.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be something exciting.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm checking out what's going on in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, the chat room just kind of saying, didn't so-and-so say that there was going to be a new mix?
[SPEAKER_19]: Didn't so-and-so say this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, until Konami puts out the press release, it's all hearsay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_19]: This is Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_19]: Can you hear me, buddy?
[SPEAKER_19]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wanted to say hey to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope she's feeling better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just chilling out, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie's in the kitchen getting herself a drink so she can feel a little better there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anything on your mind?
[SPEAKER_19]: Any comments, response to things we've been talking about in the show so far?
[SPEAKER_19]: Such as the new Europe DDR mix?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There just needs to be a new DDR for the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just bogus that they would just drop it like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, there will be a new U.S.
[SPEAKER_19]: mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just the home.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's kind of focused on home right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, if you think about it, though, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_19]: arcade mix has stopped a long, long time ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: They really did.
[SPEAKER_19]: We only ever had one true U.S.
[SPEAKER_19]: arcade mix, and it was kind of a mediocre game at best.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it's the Japanese ones that have really stopped.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was sort of shaky there, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they could do, if they really wanted to, they could do what they wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could come out with a good one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you know what's interesting, though, is that you don't see Konami of Japan putting out this press release going, ooh, DDR Festival sold 1.2 million copies.
[SPEAKER_19]: You didn't see that press release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just seems like a lot of this stuff is going down, like those websites that got shut down the other night.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR UK and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: What...
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you talking about DDRUK getting shut down?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, those websites getting shut down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but we know that it has nothing to do with Konami.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was more of the MP3s in the songpacks, at least assumably.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, we're making a lot of assumptions here, but assumably, it was the MP3s that were inside the songpacks.
[SPEAKER_19]: And remember that, if I'm not mistaken, Loki, correct me if I'm wrong, I wasn't a big DDRUK user, but they didn't just have the official songpacks.
[SPEAKER_19]: They had fan ones too, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Am I correct?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they did contests and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: They didn't have those, but they had links to the Shoei, whatever, his little sim file museum stuff, which I'm sure had a lot of crap in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would just, I think Step Mania and stuff like that, people are going to get into that more and move that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, because that's customizable to how you want it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I agree, and I think a lot of the cult scene is kind of in there as it is, but until Step Mania is something that's over the counter, I don't think it's a real threat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that is true, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: It just kind of keeps the cult thing going, and I think that's why Konami hasn't stepped in and done anything about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I think if Step Mania were to be something that was sold over the counter, well, then there'd be an issue.
[SPEAKER_19]: But then again, what is in the groove?
[SPEAKER_19]: In the groove is Step Mania, basically.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: so I don't know but until and that's why I say that I don't think Konami is going to do anything about In The Groove unless they try to invade on the home market but of course In The Groove says they have the patents okay whatever fine I'm not going to dispute that but I do think if they try to go to the home route there's going to be a bit of clashing heads there
[SPEAKER_19]: Because that's Konami's baby right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's obvious they're putting out press releases on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know it's their baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they have to be planning to do something to put out a press release.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that would just be silly to be like, we sold a million copies and then drop it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was just a little disappointed that they didn't announce anything the same day.
[SPEAKER_19]: We all know that DDR Mario is in the making in Japan.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, why not tell us US folks we're going to get it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because we better be getting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not liking the DDR Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's going to be a little bogus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Mario's a little played out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was sort of in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_19]: Regardless, love or hate Mario, it's more DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, any other comments you got for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's pretty much about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wanted to call in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my first time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, thank you for calling in.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's your virgin phone call.
[SPEAKER_19]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're glad to initiate you into Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Jamie, you may have missed it because you were in the kitchen, but he did say he hopes you feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we don't want Jamie to die on air.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would not be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, that'd be sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd be interesting for ratings.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have a good one, Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for calling in, bud.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: New callers.
[SPEAKER_19]: We like hearing from new people once in a while.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie's head exploded in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_19]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_19]: I just heard this giant achoo.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, we're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_19]: remember boys and girls in order to participate in the cage match you must be in our chat room www.orangeloungeradio.com click on chat the way the cage match works we play three songs for your listening pleasure or listening displeasure you pick your favorite the winning song per the chat room goes into rotation all week long here on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music and More program which plays 24 hours a day 7 days a week when we're not live
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_19]: So it's last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's been winning two weeks in a row now.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if it wins tonight, that'll be week number three, halfway to retirement.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see if we can do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's a clip.
[SPEAKER_19]: Song number one, Echo Image, Endless Day.
We made back in time so we can try
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: Song number one in tonight's cage match, Echo Image, Endless Day.
[SPEAKER_19]: A clip of that there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's see if it does it again tonight, but we've got to get the challengers in.
[SPEAKER_19]: First up is DarkSakura's pick.
[SPEAKER_19]: What did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Some Eurobeat song.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's been a while since we've had some Eurobeat in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Dream, their version of Night of Fire, but it's a different mix of the sort of rock mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, Dream originally did Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I thought they did.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that was the guy who did Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Dream, I think, redid it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Night of Fire, Dream of Dream Mix
Night Dog Fire Night Dog Fire Night Dog Fire
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't say those sweet, kind words.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it'll make me feel like I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even at times like this, stay by my side.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give you strength, I'll protect you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you'll always be there for me.
Because I want to sing with you and be with you.
Night of Fire  Night of Fire  Night of Fire
[SPEAKER_07]: Night of Fire Night of Fire Night of Fire Night of Fire
Night of Fire Night of Fire
[SPEAKER_19]: Alrighty, that was song number two, Dream with Night of Fire, the Dream of Dream Mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did we here in the studio find that song to be dreamy?
[SPEAKER_19]: Or not?
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess that's her final word on the matter.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was too listening to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_17]: What else do I need to know?
[SPEAKER_11]: You weren't fucking listening to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You had your headphones on.
[SPEAKER_11]: On one side of my head, just like DJs do.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I'm sorry, I did listen to it, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's still Night of Fire, so it gets like a 7.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's about it, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: No more, because it is Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Eurobeat part of it, you know, really... I...
[SPEAKER_19]: I had a lot of fear going into that, but it actually was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_19]: I actually thought it would be more Eurobeat than it ended up being.
[SPEAKER_19]: It wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was kind of catchy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I give it like an 8.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eurobeat is fun.
8.5.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It goes enough.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's get into Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki, what did you pick tonight?
[SPEAKER_17]: My song is from a group called Osiris, and it's Oneness with the Universe, is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's an awesome trans compilation I got a while back.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, let's... It's only because you don't want to fucking hear girls again.
[SPEAKER_17]: And goddammit, if this doesn't go in, you can expect girls next week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Got it?
[SPEAKER_19]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Osiris, Oneness with the Universe.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's check it out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Song number three.
DarkSakura.com
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see what folks thought of Osiris, Oneness with the Universe.
[SPEAKER_19]: Were we oneness with that song, or were we better off without that song?
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm drugged, and it was enhancing my drugged state of mind, so it gets a seven.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Angel Angel
[SPEAKER_10]: It was okay, but you know how those type of songs are, they get kind of repetitive, so I was semi-zoning out at the end of it, so I'll be nice and give it a six.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel usually doesn't give anything below a nine.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's pretty harsh.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Song number one, Endless Day with, I'm sorry, Echo Image with Endless Day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Song number two, Dream with Night of Fire, the Dream of Dream mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: And song number three, Osiris, Oneness with the Universe.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, place boat now and send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, he's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: When you listen to a little clip of that song, it sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I were to just play the clips, I probably would have given that song like a 9.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe we'll do that for the cage match one night.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'll just be a clip match.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then we could put like 30 songs in.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Remember, private message.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some folks are yelling out their votes in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Doesn't work that way.
[SPEAKER_19]: Send a private message.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you don't know how to do that, ask.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's all you got to do is ask.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, Bugged.
[SPEAKER_19]: I noticed Bugged walked into the room while we were doing the cage match there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another local Techmaster type person.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not the Techmasa of Orange Lounge Radio, but a Techmasa.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wait, get a mic.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_19]: He says get a mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the best shirt ever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bugs is wearing a shirt that says we'll work for bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's true.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have.
[SPEAKER_19]: Unfortunately, you are not the tech master of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Who do I have to kill?
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: and then probably you'd have to kill VXJ's next V too because really he's a big tech guy for the station too.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's more of the web god slash internet penis.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then Loki's the tech massa.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're just A tech massa.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I can live with A. You're from another department.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll take tech master overlord.
[SPEAKER_19]: That might work, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: You were a tech master before being a tech master was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is very true.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bugged and I went to not only high school together, but junior high school together.
[SPEAKER_19]: Long time ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know Bugged a long fucking time.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know Rob's real name.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Robert.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, that's my last name.
[SPEAKER_19]: Remember Roberts?
[SPEAKER_19]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Speaking of the VXJSONXV, our buddy and pal,
[SPEAKER_19]: He actually sent me a link, he wanted me to talk about this on the show tonight at some point I know Loki brought this up briefly, I think a couple shows ago It's this, you know how we were talking about In the Groove and how this is what Konami gets for not putting out a new arcade mix lately Well now, In the Groove is going to have some competition It's a game called Dance Tracks And it's another new game being put out by some folks Loki, have you heard about this one at all?
[SPEAKER_17]: DTX.PulseNetwork.net
[SPEAKER_19]: I will be so kind as to post a link in the chatroom there, if you want.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, there really isn't a whole lot there besides a lot of blue, but they do have some screenshots from the game, except the screenshots they have are not from the in-game mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is the select play mode screen.
[SPEAKER_19]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_21]: It's so brilliant.
[SPEAKER_19]: Woo, I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_19]: But what they do post in here is they post a partial song list.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you look at the track list here, and I noticed that LMK is on the track list.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, hmm, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: And let's see, I noticed this, this I thought was interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ace of Base with Cruel Summer, Bad Religion with Inner Logic, Mindless Self-Indulgence has a couple tracks on there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jenny Rom!
[SPEAKER_21]: What precisely are you to do to these songs?
[SPEAKER_17]: DM Ashura with Neon Rush DM Ashura with Neon Rush
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, so it looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_17]: At least they've got some good musicians behind it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if I remember correctly, I do remember hearing this way the hell back in the day, because they were actually going in the Bamai Style music production thread, and they were asking people to help them out with game music and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so I know these people signed on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that's where I remember this from, at least.
[SPEAKER_17]: But hey, at least they've got better people making music.
[SPEAKER_17]: So...
[SPEAKER_17]: I see what they have to show first.
[SPEAKER_17]: Can't really go by much of this menu graphics crap.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Watch it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Slash, he was also the guy that did a lot of stuff back in the day on the DWI Palace.
[SPEAKER_17]: You've got, of course, I can't see the guy's name under his
[SPEAKER_17]: um that was also another sim file maker I know um yeah looks like just a lot of people from the DWI community and stepmania stuff hmm it's kinda neat we'll see we'll see there's really nothing here for me yet we'll see I'll keep my eye on this and we'll see that's about all I can say
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't fuck it up, guys!
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do they really?
[SPEAKER_19]: I totally missed that.
[SPEAKER_19]: El Mullet says Queen of Love is on there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, they're right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wild Side with Queen of Love is on there.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like an English version of Bacquois, although it's not really, because it's not actually the lyrics in English, it's just the melody.
[SPEAKER_19]: But that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, so I have a pretty decent track list so far.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's very, uh,
[SPEAKER_19]: DDR Chibi-ish with a little bit of American flavor in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: More as it develops.
[SPEAKER_19]: Skype line's open again.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you would like to send us a call, you can just head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on interact with us and you can call us on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_19]: I noticed not a lot of people on the Skype line tonight so I'm thinking we might not get a whole lot of calls but it is open if you do want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_19]: Again, please make sure you have the latest version.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to be tallying up those votes for Cage Match pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else is in the news this week?
[SPEAKER_19]: I had another article I wanted to talk about and then I got sidetracked with this
[SPEAKER_19]: and DTXThing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki, how about what's going on in the sim scene?
[SPEAKER_17]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll get your sim update done.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's not going on in the sim scene is more like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Still, DDRUK is still down.
[SPEAKER_17]: Same with DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not looking good for DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_17]: They've been down for months, so say goodbye to them, probably.
[SPEAKER_17]: DDRUK is still down for a while.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to bet that they're not coming back either.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, and then you've got BamaiStyle, um, nothing really too much going on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, pretty much the only other thing, like I mentioned last week, there's, um, a bunch of different, like, food mix type stuff that's coming out, actually.
[SPEAKER_17]: A bunch of different ones that I was testing out, um, a while back, like last week or so, that are, um, in the works.
[SPEAKER_17]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um,
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we've got... Let me pull this up real quick here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, we are getting a call.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, take that call.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello, you are on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Raichan.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi Raichan, how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a while since I've called you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought I'd just call and say hi.
[SPEAKER_19]: It has been a little while.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello to you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Joyce is sitting over here working on my Katamari hat again.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's doing the last little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hello, Joyce, as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hope you're doing well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, he says hello, Joyce, saying he hopes you're doing well.
[SPEAKER_09]: She waves.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got the headphones on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, you guys are making hats together?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, she hasn't taught me how to crochet yet, which is the next project.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's teaching me how to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's working on a Katamari hat for me, and then she's going to do one for Jason, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: What exactly is a Katamari hat?
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a girl that sold a hat on eBay recently for $130 that
[SPEAKER_09]: was a crocheted hat that was like a Katamari ball.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had the little bumps on it like the Katamari have.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the little hearts.
[SPEAKER_19]: I noticed on the little hat it had little hearts in the bumps.
[SPEAKER_19]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Virgo one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine's the one with all the hearts and the pink and all that sort of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a really good one in my journal, but I did post one in Damacy Loving.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if you want to see a picture of this, go to LiveJournal and look up Dimash 11, and there's a picture of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here, let me see if I can find that one real quick, and I'll post a link in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Chat room again over at www.orangenautoradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you're going to be learning how to crochet, and you'll be doing a hat as well for yourself?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, the one being made now is for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one being made now is for me.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then you're going to make one for Jason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, she's actually got one started for Jason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you're going to learn how to crochet because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Right on, right on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, how about that DDR?
[SPEAKER_19]: Any DDR news you want to share?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I started talking to Middyhead last night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: He was saying something because I started a step file for House of Joy and recently just got things set up for Maxim.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I posted in his forum about it and he sounds really interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: He might actually do some remixes specifically for Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That guy is so cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm excited about that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was talking to him about maybe we can just take and put him up in the VIP area for his site, but
[SPEAKER_09]: He was like, no, I'd be pretty cool with you just sharing them around.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow, very cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where can folks download this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Do you have it up on the web somewhere?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually I don't because I recently recut the MP3 for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I need to give it back to Jason because he was working on the heavy steps for it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe once you guys are done, maybe we can work something out on originalsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe we can help you out.
[SPEAKER_19]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, right on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: So anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_09]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got Stepmania set up for hooking it up to my TV downstairs in the basement.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ah, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's because I've got Joyce.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got Joyce started playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's only really been playing for about a month, seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: And how's she doing after a month?
[SPEAKER_09]: She's actually just starting to get into heavy.
[SPEAKER_09]: She can do some six foot, some seven.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not bad for a month.
[SPEAKER_19]: God, after a month, I think I was graduating to threes.
[SPEAKER_19]: So very nice stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, she's got those Asian genes in her.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's half Korean, so she's got it working for her.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, Jamie just got back in the room.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got to share this with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you know that Raichan and her friend Joyce, they're making Katamari hats from Katamari Damacy?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, you read the journal, so you probably know.
[SPEAKER_19]: But isn't that so cool?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, right now, Joyce is the only one making them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you're moral support, and that counts for something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, Raichan, I'm going to say goodbye, but thanks so much for calling in, and we hope to hear from you again sometime.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, goodbye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Loki is going to finish his sim file thought.
[SPEAKER_17]: As I was mentioning before, there's a whole bunch of stuff...
[SPEAKER_17]: for those people out there that were looking for life after FoonMix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Starting off, there's a thread that was in Bimani Style on their DDR simulation stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's the Japanese DDR fan mix watch thread.
[SPEAKER_17]: And basically they have a few listed on here that you can go check out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Starting with DDR XX Mix, which is... They said they're currently testing it this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the song list so far... It's a lot of... Like...
[SPEAKER_17]: BMS stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's kind of... I don't know how to really describe it.
[SPEAKER_17]: But they've got... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_17]: They kind of reverted back.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, anyways, so I played it a little earlier this week, it's pretty decent, they've got some decent files for that, with videos in the background, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then we have DDR D3 Mix, which is, they only have really one song done on it so far, this song called J219 by Cranky, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: DDR E-Mix, which is all anime J-pop, if you like that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then we have Strawberry Steps, which is kind of more like an event, not really a mix, but interesting stuff anyways.
[SPEAKER_17]: There was another one I found too, something about like Pop Candy or something mixed, but I don't have the link for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then there's a new theme also that's on the same thread, Step Mania Siberia style, which is basically it looks just like Techno Fiend.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's pretty cool to check it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, yeah, that was pretty much what was going on in the Sim scene.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not really much.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then, of course, I mentioned last week that one bondage chick thing that was retarded, but...
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was someone with too much free time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he wasn't getting laid.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, you guys want to hear who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie says... Alright, let's find out who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ladies and gentlemen, we have a new champion in the cage match this week, and it is...
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't fucking believe it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Night of Fire by a landslide even.
[SPEAKER_19]: By a landslide.
[SPEAKER_19]: The other two songs combined did not take that one out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm surprised because I just sort of threw it in.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's in there now.
[SPEAKER_19]: The winner, Dream, Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to be sick more often.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tune in next week to see if Loki makes good on his promise.
[SPEAKER_19]: and maybe I'm going to make a mean pick next week too.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's go to a break, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: When we come back from this break, I think it's high time we got into the FUs of the week because damn it, we're getting angsty.
[SPEAKER_19]: In this break, I'm doing fourth mix songs because I'm playing Hypnotic Crisis.
[SPEAKER_19]: and if you were here with me, the B4 Zah Mix because those songs are cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: We need Saints Go Marching.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to do Saints Go Marching and we'll do Ninja Bro.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hell with it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a four song break, damn you.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Get your fourth mix on.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
Feel the heat, the vibration, on the streets, new situation, got the crazy car
[SPEAKER_18]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you miss us?
[SPEAKER_19]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds like their aim's improving.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hopefully your aim is improving.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are your allergies improving yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: When I lay down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well I hope you feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's okay, I'm just laying... I'm actually... This chair is so huge that I can lay across it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love that chair.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty comfortable.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want to make love to that chair.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just kidding, I don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Please don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to sit here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not while you're laying in it, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I'm pissed off about something.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, nobody cares.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where the fuck is Ultramix 2 Song Pack 8?
[SPEAKER_19]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_19]: It was announced like forever ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, I know, from what I understand, Konami submitted it and it's Microsoft's fault.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're sitting on it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_19]: Release it already.
[SPEAKER_19]: Listen to these songs that are going to be in Ultramix 2 song pack number 8.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cosmic Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_19]: Love that song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do I have clips of some of these songs?
[SPEAKER_19]: I hope I do.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me see if I got a little clip of Cowgirl, or Cosmic Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, we all know Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm thinking Cosmic Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is like all the way from Guitar Freak's, like, what, third mix?
[SPEAKER_11]: Cosmic Cowgirl was like my favorite song to play on Drumania.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: That song rocks.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want that damn song.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then this one I can't even pronounce, but it's a fun song to play.
[SPEAKER_19]: Balalakia, Carried with the Wind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Balalakia.
[SPEAKER_19]: By Julianne Frost in Song Pack 8.
[SPEAKER_19]: More deep version 2.1.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, we already have that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not so concerned with that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: In My Eyes, the Neuromix by Neuropa.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is so cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Naropa did like one of the coolest songs in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: They did Standing Still in Time and they sound like Erasure.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't wait to see what they do to In My Eyes.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then Kind Lady, The Interlude.
[SPEAKER_19]: Notice about this song pack.
[SPEAKER_19]: What a lot of people were bitching about with the Konami song packs is that they were recycling a lot of old garbage.
[SPEAKER_19]: Only one old song in this pack.
[SPEAKER_19]: And really, it's not even that old.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's only shown up in, like, what, two other releases?
[SPEAKER_19]: One in Japan, one in the US?
[SPEAKER_19]: On PS2?
[SPEAKER_19]: So, more Deep Version 2.1.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, you've seen it before.
[SPEAKER_19]: But the other four are all new!
[SPEAKER_19]: What a deal!
[SPEAKER_19]: Five bucks!
[SPEAKER_19]: Microsoft, get up off your ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Put this on the site.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want to download it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's new!
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_19]: What's wrong with you people?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just really upset about this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe I have a little clip of the Kind Lady interlude, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was kind of hoping I would have one of those.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe, uh... No, I only have the... I have the Japanese VRare at some point, but I think I moved it into a deep, dark directory I'm not going to find anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, well, maybe another time.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_19]: I guess it's time for us to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_19]: We don't have to.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, we could just, you know, end the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, you guys can send your FUs of the week over to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's start it off.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here we go, FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie, why do we have to do the FUs every week?
[SPEAKER_21]: Very good, now use your mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you to my allergies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And my cat for sleeping on my head.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate my allergies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm on all kinds of drugs right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not doing shit to make me feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um... Also, F you to sneezing messily in my car.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then to stupid drivers.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then to my Photoshop teacher.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because Photoshop sucks, but he's an elitist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to the seven goblins that followed my ass through the tomb in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope that some paladin came by and owned all your asses.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to how slow leveling in that game is.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it is a very blessed thing that there's not so much of the Ragnarok-style newbie talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which really sucks a whole bunch of ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to not having any real concentration.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other situations that I can't really do anything about.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to GameStop just for a situation involving my fianc.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's really it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, then let's go over to our buddy Loki with his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fucking A, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, first off, fucking A-Bit for, um, creating... I think it was A-Bit, I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, A.S.
[SPEAKER_17]: Rock.
[SPEAKER_17]: For creating a stupid motherboard with, you know, five different places to put RAM.
[SPEAKER_17]: And for confusing me for hours because I put the RAM in the wrong spot.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dope.
Anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_17]: Also, basically just fucking using my crazy sleep schedule because I'm going to be so tired tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not that I really care because it'll be fine because everyone will be getting mad at Erica because I was leaving for my work.
[SPEAKER_17]: And fucking using my goddamn case because I had to get another...
[SPEAKER_17]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_17]: They get worse.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: I'd like to give an F you to the government for getting one of my high school friends killed in Iraq.
[SPEAKER_19]: That kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, F you to the government.
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to Bush while I'm at it, because I don't like him.
[SPEAKER_19]: I never did.
[SPEAKER_19]: And F you to the fact that I have to get up and go to work early tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to me being lazy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not getting anything accomplished, but that's my own damn fault.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, F you to myself.
[SPEAKER_19]: And...
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to Angst!
[SPEAKER_19]: I've had a lot of it lately.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I hide it really good on this show.
[SPEAKER_19]: But secretly I'm plotting to kill each and every one of you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_19]: Love ya.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for the warning.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see what the other folks in the studio have to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: Starting with Bugged.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, double F you to the government.
[SPEAKER_21]: He was a very good high school buddy.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I've heard from various people that I haven't heard it from in ten years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it was a very strange phone call today, because this person was very close to the friend who died.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was strange.
[SPEAKER_21]: FU to diesel prices, as always.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not FU to running diesel.
[SPEAKER_19]: We still get way good miles to the gallon, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_21]: I get 40.
[SPEAKER_21]: And FU to Johnny Carson dying.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, that sucked, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: We did a memorial last week, but that still sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wasn't running.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, uh, pretty good week.
[SPEAKER_21]: I need to bring the hard drive to my iMac.
[SPEAKER_21]: I saved a laptop by pulling the hard drive out, moving files over for a UC Davis College student.
[SPEAKER_21]: Putting them on my elder iMac.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've had words.
[SPEAKER_21]: She was happy she had a computer that worked.
[SPEAKER_21]: She didn't want to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to people who have a problem with me and won't come to me and come to my friends instead, that's all I have to say
[SPEAKER_19]: about the FUs of the Week segment here on this program.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me get my reminder music up.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I could do this here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Boys and girls, we here at Orange Lounge Radio do the FUs of the week as a service to you and ourselves because we certainly get a load off of our chest.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, luckily, we're a small program and nobody listens to us, so pretty much anybody who submits their FUs will get it right on the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: One day, we will be bigger than God and...
[SPEAKER_19]: We're not going to read your FUs anymore because we won't have the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll have a little dark corner of the website where you can post them.
[SPEAKER_19]: But for now, we read your FUs on the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, there are some exceptions to this rule.
[SPEAKER_19]: We do not read FUs of a personal nature.
[SPEAKER_19]: In other words, if you're going to rant about somebody else, we're not going to read that FU on the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, of course, there's exceptions to every rule.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you're going to rant about your teacher, we'll read that FU because, you know what, your teacher doesn't like you either.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, fine, we'll read that FU.
[SPEAKER_19]: FUs to your parents.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, everybody has FUs about their parents once in a while.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, you love your parents, but some days you want to kill them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: They feel the same way about you.
[SPEAKER_19]: They love you most days, but some days they want to kill you and wish you'd never been born.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we will allow the FUs to teachers and parents and bosses.
[SPEAKER_19]: We all hate our boss.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, I love my boss.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love my boss.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love people I work with.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I know a lot of you work in retail, so you don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that's fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can give an FU to your boss.
[SPEAKER_19]: Those types of FUs are fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, if you're going to give an FU to like an ex-boyfriend, or an ex-girlfriend, or an ex-best friend, or an ex-wife, well, some exceptions.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still let some exceptions even with that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, for the most part, if you want to give an FU about those types of things, let me give you a phone number.
[SPEAKER_19]: 1-800-96-JERRY Okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: That is where you can go to handle your problems.
[SPEAKER_19]: Please, do not send them care of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: We don't want to get caught in the middle of your bullshit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: And now, the chatroom FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: VXJasonXV says, FU to Tifa.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rai Chan says, oh, Joyce first.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's sending Joyce's.
[SPEAKER_19]: Joy says, F you to sick, demented fruitcakes that feel they can abuse animals and then don't even bother taking them to a shelter and leave them to fend for themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rychan says, F you to all the people at Walmart on Sunday afternoons.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on, people.
[SPEAKER_19]: There has to be something better for you to do than stand in the middle of the aisle while your children run around like they're in a playground.
[SPEAKER_19]: BRP Ohio Bomani, the Big Red Pimp, says F you to Food Network for showing stupid American football party specials that make him wait for Iron Chef America to come on again.
[SPEAKER_19]: Flay vs. Ming.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Illusion says F you to the Super Blue Sphere levels in Sonic 3 and Knuckles for being so damn hard to beat.
[SPEAKER_19]: and FU to my cousin, though more of an in-your-face FU because we played Texas Hold'em last night and I started with 18 pennies and ended up with 80.
[SPEAKER_19]: Flush that, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_19]: Dark Knight says FU to freeze my ass off because of this weather and FU to school for screwing up my financial aid because without the aid I can't attend college for the summer now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Legend of Zaku says F you to currently being unemployed F you to Sony for releasing the piss poor slim PS2 and F you to the ongoing worldwide shortage of them and F you to selling my Chinese textbook last semester not knowing I was going to need it for the second part of the class this semester thus having to buy a new one and not being prepared for a murder of a quiz tomorrow SSJ100 Matt says F you to Emo Boy from Thursday Night Show for sassing me about sports games oh that was lanky style
[SPEAKER_19]: FU to... Oh, that is a personal FU.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dork says FU to girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_19]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you guys for sharing your FUs with us.
[SPEAKER_19]: We feel your angst.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, Jamie has another one.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me get your song.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you don't need to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just to myself.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why?
[SPEAKER_19]: But we love you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: When in doubt.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: When in doubt, haunt people.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hear, hear.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's a stalker.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think you have a couple in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think Phoenix, well, Phoenix said he was a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's a stalker.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think he's more of a fanboy than a stalker.
[SPEAKER_19]: You want a stalker?
[SPEAKER_11]: I do, just because it would be fun and interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I could hunt them down and kill them as revenge.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then get on the news.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, if you want to stalk Jamie, send those emails to jamie at orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_19]: And did you know it'll also work for Rob at OrangeLaunchRadio.com or Loki at OrangeLaunchRadio.com?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: If anyone puts a personal F you in, again, we stick a Nevada-ton on them.
[SPEAKER_11]: She can go after them with a box cutter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, did you know that the DanceMania folks updated their website?
[SPEAKER_19]: DanceMania, you know, being the series that DDR got a lot of its music from in Japan.
[SPEAKER_19]: They got a new album coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's Disco Viking.
[SPEAKER_19]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it's a lot of really interesting old songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Listen to some of these songs that are on the CD.
[SPEAKER_19]: Call Me by Blondie, The Reflex by Duran Duran, David Bowie with Let's Dance, Sheena Easton with Modern Girl,
[SPEAKER_19]: Heaven is a Place on Earth, Belinda Carlisle.
[SPEAKER_19]: A lot of these songs show up on a lot of dance media albums.
[SPEAKER_19]: Belinda Carlisle.
[SPEAKER_19]: An Upside Down by Cuckoo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that song is on like... Rai Chan is my official stalker now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Who is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rai Chan.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Never Gonna Give You Up by Rick Astley.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, get this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Vacation by the Go-Go's.
[SPEAKER_19]: Love that song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Telephone Operator by Pete Shelley.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that song's been in just about every other Dance Mania CD.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and this is so cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Madness within the city.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not our house.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's in the city.
[SPEAKER_21]: Madness had another song.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: The Steve Miller Band, Abracadabra.
[SPEAKER_19]: Abracadabra.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: We got to go to a break because Jamie's foaming at the mouth.
[SPEAKER_19]: She wants to get into the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's going to regulate, so we have to log out on the main screen so we can get her in.
[SPEAKER_19]: She wants to be cyber-stalked by those of you guys, so we got to make it work.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, apparently we're not doing a good enough job for her in person.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, we're going to play some Euromix songs in this break because I want to hear Video Kill the Radio Star.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we're going to do some varying Euromix tracks.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and Jamie wants to hear Kids in America, so I guess we can pull that song in there too.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Radio Star, Video King
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking out a dirty old window Down below the cars and the city go rushing by I sit here alone and I wonder why Friday night and everyone's blue I can feel the heat but it's soothing heading down I saw
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
I heard you were in love, but I knew we were meant to be
[SPEAKER_07]: I want you to want me for all that I am I hope that you will try to understand Do you feel the same Do you feel the same
[SPEAKER_07]: From StepSquad to OrangeLoud, this DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler
[SPEAKER_19]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio and we want to get into some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if you have a question for Orange Lounge Radio about anything, really, you can ask us damn near anything and we'll answer it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Send us a private message in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat, and if you're not sure how to send me a private message, my name is Sky, then just ask somebody in chat room and they'll be happy to help you out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Smiles, chat room, smiles.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_19]: very cool, no you do not need an iPod to listen, it's developed for any type of MP3 player including your computer you can just listen to the show on your computer if you want but the really cool thing is that if you happen to have some type of portable device the show is really designed to be something that you listen to on the go so check it out
[SPEAKER_19]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on Orange Lounge Radio to go.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have more programs throughout the week, more live shows, including Monday Nights, Diversion, the Orange Lounge Radio Bomani Remix Show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very cool remixes of songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's very different sort of sound for the station.
[SPEAKER_19]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tuesday Nights is Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pump up the volume.
[SPEAKER_11]: Request show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's cool and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: We've actually been live for the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to be live again this week, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_19]: All that other video game randomness, and as one of our chat room, I forgot who said this, one of our chatters put it, Emo Boy, LankyStyle is on that program as well as myself, and sometimes Rice Princess when she feels like showing up.
[SPEAKER_19]: Friday night's over on The Freak.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can hear this very show rebroadcast.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's DDR Freak Radio, www.ddrfreak.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, people, if you want to help us out, you can always listen to the station 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Places you can vote for us right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Our podcast is listed on another search engine right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, hey, you could really help us out by going and rating the podcast a 5.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it's Podcast Alley or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll give you guys a link.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you would be so kind as to go there and rate us a high rating, then, you know, we're high rated and people like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, you know, help Horace out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: And what else is there?
[SPEAKER_19]: There's something else.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, the Live 365 Awards are coming up again soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: They aren't taking nominations yet, but we'll be needing your help because we want Orange Launch Radio to be able to take over the world.
[SPEAKER_19]: So please, help us out with that.
[SPEAKER_19]: We love our listeners that help us out with those things.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's all about you guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: Comments to the show can always be sent to rob at orangelaunchradio.com or jamie or loki at orangelaunchradio.com Any of them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to go into Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, Dark Knight, send me a private message with more information on what you're saying in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm too lazy to type right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just going to talk to the chatroom tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But Dark Knight, send me a private message with a link to more information and I will do so.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's get into Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is your opportunity to ask us some stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_19]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_19]: Will we find the cure to Jamie's allergies?
[SPEAKER_19]: Or will we find a cure for Matt's big angst?
[SPEAKER_19]: There's no cure, no cure The easy answer I have to that is yes
[SPEAKER_11]: We already have a podcast-only segment.
[SPEAKER_19]: Remember, the cage match didn't show up until episode 20, and some of the segments, you know, it didn't show up until later on.
[SPEAKER_19]: And now we whore them out.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, if we didn't have these segments, we wouldn't have a show.
[SPEAKER_19]: The podcast will do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: The other cool thing about the podcast is that it's very flexible, is that we could, if we wanted to, if we were on the road somewhere...
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki's trying to build us an on-the-road computer that's going to be inside an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_19]: In fact, if you look on cam, you can kind of see Loki's head.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what he's working on right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's working on the Xbox PC.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have a plan that this year from E3, we're going to be giving you updates via the podcast every day on what we've seen at E3.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, if you were to watch this coverage on television, on one of the tech stations on TV, you'd be waiting a couple weeks to a month to be seeing these sorts of updates.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you were to be reading about it in a magazine, you'd be waiting like six to eight weeks to see this stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even other websites take a couple days sometimes.
[SPEAKER_19]: We will have live audio from E3 the same damn day.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the kind of cool stuff the podcast is going to present.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what we're planning to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: So...
[SPEAKER_19]: All those sorts of things.
[SPEAKER_19]: So thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hugs and kisses.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's get to some more questions here.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else do you guys think could be done with the podcast?
[SPEAKER_19]: Anything you guys want to add to that?
[SPEAKER_11]: We could even do other podcasts for some of our spin-off shows.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we do have that ability, honestly.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we shall see.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dead air, dead air.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry, I'm posting a link in our chat room right now on how folks can help.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can make the grudge sound again.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know if you took apart a laptop battery.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: I said I just took apart a laptop battery.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's inside?
[SPEAKER_17]: Batteries.
[SPEAKER_17]: Scary stuff that could hurt me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Legend of Zaku has a question.
[SPEAKER_19]: What licensed songs would you like to see on an American 2DX mix if it happens?
[SPEAKER_19]: Any requests for an... Shaft.
[SPEAKER_19]: The theme from Shaft.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie says Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's yelling from the laundry room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel, anything you want to see?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All of a sudden I...
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought of the BT song from Extreme.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why, I just kind of thought of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Simply Being Loved.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I was going to say that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Either that or just something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dude, Skull could be actually kind of fun to play.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Any echo image.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just mix, just honestly, team up with a different drum.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let Konami Hawaii do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And team up with a different drum.
[SPEAKER_19]: because that would be so hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that and what other songs would be good?
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, a lot of the crossovers they've had in DDR might be fun, like Dirty Vegas would be kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else would be fun?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm trying to think of songs that haven't really been in DDR yet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or 2DX.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Even though this song's already been in 2DX and it's a really horrid song, I really want to see it in 2DX USA.
Deadline.
I love Deadline.
Love it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, just go to like Robbins Entertainment and just put anything from those dance compilations.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just give us some Lasco, some Ian Vandal.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: All that stuff would be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want that Come Into My Dream song by Froggy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come into my dream.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because that has a really cool beat to it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ooh, definitely do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Illusion has a question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Illusion wants to know, okay, he's done a lot of soul searching here, and he's wanted to ask this question for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Weeks have gone by, sleepless nights, because I couldn't ask this question, he says.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here is his question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is Jem truly outrageous?
[SPEAKER_11]: Truly, truly outrageous.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jem is adventure.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jem is excitement.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jem is lame.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jem is not lame!
[SPEAKER_11]: She is not, but the dolls have really huge heads.
[SPEAKER_19]: But the misfits, their songs are better.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they're going to get her.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was all about later in the series when Jetta showed up and played that black saxophone.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was like, my hero forever.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Since we got some extra time here, since we haven't gotten a whole lot of questions, I have to play at least a little clip of this because this is so cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: You guys know Freeze Pop, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: They're the band that did Super Sprode and Science Genius Girl.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know they've got like two full albums, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, Shark Attack.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've got other songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: But one of the songs they do is so cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: You've got to hear this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got to find the directory it's in, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: My computer's a big fat mess right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is actually a cover...
[SPEAKER_19]: You're not going to believe this.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a cover of the Gem theme song.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to play a little clip of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I'm only going to play like the first verse.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jem, Jem is excitement, Jem, Jem is adventure, Jem, Jem is truly outrageous, truly, truly, truly outrageous, Jem, Jem is my name, no one else is the same,
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on, they're the misfits, they're gonna get her.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I have to tell a little story about Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, tell a story about Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_21]: Freeze Pop is from Boston, I have a bunch of friends in Boston, and they were, my friends were at a club, and this guy was going off about how he hates, hates Freeze Pop because they sound so fake.
[SPEAKER_21]: Meanwhile, the lead singer of Freeze Pop was standing behind him just fuming.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: And apparently she could really kick ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did she?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't believe so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, Freeze Pop is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was pointed out that the lead singer that he really hates the sound of was standing right behind him, and I guess he left.
[SPEAKER_21]: Much to his own behest.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, we need to get Freeze Pop on this show.
[SPEAKER_19]: I doubt that's even possible, but I would try.
[SPEAKER_21]: They tend to stick around Boston.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, they don't have to be here.
[SPEAKER_19]: We do have the phone thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can Skype them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_19]: We got MidiHead on this show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll see what my contacts can do.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_19]: Have your people talk to their people, and then have their people contact my people, and we'll have a people party.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay, people party.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or do you get the Android before?
[SPEAKER_19]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Non-stop.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, I know you're a big Gem fan and a FreezePop fan.
[SPEAKER_19]: What did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love the Misfits part.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like the best part of this all.
[SPEAKER_19]: We are the Misfits.
[SPEAKER_19]: Our songs are better.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have you heard this?
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got a... Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to play another little clip of a Freeze Pop song.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care that we're kind of off on a tangent right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's our show.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can do whatever we want.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you have to hear this song because they talk about video games in it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm only going to play a little clip of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you have to listen because in the beginning they sample a speak and spell.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Listen to this.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it spells out freeze poop.
[SPEAKER_19]: Freeze poop.
[SPEAKER_19]: Listen, listen, I'm not even kidding, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: F-R-E-E-Z-E-P-O-O-P Wrong, try again.
[SPEAKER_01]: F-R-E-E-Z-E-P-O-P You are correct.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't play with me, I'm not your toy Oh, can't you see, I am not a game boy Don't mess with me, I'm not your toy Just look at me, I am not a game boy Six AA batteries, and I'm good to go 700 milliamps, I'm here to rock the show Six AA batteries, and I'm good to go
[SPEAKER_19]: Tell me that song is not cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to play that song in its entirety later.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just you wait.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, enough free spot.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you, Illusion, for sending me all those songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rai Chan and Joyce are sending this question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Will Orange Lounge Radio ever get a studio pet?
[SPEAKER_19]: If they make ferrets legal, you guys should get one as your studio pet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to say, I thought the ferrets were the pets.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was wondering where they disappeared to.
[SPEAKER_19]: We haven't had the ferrets in the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think the ferrets got buried under crap.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know where the ferrets are.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're around somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: Look around.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: There might be some next to your chair.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't you usually have them during the show?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but if I bend over, my nose is going to start draining again.
[SPEAKER_19]: We've got the ferrets around somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, the reason why we don't have an actual pet is that... I don't know about Loki, but I am far too irresponsible to have a pet.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will kill it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm the type of person that will come home and say, Oh shit, I forgot to feed the cat this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not about caring for the pet.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's about the $500 deposit for the pet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, that's part of it too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's a lot I could do with $500.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, piss it away on some computer that I won't use.
[SPEAKER_19]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, you know, I just don't have the desire to get a pet.
[SPEAKER_17]: As far as ferrets... Yep, and besides, like BRP said, they already have a studio pet.
[SPEAKER_17]: His name is Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: And ferrets actually smell very bad, even if you... I want a penthouse pet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ferrets are mean little shits, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ferrets are nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ferrets are evil.
[SPEAKER_19]: They bite things, and they bite through your finger.
[SPEAKER_11]: Only if you raise them wrong.
[SPEAKER_19]: And at night, and after midnight, if you feed it, they turn into rabid little creatures and...
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you keep him around?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because he actually pays rent.
[SPEAKER_19]: But that's funny and we can tape him and put him on the internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, and he pays rent.
[SPEAKER_19]: Would a ferret go out and get a job and pay rent?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: My friend's ferrets were cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: He named them Kodo and Podo and he was going to give them to me before I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I found out that I couldn't have ferrets out here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rightchan would just like to add that Joyce is saying, Joyce has a pair of really sweet ferrets, and she says, ferrets you don't because they are like a large hamster.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, they're like a really small cat mixed with a hamster.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just what I need.
[SPEAKER_19]: A giant hamster.
[SPEAKER_19]: Think of all the gay jokes I'd hear with that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: What'd you sit on?
[SPEAKER_19]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm getting told by Joyce.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know how to take care of ferrets.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do not underestimate ferrets.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're illegal in California.
[SPEAKER_19]: California says no to ferrets.
[SPEAKER_19]: They will terminate the ferrets.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's got to be one of the worst Arnold impressions.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't get paid to impersonate Arnold.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did you see that stupid TV movie that they're doing
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you see that movie that they're doing about the governor?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, what about it?
[SPEAKER_17]: It has this old guy that doesn't look or sound like Arnold, but it's supposed to be him.
[SPEAKER_17]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that would be like me playing Arnold.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: California!
[SPEAKER_15]: Dark Knight is sending a question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, quick question thinking about the Capcom and Namco thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: This was posted to our website.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're doing a Capcom cross Namco game.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's going to be like an RPG featuring both characters.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was wondering if Namco and Sega will finally do a Tekken versus Virtua Fighter game for real.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: God, I hope not, because I hate Virtua Fighter.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, we are really not the people to be asking on that subject.
[SPEAKER_19]: Write letters, show love, maybe it'll happen, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want Tekken 5 to be out now.
[SPEAKER_19]: On console?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: That'd be pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan's saving a Tekken 5 poster for me to go in my cubicle.
[SPEAKER_19]: When is that supposed to come out?
[SPEAKER_19]: Do we have a release?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_19]: I honestly don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be neat.
[SPEAKER_19]: Crossover games can be neat, but we don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's a question maybe we can help with.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dark Knight says, another question I need your help on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Choosing an anime character to dress up as when I go to a local convention in June.
[SPEAKER_19]: Should I dress up as a character from B-Blade or Lan from Mega... You will so be laughed at.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or Lan from Mega Man and T-Series?
[SPEAKER_11]: Go with the second one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think you should dress up as a milkmaid.
[SPEAKER_21]: Super Milk John?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Go as Ranma, because it's one of the only animes I've actually seen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma cosplay should have been buried five years ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: What about Sailor Menchi?
[SPEAKER_21]: That really killed everyone right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, the last...
[SPEAKER_11]: AX I went to, though, had an Utena cosplayer who went as Utena in the boy's uniform.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was a guy cosplaying her who looked very female.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was really good cosplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then he went around later in the girl's style with the shorts and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then there was the Umi cosplayer who was a guy at Faname 2001.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's it the mob asked?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know how to pronounce that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Dumabass.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it's Dumas.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mr. Dumas.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love it when people make typos and everybody jumps on them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ha ha, you said Dumabass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's start internet trend now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whenever you say dumbass or type dumbass, always spell it like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dumubass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just like pwned.
[SPEAKER_17]: You heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dumubass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shut up, you demubass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Smells like demubass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Joyce wanted to clarify a few things about the pet ferret.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're tasty.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's getting... That is not what she's saying.
[SPEAKER_19]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_19]: As I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: It became illegal because of wrong scientific information in the 1930s that they are wild animals and non-domesticated.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've been domesticated for so long that they couldn't survive in the wild.
[SPEAKER_19]: The AFA is working on getting them legalized in California.
[SPEAKER_19]: But in the meantime, you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't want to go to jail over a ferret.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't want to be sitting next to Bubba.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're just going to slap a fine on you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are you in here for?
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, I asked Bubba.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bubba, what are you in here for?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm in here for committing murder.
[SPEAKER_27]: I murdered a guy over drugs.
[SPEAKER_27]: What are you in here for, gay boy?
[SPEAKER_19]: I owned a ferret.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, you're not going to go to jail for owning a ferret, but that would be funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be a great sitcom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Another big guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm in here for ripping the tag off a pillow.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's another episode of Bubba and the Gay!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, this ferret was tearing apart my curtains.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just had an image of a little Korean lady in the background going, Are you the gay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you the gay?
[SPEAKER_19]: The Korean lady can be like the warden.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it would be very funny to put gay man and bubba in the same cell.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is that accent?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't even know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Korean-Italian?
[SPEAKER_21]: Really Spicy Spaghetti, I guess?
[SPEAKER_19]: You got a purty mouth.
[SPEAKER_19]: My ferret had a purty mouth.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because we're demubasses.
[SPEAKER_19]: You need to come here more often.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: So people... Now, let me finish the question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why doesn't someone change the webcam so people don't look at the couch the whole time?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it's not going to be pointed at me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we have a ban.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie is banning herself from the camera.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll get on the fucking cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie's going to go supermodel on the cam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, fuck a cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, Jamie's inching her way towards the cam so that you can see something new.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie's made her way to the cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, Jamie is on the cam right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: A little piece of Jamie for you guys on the cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, the way the cam is set up, it's actually inside that massive arcade cabinet that Loki has set up.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it's a real bitch to take the eye toy out of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: and put it somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, there have been previous episodes.
[SPEAKER_19]: There was an episode not that long ago where we actually had the iToyCam pointed over this way.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, it's not really that much of a bitch to take... Yes, it's a huge bitch to take out of the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, the... Yeah, exactly what... Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pain in the dumb ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to make this catch on.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're going to like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just like Death Cake.
[SPEAKER_19]: The chat room has a request for you to do your grudge face on cam.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have a grudge face.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just me with my mouth open.
[SPEAKER_19]: Think fish.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, illusion.
[SPEAKER_19]: Illusion.
[SPEAKER_19]: as a question.
[SPEAKER_19]: Since you've got 10 minutes of no questions, I suppose I'll ask another.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, what's your favorite freeze pop song?
[SPEAKER_19]: Obviously, I'm having an orgasm over them recently.
[SPEAKER_19]: Science Genius Girl remix.
[SPEAKER_19]: The live one.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, you know what Science Genius Girl remix rocks?
None of them.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, Loki, none of them is not the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to kick you in the dumb ass now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't be such a demub-ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the Science Genius Girl mix that sounds like it was done on a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Listen to this.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's so cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fun times two times three When I clone a human being Isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_11]: I want that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Send that to me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_19]: I think we might use that in a show intro, like, later on.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would so rock.
[SPEAKER_19]: Pardon me, Bison coming through.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dark Knight's pissed because we're making fun of his demubass comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, he's such a demubass, we're not even being able to spell demubass correctly.
[SPEAKER_19]: Aw, but we love him.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh boy, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, think about it this way, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_19]: You are on the cutting edge of a new internet trend.
[SPEAKER_19]: My favorite freeze pop song for the record would be the... Oh God, I forgot the name of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: What a fan I am.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think we're about wrapping up the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're pretty much done, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: But we have to get everybody's final thought before this show can be over.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bug, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: Online games are addicting.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_17]: My final thought is I made a mess and didn't do anything and
[SPEAKER_17]: Now I'm back to square one.
[SPEAKER_19]: You made a mess, now clean it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: I did clean it up, that's what I'm doing right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, uh... I hate this stupid thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I could have bought a laptop for the money and built this damn thing and it would have been more powerful, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_17]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_19]: But not as leet.
[SPEAKER_17]: I guess, whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um... And then, um...
[SPEAKER_19]: My final thought would be 1-800-96-JERRY.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_19]: The final word of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bugged.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to give it to you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_19]: One word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_19]: This show.
[SPEAKER_19]: What is it, my friend?
[SPEAKER_19]: See you next week, guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dumbass.
[SPEAKER_24]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_24]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright guys, we're going to go back to our Bomani Music and More program, featuring all your favorite DDR, 2DX, and Dance Mania favorites.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you know our show is being bootlegged?
[SPEAKER_19]: I just found a bootleg site.
[SPEAKER_19]: Somebody's posting episodes of this show up on a bootleg page.
[SPEAKER_19]: We should sue them.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to sue.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're not going to sue.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange House Radio is being bootlegged.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am innocent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know you didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know who did it.
[SPEAKER_19]: They signed their name on the page.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know damn well who did it.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: We think it's cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's my official word on the matter.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have a good one, you guys.