Thanks for watching!
The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_05]: This is episode number 125 for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: January the 2nd of 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to the Bumani Scene's most happy-go-lucky radio station of all things, Bumani.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a mouthful of asparagus.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not what I heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounded like she was mumbling local street names and stuff from around here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, also in that corner, the other co-host, the fabulous, wonderful, tech master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's waving at you right now because he's not near a microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not prepared.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's doing other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have a bunch of special guests, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We always love having special guests in studio, especially some old favorites which we have here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I think some of you guys are now designated old favorites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Including... Old, maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Including everybody's favorite psycho forum goddess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Head bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Head bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to Iguana Girl.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yo, what up?
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: That mic's a little quiet.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was noticing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta... from the gut.
[SPEAKER_20]: You don't want me to go first.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm just blasting everybody out now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta yell like you're yelling at newbies.
[SPEAKER_20]: If only you knew.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, also joining us tonight, say hello to Islander.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good and loud tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: I learned my lesson.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a new microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: We finally, after about four weeks, replaced that microphone that was cutting out for our guests.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a little quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, because we had to play some mic roulette, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also say hello to joining us on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It hasn't been here in several years.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: He grew since the last time I saw him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to Jazz.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know him better as Kamikaze, though, from the Final Fantasy universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to another old favorite.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's such an old favorite that she's getting moldy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm late.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, they would have never known that because you were here right before your cue, but you just had to go and spill all the beans, so now they know you're tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our webcam wasn't even on.
[SPEAKER_05]: They couldn't see.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, can I just start off by saying, I love our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love our chat room, www.orangelonsradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this, MPQ in chat says, Every time I hear the opening, I think my mom will think I'm looking at porn or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, we have that sexy voice in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're listening to Orange Lens, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then somebody else replies here, Shade23 says, Well, why aren't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Masterbating to Pornography
[SPEAKER_05]: Big 2DX game released last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I can say last year, because we're in 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: So big 2DX game released last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to hear some music from 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back, all that randomness and chatter you've come to expect from your buddies here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be back.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_09]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_00]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 125.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's some kind of landmark number, isn't it?
125?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: A dollar and a quarter?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, we're here.
[SPEAKER_05]: for your listening pleasure or displeasure, as the case may be.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangeonstrater.com for all the interaction stuff with the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know you guys love to interact with the show, whether it be via the chat room or via the Skype line, which I should sign into at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we will have Orange Ons Radio on the Skype line so you can call in later in the show if you want and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just sitting here, sitting back, talking about...
[SPEAKER_05]: Music-based video games and, you know, Bomani-type games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just, you know, really anything that doesn't suck is fair game here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even some stuff that does suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a whole segment dedicated to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll get into that a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But first we have to start off tonight's show as we start off every week's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: 125 episodes and nothing's changed.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're going to start it off with the lovely DarkSakura, who actually wasn't here last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you were sick last week, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: I was.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was actually...
[SPEAKER_18]: Pretty damn tired last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's too bad to hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: But you seem good now.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I have sexy jeans.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do have sexy... I haven't taken a look at your sexy jeans here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not wearing them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're in the washer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we want to see your sexy jeans.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why we have a webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's never anything interesting on a webcam.
[SPEAKER_18]: Half of them are recessive.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, a quarter of them are recessive.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's that work?
[SPEAKER_18]: My jeans are a quarter recessive.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everybody's are.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_18]: So, I'm going to be changing from the exciting world of student loans going into the exciting world, again, of home mortgages.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to be working in the escrow department.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is something probably I would estimate that 98% of our listeners know nothing about.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would have to say that 98% of homeowners know nothing about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Considering our average age of the listener would be about, what, 12?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: your mortgage company has the option of paying your taxes and insurance with your house payment so they will actually set it up to where you have the money in a separate holding account which is an escrow account to pay your taxes and insurance and that's what I'm going to be doing is making sure that they're managed properly because if they're not it gives people lots of trouble with the government makes people really poor because trust me when you go to buy a house don't be a retard about it come talk to me anyway
[SPEAKER_18]: So, also making some changes, other changes.
[SPEAKER_18]: And as of tomorrow, I am back on the straight and narrow for my big resolution.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to say this on the air tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, last year I lost 50 pounds.
[SPEAKER_18]: This year I'm going to lose another 50.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to be a toothpick before long if you keep losing all this weight.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not the way I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want the Linda Hamilton Terminator 2 look.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want it to be tough.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to kick people's ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then take out a submachine gun and go blow away.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm also going to take gun safety classes this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember this was the discussion last January, is that Jamie was going to get a gun.
[SPEAKER_18]: I couldn't afford a gun last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully the discussion went away for a while, and now, great, it's back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie got a gun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: When I go postal, the first place I'm coming is here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, you couldn't resist that one.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, I'm gonna, you know, we're talking about getting like, you know, a little crappy .22 rifle, but I'm gonna work up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remind me again.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you need a gun for?
[SPEAKER_18]: To shoot stuff, duh!
[SPEAKER_18]: Stress relief!
[SPEAKER_05]: Stress relief, she says.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you gonna be shooting?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not gonna be going to golf?
[SPEAKER_05]: An animal object.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not gonna be going to golf land, are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stray dogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to remember that Roseville Golf Land, for those who have never been there, one of our local arcades we play at, it's two stories, and not a lot goes on on the second story.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except me with a sniper rifle.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my fear.
[SPEAKER_18]: Defile my machine, I dare you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you think it would be quite humorous, though, if they put like a silent scope machine up there?
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, that'd be rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was sick on Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was sick with like this nasty fatigue, which actually lasted into Sunday.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I was, I got up, I went to breakfast, went to bed.
[SPEAKER_18]: Got up, went to dinner over at Dan's aunt's house.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then when he was, I said, just take me home.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not going to be able to hang out with your cousins and play video games.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go play DDR at your cousin's house.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, Jamie, go bed.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went home.
[SPEAKER_18]: I sat up for about an hour just, you know, checking my email, settling stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: My ass was in bed.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was like, no, I can't deal with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, I was asleep for most of Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, in some ways, sometimes it's better that way to be asleep for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I did get nifty presents.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got gift cards.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which means that the day after, I was
[SPEAKER_18]: Basically wearing myself out shopping, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was very fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went shopping with Tia and Jessica, and we had a fun time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The day after Christmas is kind of a nightmare shopping day, though, because I remember that I was at Best Buy, I think, that day, and I just... Oh my gosh, it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: The line was going around the block.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just the thing is that I didn't have...
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, basically, I was really, really, I shouldn't by all rights have been out, but it's the day after freaking Christmas, sales, you know, womanly instinct is stronger than fatigue sometimes, and then I had an eggnog frappuccino.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish Starbucks would never get rid of those because they're so good and I know they're going to be gone Monday probably.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm actually glad they're gone because they proved to be too much temptation especially with the Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: The one thing that keeps me away from the Starbucks by my present location of work is the fact that it's right by a freaking Target.
[SPEAKER_18]: So traffic is enough to keep me away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people out there are very, very anti-Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for those of you guys that don't have a Starbucks in your neighborhood, just wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll have one soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a coffee shop for those that didn't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have a Mississippi orgy going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mississippi orgy can wait.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not week and day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Two.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just wanted to say Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not as bad as you people make it out to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have great, some of their coffee is so good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Even if it is a month old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I'm sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_18]: Their coffee beans are a month old.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least.
[SPEAKER_18]: But no, in Mississippi it's law that if you have more than three people in the same room, at least of course one has to be of a different gender, and they're not wearing shoes, it's an orgy.
[SPEAKER_18]: and the state of Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have got to be kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not kidding you at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie doesn't have shoes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Guana Girl doesn't have shoes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have shoes on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good thing we're not in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank God we're not in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry people in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_18]: But thank God.
[SPEAKER_05]: With all due respect to our friends in Mississippi, thank God we're not you.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, you know, I actually have room to say this because I've been in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm from Alabama.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have been in Mississippi quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: My mom works in Biloxi.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like California.
[SPEAKER_18]: And also, as far as the rest of my weekend day has been, it's just been, today has been kind of, yesterday was really just weird for me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd have to say it ended well.
[SPEAKER_18]: It ended very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: But today has just been like, ugh, rain.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed you were a little drained yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were doing the Top 10, 14 show, whatever, 10 or 14, whatever it was, over on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think we were all feeling a little drained after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're just so used to doing these things on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I had...
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: And they had KR3, and so I knew the only way that I'd get to hear Waiting For You was if I was the one to sing it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I was like, okay, well, I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And everyone was like, oh, that song's cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who did that?
[SPEAKER_18]: And so I got to be all nerdy and say, hey, that's from Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_18]: You should play that.
[SPEAKER_18]: But today's just been, you know... Yesterday, though, see, I was headachy and sick all New Year's night, New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then yesterday morning, I was just feeling really...
[SPEAKER_18]: Just out of it because I did something really stupid the night before after consuming two bottles of Guinness in ten minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for those of you that were listening about six months ago when we had our last drunk show, was it that long?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: When I passed out in your bed and then proceeded to eat four waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was the same show where I was kicking at the wall going, I'm in the Matrix, I'm in the Matrix.
[SPEAKER_18]: I will buy you some damn waffles, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next Saturday, I will take you for waffles.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, free food, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I say this on the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next Saturday, or at least a Saturday in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next Saturday, we will go get waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're backpedaling.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, next Saturday, we will get waffles.
[SPEAKER_18]: Keep your schedule free.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to tag along.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to buy me waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll buy my own waffle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Challenge Breakfast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are we going to go to Country Waffles?
Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they got peanut butter banana waffles there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Waffles blessed by Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki says that for a reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the Country Waffles place...
[SPEAKER_05]: is decorated in Jesus, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it has a Jesus theme to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you've been to places like this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some places have, like, you know, the jungle theme, and some places have the, you know, the element theme and the cave theme.
[SPEAKER_05]: This place has a Jesus theme.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was going to take you there, and then they changed management.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_18]: Do they have whole grain waffles?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I'm just waiting for the Virgin Mary to show up in my waffle so I can sell it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, damn, you can make a killing on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you remember that guy that sold the French toast that had the Virgin Mary's likeness in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't it like 10 years old or something?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, he had saved it for 10 years and finally was like, time to move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sorry to keep interrupting.
[SPEAKER_18]: That reminds me of, you remember the old Bloom County comics?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: The first opus.
[SPEAKER_18]: They had the one about the woman who had the image of Elvis in mold on her refrigerator.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then later on the crowds dispersed because it turned into Mr. Ed.
[SPEAKER_18]: The mold crew.
[SPEAKER_18]: But anyway, I'm in a much better mood now than I was.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was in a crap mood all day.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I'm happy now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Look at me grin.
[SPEAKER_18]: And of course the people listening will never ever see this because I fear...
[SPEAKER_05]: Webcams.
[SPEAKER_18]: The webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't heard a lot from you yet tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: But little does she realize, we've hidden a hidden camera up above Rob to capture her without her knowing... Oh, just a second.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can bite me.
[SPEAKER_18]: HotOrangeLoungeUpskirtCam.com I'm wearing jeans.
[SPEAKER_18]: Doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why nobody visits that site.
[SPEAKER_07]: New Year's Eve?
[SPEAKER_07]: We played Trivial Pursuit 90s Edition and watched South Park.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and Torture the Cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um... But not with a gun, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, with a whip.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about all I did, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I didn't have to do any more potlucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid company.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I'll go later, so let's hear from some guests.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the mic getting handed over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Jazz, who, by the way...
[SPEAKER_05]: won one of our Kiryamoka CDs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I remember right, one of the rules for the contest was that being here so many times rendered you ineligible, but you were like just under that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been here once before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so now this is your second.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it, like three times?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was going to say, that's kind of funny if this would push you over that limit after you already won the contest, but... He, he, he.
[SPEAKER_03]: Technicalities rule.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't you end up giving away that CD to one of your friends?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, for Christmas I gave it to my best friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what did she say?
[SPEAKER_03]: She said, oh my God, a bunch of times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and every time we got teamed together we would kick ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a rule about when Rob plays Mario Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be Princess Peach or I throw a fit like a little baby, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I took Daisy because Rob already took Peach and I got mad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so after New Year's I slept for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I woke up and then I came here for the Top 14 show and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then we went back to Jessica's place and we all slept.
[SPEAKER_03]: Together?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, we played Rumble Roses a lot and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, don't be sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumble Roses is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: The story mode is just hilarious for that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so today I went to RVGL for the first time in like ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not as bad as it was about a year ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: If he'd gone about a year ago, it would have been like, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now, it's improving.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you say hello to the new 2DX machine that has no monitor?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, I just played Taiken 5 all day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I finally have a card.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though it costs $5.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's good, damn it.
$5?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's $5 for a card.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, the chick related to, uh, Jun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Asuka?
[SPEAKER_18]: Asuka, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same person as you?
[SPEAKER_18]: Just because Jin's moves are not fun anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm kind of a Tekken retard, so explain something to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: What exactly is the difference between Tekken 4 and Tekken 5, besides the card thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tekken 4 was dumb and Tekken 5 isn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Tekken 4.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like Tekken 4 a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tekken 4 was basically, to me, it seemed like Tekken was trying to be like DOA and it did not work at all for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Tekken 5 is a lot more like Tag, which I loved, so it worked a lot for better.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't care for Tag, but I do like Tekken 5 just because I was a Jin player in Tekken 2.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's why I played Jin, because I was also a Kazuya player.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's the guy without the shirt that all the girls swoon over?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jin?
[SPEAKER_18]: Then again, there's also Hwarang.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he was the Korean guy with the red hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, no, I'm not talking about Hwarang.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about Jin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is Jin in Tekken 5?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he's still hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was my next question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that was about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to Islander.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_22]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_22]: Week was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just spent all... Work was so damn slow.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just spent my entire day trying to find stuff to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was to the point where we were cutting papers just for scratch paper.
[SPEAKER_22]: I spent about a day doing that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just out of sheer boredom.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was horrible.
[SPEAKER_22]: Were you making little crafts out of them, too?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, it's really funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: One of our roommates downloaded... He actually printed up some papers on how to make origami rhinos and left them at work.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I was half-concerning actually making some, but didn't get around to doing it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, anyways.
[SPEAKER_22]: Other than that, you know, spent New Year's... You know, I didn't have as many jello shots as I should have.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, absolutely, good stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah, like, you know, Jazz and I played a lot of Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_22]: He played Tekken 5, I played DLC, like I always do.
[SPEAKER_22]: because DLC is my crack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it just me, or is there now starting to become like a little Roseville Golf Land following for Derby Owners Club?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, there is, there is.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was actually playing, and there was this one guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there are people I've never seen before.
[SPEAKER_22]: There was one guy who was playing, and he had some pretty good horses.
[SPEAKER_22]: And whenever he saw mine pop up, he was, I could always hear a sigh from the back.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like, ah, damn, I'm going to be in for it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I could not beat this fucker.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could not beat him.
[SPEAKER_22]: When we finally left, he actually turned around and said, hey, man, you're pretty good, and
[SPEAKER_22]: I was like, wow, okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah, there is a little following there, and I hope it really takes off.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the beginning, though, if I remember right, half the following was just Milpitas people driving up to see their machine.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, and the people calling in saying, hey, we want our machine back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, whatever happened with that?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: That does kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're in that area, in Milpitas area, and to have a machine like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poop, poop, poop.
[SPEAKER_06]: True, true, true.
[SPEAKER_22]: They can pay twice as much money.
[SPEAKER_22]: I did that for a long time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: About RVGL, though, there was one very odd thing that I saw.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing Drum Mania, sucking like usual because I don't play Drum Mania, and there's this guy next to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was obvious to me that he's kind of mentally handicapped in some way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then he went up to the Guitar Freak's screen and either licked it or sniffed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was just mortified beyond all belief.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe he didn't understand how to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was like sniffing Tran or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, what the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, that was a little scary, so I ran away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can smell your cunt from here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh no, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a film reference.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob is red.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think what made that so funny is because that was really out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, just... Not only was it out of nowhere, but it was so obscure...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, that's what we're here to do, to fulfill your naughty words quotient of the week.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what I get for missing Rocky all this time.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to get it someplace.
[SPEAKER_20]: Week was relatively calm.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like Jamie was saying, we did the whole big, massive shopping trip on Sunday, which was pretty cool because...
[SPEAKER_20]: I have really, really, really, really, really needed new clothing.
[SPEAKER_20]: I've been shrinking out of everything that I own and it's very difficult to find new clothes that are at a decent price for big people.
[SPEAKER_05]: But best new reason to buy new clothes, though.
[SPEAKER_20]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I took my $200 and got a bunch of new bras and all that.
[SPEAKER_00]: La, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, those suckers cost a lot, buddy.
[SPEAKER_20]: I paid $52 for four bras, and that was on sale.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Walmart, $5 for a three-pack undies.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's hard to find... Okay, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's hard to find bras this big for cheap prices.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like, you know, it truly is an over-the-shoulder bra-ble-harter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear that, boys?
[SPEAKER_05]: Big bras.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what that means?
[SPEAKER_20]: I need this reference!
[SPEAKER_20]: But we ended up going over to Old Navy and found my jackpot.
[SPEAKER_20]: I managed to get four shirts and two pairs of pants for $100, and I was all super happy because I told myself I wouldn't get anything over a certain size, and I didn't, so yay!
[SPEAKER_20]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: My week was pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_20]: I fell asleep a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what the holidays are for, though.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was really tired.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I pulled a butt muscle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now how did you pull a butt muscle?
[SPEAKER_20]: I was at the gym on Friday doing my FitTrack appointment with Jamie's and my mutual trainer.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I was doing some sort of chest press, and as I stood up to move to another machine, my butt muscle just went, tweak!
[SPEAKER_20]: And suddenly my butt muscle hurt like hell.
[SPEAKER_20]: So my butt muscles hurt ever since, kind of on and off.
[SPEAKER_20]: My butt sores.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think I need one of those little butt pillows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something you can strap to your bottom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh, I'm so glad like half our studio isn't wired up right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: I won't torture you with more butt muscle stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what they tune in for.
[SPEAKER_20]: And my socks are in the dryer.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because my feet were wet.
[SPEAKER_05]: This show, honestly, it's about Bomani and it's about Iguana Girls, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh yeah, and I did that show yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about the show a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to recap the whole show because I assume that it's going to be played again later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we'll talk about the show.
[SPEAKER_20]: I already made my AIDS joke for the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_19]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_19]: I spent the holidays up in the bay with my folks.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it was pretty good except for the fact that I had internet on Tuesday, the day that I arrived there.
[SPEAKER_19]: By Wednesday, I didn't have internet until Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which didn't really matter anyway because I ended up being sick from...
[SPEAKER_19]: Christmas Day till the Tuesday that I had, or not the Tuesday I had to leave, but, you know, the last day I was supposed to be at my folks.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, that kind of sucked, because I didn't have internet, and then I got sick.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, yeah, it was basically like a stress panic type deal, because it was like the first time I had been back to my parents' house since I moved out.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I don't know why it happened, but I guess stress is kind of...
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, known to do that, I guess, and that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But Christmas was good, got some DVDs I wanted, and all that.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I was happy about that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And New Year's was spent just, or New Year's Eve rather, was spent just watching the TV until the fireworks went off, and then the news station was kind of cool because we had, you know, four sets of fireworks going off at the same time, so that was pretty interesting to watch.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then I had a Bloody Mary for the first time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel drank, oh my god!
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, no, I cheated, because I only had a third of that, and then, like, a third of a glass of champagne, and then I was just like, done.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I still don't like champagne.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, there's that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, I've been bad, because I've been on a certain game for the past... Let's see, wait.
[SPEAKER_19]: Probably since... Wednesday...
[SPEAKER_19]: Not as bad as the other two in here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I've been playing that just a little too much, but it's okay, because it took me four months to get to that point, so you know what, just yay, alright?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd just like to point out for the record that I have not been quite the addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did sign on to Final Fantasy XI for a little bit this morning, and I got a message from DDR Angel, and suddenly I noticed that, like, dang, that girl's gained six levels since yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much has she been playing?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, lots of PL, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So my week and my day, yeah, okay, a little bit of Final Fantasy XI, but not too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did go out and do some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Iguana Girls New Year's Eve, bashed a little gathering of people there, and I learned how to play Texas Hold'em by watching Celebrity Poker, which I hadn't done before.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I love Kathy Griffin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my God, I love her.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even though she annoys the hell out of most people, I think she's so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she was on the show, and she was the first person booted out that particular episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to ruin it for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was the first person booted out that particular episode, but it was a good watch, and I learned how to play Texas Hold'em.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, next time you guys have a poker night, it's on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, outside of that, New Year's Day, one of my buddies had his birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he lives out in the middle of nowhere, California, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: He lives about an hour's drive from here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And once you get about an hour out of Sacramento, this is why they call it Cowtown, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're going the hour towards the bay, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other hours all around it is nothingness.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looked like the town out of Elvira, Mistress of the Dark, kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be able to pass Katas back to back again without having to stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is how it's been lately, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than that, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a whole lot else for me to report that I can think of off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe later, so we go through the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, we're going to go to a break here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back from the break, we're going to talk about...
[SPEAKER_05]: and some New Year's news.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want to talk about that other new music game that I finally got to take a look at today, even though it's been out for like three months.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll talk about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that'll be it when we come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: This break we're going to have some music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some things that Jamie was saying there kind of inspired me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I thought we could do a break of music that makes Jamie angry.
[SPEAKER_18]: That makes me angry?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was it all solitary?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's going to be the safari.
[SPEAKER_05]: to start it off.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like the song.
[SPEAKER_18]: As long as you don't play the fast, crappy one.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually like the song, but it pisses me off to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are going to be songs that piss Jamie off to play.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although I did manage to stay about a 50% on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_14]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, our old buddy Mel there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know when he's coming back to the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was one of our very early shows.
[SPEAKER_18]: That...
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe Mel came out for episode 6, which was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_18]: Back when I was still using the headset.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh gosh, oh yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: That I acquired from... Memories.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to have an official nostalgia segment of the show, I think, because it comes up every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember back when Orange Lounge was cool?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, we're always cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I'm just playing around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, what's going on this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: We had the big show we were doing here yesterday over on that other radio station, DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun, it was a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always fun to partner up with another station, kind of put your resources together to do something fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty cool to be a part of the first live show that DDR Freak had really done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it the first live show?
[SPEAKER_20]: There was a very, very brief, like, 15-minute thing that I did that was just me being incredibly bored and experimental.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I did, you know, the whole radio DJ bit for a whopping... You're listening to DDR music!
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the top of the hour.
[SPEAKER_20]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I consider yesterday being the first DDR Freak Live special.
[SPEAKER_20]: The first...
[SPEAKER_05]: Horde Show, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: The one you've got to whore out to the masses to get people to tune in.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because, you know, I've done all of the other crap with the history of DDR.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, it's cool and all, but I want interaction.
[SPEAKER_20]: I want to be able to get the people involved.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whenever we get the people involved, that's when we get the numbers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was going on and a very interesting list.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a top 14.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was originally going to be a top 10.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, because not enough people got their butts out there and voted.
[SPEAKER_05]: To their credit though, it was only a day, but still more people could have done their part.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's alright, it happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the holidays, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it ended up, because of all the ties, there was a top 14 list they came up with.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to ruin it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of you guys probably already figured it out for yourselves, maybe, if you know how to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or some of you guys may have tuned in.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there are going to be replays coming up soon, and those will be announced over on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: For you dial-up users, because I don't think it's going to show up on DDR Freak low-band, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_20]: Low-band is pretty much dying out, and it will probably be disbanded after...
[SPEAKER_20]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: We can say a pretty good quality.
[SPEAKER_05]: And again, if you guys don't know what MP3 Pro is, and we're not sounding like FM quality to you, then you're missing the MP3 Pro codec.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you want to just get more information on that, go to www.orangeonsradio.com and click on the FAQ, and that'll give you all the information on the MP3 Pro codec.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're listening to us in your iTunes player right now, iTunes does not have MP3 Pro codec.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's actually a much clearer version of the stream available.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the information is over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and I want to say that the DDR Freak Top 10 Countdown we will broadcast for our dial-up users and for those that want to catch it one time and that's Tuesday night as part of Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have to tune in to Jamie's show because she'll play the Top 10 show as part of her show.
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you don't, I'll kick your butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same rule as always.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tune in or she'll kick your butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, what did you think of the list that ended up, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you kind of surprised with it?
[SPEAKER_20]: It was... I'm not incredibly surprised.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm surprised at how many songs from how many different mixes got in there.
[SPEAKER_20]: Which, you know, pleasant surprise on that front.
[SPEAKER_20]: But I'm really going to fucking kill Dawn.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm killing Frequency.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's all there is to it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dynamite Rave should not have been in that list at all.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_22]: And let alone people voting for Dynamite Rave.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true, because not only did it have to get nominated, but it had to get voted on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're not stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know that folks have their little cliques out there, because, you know, hell, I had my friends voting for Skulk.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, but there were other people voting for Skulk, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's why it made it in there, but.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, you know, overall, I was pretty pleased to see some of the stuff that ended up on the list.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, you know, I'm glad.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was very happy to see a lot of 2DX representation.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of 2DX representation.
[SPEAKER_05]: My biggest surprise was the fact that I think on the whole list there was only two songs that were actually new in 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe there's another couple.
[SPEAKER_20]: Not enough love for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: original stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, and that kind of surprised me because I thought...
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize that some people have issues with the US mixes and the way that they've been presented.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, Extreme, people bitch about the interface, although... They don't bitch about everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, they bitch about everything, but the biggest bitch being the interface, although, you know, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, most people are okay with the songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I hear a few bitches here and they're like, eh, why is YMCA on there?
[SPEAKER_05]: That song's gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, usually, people seem to enjoy the US exclusive songs, especially Max 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think nobody can really complain about Max 2.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was great music.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_20]: All of the Max 2 stuff, even some of the Max stuff, it was just great.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, oh well.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, don't go there.
[SPEAKER_20]: DarkBlackForest.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was a running gag on this show for a while, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was, thanks to Darkstown.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Darkstown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who don't know what the Heleguana girl's talking about, here is a little clip, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a long way to go, honey.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm afraid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where are we going?
[SPEAKER_11]: Into the dark.
[SPEAKER_11]: Big.
[SPEAKER_21]: Black.
[SPEAKER_21]: Far.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, you need to get...
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm afraid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where are we going?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up and take your clothes off, bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: I paid you cash up front.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now take it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well... And Dark Black Forest could be a euphemism for something if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't need to go there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone who isn't very well kept...
[SPEAKER_18]: We've had the C-bomb once.
[SPEAKER_05]: Both boys and girls can have this issue, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Shaved ears, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave it to this show to go straight to the toilet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thankfully that song was not on the countdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because heaven forbid that subject came up yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I guess I have to, this would be a good time to ask this question, because, you know, DDR Freak, although I don't like to just sit here and talk about DDR Freak, let's face it though, hon, it's a big part of the community, and anybody that listens to this show knows what DDR Freak is.
[SPEAKER_05]: They may not post everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Freak is kind of family friendly, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of people get frustrated because they can't type shit and fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets censored.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although some of the censored stuff is really funny.
[SPEAKER_20]: I personally like doggy.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_20]: I like poopy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like cigarette.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, the best was before when they first tried to start it, ass turned into butt.
[SPEAKER_22]: So someone would try to type Massachusetts and type M-A-S-S and it turned into M-butt.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now it's just buttocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And buttocks choosets?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so is there a lot of youngins on DDR Freak, or do you just want to keep a G rating?
[SPEAKER_20]: We're trying to keep it as G rated as possible just for...
[SPEAKER_20]: The overall audience.
[SPEAKER_20]: We get quite a few mentions on all of the different mixes that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_20]: And one of the first places that people are going to go when they look up DDR is going to be DDR Freaks.
[SPEAKER_20]: So we have to kind of try to keep that family-friendly vibe going so that somebody's 13-year-old kid isn't going to be coming on there and their parents are going, Oh my God, is that the word fuck on your screen?
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, freaking out or something.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, obviously, there's ways around the filters, and if you're smart enough, you can kind of... Just ask any of the ops in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: They know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Or just quote somebody's post, and you'll be able to see it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, wait, I gave away a secret.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, yeah, we don't really... We don't really...
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel kind of bad because I dropped the F-bomb on yesterday's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of forgetting that whole family-friendly vibe.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I didn't say what Loki said earlier.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not too concerned about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was the one sitting there making AIDS jokes.
[SPEAKER_20]: If there's nothing less family-friendly...
[SPEAKER_20]: Or politically correct, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just had to ask about the family thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Here's the catch-22 that we have.
[SPEAKER_20]: We have specifically, when you sign up for the site, when you sign up for the forums, it asks you, it says, I am over the age of 13.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you cannot agree to that unless you're over the age of 13 or you're lying.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, unfortunately, we do have, you know, 11-year-olds, 12-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, how old is the youngest poster, though?
[SPEAKER_20]: We've got, like, DDR Bot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, wow.
[SPEAKER_20]: And isn't DDR Bot, like, 10 or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so, I think so.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, the youngest, I think, is probably around 9 or 10.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it's not... We usually don't cause problems about it unless they're causing issues.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it's just a matter of maturity, typically.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you could...
[SPEAKER_20]: So I've met a lot of 16-year-olds that were less mature than the 9-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've dropped the F-bomb quite a lot on DDR Freak on the boards, but, you know, you just... They're going to learn it sometime.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the way you say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes it's not what you're saying, it's the way you say it, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I am an instructor of customer service.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can tell you kids, if you ever go out and get a customer service job, your instructor is going to tell you the same thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Respond.
[SPEAKER_20]: Don't react.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not about what you say.
[SPEAKER_05]: What you say is only 10% of how the information is perceived.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, 35% of statistics are made up on the spot.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought it was 43%.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's how you say it, kids.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I really don't give a crap about your problem, but let's try what we can do to just BS our way through it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_05]: See, when DarkSakura said that it had a nice friendly atmosphere to it, you know?
[SPEAKER_18]: Who's been doing customer service for too damn long?
[SPEAKER_18]: As I raise my hand.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ironic enough, I just went through a stupid class in school doing that exact same shit.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_20]: All that just for one stinking little piece of paper.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_05]: Freak
[SPEAKER_05]: So tune into that, definitely.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sure with a hefty disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just the standard disclaimers that... Well, we have a disclaimer right in the intro to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does say, there may be a scene of nudity in this program, and there may be... This program contains naughty language!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, shit!
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's not my fault if you tuned in halfway through.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should have been here on time.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not like I started at a different time every single...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're here whether you are or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: And believe me, we've done this show when nobody was here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of nobody being here, I happen to know that a lot of folks weren't here for last week's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know because I got the ratings, okay people?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, this Friday on DDR Freak, great chance for you guys to catch that episode if you missed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Friday, 6 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I'm going to say, I don't want to ruin what went on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we had our own DDR Freak the movie parody thing going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Priceless, you gotta hear it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Man, that's a subject that hasn't been heard of for years.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just took that subject and ran away with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that it's old news, but somehow it got brought up last week and we just ran away with it.
[SPEAKER_20]: On a random side note that I just remembered again, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: We've been playing DDR for four years now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh, this is our official four-year anniversary of DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really.
[SPEAKER_20]: Today is?
[SPEAKER_20]: Actually, last Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not today, but the first day we went to play DDR was sometime between Christmas and New Year's.
[SPEAKER_20]: I played for the first time, well, not for the first first time, but, you know, for first regular time.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like our first regular session was... Yeah, that was on the 26th.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little known fact, Iguana Girl and I played our first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most people that listen to the show know that now because I know it's not the first time it's come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we played our first game of DDR together in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_21]: October 2000.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 2000.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we didn't play regularly until one of us spotted the machine at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it me?
[SPEAKER_20]: You did it.
[SPEAKER_20]: You saw it.
[SPEAKER_20]: You played it.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then I was jealous because I couldn't play it until the day after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember now.
[SPEAKER_05]: My memory's being jogged.
[SPEAKER_20]: I went down there because... You went there on Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went there to go play pinball or something.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I was all pissed off because you had two more days than me and that's what I kept...
[SPEAKER_21]: The reason why you were so much better than me is because of those three days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazingly enough, suddenly I was passing nine-footers on the third day and just left Iguana Girl in the dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not quite.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not quite, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: It took me a long time to pass a nine-footer.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember a certain expedition to a certain golf land in a certain Milpitas to see a certain machine.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember the first time I met Islander.
[SPEAKER_18]: was at Fanime 2001 when I was cosplaying Emi.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, it wouldn't have been then.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it was before that, but I mean the first... It was February.
[SPEAKER_18]: February.
[SPEAKER_18]: Right, because of the... The Milpitas trip.
[SPEAKER_18]: Right, but the second time then was at Fanime.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was sort of a little standoffish because of the shirt.
[SPEAKER_20]: He was wearing a flip shirt, wasn't he?
[SPEAKER_20]: A flip shirt, yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was something to wear.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was just something I didn't have.
[SPEAKER_22]: At the time, I was collecting just random shirts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, boys and girls, what you don't know is he went home later and changed the oil with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I also remember that that's when I met a bunch of people in the community.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was at that particular convention.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was a great convention.
[SPEAKER_22]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember sitting on the floor after two days of sleep deprivation.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then Wendell sits next to me, after two days of drinking.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, he was drunk, I was sleep deprived, so we were both in about the same frame of mind, having an interesting conversation.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then he fell asleep.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was actually in the arcade room, and I fell asleep on the chair that was right next to the DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_18]: That big comfy one?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_22]: And so I was sitting there, and people were walking up, and they were looking at me going, Oh man, this guy's not doing his job.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm like, what's...
[SPEAKER_18]: My first DDR machine, though, was the year before that at Anime Expo 2000.
[SPEAKER_18]: They had the third mix there.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was like, why are the arrows have colors?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I started playing with the first one on PlayStation in 98.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then the only one I had ever owned was my second mix on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: What's this boy song?
[SPEAKER_05]: This song's great.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, God, you whored that out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, my God, you whored that out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was so tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I whored Boys by SmileDK on DDR USA.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it pissed me off because when we were first starting out, it was hard for me.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was having a hard time doing that on basic.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, it's like, it's kind of frustrating, you know, thinking back on it.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, yeah, I was...
[SPEAKER_20]: Pissed off at the fact that you kept doing boys, because I was like, you're going to kill me!
[SPEAKER_05]: But I love boys, the song.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sure, the song.
[SPEAKER_20]: But then again, I forced you through 20 November about 5 billion times, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember 20 November-a-thons, yes I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_20]: And our massive attempts at trying to take on the board, the high score board.
Oh.
[SPEAKER_20]: Those are the days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back then, that was when Konami was doing their net ranking, right?
[SPEAKER_20]: And back then, you could score the same on a basic song as you could on a maniac song.
[SPEAKER_20]: Or it was something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think it was... I think what it was is that you... Honestly, there weren't that many people playing DDR yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there wasn't that many people on the scoreboards, and we were kind of like, wow, if we could...
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember at least a couple times that I had to do EOTC five times in a row.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were in the top five.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were we really?
[SPEAKER_05]: We were in the top five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were we?
[SPEAKER_20]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_18]: I worked my ass off to get first place on that damn machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie was the buns, because she was first and last.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was first and last.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Brad, lanky style, on Thursday Night's Program, was the meat, because he was in the middle.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was third, and I was the fruit, second and fourth.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know how I got first place?
[SPEAKER_05]: How?
[SPEAKER_18]: I ended up getting first place by doing Dynamite Rave doubles basic.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were one of those ones that whored Dynamite Rave in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was one of the ones that whored Dynamite Rave.
[SPEAKER_18]: But then again, I was very proud because Dynamite Rave was the first five-footer I could do in doubles.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what song I used to do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Love to Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nostalgia City.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when all the cool kids were doing that?
[SPEAKER_20]: I was never a cool kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never did that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not even once?
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm too fat to do that.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm serious!
[SPEAKER_20]: I would have fallen over if I tried to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to remember that you did some kind of white girl freestyle.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I was doing white girl freestyle that didn't require me to actually have to hit the pad with my hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I... well, alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: When you get down there, it's hard to bring yourself back up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard to bring yourself back up, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one thing to fall.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you gotta keep in mind that when I first started, I was 270.
[SPEAKER_20]: So it took me quite a long time to lose my initial 30 pounds.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, you know, unfortunately I gained more than that back.
[SPEAKER_20]: But...
[SPEAKER_20]: I've lost it again, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're a clean slate now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for those of you guys that weren't, you know, you've only been playing DDR since like 4th, Max, whatever, and you kind of missed out on those USA days, if you want to see what we're talking about, go to DDR Freak, look at the step chart for Love To Me Basic, and you'll see several portions of the song.
[SPEAKER_20]: The left-right jump.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, you have left-right jumps, and then down-up jumps.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you would jump on left-right, and then hand-plant backwards, and then go forwards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you demonstrating on cam, even though it only updates every 30 seconds?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Islander will demonstrate in super slow motion for you to see this guy's on cam.
[SPEAKER_05]: He looks like he's going to take a shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we'll see something on cam.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's taking a backward shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes I wish we were a TV show, I really do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that we could get booed by the Nilsons?
[SPEAKER_05]: Please, our ratings couldn't be any worse than G4 Tech TV, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're getting beat by the Golf Channel, okay, something's wrong.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, Tech TV came up in conversation over lunch today.
[SPEAKER_05]: How so?
[SPEAKER_18]: The Soul Calibur dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soul Calibur dates?
[SPEAKER_18]: Dan was telling me about something they had on Tech TV where they had someone going on a blind date with Cervantes from Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_18]: What are you going to have for dinner?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want your soul!
[SPEAKER_05]: We never had Tech TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was G4 and then G4 basically assimilated Tech TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If any G4 Tech TV people are listening, as much as we give you guys shit, we would sell our souls to you in a minute, so call me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think now's a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: On that note, let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could do some music that would remind us of the good old days.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's start it off with... I'm looking, I'm looking to see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back after this, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everybody, when you hear this song, practice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get up off your chair and practice the move that Islander was just showing you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's your name, Brian, and what's your storyline?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dreaming, dreaming, grooving, if you know what I mean, it's moving on the scene, alright Take the bumping, take the whining, take the moving, I'm with the DarkSakura King
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: With apologies to Iguana Girl, I can't resist this next one.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Jess, I just couldn't resist.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's been like a good, like what, three, four years since you heard it last, maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, so many memories, so little time.
[SPEAKER_05]: How can I choose?
[SPEAKER_18]: That's still the sluttiest song ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm being told F you in the chatroom, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, we'll get to the F yous a week a little later, alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: She's not... I'm Sawi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm Sawi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will be Fawi.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's typing messages.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, she says I'm not cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and a couple minutes here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I opened it up for a particular person to get through, which I'm hoping to hear from in just a second here.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, I thought maybe we would kind of start moving into the sim update for this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know Loki's got a lot he wants to say for the sim update, so I'll let him get started, but just keep in mind I might have to pick up a call midway through.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad I'm top priority there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, this week there's a few things as opposed to the normal nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDRUK, still new, no new sim files, they're still waiting on beginner steps for the Ultramix 2 stuff, but it's close to being done, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, there's also a little theme that just got released on Bomani Cell right now, only because DDR Mania X is down, and that theme would be Techno Fiend 3, that's right, the most kickass skin ever for Step Mania has now released its final version of it, and it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I don't even play Step Mania, really, and I know what Techno Fiend is, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's that good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I really think the skin is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it just, whoever did the work on that, kudos to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is the sexiest skin out there, and you gotta check it out, it's just, it's really awesome, lots of humor and little Easter eggs thrown in the background there, but, um, it's just, it's really nice looking, they've added, um, it's just completely redone almost, and I don't know how to describe it, it's just very well put together, very, um, optimized, and just runs really well, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, you'll have to go check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of hard to find right now, only because, you know, DDR Maniacs is down.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what you need to do is go to my style, go to their DDR sim file section there, and just do a search for Technofiend.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll find it probably, it's actually on the second or third page on there right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you should find it to download, and it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a good 14 megs, but it is a really good sim skin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, there's also the OSC3 Plus Remix, which is the step-file contest where they had all the songs where they're taking new steps or they're being remixed or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: that's available for download also on my style and they also have their own download pack that's available right now with just I think a couple more sim files and it's DR5Key Classics is the theme for this one so check those out over there as well and that's all okay for those that don't really know what Technofiend is all about what exactly makes this skin so damn cool
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say Star Wars because it has a lot of Star Wars parodies in it, but not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's just very different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes DDR all futuristic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes it feel like a 2010 game or something, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just gives a very futuristic theme to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be the way I would put it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's sexy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that would probably be the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like what a new, if they were to reinvent DDR and release it now, what it would look like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe not, because, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: If they were to, you know, spend the amount of time that they did on, like, finding good music with designing the interface, this is what it would look like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any comments from anybody else about Techno Fiend?
[SPEAKER_18]: I know... It was purdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You saw a little bit of it?
[SPEAKER_18]: It was purdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very pretty.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, Jazz... I felt excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've used this Techno Fiend before, yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the first time I've seen it, but I'm definitely going to download it when I get back to Walnut Creek today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's sexy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: What now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess we're going to go ahead and get into the cage match, and we'll come back, and hopefully that call we can get to, and then... The new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're talking about the new game now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I keep putting it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's talk about the new game now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about the new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I finally got to check out this game for the PlayStation 2, thanks to Islander and Iguana Girl bringing it over for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Technic Beat, and this game's actually been out for like two months, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been out a little while, but I'm just now getting to see it, because I somehow completely missed this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard about it like a month ago, but I'd really missed it somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're pretty familiar with this game, right, Jazz?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us about how this game works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the way this game works is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you choose a character, and you start walking around on a kind of liquidy-type surface, and then circles will appear.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then little circles will appear coming from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you think of the big circles as, like, guide arrows in DDR...
[SPEAKER_03]: and the little circles coming out towards the other circle like the actual arrows then that's what it's kind of like it's basically you want to hit the ripples right so basically you have a little character you start running around and start hitting the ripples and the game is full of a bunch of Namco original songs like old school Namco stuff like Thema Daruga and Pac-Mania Pac-Mania which is awesome Dig Dug even Point Blank but now there's kind of a tie into Bomani isn't there here
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Mania
[SPEAKER_05]: That I heard you play was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was by Sampling Masters Mega, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a little... Like, it was different, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was very different compared to other music games I play lately, which is good, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they need to get away from the moving thing towards the line and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, every game's starting to look like DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot more obscure, and that's what I like about it, because it has...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, like you said, a lot of things are basically wait for it to get to this screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one you have to run around and some characters can't run fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you have to kick the notes around sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then depending on which note you hit, you'll actually kind of change the pitch of the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is pretty cool, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of fun to sometimes play it and you get to remix your own a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of like Amplitude allows you to do in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can have a remix mode in the game where you can make your own stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there look to be a lot of modes in Technic Beat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really get to play with a lot of the others.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you checked out some of the other modes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it's basically the normal stuff they have, like non-stop mode is in there, free mode, like 2DX is in free mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: After you play a song, it's unlocked in free mode, which is hard because there's not really a way to keep track of the songs you've passed in regular game modes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're kind of guessing which ones you've passed already in free mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you go back and check, oh, that's unlocked, yay, oh, that's, nah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, it gets a little annoying, but still it's a great game because it has about 80 songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's only $20.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's one of these budget games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Namco did this one, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was Mastiff and Eureka, which are basically a branch off of Namco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but Katamari Damashii was also by Namco, and I think these two games came out together, actually, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: This only came out in the same manner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it wasn't released that much because they didn't think there was going to be a high demand for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there hasn't been, so it's kind of like... At least for Technic Beat, there hasn't been.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Katamari Damacy, they probably thought the same thing going into it, but boy, were they wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: and I but Technic Beat and we've got a lot of folks in our chat room saying they never even heard of this game yeah so and it's not you know not surprising at all but it is a new music rhythm game that's out there and it's kind of different the way it works you're not going to know a lot of the songs in there are going to be unfamiliar to you unless you play a lot of old school 80s arcade games if you're a mame whore like you have you're a mame whore you've got that multi what does that mean multi arcade machine emulator that is exactly it oh I'm oh I remembered um
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've got that on your computer and you have all these ROMs from crazy places of games you've never heard of, which you're not supposed to do because that's illegal, boys and girls, and I'm not encouraging you to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying if you've already done it, then you probably are familiar with a lot of these old games and they've remixed a lot of these old themes, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only $20.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, this would be a great opportunity to sell it on our website, but we just, you know, we're not that smart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did see that game while I was Christmas shopping, and the first thing I thought was, ooh, should I get that?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, what if it sucks?
[SPEAKER_19]: But now I know, so I might just have to go down and get it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, speaking of music games that suck, I know Islander, you got a chance to play one not too long ago, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Music games that suck?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let me give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: All those people complaining about GameCube DDR, there's something out there for you.
[SPEAKER_22]: And really, you're not missing out.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's by MadCatz, who, you know...
[SPEAKER_22]: for a long time have been making third-party controllers and such, and memory cards and other various accessories, but this being their first game, it was lacking.
[SPEAKER_22]: Boy, was it lacking.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's putting it lightly.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yes, very lightly.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was a pile of steaming poopy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, yeah, the one saving grace was that the soundtrack wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: I liked a lot of the music in there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dear Lord, do I really have to play the full-length, five-minute version of Parents Just Don't Understand on eight arrows?
[SPEAKER_22]: Do I really need to do this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do the arrows even make any sense?
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, imagine we were just discussing Technic Beat, how it has a circle and another circle that comes out to meet it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your arrows are set up in a circular manner.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have up, down, left, right, and the four diagonals.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the arrows appear from the center and move outward.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's very strange looking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is confusing to begin with, a setup like that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Now, another option is the scroll mode, which makes it turn, which turns it into DDR, but up and down are switched.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that was really confusing too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was like just, uh, I'm not, damn it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was real bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: As a matter of fact, I played it for about maybe 30 minutes, looked at Iwana Girl and said, this is a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_22]: Threw it back in the box, went back to GameStop the very next day and said, you know what, let me get a game that is actually cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can I try this in for Mario Party 6?
[SPEAKER_22]: And sure enough, I was able to do that and get some money reimbursed to me, and I was very happy about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: MC Groove's Dance Graze
[SPEAKER_22]: How much was it?
[SPEAKER_22]: At the time, $60.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right now, it's going for $50.
[SPEAKER_22]: You've got to be kidding me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Does it come with a pad or something?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, it comes with a game and a pad.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, but still.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_18]: But even the Mad Catz pad wouldn't be worth $50.
[SPEAKER_18]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, it actually worked well, but I was like, oh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just, oh, it's just bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: People, stay away, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get On The Mic Get On The Mic
[SPEAKER_22]: The game itself is actually pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: It uses a lot of, I mean, of course, it's all hip-hop, but it ranges from stuff like the newer stuff, oh gosh, like Turn It Up and some other strange things, or like Party Up DMX, to like old school stuff like Humpty Dance.
[SPEAKER_22]: and the characters are just hilarious because there's this one stage where you're just starting out your career and you're in your bathroom looking at yourself in the mirror trying to be all hardcore.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wasn't that a scene in 8 Mile?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it's funny because your boombox is on the shelf and it's bouncing and if you're doing well, the whole room starts bouncing and having fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like Parappa's bathroom level.
[SPEAKER_22]: Basically, there you go.
[SPEAKER_22]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except he's not rapping about having to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but that's honestly my favorite song in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great song.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the rain or in the snow, I really gotta go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That made me laugh so hard I peed a little.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah, people, please stay away from NC Crew's Dance Grace, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: That reminds me, I got to check out a little bit of Donkey Konga this week, because one of my buddies got it for Christmas, and he said, you have to play, you have to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he brought it over, kind of like how you guys brought it over a couple weeks ago, but this time I actually had time to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel bad, because you guys brought those games, we didn't even really get to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, got to play a little more Donkey Konga.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I'd seen it at E3, and really, the game was pretty much what I remembered at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: There wasn't a whole lot different, but it's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun!
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some songs in there that are really freaking cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's a cover of, uh, I think I love you, so what am I so afraid of?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's all, like, Happy Britney style, kind of, but not, like, Britney bad, but, like, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but it has that, like, cute Nazi feel to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta get some of those songs and get them on Orange Lounge Radio, because there's some really cute Donkey Konga songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Absolutely, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then there's some, like, really, really, like, okay, this game is obviously for five-year-old songs, because there's, like, the Campfire Medley.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's Foster's Medley in Taiko Drum Master too.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I came this close to picking up Taiko Drum Master today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw it sitting on the shelf and I was like, it's calling my name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it, get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I was like, I must save money for something else.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want that game.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I still want a freaking second pair of maracas.
[SPEAKER_09]: They stopped making Samba de Amigo like three years ago.
[SPEAKER_18]: I wanted them to bring out the tambourine one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, the tambourine game?
[SPEAKER_18]: I would be all over the freaking tambourine game.
[SPEAKER_05]: This coming from somebody who has played Dance Dance Revolution, Para Para Paradise.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played just about almost every music game out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Tambourine Game is the gayest music game I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate the eye toy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So travesty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, just curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, how about that cage match?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about that cage match?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into the cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get into it here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, last week in the Orange Lounge Radio cage match, we were missing a host, so we didn't get a song, because Jamie was out sick.
[SPEAKER_18]: Got the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shakato Tambourine, I think.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, what, shake that tambourine, basically?
[SPEAKER_18]: Basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, we were down to host last week, so we let you guys, the listeners, do something that you have been begging us to do for years now, and that is a chatroom choice song for the cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we let a random chatroom listener, which was, I believe it was Big Red Pimp ended up picking this, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Angel, you helped them find it or something?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, no, actually he already had it, and he told me what it was over private message, and I'm like, ooh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: So it was all him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we had everybody in the chatroom submit a random entry, and we picked one at random, and it was this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And sure enough, you let the chatroom put a song in the cage match, and of course they're going to vote for it, so that song won.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I thought you had a comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: What that means is that Cage Match is all screwed up now because we have a chatroom choice sitting there in the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what we're going to do is this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since Jamie stepped aside last week for the chatroom choice, I will step aside this week so the chatroom choice can be in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if, for whatever reason, it wins again, Loki will be out next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: That means you just didn't want to pick a song to sing.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because I have a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a good song, but I'm going to step aside this week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you listen, by the way, at my suggestion?
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't had a chance to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to hear it for the first time tonight, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So song number one, last week's winner, is a group.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys know this one if you listen to any J-rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Larkin Seal did this song, and the song is called Ready, Steady, Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no, it's not anything like the Paul Oakenfold one, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so again, the way the cage match works, we play three songs for your listening pleasure or displeasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pick your favorite, and your favorite song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Launch Radio's Hermione Music and More program, which runs 24 hours a day, 7 days a week on this station when we're not live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and remember, you've got to be in our chat room to participate, so head on over to www.orangelaunchradio.com and click on chat now so you can participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that being said, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, a clip
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it won last week, so you already know what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_05]: A clip of Larkin Seal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ready, steady, go.
Kato wa kirenai kizu kakaekonde ite mo Chotto ya soto ja tamashii made wa ubawasenai Aoka no nukou de kimi ni deaeta nara Nani kara hanasou
Hey, everybody
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatroom choice, which I'm stepping aside for, is that that song can continue to stay in Cage Match until it gets voted out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Larkin Seal with Ready Steady Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so let's get into tonight's two challengers that will be battling that song.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I just have to make one comment since I wasn't here last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: I do really like Larkin Seal.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't like that as the opening theme for SMA.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: So, chat room did okay on that one, so I'm not going to complain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number two tonight is going to come to us from Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, Loki, what are you picking tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm picking a... First, I found the remix album.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I found the original CD.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is from a group that's calling themselves ProdigyRemix.com And it's actually a group of about four different remixers that completely remixed the brand new album from Prodigy, which is
[SPEAKER_07]: Always Outnumbered and Never Outgunned
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I just want to preface, before we judge the song, I want to preface with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been doing the cage match for about two years now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have been waiting that entire two years for a moment like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That being said, Jamie, what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_21]: It stopped!
[SPEAKER_21]: Zero!
[SPEAKER_06]: Islander, negative two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jazz, girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't like girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guana Girl.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was something from Prodigy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I was waiting for a number, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know...
[SPEAKER_07]: What's sad is that this remix version was better than the original.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the worst part of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just picked this song because I had nothing else.
[SPEAKER_07]: And next week is when I'll have the good song.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I was trying to download.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, I just found it too late.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I give it a zero just to go with everyone else.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, after all the shitty songs I've put in the cage match, because there's been a few, I'm really glad that it's not just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel?
[SPEAKER_19]: Negative 999, that's all.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god, she didn't do something nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Holy crap, you've given the 10 to some really bad stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I'm not meaning this in a mean way, but I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: We'll remind you though, your singing actually did get voted in for the weekly pick.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I think your singing is better than girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to point this out.
[SPEAKER_20]: Girls, girls, girls, girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki now can attest to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the first time a song has ever been put in the cage match and gotten zeros from every single judge, including the one who put it in.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have our show's history tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we've had one where I put it in and everybody else gave it a zero, but I gave it a hundred to balance it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember what song it was, but I know I've been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But remember, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Our opinion sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will the chat room vote it in just to be funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: And let me tell you, that would not be funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll find out because it's really up to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_20]: Jamie... Jamie...
[SPEAKER_18]: I forgot who it is that did this again, but there was a song, and I think, I really do think that this is one that I had on a tape that I bought at the Limited back when I was in my senior year of high school, taking French.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I bought the tape because it was all in French.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was like, oh, cool, I can use it to, you know, practice.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a song called Jolitaxi that I really liked.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, it was a cute song, and I was looking for it and found a remix of it, and this has actually been sort of edging me back into trance, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_18]: So this is a trance mix of Jolitaxi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, now the full name of this is huge, so I'm only going to read it once, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: The artist, Aria Posey, and the song, Jolitaxi, and it's the Jan Wayne remix radio cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow, that's pretty damn long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jolitaxi Jolitaxi
[SPEAKER_11]: In your yellow castle, you know all the streets by heart In your quest, the goal is four days It's the game, the game, the game, the game
Sake, La Musica Jo, C'est La Rumba, Le Duroc au Mambo
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see what everybody thought about song number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll just call it Joe LaTaxi for short.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_18]: I've just been listening to that song on repeat.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, actually, it was... I was listening to it earlier today just trying to keep myself in a good mood, and I give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm still not quite in my trance minute.
[SPEAKER_18]: It does have a couple of slightly overly trance-y annoying things in it, but overall it's such a good song and I like the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you want to get your thought in before you head off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jazz?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It seems very kind of J-trance-y to me, like something Ayumi would do a lot to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's okay, but I don't know, it got a little too trance-y for me, just generic trance-y for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was still good, so I'd give it like a 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Islander?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, that was actually the same score I was going to give it myself.
[SPEAKER_22]: I did like it a lot, and I liked it a lot better than some of the other stuff that was played.
[SPEAKER_22]: That being said, yes, a good solid 7.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sounds very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that song was kind of odd, but it was odd in a good way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, it was kind of one of those songs I just go, huh, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, and honestly, this week it better win, so I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's bouncy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you've heard what we have to say, now let's hear what you have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will pick the winner by placing your vote right after this recap of the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, Larkin Seal, Ready Steady Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number two, ProdigyRemix.com, Girls, the Idiotex Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number three, Girls...
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number three, Jolitaxi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's crying foul.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a little bit longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, there it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might change my F.U.
[SPEAKER_05]: music to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Place your vote now, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully somebody will remind you there in the chat room how you can place your vote if you haven't done so yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to take a call on the Skype line, but I'm going to hold off on that for just a minute because I just remembered something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, oh yeah, let's wait on it for a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll do that Skype line thing in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to go to a quick break, I think, and then come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before we go to the break, though, I thought I'd scan around, see if there's any big news going on here we should talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about the, oh yeah, tell me about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is another game I got to play for the first time this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Guy Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us about what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lovely, lovely, lovely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dun, dun, dun.
[SPEAKER_22]: So now the game's getting recalled.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: So it's being yanked off store shelves with the quickness.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was able to snag an Xbox copy for my cousin for Christmas, and I told him, if you ever sell this thing, I will fucking kill you.
[SPEAKER_22]: You could eBay this probably in about a year for some big cash.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a collector's item now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's right up there with, like, Custer's Revenge now at this point.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to go to a break now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back from this break, we'll go to the Skype line and we'll hear who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Busy show still ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back after this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I haven't even really thought about what kind of theme we should do this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe... No, we're not going to play girls again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's play... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to play a song we don't usually play.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about some Beatmania 5-key stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't heard some 5-key stuff in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's something from Beatmania Final.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Fellows.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
and many more.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[SPEAKER_16]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back here at Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 125.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's find out who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you boys and girls are really excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: By one vote, this song won.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't say, I'm sworn to secrecy.
[SPEAKER_05]: One vote over song number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some folks trying to be funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: The chat room is full of fun cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, not forgotten about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not forgotten about by any means, but a little bit left in the dust there with the rest of the controversy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: But maybe we'll do the chat room choice again sometime at a later date.
[SPEAKER_05]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what we're going to do is we're going to go to the Skype line in a minute here We're going to do that and also we're going to be doing the FUs of the week momentarily So send those FUs over to Sky via private message and we'll take those In the meantime, let's go to the Skype line Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio Is this me?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, this is me Hi, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi on the air, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm, I'm, I'm moist.
[SPEAKER_20]: Aren't you always?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, when I think of you, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the minute I hear Rob's voice, it shrinks up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell him who you are, asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you want to be my friend?
[SPEAKER_21]: Asshole formerly known as the asshole of the dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't make me come back there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The one and only and never replaceable asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, come on, say it, say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Travis from UnderSedationLive.org Oh, you like that, don't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you like that bitch, don't you, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want, Travis?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you just call in to taunt us?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, I had a rant, but I'm going to get to that in a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys were talking about, obviously, you had an annoying song on earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it was something that was catastrophically annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I found something worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't this annoying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like a game, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you even hear it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's from The Life Aquatic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so that's the trailer in the movie The Life Aquatic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's from the movie The Life Aquatic.
[SPEAKER_20]: Is that supposed to be going under the sea music?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going under the sea music.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the music that's playing in Bill Murray's helmet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of funky.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's right, that was on the trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and he starts doing that little butt shake.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to see that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was, I don't know, the girl's song, not funky.
[SPEAKER_05]: That song, funky.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, that one's kind of groovy.
[SPEAKER_18]: If annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm amazed Rod didn't play this when that song was on.
[SPEAKER_01]: In my opinion, and I have an opinion on this show, they are losers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, your man is back in what, two weeks, three weeks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Simon, my idol, yes, he's back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually going to try and watch American Idol this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't watch it last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do, I have an FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we're going to be getting into that soon, so why not give us a preemptive FU here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, a preemptive FU?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever, a pre, pre, pre, I don't know, fine, we'll call it a foreplay FU, how's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well let me transition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to transition into FU mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're like the only outlet I can go to when it comes to video games, is you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's what we're here for, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so I thought I'd get this out in my, you know, out in the open now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fucking, can I say that on this show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you fucking can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank you fucking much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sick and fucking tired of all these jack-ons on Halo 2 who are fucking cheating out the ass with standbys on their cable modems.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you cheat in Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: You put your cable modem on standby in multiplayer games like Capture the Flag, Assault, and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So while everyone else goes into reconnection oblivion, you're still playing your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got the bomb, you got the flag, you go right to the goal point, set the bomb off or capture the flag, take your modem out of standby, and boom, you've suddenly got a point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Genius.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for telling all our listeners how to cheat at Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure they're all going to go do it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What everybody needs to do is go to Bungie.net, the people behind Halo 2, get on their forum boards, report people that do this shit, and get these people banned off Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Notice also, Graves, those people that mod their controllers for burst firing in Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen that also.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just competitive play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Meaning that Travis does it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's called taking advantage of the scenario.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like grabbing the flag through the wall.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fun as hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it true that Bungie erased everybody's data sometime in the past couple days?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like all the Rumble Slayer stuff went bye-bye?
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard this.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they haven't already done it, they are in the process of doing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've talked to a couple people in the community and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Bungie, they're even trying to find a way to work around the standby mode and all of us who play Halo 2 Online thought that was the neatest thing in the world was when your game goes into lag and you disconnect you don't lose the game entirely you just pick up where you left off everything's fine and you just keep on playing
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, unfortunately, these little, you know, 14-year-old asswipes who, you know, get off on gushing on pictures of Lindsay Lohan in Entertainment Weekly, who have no life but drinking Yahoo and eating Ding Dongs, have found this little loophole through their cable modems.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know... These, by the way, being the same 14-year-olds that get on Xbox Live and while you're playing them go, Nigga, nigga, nigga, nigga, nigga, nigga, nigga, nigga!
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're as white as you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whiter, in fact, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and you can hear it in their voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's funny is when I'm playing with one of my friends, who happens to be a man of color, listening to him crack up, listening to these guys go, Oh, you nigga this, you nigga, oh, I got you, nigga.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and he just, he takes great pride and pleasure in coming behind them during the game and just beating them down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jack Black, NotFunny
[SPEAKER_20]: stuff like that I mean, us white people, we got Jack Black and unfortunately, the African American community has Dave Chappelle alright wait, wait, wait hang on you have to go back a little bit with the Jack Black stuff and you have to go back to Mr. Show he ruined every episode he was in no way, no way, I'm sorry don't put your dick in these holes that's classic
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeepers Creepers, he ruined that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: He ruined the farmer bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's ruined all the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I don't like him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hated him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't stand Tenacious D. Have you even bothered to see School of Rock?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, my place has a habit of showing it multiple times on the electronics section.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I unfortunately am cursed with seeing that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, how are you doing, Jeff?
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm in pain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong, hun?
[SPEAKER_20]: My left side hurts for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it has been since, like, Friday.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I'm trying to determine if it's because of working out too much or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know what it could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not pregnant.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't have AIDS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be a tumor.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not a tumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I envy your soundboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have anything that fancy.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why I came up with the other idea, which I'm emailing you all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've set a date tentatively, and I hope you all are capable of participating.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to pencil it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just pencil in the 29th of January.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow, that happens to be my birthday weekend.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good planning on my part, huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: Potentially bad, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your birthday's more important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll remember that.
[SPEAKER_20]: At least, you know, I'm only turning 28, you old fart, but it's still important.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Travis just shot himself, ladies and gentlemen, live on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, have you even told... No, it's just Texas.
[SPEAKER_20]: You get all sorts of gun noises out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You forget, we live in shit-kicking Texas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have we even told them what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, I know Jess knows, I know you know, I know Jamie knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else around knows about the little thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I... Angel says yes, she does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: And Ross knows, but he doesn't realize he knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: People know, they know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to steer too off track here, but I do want to say some folks in the chat room think you're pretty funny, Travis.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have some fans in the chat room already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I said when I read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you guys think Travis is funny, then you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Scream me along!
[SPEAKER_05]: You can listen to Travis' show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.undersedationlive.org It's where Iguana Girl and I got our start on the internet radio and DarkSakura to some extent as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was the number one most often guest.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know you were.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I just got one thing to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: You really think you can do all that bullshit you just said?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just trying to help you out, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a weird echo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hanging up on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you're not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Use the force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you honestly want to get into that type of war with me?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know you'll lose.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're going to be in the process, too.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: You're being in the front.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turn your goddamn echo thing off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can make everybody sound like chipmunks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I can do 3D effects.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, this is what happens when I waste my money on toys that I don't need instead of, you know, getting stuff that my daughter really needs, like diapers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of hard wrapping her up in brown paper bags.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say Walmart on the side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, never mind, I won't go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget, the 29th, if that's a conflict, let me know ahead of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will attempt to reschedule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we need to test out how it's going to work in sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our people will be in touch with your people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, get your people with my people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no people.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have little people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Rob just has people that come around him going, Ooh, Rob's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Want to touch him?
[SPEAKER_04]: I touched him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, I touched him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who hasn't touched Travis?
[SPEAKER_05]: Travis.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is going on on your end?
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like you guys are pushing some weird button.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you've got the echo thing on.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I turned off all my echo shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You scare me, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks for calling in, Travis.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was not on my end.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh look, it's gone!
[SPEAKER_20]: Magically!
[SPEAKER_20]: I wonder how that happened.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_20]: I swear he does that just to piss us off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, again, if you thought that was funny, I don't know why, but, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Understationlive.org, we do love Travis, and of course Jenna.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love Jenna even more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because Jenna is hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all about Jenna, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jenna is hot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jenna is a hottie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's all about Kira.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Kira's a cutie.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to find out what we were talking about there with the 29th, just head on over to understationlive.org and there'll be more information soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it involves us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm so glad that we get to go from that phone call into this next segment because this next segment is a good one to follow that up with and it's the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's our chance to rant a little bit about the things that have been pissing us off today or all week long.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jamie...
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is it that we have to do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because of girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: My first FU of the week goes to your dryer.
[SPEAKER_18]: My second FU of the week goes toward the fatigue flu.
[SPEAKER_18]: for making me feel like crap.
[SPEAKER_18]: Another one goes to stress.
[SPEAKER_18]: SD goes to distance, money.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I am very glad, though, that I am getting a raise with my new job, which is probably going to go to pay for bills.
[SPEAKER_18]: Humongous F you goes to GameStop Incorporated.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you goes toward the holidays in general for screwing with my head.
[SPEAKER_18]: And F you goes toward stupid fuckers who drive really stupidly in the rain.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, let's go... You know, it's one thing to drive five miles under the speed limit when you're, you know, in the rain.
[SPEAKER_18]: Five to ten speed, you know...
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, miles, depending on the conditions, is smart.
[SPEAKER_18]: 30 miles under the goddamn speed limit!
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone was going 20!
[SPEAKER_18]: And, like, unless you, you know, if your car is so bad to the point where you cannot drive in the rain, you need to either get a new car or take the damn bus.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Um... It's... It was just one thing after another.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm a very easily frustrated driver, though, so that could just be it, but... And another one goes toward...
[SPEAKER_18]: People who have 20 items when it says 15 items or less in the damn express line.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that, I got a little bit of Loki's music in there because I ran into the other room for a second there to try and fix that out of the situation.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now we will get to Loki's FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... Yeah, I'm... God damn it, I don't have enough cord.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'll make this really quick because I'm cooking stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you, stupid drivers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you to the fact that I don't feel good right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I caught someone's cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you to work because they're not paying me enough so I have to get a new job.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure there's some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a lot of stuff earlier, but hey, we're going to keep it short.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my gift to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like to give an F you to people that try to drive in the rain because it's obvious that nobody knows how to do it because whenever I get out there and I try to drive and it's been raining just nobody knows what they're doing so I just what's wrong with people what is it about rain oh my god water falling from the sky I need to start cutting more people off and driving 25 under the speed limit or 25 over the speed limit and coming up on your ass and you know refusing to pass you I hate people and I hate parking lots
[SPEAKER_05]: A big F you to Roseville and this place that I call Whitey Plaza.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, damn, what a bunch of yuppies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just, oh, I hate that place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, everything's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can't really complain a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And going around, let's start it off with, who's got a mic over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jazz!
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to people who do not signal when they merge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Holy crap, I have never seen so many people do that here and try to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, F you to people who don't signal when they're making a left turn that isn't protected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: People in Milpitas do this all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to get out of a shopping center and it's raining, so it's hard enough to see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people keep turning and turning and I...
[SPEAKER_03]: and I can either go straight or left and I'm assuming they can too I'm like oh my god what are they gonna do no one's signaling but oh my god they're all turning so I'm like oh no oh no and finally they all go through and they all turn and I'm like fuck you all and I'm just going my merry way uh I'll do FU to Taiken 5 because I suck at it uh yeah that's about it alright Islander
[SPEAKER_22]: The only FU I can think of really is FU to my car doors for not closing all the way and letting rainwater in.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have to keep a stack of newspapers on both seats to keep it dry.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want a girl.
[SPEAKER_20]: F you to my side for hurting right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know what caused it, but it's really, really, really, really annoying and it's painful and I want it to go away.
[SPEAKER_20]: F you to my butt muscles for tweaking out.
[SPEAKER_20]: F you to body sculpting class because it was extremely evil and...
[SPEAKER_20]: and Awful and I have to do it again on Tuesday and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to Size 20 Pants That Don't Fit.
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to Lane Bryant for carrying Size 20 Pants That Don't Fit.
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to Lane Bryant for charging $52 for four bras on sale.
[SPEAKER_20]: And...
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to my vacation time coming to an end soon from school.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to second the school FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's see what DDR Angel has to rant about tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Third about the school thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, no, fourth because Jazz just said third.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_19]: FU to the spare TV in my parents' house not working because then I couldn't play 2DX and stuff at my parents' house.
[SPEAKER_19]: FU to the internet going down while I was at my parents house because then I couldn't do anything of that so I was like bored and stuff and that sucks aside from going to people's houses and whatever but yeah okay and I suddenly forgot everything yeah FU to school starting in two weeks and that's about it let's go on over to the chat room and see what they're pissed off about tonight
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, let's see, um, Misty says, F you to my grandpa.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to learn to drive from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your skills may be leet, in your opinion, but your temper sucks too much for me to put up with you at times already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to put up with your shit when I have to put up with the other retards on the road.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpha 24 was the most recent one that actually worked for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it won't load at all, and I can't find any older alphas to download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dork says, F you goes to work for cutting my hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: I so can't wait till school starts again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, F you them for not giving me my Christmas bonus.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to myself again for having a girl over and not doing anything about it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just need to touch her boobie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: MPQ says, F you to feel the magic on Hell Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those of you who have played know exactly what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Allusion says F you to Bill O'Reilly for being a douchey blubbering vagina.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to the new Tilt Arcade that opened up and turned out sucking with its fabulous arcade games such as Skee-Ball and generic racing game number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also F you to Going Back to School Tomorrow and sorry to Iguana Girl for saying community college sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_20]: DJ Ranma... You better apologize to Miss Dark Sakura also.
[SPEAKER_20]: Better?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can send those cards and letters.
[SPEAKER_05]: And me too.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're just fucked all around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S says, F you to my job for fucking me over, you bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will have my revenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Misty says, Oh yeah, F you to school starting January 10th.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to refrain from comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raym says, F you MS, depression, and ADD.
[SPEAKER_05]: K-Dash says, F you to New Year's, cause I was all alone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, next time tune in to see what's going on with the internet radio, because we're around sometimes on New Year's, so I know, what little concession.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jaded2005 says, F you to people who think I know everything about computers when they can't work them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly, BlackDevilerX says, F you to going back to school tomorrow, and F you to being jet lagged.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: We were talking about home versions a little earlier, so I thought maybe we could play some good songs that were on home version stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki says I have to play a certain song from 2DX, so maybe we'll squeeze that in somewhere too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to start it off with a very popular track from DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
DarkSakura.com
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Simply being loved, yeah, yeah Simply being loved, yeah, yeah Simply being loved, yeah, yeah Simply being loved, yeah Simply being loved, yeah Simply being loved It's more than enough Simply being loved
[SPEAKER_11]: It's more than enough Simply be loved It's more than enough
Thank you for watching!
I heard you were in love, but I knew we were meant to be
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you want to be staffed by Hollywood?
[SPEAKER_08]: No!
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_17]: Extreme Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's us.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're kind of getting into the home stretch.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, some folks in the chat room were kind of asking tonight if we were going to do an Ask Orange Lounge segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I said, you know what, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been a few weeks since we've done Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did Listless a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did Match Game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we haven't done Ask Orange Lounge in a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is a segment where you can just basically ask us whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a great way to get us to actually talk about DDR, if you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: or you could go out of left field.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you have a relationship problem you want to ask us about.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jamie will give you straight up advice, really.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may not want to hear it, but she'll give you the honest answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: But remember, we love you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why we're honest.
[SPEAKER_18]: For dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that being said, let's get into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we kick it off with me making an ass out of myself with a little opening theme song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is someone bound to ask a stupid dating question?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope not, because DarkSakura will tear him a new butthole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you cooking over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's garlicky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's cooking, it smells like garlic, and now all of a sudden I'm like, garlic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're doing the fried rice thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, his fried rice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: He learned from the Benihana chefs.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to question number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Illusion.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a question from Illusion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brace yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: You knew this would be random.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you throw a blender off of the Leaning Tower of Pisa and it lands in the Gulf of Mexico...
[SPEAKER_05]: Who did the rapping in that one Paranoia remix Loki did?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Paranoia Revolution or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said it would be the last one, if that helps any.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki did this remix of Paranoia Revolution, and I guess as... I remember this remix that Loki did a while back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was, um... What the hell was the name of this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we tear you away from the kitchen for just a minute to ask you about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: The rapping?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what was the rapping in it from?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was from a song actually called Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's by BT.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forget who he has that does rapping, but he's on a bunch of different albums.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it said who his name was in... I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Scotty D. It's not Scotty D. That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: While you look for that, let me play a clip from Paranoia Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rapping was towards the end, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, here's a little clip of Paranoia Revolution so you know what the hell we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a Loki remix that you can find on his website, which is what, LokiFusion.tk still?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, very sexy clip there from Paranoia Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to download the whole thing, it's LokiFusion.tk.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've heard that clip, the revolution will be televised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I saw that on a bumper sticker once.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what the guy said in one part there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: While Loki does some more research on that, I'm going to go ahead and move on, and you can come back to this question a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's from BT, basically, the short answer to your question.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Illusion would also like to add...
[SPEAKER_05]: On a note, and I'm going to play some apologetic music to match his mood here on this note here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll play some very solemn apologetic music here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, Loki found it.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn, who the fuck is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, it was in the song, uh, Mad Skills, uh, Mike Cheka is the name of the song that was, um, on his album, Movement and Still Life, and they actually, I think, in the song, he says who it is, because, you know, they do that stupid, you know, shout out crap in it, so, um, I don't remember who he's partnered with, but it's the same guy that's on, like, all these albums, and, uh, Movement and Still Life would be a good one, the
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let me get to another note from Illusion here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He would like to offer a formal apology.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm adding the crying noises because I know he's making them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry to everyone that I pissed off
[SPEAKER_05]: I too will be going to community college, though I'm not too excited about it, nor would I be excited about any college.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A formal apology courtesy of Illusion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there will be a replay of that apology next week on DDO Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: In case you missed it or you want to tell your friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: K-Dash has a question about Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm planning on buying 2DX and I would like to know if anyone has any tips for me concerning whether I should get a flip top or just a Japanese PlayStation 2 and the best place that I can purchase them from.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Japanese PS2 and CSX.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would also go with the Japanese PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The flip tops are becoming a little more... Like, you know, if you'd asked us this two years ago, we would have said straight up, do not trust the mods, go for a Japanese PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're a little better now, and I think there's more out there that you can kind of trust, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Islander
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, no, I second the whole, you know, getting the Japanese PS2 wholeheartedly.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't trust the flip-top still.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_20]: And make sure when you buy it, you buy a Japanese PS2, not an Asian PS2.
[SPEAKER_20]: There is a difference.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_20]: Even though it is cheaper and it looks like it's going to be a good deal for you, you actually have to use a converter because it is different power than the Japanese PS2, American PS2 voltage.
[SPEAKER_20]: So you end up putting that amount of money back into a good converter that you don't fry your PS2 with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very good tip.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of something people don't think about sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, as far as that goes, it sounds like we kind of give the consensus, you know what, just go and get the Japanese PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cheap, and you won't regret it later.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, was she asking what style, too, or did she just ask other tips, or he, I'm sorry, I don't know if it's he or she, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure, so we'll just move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say as far as styles are concerned, because usually that's another question that goes along with it, is what style should I get?
[SPEAKER_05]: You really just have to evaluate the song lists and look at the one that has the songs you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as beginners go, though...
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't go with 3rd or 4th if you're a beginner just because 5th and later had more beginner-friendly modes in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Overall, I would say as far as song selection, actually 8th style doesn't really have too many beginner-friendly songs, even in Light 7.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would actually point people to 5th style.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd say if you're going to start anywhere, start with 5th style.
[SPEAKER_18]: It has a lot more beginner-friendly songs, except that 6th style does have the beginner mode in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, it really depends.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, as far as song selection, 8th style's got a bajillion.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, 7th style has a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I think overall you're best starting with 5th or 6th.
[SPEAKER_05]: A goal for 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have any goals that you'd like to share?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll start it off.
[SPEAKER_19]: I really want to get to Maniac Mode this year.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I gotta do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And probably get better at 2DX as well, although I don't really know where I'm going with that, but let's just stick to DDR first.
[SPEAKER_18]: My goals for this year are very simple, and actually I met one before the year began, because my goal was to be in a new job.
[SPEAKER_18]: One of my resolutions I put in my live journal was to have a new job, and I actually got that right before...
[SPEAKER_18]: Goal number one is to lose 50 pounds.
[SPEAKER_18]: Goal number two is to be enlisted in the Air Force or Army Reserves by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least to get my man over his anti-military thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything you guys on the couch want to share?
[SPEAKER_20]: I have three of them.
[SPEAKER_20]: Two of them are most definitely going to happen and the third one is going to take a lot more work.
[SPEAKER_20]: Goal number one, I'm going to graduate again this year.
[SPEAKER_20]: So basically my goal is to pass my last class that I have to take in order to graduate and hopefully convince my teacher that I don't have to be there for the day of the final because otherwise I'll be stuck here instead of at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Painful.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Second one is, this is the year that I'm going to be getting out of debt, thankfully, so I have to finish that out.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would anticipate it probably will be done by about August, so I'll actually be 28 years old and completely debt-free, which is not something that most 28-year-olds can say.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I'll own my own car.
[SPEAKER_20]: No making payments or anything like that, and that's
[SPEAKER_20]: Coming up in about two months.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then my third, and probably the most important, and the one that's been the biggest problem for me, I'd like to lose another 80 pounds.
[SPEAKER_20]: Even if I don't lose the weight, and just get down into size 12 or 14, I'd be ecstatic at that.
[SPEAKER_20]: But I have been working my butt off to try to lose the weight, and it's hard, especially with my conditions and everything.
[SPEAKER_20]: But I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're here to support you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Launch Radio, anybody that is trying to do that right now, your friends are the best support you've got for things like that, I think, sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can look to for encouragement.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we definitely encourage those of you guys that want to be more fit, and especially Jamie is always telling you guys to go outside once in a while, even though you do have to sit indoors to listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that was the Lord's Day to rest, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: For anyone who uses LiveJournal, I've made, and I actually am thinking of making this just a big support group.
[SPEAKER_18]: I made a community called GeekFit on LiveJournal, and I just made it this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_18]: But just for anyone who wants tips, advice, just to share what you're doing, what's working for you.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't even have to post every day, but I would encourage people to make use of this that I've opened up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_18]: LiveJournal.com slash community slash geekfit G-E-E-K-F-I-T
[SPEAKER_05]: GeekFit, I love the name, that's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So LiveJournal is a great way of support.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, a lot of folks in our chat room are bringing up GetUpMove.com, of course, the DDR fitness site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although GetUpMove.com, a little bit commercial because it's kind of a red octane thing, but I have kind of looked at, I've lurked on the forums a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the forums are really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think if you want to find people in the same boat that are kind of using DDR as a way to get more active and lose weight, I think the forums are really great help over there on GetUpMove.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check those out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess we should move on or else we're going to run out of show time and not get to everybody's questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to breeze through these last few questions here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other goals?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody want to get out there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have some other goals and that would probably be just I want to... I'm kind of looking forward to 2006 where I want to buy a house in 2006 and not be a renter anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to do one more year of renting something and then I want to try and buy in 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to take establishing more credit and things like that and being a good boy and things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, there's relationship goals, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, I don't think you can really set those kind of goals because then you'll have these expectations that may not be met.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're just setting yourself up for disappointment.
[SPEAKER_05]: So while the wish is there, it's not really a goal.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, MPQ wants to know, why did it take my Poppin' Music 5 soundtrack so long to arrive?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I imagine the mix is several, or it's a couple years old now, so it's probably just hard to find.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the holidays.
[SPEAKER_05]: That too?
[SPEAKER_05]: Makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: There, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll take a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bad weather, holding up packages.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tsunamis.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody knows it's Al-Qaeda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's ranting about Al-Qaeda?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S wants to know, did you all get everything that you wanted for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I did not, and I don't care because I can work on it this year if I really want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_18]: There were a couple of things I wanted, but I for the most part got what I wanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me personally, I didn't really have a list of demands.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just said I wanted to hang out with people more, and I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to some pretty cool parties in December, so, you know, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really have... The one material thing I wanted, I went out and I bought myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got it, so, the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: My raw plutonium's still in the mail, they tell me.
[SPEAKER_18]: You didn't get your portal to hell, did you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't started it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't really leaked
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy has kept me away from contacting the dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was watching something on TV where I don't remember the show it was because I just happened to pass it while Dan was watching where they were talking about your experiment as going to be something that they were doing a news report on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was a movie and they were talking about the movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I was like, oh, that's Loki's portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just want to be like you.
[SPEAKER_18]: You cool guy, you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I gotta wrap this up, so I'm sorry because I'm cutting a few people's questions off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really sorry to you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have to make this the last question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vidpower wants to know, I recently picked up Tycho Drummaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you guys think of this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any advice?
[SPEAKER_05]: Real quick.
[SPEAKER_19]: It makes my hands hurt.
[SPEAKER_22]: Freaking badass.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love the game.
[SPEAKER_19]: I love it too.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still can't get over Katamari on the Rock, so you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Deal with it!
[SPEAKER_05]: I have yet to check out the US version, but my advice to you would be, if you like the US version, there's about five of them in Japan that are just waiting for you to pick them up.
[SPEAKER_20]: Take breaks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Otherwise you're going to kill your forearms.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a friend, my friend that got Donkey Konga complained of the same thing from playing it too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even though it's a little bit different style still, I mean, as with any game that requires you to move motion, even DDR, take breaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, take breaks once in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why you get a break stage on workout mode and things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other advice?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's going to bring that segment to a close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys for the good questions tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, PumpUpTheVolume
[SPEAKER_05]: and also this Tuesday I will be playing the repeat yes, the one chance to catch the repeat on Orange Lounge Radio you'll catch that this Tuesday your one and only shot but DDR Freak Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and what else?
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll actually see a lot of faces two years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you're one of the few people that was here two years ago that's still here.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of folks that were here two years ago aren't here anymore, which is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except Loki, he's still here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He smooched his way onto the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: And see, when I was on the show, he was sitting on the floor.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now he's sitting on the floor!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's his apartment now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also Thursday night, Outside the Box has been hitting some road bumps lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that Rice Princess and Lanky Stahl have had other commitments.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to try and maybe play with that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we can bring Outside the Box back this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: If not, we might kind of change the format a little bit and try something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep your eyes on OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something exciting is coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I can say right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Friday nights, DDR Freak Radio, working together with us to bring you the Orange Launch Radio Rewind, 6 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you missed this show, any part of it, or a previous week's show, tune in over at The Freak, 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's about all the whoring I needed to do tonight for all the various stuff we're involved with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any of our guests have anything they want to plug?
[SPEAKER_05]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: Think we hit it all?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Gwana Girl?
[SPEAKER_20]: When you're not listening to Orange Lounge, go listen to DDR Freak Radio, that is all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, just support internet radio in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: just turn off your regular corporate commercially fed and I know a lot of people bitch that Life 365 plays too many commercials but you know what guys it is nothing compared to corporate radio turn on your FCC regulated censored airwaves sometime and take a listen to the crap they have on there and then tell me Life 365 sucks I have some great news for everybody too also G4 Tech TV or G4 TV the two girls on G4TechTV.com promised that they wouldn't suck this year
[SPEAKER_07]: I know everybody's so enthusiastic because the channel's not going to suck anymore because they said so.
[SPEAKER_22]: But what if you're one of their boyfriends?
[SPEAKER_07]: But they also promised to do some lesbian action on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was their promise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I will one-up that.
[SPEAKER_05]: This year we will continue to not suck and we will bring you a hot lesbian action at some point during the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That gives us 360 days to work with here.
[SPEAKER_05]: At some point we will bring you hot lesbian action.
[SPEAKER_05]: and maybe some hot gay action too for you folks that are into that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll not only give you one instance of lesbian action, we'll give you two!
[SPEAKER_07]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: How do you like them apples, G4TV?
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also the email boxes are open.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have email.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you ever want to say hi to us in email, you have a suggestion, comment, send us email.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's rob at orangelongerator.com or jamie at orangelongerator.com
[SPEAKER_05]: or loki.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now folks, I know that you guys like to tell me that my penis is small and that my breasts need enlarging, but I'd like some actual male too, other than these other things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have any problem with my sexual performance, so I don't need any of those pills either, but thanks for the offers anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we got to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're running over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start with Islander since he has a mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_22]: None at the time.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't think of one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come back to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want a girl.
[SPEAKER_22]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_20]: My side hurts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Feel better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take drugs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jazz.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: The addiction helped not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_05]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go out and play a real game.
No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Playing 10 minute long marathon courses in Stepmania may hinder your ability for masturbation.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I still got to work in my 20 minutes of DDR today so let's call it a wrap, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: One word to sum up the whole damn show.
[SPEAKER_05]: In one word...
[SPEAKER_05]: Jazz, don't let me down.
[SPEAKER_17]: Girls.
[SPEAKER_17]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_17]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
La la la la lasagna You want a summer lasagna Magnifico or a maybe spaghetti
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, you toppers are ready, now where do you go?
[SPEAKER_00]: Mamma mia, bambino Mamma mia, bambino Samara you, Samara you, Samara you You should taste my lasagna Hey, you don't like a lasagna?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's okay too How about a calzone?
[SPEAKER_00]: Some nice minestrone That's good for you, have a Samaranada
[SPEAKER_00]: Have some maranara, I know you'll like, I know you'll like, I know you'll like La lasagna La lasagna La lasagna Would you like some zucchini?
[SPEAKER_00]: Or my homemade linguine?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's harder to beat, have more fettuccine
Hey, you get it, Cousini, you gotta do it, imagine, imagine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, you will pass the lasagna, don't you get any on ya, you floppy pig, have a moravioli, you will get roly-poly, a knife in the beak like your cousin Luigi, Luigi, Luigi, capiche, python, capiche, python, capiche, python.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright guys, this is the part of the show called the Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now what I have to kind of put out there is that our Afterbirth segments are going to be changing a little bit in the future because of something else that we're doing and I can't...
[SPEAKER_05]: Spill the beans just yet, but trust me, you'll be cool with this once you find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So our afterbursts are going to be a little bit shorter.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just so you guys know, when our shows are over, you're going to be going back straight to the Orange Lounge Radio Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does mean you get dumped from the stream.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to have to reconnect in 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's no big deal, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys still love Orange Lounge and will listen to it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they hate us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, they hate us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was a good show tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a very good show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it when Iguana Girl and Jazz comes in from out of town and Islander's here and Angel's here, of course, and Loki has food so he's happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you look pretty pissed off at the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you tripped on something and I saw you just go into anger mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_07]: I tripped on two sets of cords.
[SPEAKER_07]: First, set number one going from the cabinet to the chair.
[SPEAKER_07]: And set number two going from the table next to the cabinet to somewhere towards the wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like two trip wires that we have in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I hit them both.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that and I had a fucking headache.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it seems to be going away now that I have food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's probably because I didn't eat since 11.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when I did eat at 11, it was four day old twists.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_07]: Literally, my jaw was sore from chewing those twists.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you know, if you work out, you know, while you can't move your arm, well, that was like my jaw.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, so I made my fried rice thing, and I have enough now for the whole week, so I'm gonna eat it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to comment in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's still a few people in there over at www.orange.com and chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Knight says, dang, the studio cleared out fast, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, this is very typical where most of our guests take off during the closing credits there, just like a lot of our listeners do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we understand it's kind of late for you guys out there, especially on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's, what, 12.30 your time out there, so pretty late.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, obviously, Iguana Girl is kind of hurting there a little bit, and Jazz...
[SPEAKER_05]: Jazz had to drive back to the bay tonight so it's very typical where people have just got to get somewhere else so it's kind of interesting with radio though sometimes you can't always tell people will run into the studio sometimes while the opening is playing and be in their seat right in time for the show to start and you know live TV and other live radio programs work this exact same way so it's just kind of funny the illusion that it sometimes gives that we've been sitting here for a half hour waiting for the show to start no I don't think so
[SPEAKER_05]: We love you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!