Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_03]: This is episode number 127 for this episode.
[SPEAKER_03]: January the 16th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned into the B-Money Scene's most fabulatastic radio station of all things music, video, gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe you know me as Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe you know me as Asshole, as some people refer to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ski!
[SPEAKER_03]: Also joining me tonight are my lovely co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: In that corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you need to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had... I resisted temptation, which everyone's going to hear about later.
[SPEAKER_16]: But everybody needs to be proud of me.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're special, and that makes me proud.
[SPEAKER_16]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_16]: So are you.
[SPEAKER_16]: When are you going to join the Olympic team?
[SPEAKER_03]: When they make DDR an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: When's DDR going to be in the Olympics?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jumping on a trampoline is an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, don't knock the trampoline, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't, but I still think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trampoline is fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was actually like looking into wanting to join like a trampoline class because they were showing it on the news and everything when the Olympics were around.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's like taking bowling for college credit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, also joining us tonight, I actually looked into the bowling class, I'll tell the bowling story later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to the Tech Massa, with a Massa plan, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who has one of those looks of, I don't know what to do tonight, these people are very strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also joining us,
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to our very special guest this evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's also special, just like DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is this a non-credible mic?
[SPEAKER_17]: Or is it a new non-credible mic?
[SPEAKER_03]: That microphone actually works, but it's kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're kind of quiet, so you're really going to have to try tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen in!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you don't have to yell out there to listen in, because obviously they're already listening, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, maybe I'll help them to listen a little closer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come really close.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come close to me for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come close to the speakers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, yeah, anyway, we got tons of interesting stuff to talk about tonight, or at least in theory we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just keep thinking this show is good, and then it will be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be interesting because it's somewhat of a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do have a couple big things we want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the favorite usual garbage you're used to, we're going to talk about that when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_03]: In this break, we're going to do some music from Dancing Stage Fusion, which is the Europe DDR that just came out a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it was more than a couple months ago, but end of last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they got some cool licenses in their version of DDR, and you're not going to believe some of the stuff you're going to hear in this break.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is all in the British DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: So enjoy this, and we will be back after this with more of the same old crap you know and love here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Join our chat, www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after this, starting it off with DJ Sammy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not Heaven, the other song.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Fire in the disco Fire in the Taco Bell Fire in the disco
[SPEAKER_13]: Fire in the gates of hell Don't you wanna know how we keep starting fires?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's my desire It's my desire It's my desire Don't you wanna know how we keep starting fires?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's my desire It's my desire It's my desire Danger, danger High voltage When we touch When we kill Danger, danger
[SPEAKER_13]: High voltage, when we touch, when we kiss, when we touch Danger, danger, high voltage, when we touch, when we kiss Danger, danger, high voltage, when we touch, when we kiss
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell me, is life just a playground?
[SPEAKER_14]: Think you're the real deal, honey And someone will always look out for you
[SPEAKER_21]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and in that break you heard some songs from Dancing Stage Fusion.
[SPEAKER_03]: To give you an idea, if you didn't know what some of those songs were...
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Sammy with Sunlight, Kylie Minogue coming to my world, Electric Six with Danger High Voltage, also known as the Taco Bell song, and Basement Jacks, Good Luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of those are songs that are really cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: We played that song in my spin class.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because I introduced my spin teacher to Good Luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that a former cage match pick of yours, too?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it was also in the Queer Eye soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: And look, it ended up in DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Kylie Minogue... I am so damn talented!
[SPEAKER_03]: Kylie Minogue, coming to my world, was once in the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ended up in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So people don't think we know what we're talking about, but, you know, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just cross your fingers that Girls by Prodigy will not end up in DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: It will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_03]: and David Hasselhoff
[SPEAKER_03]: We did get some good stuff, but I would have rather had that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it kind of sucks because it's really hard to import the Europe DDR because you have to get one of those converters for your TV as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's easy to import Japanese.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just get a Japanese PlayStation 2, get the Japanese game, and the TVs are the same format.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you want to do the Europe, the TVs are in a different format.
[SPEAKER_03]: The screens are actually a different resolution over there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Stupid Europe and their base 10 measurement systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid metric system and everything being easy math.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like the rest of the world uses.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at the comments in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: www.orangenautoradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jaded2005 says, Girls would probably end up in DDR as Konami's way to shaft us again.
[SPEAKER_16]: I would cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to write a letter to Jason Enos myself and request that girls be put in the next DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: As much as that song bugs me, I just think that would be funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: A very strange video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prodigy was famous for that one video, the Smack My Bitch Up video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it just as good?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the Smack My Bitch Up video was just, wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, this obviously doesn't help for the people at home, but I have... It was an edited version of the video for the first remix of Girls I Submitted to the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... It's a really bad one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, anyways, um... So, just to give you an idea, I mean, this obviously is not going through to listeners, but it's just really very strange.
[SPEAKER_24]: They've got, like, some person that looks like a kid with, like, some army costume and a floating head, giant lips talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got, like, the Rocky Horror lips mixed with Max Headroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do, like, the Rocky Horror lips with White Wolf RPGs.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then it just gets even stranger with this thing moving around and giant lips watching it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, the chatroom can't see it, but where could they maybe get a copy of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you got this from somewhere, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: I believe this was on the... Oh, God, who was that?
[SPEAKER_24]: It was the group that remixed it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I believe it was...
[SPEAKER_24]: The fake ID's website.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fake ID is the band name.
[SPEAKER_24]: And there's a link in their download section to the video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so if you want to check out random 80's flashback to a cruddy song, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'll change the topic.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or else I'll put in another version.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've got two more.
[SPEAKER_24]: They will go in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be Loki's threat all night long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't piss me off or I swear to God I'll do it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I dare you.
[SPEAKER_16]: I double dog dare you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat room's very divided there.
[SPEAKER_16]: I triple dog dare you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat room's very divided.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some are yelling at you to do it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I quadruple two-headed dog dare you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day, but we did have a newcomer join us during the break there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not much of a newcomer because she's been at this show a gazillion million times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: and why are you tardy, ma'am?
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, traffic and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's no excuse.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should have left earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to mark that down as tardy.
[SPEAKER_16]: FIRED!
[SPEAKER_16]: I am not.
[SPEAKER_16]: You lie so bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: She just, she knows she can get away with it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Besides, I brought you something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, she brought me, okay, gifts make it better.
[SPEAKER_03]: What'd you bring me?
[SPEAKER_03]: All is forgiven because I got free stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, soda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, what is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Diet Cherry Vanilla Dr. Pepper?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gross.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I will be the judge of that.
[SPEAKER_16]: It is foul.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be the judge of that, Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had it in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had this in November.
[SPEAKER_16]: When I went to Alabama, I was like, oh, that looks neat and interesting, and the commercials are on the radio all the goddamn time.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think I'll try one.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had three sips of it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I gave the rest of it to a homeless person.
[SPEAKER_16]: He threw it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gave your soda to a homeless person?
[SPEAKER_04]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I don't know if he was a homeless person.
[SPEAKER_16]: He looked like a beach bum.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was out Pensacola.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, comment.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, because, you know, I always like taking shitty soda and adding shit to it.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, this soda would be just all that better if I put vanilla and cherry in it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't like Dr. Pepper anyway, so... They've had this...
[SPEAKER_16]: at least in the southeast for a while now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go over to the webcam and sample the Diet Cherry Vanilla Dr. Pepper.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll have the barf bag ready.
[SPEAKER_03]: Webcam's over at www.warnersonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the meantime, since I can't expect everybody to be looking at the webcam, we'll start off our show as we always do, playing a little bit of How was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: And Jamie's going to start us off, as always, by letting us know, How was your week?
[SPEAKER_16]: My week was sick, as in I've had this cough that hasn't wanted to go away.
[SPEAKER_16]: and Holiday Spice Pasty is just as nasty.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, it was my last week over in the student loan industry.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank God!
[SPEAKER_16]: And I swear the VP was kissing my ass the whole time trying to get me to stay.
[SPEAKER_16]: And my boss took me out to eat.
[SPEAKER_16]: And oh, this is funny.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't take a very big sip because the chat room just told us that the webcam isn't up still, so we're going to turn it on right now, and I'll take another sip.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, it was kind of a really messed up, sad week.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was a very frustrating week.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I just didn't have the energy to do much of anything, although I tried step aerobics and I didn't care for it.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was my new thing that I did.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, although Friday I took the day off and, uh, oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_16]: But, uh, Friday I took the day off and went to the Skywalker Ranch.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, I have a friend that works for LucasArts and she got us into the Skywalker Ranch and so we were gonna go, uh-oh, I'll wait, I have to see this.
[SPEAKER_16]: Take your drink.
[SPEAKER_16]: Suffer!
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really just tastes like regular Dr. Pepper to me with like a funny flavor to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not cherry or vanilla.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just hilarity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Dr. Pepper flavored with hilarity.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the aftertaste is... Mmm, Dr. Pepper vaginal juice mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, I went to the Skywalker Ranch.
[SPEAKER_24]: Disgusting.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_16]: Speaking of altering Star Wars, we're sitting there at our table eating.
[SPEAKER_16]: All of a sudden, guess who walks by behind us but George Lucas himself and the business associate discussing things.
[SPEAKER_23]: I hope you flick your mashed potatoes at him.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't eat mashed potatoes.
[SPEAKER_16]: I really wanted to flick my meatloaf at him but the meatloaf was really good and I didn't want to ruin it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You might have gotten kicked out too.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: But it would have been worth it.
[SPEAKER_16]: But we next went and raided the employee store.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I actually have an episode 3 hoodie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just because I really wanted a hoodie, and I figured Episode 3 hoodie, nobody else has one unless they work there, so hey, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you're special.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I just figured it was an opportunity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know you don't like to go on cam, but can we model your hoodie?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll model your hoodie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, model my hoodie.
[SPEAKER_16]: I also got an ILM shirt, and on the back it says Visual Arts Crew, which I thought was really nifty.
[SPEAKER_16]: Better watch out, it smells like me.
[SPEAKER_16]: It smells like camo, which is what I'm really wearing.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's upside down, Rob.
[SPEAKER_16]: And backwards.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, you're just infinitely amusing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hold the hood back and hold it out by the shoulders.
[SPEAKER_16]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: See, I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, we also, I got a really nice leather business folder for Dan.
[SPEAKER_16]: and we actually got everything, all this expensive shit at half price because one of our friends, because our friend was of course with us and I also had a latte made by a $10,000 latte machine and it was like a really damn good latte too it was like professional and shit, it was really yummy
[SPEAKER_16]: and so we sat in this sort of lounge area enjoying our latte.
[SPEAKER_16]: They had a bunch of old Star Wars and Indiana Jones toys in there.
[SPEAKER_16]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because we went by the marketing director's office.
[SPEAKER_16]: The licensing director, that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to clarify, the food was better than episode one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, incredibly.
[SPEAKER_16]: The food was excellent.
[SPEAKER_16]: The movie was not.
[SPEAKER_16]: We sort of were too stunned to go mob the man and say...
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, Jorge, what was wrong with your head?
[SPEAKER_16]: And it was funny, we were talking to a couple of the receptionists there, just, you know, seeing who all they've met and everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like, oh, a George sighting!
[SPEAKER_16]: So it was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Nothing beats watching a really shitty Star Wars movie that's been bootlegged with really shitty subtitles.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, for instance, you know, lines like, You'll be the desert of me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Or Sup, Yoda That's funny Sup, Yoda But, you know, after that we took a trip to Network Video Because our friend still had to work And at Network Video we made some purchases We bought Saturn AV cables We bought Street Fighter Alpha for the US Saturn Because we didn't have it, believe it or not I have to ask
[SPEAKER_03]: How many times do you actually play these games after you buy them?
[SPEAKER_16]: I play them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, I also bought a Japanese game for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, what game?
[SPEAKER_16]: Dobutsu no Mori, which was Animal Crossing in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_16]: And the whole reason I was basically peeing in my pants the whole time watching this game was because...
[SPEAKER_16]: I thought, because you know in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_16]: one, it says each individual letter when they're talking.
[SPEAKER_16]: But people usually go through it, and I was like, okay, well, you can't really understand the letters.
[SPEAKER_16]: And...
[SPEAKER_16]: On some movie files, I had people playing the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_16]: I thought they were just speeding through it because they were saying it all so fast, but I could tell that they were saying each of the kana.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I thought, well, maybe if I let it go slow, I'll hear what they're saying and can use it as practice for, you know, my comprehension.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because that was the whole reason I won it, is because all of the text in the game is in hiragana.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, yeah, I don't have to worry about reading any kanji because, like,
[SPEAKER_16]: One of the 30 kanji I know is in the title.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Go find a homeless person and give them a Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_16]: The fuck am I going to do with this?
[SPEAKER_16]: I put it in, and to my disappointment, they spoke just as fast as it did in the thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: But it's actually neat because I like how you enter your text.
[SPEAKER_16]: Instead of having to go to that little screen where you choose your letters, instead you use your analog pad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because the quote alphabet is done in a series of, like, you have five in each group.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, I, U, A, O, Ma, Mi, Mu, Me, Mo, Sa, Shi, Tu, Te, To, like that.
[SPEAKER_16]: A, I, U, Me, Mo But the way that you do is you pick each of the first ones in the group The A sound like you could pick the A group or Ma group or Sa group, like that And then you choose that on your analog pad And then it pulls up all of the ones in that one So you choose everything with your analog pad It's very, very smart Very cool It wouldn't work for English, of course, which is probably why they changed it But it makes it a lot easier
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so looking forward to Animal Crossing on the DS, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, so am I. So am I. Happy thoughts.
[SPEAKER_16]: But also, I'm looking forward to actually being able to play Zelda and Mario without having a code.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because they were just, you could dig them up in the dirt.
[SPEAKER_16]: But, um, I figured it'll help me with my learning.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, and I did a pretty decent job reading it through, uh, through, uh, with, uh, what was his face?
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't believe I forgot his name.
[SPEAKER_16]: But, um, the dog.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, KK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Tom Nook?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I'm trying to remember his actual name.
[SPEAKER_16]: Toto KK.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Toto KK.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I had a pretty good time with that.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then yesterday, I went over to Iguana Girls House, and we played lots of 8-style and lots of Poppin' 9.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have to thank Raichan for selling me her Poppin' 9.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_16]: and Navi for selling me his controller, which still works beautifully, I might add.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good.
[SPEAKER_16]: And my five-year-old 2DX controller still functions as perfectly as when I opened the box.
[SPEAKER_03]: You lucky bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we actually... Mine is broke as hell.
[SPEAKER_16]: We've only cleaned it out twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried to clean mine out like five times and still it was on.
[SPEAKER_16]: But this last time we actually took it out and actually cleaned the circuit board.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it was, it's almost flawless now.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, you can tell it's kind of old.
[SPEAKER_16]: But we played lots of 8th style.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: and then we had Musical Night where we watched Little Shop of Horrors and Chicago.
[SPEAKER_16]: Didn't you guys go see Phantom?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I'm going to go see it tomorrow with Tia.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I have to say this about Chicago.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is the first movie I really liked that I hated all the characters in.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate every single damn character in that movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hated the blonde whoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Renee Zellweger?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, and I hated Catherine Zeta-Jones' character a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_16]: I liked the...
[SPEAKER_16]: The ballerina girl who got, you know... Spoilers.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not going to spoil.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, but... The one that didn't speak English.
[SPEAKER_16]: She was nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You, of all people, must have loved that song where they talked about killing all their boyfriends.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah, that was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I also liked the whole scene with the courtroom with the tap dance.
[SPEAKER_16]: The thing is that I really love the cinematography in the movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like how they integrated all the song numbers with the reality.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I love the music.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love the songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everybody sang well.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I hated every single last character.
[SPEAKER_16]: And the character I hated the most was the woman's husband.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't feel sorry for him at all.
[SPEAKER_16]: Guy asked for it.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was a big, stupid sap the whole damn time, and if he had any balls to him, he would have divorced her that moment.
[SPEAKER_16]: He wouldn't have done anything.
[SPEAKER_16]: He would have said, excuse me, bitch.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're quite feisty tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm enjoying this.
[SPEAKER_16]: I am in a mood.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I'm going to go see Phantom of the Mars.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you my favorite character in the whole movie, and this is totally the gay in me talking, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you're good to mama, mama's good to you.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was actually, I have to say, that's my second favorite song in it.
[SPEAKER_16]: She's a really nice voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have never expected Queen Latifah to be in that role, but she's awesome.
[SPEAKER_16]: I heard her sing at the Oscars, because they televised that, and that's actually the only part of the Oscars I watched that year, was just to hear her sing.
[SPEAKER_16]: She rocks.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because she filled in for, what's her name, because she was pregnant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_16]: She did very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never realized just, like, what a great voice Queen Latifah has.
[SPEAKER_16]: She's a very good voice.
[SPEAKER_16]: But one thing, though, that I really have to say this, though, costuming-wise, is that they should not have put Renee Zelliger in some of those clothes because she just doesn't have the figure for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I remember originally... She's built like a boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Madonna was supposed to be in that movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would have been interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: She would have been really good in that role, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: That would have been wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, she was supposed to be the Catherine Zeta-Jones one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_16]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are here to listen about video games and here we are talking musicals.
[SPEAKER_16]: The thing is, believe it or not, we did not watch Rocky.
[SPEAKER_16]: Really?
[SPEAKER_16]: We had a musical night and didn't watch Rocky.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was my week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I have issues with certain things.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't like anybody in that damn movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Not a one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're done?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was actually going to see, I thought I actually had the When You're Good to Mama song from Chicago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to play a little clip, but I can't find it, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our listeners are spared from musical night.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should have musical night.
[SPEAKER_16]: Dude, do you have the Husband Killing song?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know where it is, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: We should play that during the break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe during the afterbirth, even though we don't really have an afterbirth anymore, but.
[SPEAKER_16]: We need to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see what I can find.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I will find it for you and you can use it as a fortune cookie next week, maybe.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want to go find the... Okay, I'm going to download it when I get home.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to find the soundtrack and play Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I look forward to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll pump up the volume.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to plug Pump Up the Volume real fast, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, Pump Up the Volume is Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_16]: Tune the hell in.
[SPEAKER_16]: At six... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's supposed to be at seven o'clock for the pre-show, but I usually start around 645.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on and as much as it pains me to move away from musicals, we're going to talk to Loki for a minute and ask Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_24]: My week was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got the rest of my stuff in from my computer thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: I haven't really gotten to work much on that because I spent most of the day, well, part of the day yesterday looking for my drill bit set and I finally found it on top of the cabinet.
[SPEAKER_24]: So...
[SPEAKER_24]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: What else?
[SPEAKER_24]: I went out to dinner last night to Tahoe Joe's.
[SPEAKER_24]: And they're okay, but their mashed potatoes taste like shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Other than that, their food was decent.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't really like going back there because, I don't know, there was a lot of stuff I didn't like about them.
[SPEAKER_24]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was fun to try because I had a gift certificate, so, you know, free dinner.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thanks for watching and see you next time!
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I don't remember if I mentioned this last week, because I can't remember exactly when in the timeline this took place, but apparently the store chain that I do customer service for, Movie Gallery, purchased Hollywood Video, in which case they're probably going to go to self-distribution, which I don't see how that's possible, considering they're retarded.
[SPEAKER_24]: So that means I might be out of a job anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, no, they just relocate me to some customer service job.
[SPEAKER_24]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_24]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_24]: So, basically, after spending seven straight hours title matching, which I might add to you is very draining and very tedious, I finally got done, and so I submitted the stuff off to them, and, you know, they were happy.
[SPEAKER_24]: They were like, well, we wouldn't have had you do it if, you know, we knew it was going to take that long or, you know, it was going to be that much work, so, yay.
[SPEAKER_24]: But...
[SPEAKER_24]: Because I was worn out or whatever, I somehow forgot to delete the order, so one of each of these 3,000 titles or whatever came into one of our branches.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think that mistake cost the company, well, right now it's costing them about, I don't know, a couple, I don't know, tens of thousands of dollars, which in the grand scheme of things isn't that much, considering they can turn around and return all this stuff, but they're just making a big deal about it right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know why, but, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, that's that.
[SPEAKER_24]: And so I gotta deal with that on Monday.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: So that was pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, kinda sucked.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, I gotta be looking for a new job anyways because, uh, you know, this one isn't doing a very good job paying the bills.
[SPEAKER_24]: Need more money.
[SPEAKER_24]: And besides, they're not moving me anywhere, so.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yep, need out.
[SPEAKER_24]: So that's pretty much all that happened.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, and that and a lot of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_16]: I did have one thing to say since you said the evil addict word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because the copies literally fell onto my lap.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, this was fate saying something.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was doing some cleaning out of some drawers and onto my lap fell a series of discs in a box.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right next to them is a book that has certain key codes in it.
[SPEAKER_16]: And right next to that was a little notepad with all my passwords on it.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I'm going to be rejoining the stupid world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of?
[SPEAKER_16]: Stupid Addict Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean you're going to sign up for Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because I'm canceling AOL.
[SPEAKER_16]: Addict!
[SPEAKER_16]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's for multiple purposes for me, and that and the fact that gravity has turned into a bunch of retards.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I'm actually going to quit Final Fantasy XI when Ragnarok 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_24]: They turned into?
[SPEAKER_24]: Meaning they weren't before?
[SPEAKER_16]: They got increasingly stupid.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because I was thinking about rejoining RO and World of Warcraft and when they filled up their servers in two weeks I just decided no.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may remember back to when LankyStyle and I used to impersonate the Gravity personnel.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to talk bad about company?
[SPEAKER_04]: We ban you!
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to have bots on our server?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ban!
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, you know, why not?
[SPEAKER_16]: And I have people to play with.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I figured I'm probably going to be so bombarded with school and everything else, it's going to be a good distraction.
[SPEAKER_03]: The nice thing is that Angel plays on Final Fantasy XI now, and I love Angel because she is such our bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she will be your bitch, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, Thief.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: I guess Warrior to start off with because that'll be the easiest.
[SPEAKER_24]: You just hit shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can't get any easier than that.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want Thief stuff to get money.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I was just thinking that, you know, I just thought, ah, Ninja stuff is hella expensive.
[SPEAKER_16]: Then I thought, wait a minute, Ranger's the most expensive in the game.
[SPEAKER_16]: Maybe there's not any merchant class like there is in Ragnarok because merchants are owned.
[SPEAKER_16]: You just go outside and...
[SPEAKER_16]: Petal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe they'll add something to Final Fantasy XI in the future, but I don't want to turn this into Final Fantasy XI chat.
[SPEAKER_16]: I figured that I would mention the decision, so.
[SPEAKER_16]: Should I bring up that Gravity thing, since she kind of mentioned it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_16]: Gravity came out with a new game that has, like, the same sound effects as Ragnarok, which was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's called Rose.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know if you've heard about it, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, I have, and I've actually signed up for an account on Rose Online.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I've got one as well, so we can play there, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rosarock Online.
[SPEAKER_24]: There, yes, we're going to just change the name of this.
[SPEAKER_16]: Dude, you can be a pirate on an airship.
[SPEAKER_16]: How rad is that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I forgot what it stands for, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: My brain drew a blank.
[SPEAKER_16]: Something of seven events.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to be pirates, you better follow rules, or we ban you.
[SPEAKER_16]: We make you walk plank.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think it's Road of Seven Events or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: What exactly do you do in this game?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like Ragnarok, but it's 3D.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, 3D and, yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's just like Ragnarok, but it's more 3D and it's cool and, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, yeah, more game stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this time when you sign up, you're going to be a good girl and go with Sandoria as opposed to Bastok, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_16]: I learned my way around Bastok pretty damn well because I kept dying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or as we call it, Lastok.
[SPEAKER_16]: Maybe I'll go to Winters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Winters, the only problem with Winters is that you get lost there very easily.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it went back to Final Fantasy XI chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad host, bad, bad, bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how was your week, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm so glad you asked, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you done, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, well, Winters sucks because it's so big.
[SPEAKER_24]: Stop it now, stop now.
[SPEAKER_03]: My week and my day were pretty good, I guess I also played a lot of that
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm looking forward to tonight because I'm actually going to be going out tonight and I'm going to the Goth Club.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we've joked about this on the show a few weeks ago before, you know, last time I went.
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually when a three-day weekend comes up, Rob does one of two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either Rob drinks on the show or Rob goes to the Goth Club.
[SPEAKER_03]: So tonight I opted for Goth Club because Gwana Girl is going to meet me out there because she hasn't been to the Goth Club for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to go and as you can see, I'm dressed in all black right now and I'll go model on the cam again in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: and um and uh we're just gonna go and we're gonna look sit in the corner and look tragic you're gonna goth serve we're totally gonna goth serve people it'll be great um and um
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy Handbag Sylvia Drive
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma 1.5
[SPEAKER_03]: and I got to see the first couple episodes and it's one of those animes I actually enjoy I think it's so cute, it makes me laugh and we were going to play Metroid Prime 2 Echoes because I'm really curious to check out that game but I don't know, we ran out of time we ended up watching A Mighty Wind instead
[SPEAKER_03]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, well, Christopher made us watch episodes of Upright Citizens Brigade, which was this old show that was on Comedy Central a couple years ago, like five, six years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, some of it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: The concept, I really liked the concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the humor was a little, like it was hit and miss, but I thought the concept was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the girl in that show rocks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's pretty much it for my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't do anything that exciting, game-wise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except that one game.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, speaking of anime, a friend of mine got me onto an anime lately.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've been watching Fruits Basket.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't think I'd like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, you meanie!
[SPEAKER_16]: I would have bought it from you.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sure they have it cheap, not... That's okay, because I have rips of the DVDs.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, pictures of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us, for those of us that are not as into anime...
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't want to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's kind of the main part?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us about some of the characters or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: The best character is Kyo.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because he's violent.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you like violence.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_16]: And no, I'm not watching Naruto because everybody in the goddamn universe is watching Naruto.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not watching it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've been reading the manga, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't watch any anime.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that they got me to watch Ranma is amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on, Bradley, Arcadian42, our quiet man in the corner there.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: My week was just a regular old week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Work and not much else.
[SPEAKER_09]: Though I've had, for like the past two weeks, I've had crappy cold and sniffly and coffee and all this kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of probably the same stuff that Jamie's had.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of, it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: This weekend I played some old school Super Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Played Actraiser and played Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are two very sexy games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, and that's about everything I did of any interest at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: On to the next.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just thinking about Actraiser for a minute and what a great game that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know, people keep mentioning stuff that makes me remember the stuff I did during the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: What did you think of now?
[SPEAKER_16]: Last night, falling asleep watching Dan play Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Metroid or like old school?
[SPEAKER_16]: Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's hot.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Bionic Commando.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man.
[SPEAKER_16]: Watching Hitler blow up.
[SPEAKER_03]: All these sexy games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to have like a sexy retro night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, if you're going to do that, though, I'm going to be bringing over... No, I'll bring over Sexy Parodius.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll bring over the... Sexy Parodius didn't have an arcade release.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we need to play... This is what we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: We would have to play Actraiser, even though it's not multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could have it on for like 30 minutes at least.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we would play Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_03]: We would all sit around and watch... Oh, hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: We would all sit around and watch me play Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then we would sit around and watch me play A Link to the Past and then you guys are going to sit around and watch me play Actaracer again and then you would sit around and watch me play Metroid and then what else can you guys watch me play?
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't this night sound like fun?
[SPEAKER_16]: I just thought of one but you're going to hit me so never mind.
[SPEAKER_16]: You'd be playing Guardian Legend and then I'd take the controller and show you how to play Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh snap!
[SPEAKER_16]: The only levels I actually couldn't beat there were 10 and 20.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_16]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Had to get ready for school and stuff because that starts this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Didn't play too, too much of that evil game that I can't mention now because you're going to fire me, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Lots of... Well, I played a little bit of it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: Other than that, not too, too much.
[SPEAKER_16]: I do have to work tomorrow, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yuck.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, well, oh well.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, see, Loki does.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_16]: Other than that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, and, um, LiveJournal went down this week, if anybody knew about that, for 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, my world ended when LiveJournal collapsed.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously, did you notice how many people suddenly were like, I have to go outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: LiveJournal's down.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, that was pretty funny, because as soon as it came back up, all of my friends were going, Oh my god, I couldn't live without LiveJournal!
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my god, it's back up!
[SPEAKER_16]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: As soon as it went back up, everybody was posting about it and whatever, so everyone had their withdrawal.
[SPEAKER_16]: I only jumped on just to see, you know, what friends lists were doing and all that stuff, and to see if a certain other show was going on, but I couldn't do that because LiveJournal was down, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of LiveJournal, what an excellent chance to plug our community.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have a LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's username OrangeLounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's really difficult to remember.
[SPEAKER_16]: Some of us, though, had DeadJournals to go to.
[SPEAKER_03]: And DeadJournals that never get used unless LiveJournal's down, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's it for your weekend day?
[SPEAKER_16]: Before I forget, I forgot to mention the website for that Rose game.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's RoseOn.com.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all one word.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry because I don't know who said this first, but another game at our sexy retro game-a-thon where you guys are going to sit around and watch me play games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blaster Master.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are going to sit around and watch me play Blaster Master because that would be probably the second best 8-bit game ever made.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's when I actually bring over the collection.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I have to say, the collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and then we can sit around and talk about how much the other Blaster Master games sucked.
[SPEAKER_16]: All of the Mega Man games to date, up to, I think, I think I have that through X4 on Saturn, and then I have, like, I think 5 and 6, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I have all of the NES ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what would be great?
[SPEAKER_03]: I will never forget this.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the very first times I met DarkSakura, I went to her house, actually, because I got invited to her house pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when I walked in,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I noticed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea why, but there was one random Splatterhouse.
[SPEAKER_03]: All these guys in the house playing Zelda and yelling and screaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was in heaven.
[SPEAKER_03]: And didn't you call that a LAN party?
[SPEAKER_03]: A local area Nintendo party?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, it was a LAN party.
[SPEAKER_16]: Local area Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_16]: And they did the same with Mega Man 2 after.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I was going to say, you need to do something like that, but on each TV have a different Mega Man game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be so hot.
[SPEAKER_16]: Watching Andrew do that in an hour was scary as hell.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going, holy crap!
[SPEAKER_16]: But that's Andrew for you.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's Mega Man boy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've done the dragon level of... I've actually beat the dragon on Mega Man 2 blindfolded.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't do it now, but when I played that game all the damn time, I had all of my jumps
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like, basically, when you get to the platform right before you jump, that's when I was blindfolded, and I made all my jumps, hit it up there, and knew exactly where all my jumps were.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see, like, I could just picture it in my mind, Jamie sitting there in her camo, with a blindfold on, and the controller in her hand, and a candy cigarette in her mouth, because not a real one, because she doesn't smoke, but a candy cigarette in her mouth, just sitting there, bring it on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a non-flashback or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: The only other game I can play blindfolded is level 8-1 on Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Knight says Jamie was like Zen.
[SPEAKER_03]: You channeled your Zen warrior power.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is supreme geekness.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't even know I had any when I was 12.
[SPEAKER_15]: So hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm being poked fun of in the chat room for going over to a girl's house.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't you know they have goodies?
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't you know they have cooties?
[SPEAKER_16]: Remember the one guy who had his computer case built out of a toolbox?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was a camo toolbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wallowing in geek right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explicit joined us.
[SPEAKER_03]: He walked in during the break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Tardy there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Tardy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Explicit, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some ups and downs, but most likely ups.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any games you were playing this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I finished Metroid Prime 2 in like one week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And beat Final Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Dawn of Souls one?
[SPEAKER_07]: In three days.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I can't touch Final Fantasy 2 until I beat Final Fantasy 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2 is a bitch to level up on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to get used to the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear you can do something in the beginning, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make it really easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you level up your characters uber strong in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have enough time in your hands to cheat and level up so you can... There's always time for cheating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll explain that on the FU's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else going on with your week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, man, I was thinking of getting into a relationship with a close friend of mine, and you know that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, relations, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been having relations.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, updates on the tournament on February 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you're having a tournament in Sacto February 5th?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sacto Smackdown February 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love these Jesus tournament names.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or some people call it Piss because it says Sacto Smackdown.
[SPEAKER_03]: Paradise Island Sacktown Smackdown, you're calling your tournament piss?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was not expected!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, but scat was funny, but piss is really funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was not expected, I was just like, oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now, for the golden shower round!
[SPEAKER_04]: Where we shower you with gold!
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I co-emcee that tournament or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can come out and then throw gold glitter in the air and say, It's a golden shower here at Piss.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do whatever you want in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, this is so 7th grade, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do the posters say piss?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Chaos is the one that came up with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, ooh, it spells piss.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was trying to prevent the word from saying ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, ASAC tells Smackdown, but now it says piss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because, you know, ass would have been... Ass is looking pretty good right now, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only time I'm going to get him to admit... Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of tournaments are you having again?
[SPEAKER_07]: At Piss?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it starts at 11 or 12 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will contain DDR, PA, which is... The Piss begins at noon!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I just killed Sky on this one.
[SPEAKER_24]: So will you be starting off on Heavy and then working your way to Light?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that's two divisions.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Perfect Piss, and the Freestyle Piss.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first round, of course, is a PA.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first round will determine if you're going to the intermediate or the expert division.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're applicable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully you'll make it, unless you're really like the lowest seed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_24]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did you finally taste that piss in the bottle?
[SPEAKER_24]: Fucking Dr. Pepper nasty shit?
[SPEAKER_24]: Did it finally hit you?
[SPEAKER_24]: Honestly, because that stuff looks nasty.
[SPEAKER_24]: Diet Dr. Pepper cherry vanilla ass juice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those that couldn't see what just happened, I had one of those moments where I was about to laugh really, really hard because Loki just gave me that look of I'm thinking something really funny right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I had to run over to the kitchen sink and spit out the drink.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was of course drinking that Dr. Pepper.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Explicit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead and finish.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone's all cracking up with the title, Piss.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, there's also initial D version 3 tournaments for those interested in racing their cars.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that should be, it's also going to be held at the same time with DDR PA as well, so time goes faster.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's a freestyle at 6 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_07]: This should be pretty interesting, a two-rounded DDR freestyle.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first round is an improv with a prop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get to use a prop.
[SPEAKER_24]: So you know the initial D term in there.
[SPEAKER_24]: You could actually call it I'd Piss because, you know.
[SPEAKER_24]: The initial D, Paradise Island, Sacktown Smackdown.
[SPEAKER_24]: Two.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, I'm done with the piss jokes.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: We will bury the piss jokes, but you have to admit, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never expected it to be called that initials.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, the last round is the routines.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep in mind that you can actually do a group routine if you wish to.
[SPEAKER_07]: For two group pissing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the last.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear that was the last.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: I come in from the bathroom and you're still talking about piss?
[SPEAKER_16]: What would you do without me to babysit you?
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't be pissed off This show is so full of shit
[SPEAKER_16]: Not tonight, it's full of pee.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know what you should give as refreshment to everybody at the tournament?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, okay, seriously?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: Red Bull and little plastic clear cups.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because Red Bull looks like pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, this seriously has to stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I said that this show went to the toilet, I wasn't literal, you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now our chat room is just going off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, breathe in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so February 5th is when it all goes down.
[SPEAKER_07]: It all goes down February 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, by the way, there will be food supplied as well for those who enter the tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Red Bull.
Yep.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, everyone, be sure to come out and PA with us.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, that was bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we need a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: In this break, we're going to hear some music that was in some various Japanese DDR releases.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the newer ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted an excuse to play Superstar and Paranoia Respect and some cool songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then we're going to come back and we actually have some Bomani news I want to talk about when we come back, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually a new Bomani game being tested right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it the DDR with Mario?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: We talked about that last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no new details on DDR Mario yet unless I missed something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll check to see if there's any new details on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another new one that's being tested right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we will... I'll do Aoi Shodown next break.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after this with more
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what it is that makes me feel like this I don't know who you are But you must be some kind of superstar
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: No matter where you are No matter where you are I don't know who you are I don't know who you are I don't know who you are I don't know who you are
Thanks for watching!
What's going on?
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, recovering a little bit during that break here, and we're back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, it's been kind of a slow week in the Bomani world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a whole lot of news, but there was one pretty big thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That I thought was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's actually something that kind of, I don't know, it's been leaking around on various live journals out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now you're seeing it kind of pop up on DDR Freak as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know somebody had posted about it over there in the forums over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's actually a new game by Konami that's being tested right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a game called Dance 86.4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I guess it's supposed to be some kind of radio station parody or something, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think Raichan posted something about it in her live journal, and she posted a picture of the actual machine, and on the title she was like, Nuba Money Game?
[SPEAKER_16]: And I saw it and I'm like, dang, that's pretty cool, except it was funny because one of her friends commented and said that the bars were smaller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, this looks like a game that's obviously geared at kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just posted a link in the chatroom if you guys hadn't seen this yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's some pictures, some full-length pictures you can bring up of what this game looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks very kid-like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you could say poppin' music-like, but then again, we all know poppin' music was a game that was kind of aimed at kids originally, and it's now quickly become, like, one of the tougher Bomani series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some would argue it's the toughest Bomani series, but that's, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Something you could be argued about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has a very similar look to DDR, except I noticed this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three panels.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got a left...
[SPEAKER_03]: Middle, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which sort of reminds me of DDR Solo's three-panel mode, if you remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, but DDR Solo had like a three-panel mode that was very similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can see in these screenshots, you can see a little character there dancing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks very similar to the DDR concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little hard to tell without some moving screenshots, but that's what we see right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then these little miniature bars that this time, they're in the front as opposed to the back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why you have the bars in the front as opposed to the back, I have no idea, but that's the way it's built.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, take that as you will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now here's the other interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: When looking at the song list, some of the early songs that are supposed to be in this, you'll notice there's a couple songs that were actually in DDR Festival that are showing up here.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them being the Cutie Honey theme that was in DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_03]: So some of those are crossing over into this new Dance 86.4 game, which is very interesting, I must say.
[SPEAKER_03]: and yeah, I'm being corrected in the chat room that the three panel solo mode was actually bottom was involved so you weren't just moving back and forth side to side like this one set up where three arrows are all next to each other it was kind of like you could do upper left or left and upper right or right and then bottom so you kind of had a little bit of different motion but this one is kind of like, I don't know I would think that the way you would dance to this would be more like a hoedown but obviously this is something that's written or being done for kids I don't know, we'll see
[SPEAKER_03]: Any comment on this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Dance 86.4 Funky Raider Station?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll have to... You know, I would think that they would have just done the Ohasta.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, kind of weird, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you posted some more pictures there, didn't you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I think is kind of weird about this is that
[SPEAKER_03]: Part of me is kind of scared because you hear that we are starting over with DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this starting over?
[SPEAKER_24]: This isn't even DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're not even close.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a spin-off of Bishi Bashi.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's just like they have the Bishi Bashi type dancing game thing that had three... It was exactly like this, except it wasn't on stage.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was just on some stupid little pad.
[SPEAKER_24]: They have it at AI.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's honestly, it's nothing new.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's nothing exciting.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's just like a new Bishi Bashi game.
[SPEAKER_24]: They actually had... There's some other shit I posted, too, in here that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: There was... Where did I put it here?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um... Oh, this one right here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm all, looks like Banjo Freaks.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, you know, it's, um, some, like, banjo game thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: They have, like, a bunch of stuff that was on this one website here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Keep it alive, Namco came out with a whole bunch of music games I never saw.
[SPEAKER_24]: Location testing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, like, yeah, they have the, um, this karaoke game, I think, that's actually, um...
[SPEAKER_24]: Idolmaster, another Namco music game that's coming out where you have to become a pop idol type thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Of course, Guitar Freaks V, they have stuff about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Funky Radio Station Dance 86.4.
[SPEAKER_24]: But yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: It looks interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know, I can't help but feel a little bit of, come on guys, you gotta work on this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my new DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want this Dance 86.4, so I want DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's my DDR, Loki?
[SPEAKER_24]: Uh, you just got, um, Festival on me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Shit, what do you want?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Arcade DDR!
[SPEAKER_03]: They can, they're, I can't believe they're making this whole new machine, this D&D 644.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, and I understand, maybe there's a market for kid games and stuff, but, eh, it's frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are they spending time on this when they could be making me a beautiful new DDR machine?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because this is cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what's going on in the sim scene right now, anything?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, finally, finally, the sim files have been released for DDR Ultramix 2, Dancing Stage Fusion, and Festival.
[SPEAKER_24]: Finally, they're, well, done, I guess.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um.
[SPEAKER_24]: They would be found at... Well, they have a preliminary thing up right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's pretty much... I mean, they're as done as far as you and I are concerned.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because... I mean, oh no, they're missing the beginner steps on doubles.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_24]: But other than that, it's perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: They have them all done.
[SPEAKER_24]: Including, I think, the first... No, not the first service pack.
[SPEAKER_24]: But everything else is done on it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, I have a very long link I'll post later for where you can find these at, but check in DDRUK if you want to know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Keep up to date with their progress on SongPack 6 and 7, or 7, whatever the two new ones are.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because that's what's going to be happening there.
[SPEAKER_24]: DDR Maniacs is still down.
[SPEAKER_24]: Also, I think, I'm not sure if I mentioned it, because like I said, I can't remember...
[SPEAKER_24]: There was the Legend of Tak, the Gravity, DarkSakura, Burn Nation mix, and the Ecstasy 14 Hours Club mix, I believe.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, that was an older one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: So yeah, that's pretty much all that's going on right now, scene-wise.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, that and Bomani's still talking about rolling out a site called Simulation Style, which I think is like Bomani Sims 2.0 type thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's supposedly coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, how you doing over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything interesting going on on the forums over there?
[SPEAKER_16]: There isn't crap happening on DDR Freak right now Except someone PM'd me asking me what post-touring is Could you explain for the masses what post-touring is?
[SPEAKER_16]: When you post a whole bunch of stuff unnecessarily especially for people who post three damn times in a row instead of editing your post I consider that to be a version of post-touring Okay
[SPEAKER_16]: But, no, there's not really a whole major lot going on the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so, you know, slow news week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Slow news week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Slow everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think people are just trying to get adjusted to the new year, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think everybody's kind of sitting on things until E3, so we're in for a slow couple of months.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, there is this stuff kind of brewing in Japan with DDR Mario and supposedly being showed at that show that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised we haven't heard anything about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it'll leak out on the net in the next few days, depending on what capacity this game's being shown in.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, as far as these new games getting test locations and stuff, we'll just kind of have to get the news as we get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, as far as American releases go, we're probably not going to hear anything until E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be the big time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, if there is a new DDR game coming out this year, which I'm confident there's going to be, we won't get the details until E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we're in for a very interesting next few months.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys ready to have a cage match?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Launch Radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way the cage match works, we play three songs for your listening pleasure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Launch Radio Live's Vimani Music and More program, which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week on this station when we're not here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The song is called Joe LaTaxi
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to participate in the cage match, you've got to be in our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is, song number one, Oria Posey, Joe LaTaxi, the Jan Wayne remix radio cut.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy.
S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_03]: Having mics on would help There it is, song number one tonight A clip of Joe LaTaxi Alright, will Joe LaTaxi win again?
[SPEAKER_03]: We shall find out But we have to put two new songs up against it And the next song comes from Loki Loki, what are you putting in tonight?
[SPEAKER_24]: Is it a remix of Girls?
[SPEAKER_24]: No No, it's not a remix of Girls Because I haven't cut those down to size yet So that's the only reason why you're not getting Girls
[SPEAKER_24]: I will make a remix of that song if I have to in order to make another entry.
[SPEAKER_24]: But this is not gross.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is our favorite friend, MidiHead, and his debut track that is going to be on his next album that he demoed for the wonderful people on his website.
[SPEAKER_24]: Unfortunately, you have to buy something or be a member or whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, this is exclusive.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not released yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is...
[SPEAKER_24]: This is Take Me Away by MidiHead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does he know that you're doing this?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you're bootlegging... God, if we get a nasty letter, it's your ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm, you know... I'm creating buzz.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Buzz.
[SPEAKER_24]: Buzz is not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buzz is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see what kind of buzz this generates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number two, MidiHead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take Me Away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't you take me away from here Away from all this madness Take me away from here Away from all the madness
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and see what they thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: What we thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me, Jamie, your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, Explicit.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7 from Explicit, Arcadian 6 from Arcadian, Loki Angel
[SPEAKER_16]: I really do like mom book stuff, so, and it was really kind of bouncy kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Eight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I like Monolithic quite a bit too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he has a very distinct voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not for everybody, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing about that song for me is that I think he said this on his forums too, which is why I kind of gave Loki a funny look when he put this song in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he said the song isn't quite finished yet, that it's kind of still a work in progress.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and see, it's got that demo feel to me, like it's missing...
[SPEAKER_03]: Something, there's something missing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't put my finger on it, but I'm not the musician.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to figure out exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like what I hear so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I definitely will pick up his next album when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: If for no other reason than I just think he's a cool guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so an 8 for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And moving on, it's my turn to pick a song.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I really didn't want to do this tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not want to put this song in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Surprisingly enough, I didn't want to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like I have been listening to nothing but this song non-stop this week that I would be doing myself a personal injustice to not put this song in the cage match tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no, it's not girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Get Bumped!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that was song number three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Echo Image with Endless Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's find out the scores.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: I actually really like that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Except I think his voice is just slightly over for that one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like it's a little too loud.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because on the other ones I've heard he has a really nice blend with the music.
[SPEAKER_16]: Almost in Ben Halen's Sammy Hagar era type blending.
[SPEAKER_16]: This one I think is a little overpowering, so I give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, nine from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually like the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I give it like an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there's something about it that just makes it far from perfect in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very great song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has a lot of originality and variation.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very good music.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has an all-ticket cutter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the pauses is what kills the song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big fan of pauses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I like some of the positive, but it looks like it's done wrong in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't feel like it's something appealing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, it's a very good song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I give it a 10 because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: 10 because it's Echo Image and it's still awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, me, my opinion, in my opinion...
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, that song is perfection.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that is the first true 10 I would give to any song in the past 120 episodes that we've done this K-Dimension.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for you guys to vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to place your votes in a minute here after this quick recap of the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number one, Jolitaxi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Song number two, Midi Head, Take Me Away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm picking really bad clips of the songs tonight, I'm sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: And song number three, Echo Image, Endless Day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I had my reasons after all
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song number 1, 2, or 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can call them Joe LaTaxi, Take Me Away, Endless Day, Echo Image, Midi Head, and if you can pronounce the other one, that's fine by me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever will get the message across.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: More stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when it is a slow news week, I like to go around and I like to browse some of the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like to be inspired by certain topics that are going on in some of the various web forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, one of the largest being DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, we like DDR Freak because not only do we have a host who happens to be a moderator there.
[SPEAKER_16]: I wonder who that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our webmaster is a moderator there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then...
[SPEAKER_03]: Several of our frequent guests are moderators there.
[SPEAKER_16]: One's an admin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we get rerun.
[SPEAKER_16]: The admin.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now we are a small part of DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to bring the site down with our dumb little show we do, which you can hear Friday nights at 6 o'clock over on DDR Freak Radio, which is a cool station.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't you wish you had a girlfriend that played DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is like every guy I know's dream to have a girl that will play DDR and actually be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on, wouldn't that just be awesome?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, except for the part where she steals all the glory or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be cool to have a girlfriend that plays DDR?
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: There goes another F you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wouldn't it be awesome to actually touch a real girl?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't it be awesome to get laid?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't it be awesome to rape a woman instead of a freaking bar?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_24]: God, this is sad.
[SPEAKER_24]: Someday I'll get laid!
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, don't you wish you had a girlfriend that played DDR?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to ask my fianc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, surely you must have some kind of comment on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me look here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me find that quote again.
[SPEAKER_03]: To have a girl that will play DDR...
[SPEAKER_04]: and actually be good!
[SPEAKER_16]: I wouldn't know anything about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So are you saying that there's no girls that are actually good at DDR out there?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, of course we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though you can pass CATAs and... You know what?
[SPEAKER_16]: My comment is completely off the record as we are probably being recorded by a few people.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: But...
[SPEAKER_16]: That's probably the most dumb thread I've ever freaking heard of in my life.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's almost as dumb as show off your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is going on a random chat right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: This has turned out to be a dumbass, dumbass revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, you know, the guy just wants a girlfriend that I can sort of see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't we want to date people that have similar interests sometimes?
[SPEAKER_07]: But you've got people like DJ Ness saying, ooh, is there any hot girls in NorCal?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or shit like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are no girls in NorCal, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should tell them that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually no girls here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one big gay bar, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not responding to this.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, why would they even ask?
[SPEAKER_24]: Is there any hotties in NorCal?
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, they're gonna talk to you, sure.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, if you gotta ask, they're not gonna talk.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, really, really.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_24]: Someone's looking for Hotties!
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe I'll go date him!
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_16]: Cause I really go to an arcade to pick up dates.
[SPEAKER_24]: I drive a ricer!
[SPEAKER_24]: I am pimp!
[SPEAKER_24]: Date me!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_24]: Allow me to spread my seed and genes!
[SPEAKER_24]: So that we'll be able to create the ultimate dancing person.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who, yes, will not get laid.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, not responding to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually went in the thread and I responded.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually responded.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here was my response down here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nah, I don't really want a girlfriend that plays DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it would be cool to have a boyfriend that plays DDR though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my response.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, any feedback?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, considering...
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, I'm going to have to switch this around.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, at one point I did, uh, want to find a guy to play DR, but, you know, that's kind of, I suppose it's kind of easy because it's all guys, but, hey, it kind of happened, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Miraculously, yay, okay, um, so, whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, gee.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to give this guy a little credit here.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's probably young.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we see these threads all over the freaking forum.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But let me give you guys some advice.
[SPEAKER_03]: People assume that they want to date somebody that has similar interests with them so that they can go out and do stuff together.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But remember, guys, your interests don't always have to match up 100% for a successful relationship.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I've been in relationships where
[SPEAKER_03]: We weren't alike at all, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, we were not even into the same types of things, but part of the relationship was learning about each other's interests.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think as long as your potential partner is open to the idea of, you know, hey, you play a dancing video game, you know, as long as maybe your potential partner watches a soap opera that you think is stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: but they watch it every day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you've got to be kind of open to that and kind of see it from their perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: Part about relationship is kind of learning from each other, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're never going to find anybody that's 100% just like you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we all want to fuck ourselves, but let's face it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about that, Scott.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, I mean, opposites attract and that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't you guys agree with me, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: I totally agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, no problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can settle your differences and make sure you understand each other in a way.
[SPEAKER_16]: The main thing is communication, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: We all know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That reminds me of that old Paula Abdul song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two steps forward, two steps back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I have no career and I'm on a stupid show that makes fun of people that suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: She begs!
[SPEAKER_24]: God, Paula Abdul, so... Last century.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why do people start threads like that, really?
[SPEAKER_24]: Go talk to real people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop using forums.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why don't you stop wondering about girls and go discover what girls really are?
[SPEAKER_03]: What if we didn't have that luxury of living in a somewhat big town and being able to go to the arcade and find people like us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we all met, like it or not, we all met playing DDR, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, maybe we've got a luxury this guy doesn't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Comment?
[SPEAKER_16]: We're special.
[SPEAKER_16]: I told you you were so talented.
[SPEAKER_16]: And on top of that, you want to know, I actually met Dan online through anime and video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can find love on a forum.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I didn't know what the fuck a forum was when I first went online.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was just someone my roommates knew.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll tell you how I found everything.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's basically like this.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was bored, so I read the manual for DDR, USA, or whatever, and in the back it gave special credits to DDRFreak.com.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then in turn I went to DDRFreak.com, found that, found the regional forums, found the link to the Sacramento's webpage, joined their forums,
[SPEAKER_24]: Found a meetup and then went there.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's basically the whole chain of events.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if I'm hearing this right, you're suggesting maybe what this guy ought to do is if he wants to find the girl that's into DDR, go to a meetup in your area where there are going to be people playing DDR, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's going to be 20 smelly guys all fighting over that one girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I mean, go Friday night, Saturday night, or even into a tournament.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, go to your local tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: If someone dares to even organize one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's hard to say because I don't know where this guy lives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we're going to go to... I was going to say we're going to go to a break, but I think we're going to go to find out who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who do you guys think won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_16]: I think that Taku won with Holic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Taku did get another few votes tonight for Holic, but unfortunately we throw those out and shred them.
[SPEAKER_16]: Eventually he's going to win.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you guys think won?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any guesses?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm guessing... Echo Image, maybe?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I was going to guess Echo Image, even though Midi Head's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Jamie's pick is also cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I'm still going to guess Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's find out... What, Logie?
[SPEAKER_24]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was just quoting them all.
[SPEAKER_24]: Imagine how it would be to be at the top making cash money to touring all around the world telling stories about young girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight's winner of the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match by one vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only one vote made this song win.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always one vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: By one vote...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a new champion, Echo Image with Endless Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: One vote over Jolitaxi.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why am I not surprised?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very close vote, very close vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: And MidiHead picked up quite a few votes of his own too, but one vote over Jolitaxi.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you think your vote doesn't make a difference, woohoo.
[SPEAKER_15]: I already know what I'm going to pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: The chatroom knows what I'm going to pick too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what I'm going to pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blue Impulse
[SPEAKER_03]: Ali Shuttle
Thank you.
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
I want your everything Every night I'll give you everything I want you I want you I want you
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening as we are usually here every Sunday night from 6.30pm to 9.30pm Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was being such a camera whore during the break too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I might get on the cam.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_16]: I wanted to go to Fanime, but I want to cosplay this year.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, you know, that would be a good way to... I'm thinking about making an idea I had a while back.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should write the Fanime people and get one of those lecture things.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want to make a white mage outfit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go as a warrior.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go as a warrior in Subligar.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want to do the Yuna 10-2 white mage outfit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: That one was really neat.
[SPEAKER_16]: Those boots.
[SPEAKER_03]: I definitely want to do the warrior in Subligar, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh-huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: When is what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Fanime is usually... Loki, isn't Fanime usually around Memorial Day weekend?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, it was actually on Memorial Day weekend last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, I remember Fanime was only like a week after E3 last year, and I was so tired.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to talk to the Fanime people, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think we're good enough to get our own little lecture thing?
[SPEAKER_16]: We are hot, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: We're hot shit!
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, honestly, honestly, they had Tanpopo Arcade there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do you remember what Tanpopo Arcade was?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Question answered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll go if somebody wants to kidnap me for a weekend.
[SPEAKER_16]: That sounded really bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fanime is May 27th, 28th, 29th, and 30th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I know, okay, everybody in the chat room is going, why Fanime?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come to our local convention on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Anime Expo sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Fanime Expo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's the fact that Fanime we can drive to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we can all pile in the OLR van.
[SPEAKER_03]: that doesn't exist except in my imagination but we can pile in the mystery machine which is the OLR van and go whereas to go to the east coast costs money that we don't have until we become rich and famous so we'll see that's what you can do E3 is the weekend before if you want to see us at your east coast con help us be rich and famous send us money E3 is the weekend before alright we'll see
[SPEAKER_03]: We would love to come to more conventions, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will whore ourselves out to anybody that wants to have us.
[SPEAKER_16]: We could try Pacific Coast Con.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll even fly southwest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we're not picky.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll fly southwest and stay in a Motel 6.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's the one that the people who originally started AX do now.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think it's like Pacific Coast Con or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: That basically is back to what AX originally was before it got stupid.
[SPEAKER_16]: And here's a pretty good con.
[SPEAKER_16]: We could do Yowie Con.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my god, we should do YaoiCon and go all like, like, J-Rock style.
[SPEAKER_16]: You just made me blink and run away, but maybe that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: YaoiCon's supposed to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, wouldn't you want to do YaoiCon?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh yeah, look at me all excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I think what we'll do now is actually we're going to open up our Skype line for some feedback.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you guys want to call our show, we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to open up the Skype line right now for you guys to be able to call into our show and have a chat with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, in the meantime, I know you wanted to talk about something that's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were talking about LiveJournal a little bit before, and I know you've got a new little project going on over there, so go ahead and plug away.
[SPEAKER_16]: Over on LiveJournal, I've made a community called GeekFit, G-E-E-K-S-I-T.
[SPEAKER_16]: For anybody who was wanting to
[SPEAKER_16]: Have feedback on getting in better shape.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's a few of us on there right now, basically just like a big support group for each other, sharing tips, asking about exercise, different things that are helping all of us.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if you're interested in bettering yourself, then join up.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what we're for.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DDRs and Means for Exercise
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, there's more to, though, you wouldn't, you know, somebody wants to join this community and talk about how DDR is their exercise program.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool and all, but what are some other alternatives that you guys would be encouraging over in the GeekFit community?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, it's more or less just leaning more toward healthy attitudes.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, we would encourage, like, if you say, okay, if I need to play how much DDR to lose how much, then, you know, we've been sharing in there, like,
[SPEAKER_16]: Like our last thing that we put in there was different snacks.
[SPEAKER_16]: And about at least three people on the community now are doing low carb diets.
[SPEAKER_16]: We have other people who are highly active.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then, you know, there's my high protein thing that I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_16]: But mostly we just support each other's style of how we're doing it and give feedback.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to follow up with you in a minute here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually just picked up a call on the Skype line here because I want to actually pick up a call while we've got somebody on the line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Silence Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who dis?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Jaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Jaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yourself?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this is the first time you've called into the show, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fresh blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any comment you want to make about tonight's show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any comment in general?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, actually, we were tired.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just lost you there, bud.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might have some bandwidth going there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got bandwidth issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might want to stop anything else you're doing, even if you're listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we might have lost him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you hear me, guy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pardon me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your bandwidth, you're really choppy right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got a comment for us?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because my bandwidth is not being used at the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, just must be a shoddy connection.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, try it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was noticing it, to tell you the truth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, what was the comment you wanted to make?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll try to pick it up as best we can.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, the comment I wanted to make was about meeting the...
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, our crew, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: The comment was, basically, that would pay, like, a great random prize, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of more or less as, like, a game show, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like the first date.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay, he's breaking up a little bit, but as I understand what he's suggesting here is that we should do some type of game show, and the big prize would be fly out here and meet the OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, my God, that means one of us would have to put this person up and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be a little weird, but I like the idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just involves money, which is non-existent in our budget.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much was in the budget this year, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: How much did we have in the Orange Launch Radio budget?
[SPEAKER_16]: and some sun-dried tomatoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I believe we had some sun-dried tomatoes and about five jelly bellies in this year's budget.
[SPEAKER_16]: I contributed cashews, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: You did, so that was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully we can sell that stuff on eBay and we'd be able to have this contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't know if we can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would you enter if we did it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I would.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you're not one of those freaky stalkers that has an axe that would chop us up or anything, are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, any other comment you want to make?
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, no, that's the only comment I really wanted to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, I like the idea, Jaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope one day we're rich and we can make it work for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: We like new people calling in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, if you want to call in, Skype line's open.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a call there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie actually is over on the cam right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gasp.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_03]: www.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to head over there and look.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually...
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what would be a good idea, is that instead of flying somebody out here necessarily to hang out in our studio house and everything like that, maybe if we were to do the Fateme thing or the E3 thing, we could actually have a Come With Us to E3 contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: How cool would that be?
[SPEAKER_03]: People would be murdering each other to do that, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: One day we'll make one of these ideas work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we've got another call on the Orange Launch Radio Skype line, so let's have a chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are going to be...
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's another thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seven new CS songs which are going to be exclusives.
[SPEAKER_06]: Including songs from L.E.D., Garoovy, and Megumi Over Slope.
[SPEAKER_03]: So surprise, we're seeing a lot of the same people that were in 8th style coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: New L.E.D.
[SPEAKER_03]: is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Meg wants to do another video where she shows off her rack, fine by me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I heard that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it off!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the last one here is a remix version of the popular song Usual Days from Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be on Nonstyle CS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, okay, so we're getting a Poppin' Music remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, wasn't there another song in 8th style that was crossed over from Poppin' Music as well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's Everyday Lonely Day by Rosanna.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I love that song, so hopefully that's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other details on 9th style we know so far?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the last thing there was on the message.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I need to get back into 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so far behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to pick up 7th, 8th, and 9th style.
[SPEAKER_03]: But 9th style, seriously, is like my favorite song list since like 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have to have to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So one of these days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other news going on out there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is the only one I've brought so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any quick comments you want to make?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The site that I gave you, I mean, the Dust Bacon site I gave you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dust Bacon, which... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just check it out after the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will have... It has a lot of videos in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to zoom out to the goth club so I can look miserable tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, probably after the goth club or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anytime.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will make that happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for calling, my friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, bud.
[SPEAKER_13]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: And look at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting back-to-back phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you, my friend?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am doing good, Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about yourself?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very happy that lots of people are interacting with the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is making me very happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you were sitting on hold there for quite a while, so I appreciate your patience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, no problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody beat you to the punch a little earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's new, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much new.
[SPEAKER_08]: Took it to the ITG guy, like I said I was going to do last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, yes, I remember this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were having it out with the ITG guy in your column over on Inside Pulse.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any feedback from that so far?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, not direct feedback, except actually one person directly replied to the column on the site saying that he tried In The Groove and wasn't too impressed.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said it didn't have the
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: All that has happened now is one appears in my area so I can try it for myself so I can develop an opinion on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you win the Come to Orange Lounge radio contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: At this rate, we're going to save our jelly bellies and that contest will be happening in 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully, if I can ever get a boatload of money, the first thing I'm going to do with it is to fly out and see you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now you've got a wedding coming up, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I got a wedding coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta spend it on the missus first, but then us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're talking, like, lots of money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, hey, this makes me think of a topic we were just talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does your girlfriend, or your fianc, does she end a DDR?
[SPEAKER_08]: She knows I play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's not too into it because she can't play very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something's wrong with her leg.
[SPEAKER_08]: She can walk normally, but she's had some surgeries in the past and she can't necessarily play.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know folks like that and they just have a hard time playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, RicePrincess, I don't think she has a problem with me saying this, RicePrincess actually doesn't play a whole lot of DDR because she had surgery on her leg some time ago, and it causes her not to be able to, I mean, she can play it, but she can't play it as intensively as most of the addicts do, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried getting her into it when we first started going out and nothing doing, so I said, okay, you got your opinion, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did get her into Pokemon, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, but even though she's not into DDR, it worked, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: And is there anything that your girlfriend did that maybe at first you were like, okay, I gotta learn how to like that, or...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, nothing I can think of on the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably for the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keeps you out of trouble that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other stuff going on at Inside Pulse this week we should be aware of?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we have something new coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometime in the future we're going to have a Shining Force feature pop up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what is that all about?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's an RPG series, The Shining Force.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing like shamelessly shilling my own site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, nothing like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why people call into this show, really, is to whore out their own projects, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come to my website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any comments on what we talked about in the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I've got to get going real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's fair by me.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, bud.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been playing over there on the webcam like crazy, haven't you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: All of a sudden I saw in the chatroom somebody had posted, Jamie's hot!
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at that, I see it right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie is so hot, says Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie's selling it on the webcam tonight, awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine, put my magnets on the cam, but don't F up the TV with the magnetic fields and all that stuff, that would make me cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's see, we have the Skype line still open, if you guys want to call in, we'll keep it open a few more minutes for you guys, just in case you want to call in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to think of what else is going on in the scene right now, there's really, oh, Angel, you have a comment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting up there?
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, I don't know, well actually it's something that all of us can make fun of because, oops.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, um, AIM, or AOL Instant Messenger came up with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, wait, hold this thought because I'm going to go off on this for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know where you're going.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to talk about this in detail a little bit.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, you didn't hear anything.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, raise it from your minds.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what we get for not preparing this show in advance, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've dealt with that for years, you'll continue to love us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, we're going to go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Dark Knight with a shameless plug to get OLR on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_03]: and what the hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, go for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that project ended up taking off or what, but I guess not, because I haven't heard anything else about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLR East Coast.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'd love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it was in the budget of jelly beans and cashews, I would do it, but you know... And the sun-dried tomatoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, and the sun-dried tomatoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't forget about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good third of the budget.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think that we had a vote to up our budget to add spinach, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to have to fire somebody to add the spinach.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need spinach more than an archive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Dark Knight, if we were to come out to the East Coast as Orange Lounge Radio, what would we do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where would we be doing our show from, and what kinds of stuff would we report on, do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, I would probably have y'all in New York, in the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very fine, very fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Covering in the groove.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This project's cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would do a show live from 8 on the break with my ass planted on the up arrow of the in the groove machine if we had the money for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: And Jamie could have her ass planted on the down arrow on the two player side.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about him.
[SPEAKER_16]: Maybe flipping it off or taking a piss on the back of it or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: Since I hardly ever get to do this, hi Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because you know me and my public urination.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I think I just started to piss Dane again.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, don't go there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki could be on the Parapara machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little ways down.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he could be doing his white freestyle on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, if you say so.
[SPEAKER_05]: But like I said, give OLR money so you can bring them to the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that give OLR money idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, people have been telling us we should open up a PayPal thing for the longest time, a give OLR money thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: We do have the unofficial give OLR money thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can PayPal to nightmare underscore hunter at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_24]: Any amount of money is fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: All that money will not be going to Tsunami Relief.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you can give it to me, and I might.
[SPEAKER_24]: If the price is right, I might.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, that is not the give OLR money.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is make Loki's porn collection bigger fund, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: That is all you're going to do is make it... Buy porn?
[SPEAKER_16]: Who buys porn?
[SPEAKER_16]: Send to jamie at orangedownradio.com your links to your PayPal accounts and passwords.
[SPEAKER_16]: and the money will be well used to fund my let's go visit everybody and not go to work yeah right the pay our rent we'll have the Orange Lounge RV how about that
[SPEAKER_16]: Dude, we'd be like the freaking Partridge family.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be rad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Maybe we'd get our own cult.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we could wing it, if we had the money and we could all get like a week off of work, I would pile us all in a van and we'd drive around the country for a week.
[SPEAKER_16]: My work only gives leave of absence in increments of 30 days, so hey, that works for me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do I get to come or am I still fired?
[SPEAKER_03]: It depends if the spinach can come or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: Spinach would probably be consumed, so I guess you can come.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like spinach, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say, Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd love to do the East Coast and talk about DDR out there, the whole scene out there, but until we have the money, we rely on you guys to report on the East Coast scene for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can give us money.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what is going on on the East Coast scene right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's so freaking great about In The Groove, anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, I'm in Richmond, so we'll never see you in the groove, knock on wood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what else is going on on the East Coast, then?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing much right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still kind of griping over the fact that we no longer have 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, what happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: The machine wasn't taken care of, so they basically, the people up there called it a dead weight and got rid of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the last thing they did was put an upgrade in this machine to a V3, and that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_03]: you know we had a very similar sob story in Sacramento R8 style dead, gone, finally mailed away it's sad but you know the machine it's in a better place now it's in a better place now alright we're gonna let you go buddy we're gonna go to break have a good one though thanks for calling in later we heard from a lot of people tonight that was good thank you guys for calling in and making the show interesting because lord knows we're not good at it just kidding
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to go to another break, and in this break, let's do some US DDR music, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know if I don't start it off with this song, that Jamie will kill me.
[SPEAKER_16]: We can't have that, can we?
[SPEAKER_03]: We cannot, so we'll be back after this with more Orange Launch Radio and the FUs of the week, coming up.
It's got to be forever, the green grass blows and the wind is dancing
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be a much better fight with you, with me If you hadn't met me, I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
[SPEAKER_13]: So now what should I do?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm strung out, addicted to you My body aches, now that you're gone My supplies fell through You had to give me everything you had and more You craved my happiness When you made me feel joy and made you smile
DarkSakura.com
Let me tell you something you don't know Let me tell you something you don't know
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me tell you something you don't know Take to keep the secrets I will show Take to keep the secrets I will show
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Gaming Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: So uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, honestly, guys, that is what I absolutely love about this show is that, you know, we're supposedly about video games and DR and all that nerdy stuff, but man, when Tom Brokaw says cunt, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we have to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Skyblind's open again.
[SPEAKER_03]: A few of you folks in the chatroom requested that we open it back up, so fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're opening it up for a little window.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's open right now, so you guys can call in right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only for a couple minutes, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we're going to go on to bigger and better things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, that you have to be in our chat room to send in your FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get into that segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please, though, we do have a lot of folks listening tonight, and explicit's here, which means it's going to go long anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please, if you would, try to keep your FUs of the week short, and we'll get to those in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we've got a call on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear stuff moving around, but I don't hear you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Static Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Static.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Static Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you can hear us, we cannot hear you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make sure your microphone is turned on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, we got the hang up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Live radio, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: No phone screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not in the budget for a phone screener, either.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had to cut that out to make way for the jelly beans.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what can we do?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll try it again a little later.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll try opening up the Skype line again a little later.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for now, I want to move into another topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel, you were mentioning this and then I cut you off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so sorry, but please.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going on, Angel?
[SPEAKER_16]: I found something that we could actually make fun of if we wanted to.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was talking to Sky on AIM earlier, just chatting it up, and then I saw a little link that...
[SPEAKER_16]: It was something about an AOL Instant Messenger game, but it had something to do with dancing and I was kind of intrigued to click on it, but then I didn't want to because it was going to charge me money after a certain amount of songs and whatever, but I was almost tempted just to see how crappy it was going to be or good or however, but if it has to do with aim, usually it's crappy, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we will see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I investigated a little bit here, and sure enough, there is this new game that's showing up on AOL, on the Instant Messenger, in the games portion, called Groovomatic is the name of this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Groovomatic, and I'm actually downloading it and installing it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you're hearing a couple skips and things like that, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just moving in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's go ahead and see if we can't...
[SPEAKER_03]: Get in this Groovomatic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Angel, you actually didn't check this out yet?
[SPEAKER_16]: All I know is that you get one character and ten songs for free, and then you have to pay after that, I believe.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I know about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: But we'll see in about a few minutes if it's any good or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this is a game made by Wild Tangent, which I know AdAware recognizes.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is an ad bot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have just installed an ad bot on my computer for you people, so you better appreciate this sneak preview of Groove-O-Matic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so I'm going to go into single player mode here, and we're going to go into Groove-O-Matic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to hear what kind of songs this Groove-O-Matic game has.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes, it's saying Wild Tangent.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the company that made this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Groovy little songs there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we're going full screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to do this dance to the beat option.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, look at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get little characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a mama on the right side there with big chichis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Her character's got some chichis there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's her name's Janet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now I can...
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there's only one song I can play in this mini version.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called La Fiesta.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys ready to see La Fiesta?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they should be able to hear this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so I'm going to play the song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, is this like Bust-a-Move?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of set up like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, run commentary while I play.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is, um, interesting for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Bustamove!
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is just like Bustamove.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't DDR at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's what?
[SPEAKER_03]: This song is really hot, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, wait, I'm going to back out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I hit escape.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's actually, it looks like there's a mode in there that is something about freestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like you can play with your own MP3s.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to do that mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see if I can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little goody, I can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would be a good song to dance to in freestyle mode?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we're not going to do girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to do something...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm using here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't want to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, hopefully I have something in this folder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, it's glitching out on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm already getting really bad glitches here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: It fixed itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's a song I can do here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to do this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see how this works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so it's loading the song I just picked right now, and let's see how this plays.
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, commentary please.
[SPEAKER_24]: Same shitty game still.
[SPEAKER_24]: Same background.
[SPEAKER_04]: And wow, this rocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's just sitting there doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just dancing back and forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's like DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is exactly DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow, we ripped off DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: What the hell is that chick doing on the side?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why is she getting naked?
[SPEAKER_24]: I like this game, but why... What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is like the guy game, but not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not even playing the damn MP3 I told it to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's hokey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, what can we say?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was interesting, to say the least.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it had Buster Groove and DDR stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: That blows.
[SPEAKER_03]: It stole ideas from two games there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that about?
[SPEAKER_07]: That blows hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, I can't believe we're going to advertise this game that we just did there.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to check this out for yourself, open up AOL Instant Messenger and look on your games panel because it's right there waiting for you to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, have at it, people.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sorry we were not able to put that on the cam.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll try to do that next week for you guys because we have to actually load it on a different computer to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that would involve putting spyware on Loki's computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much for bringing this show down with that crappy game, Angel.
[SPEAKER_16]: I knew it was going to be a crappy game.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just thought it was
[SPEAKER_03]: To that game's credit, it's not as bad as some of the knockoff games I've seen out there available for download.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that one that had all the classical music in MIDI format?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was by, like, GameHouse or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Tapajam, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tapajam.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game's... oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that game was bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a bad game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we are going to go into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, why is it that we have to do the FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because we're not going to take it anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is punishment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_16]: A big F you goes, of course, to the usual traffic, fog, sunny skies that get in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Really, I think it had to do with just being sick when I was out in the Bay Area on Friday.
[SPEAKER_16]: And also a big F you to not being able to purchase Twinbee for the Game Boy Advance because Network had it.
[SPEAKER_16]: and a big F you to Nintendo for giving them better packaging in Japan because the old releases are really awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_16]: They come in very tiny versions of the original boxes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Another F you goes toward time-distance lack of money.
[SPEAKER_16]: School's starting next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Really, this is not a whole bunch I'm overly angsty about immediately.
[SPEAKER_16]: Shock.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, yeah, and, uh, and FU to, uh... Oh, not being able to install certain games on my system yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Gravity for being assholes, and Ragnarok Online 2 for not being out yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, and the scale at the damn gym.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, dear.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your turn.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm... I'm getting tired now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_24]: The only F you of the week goes to me for being stupid and making a dumb mistake.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, um... Fuck you to, um, actually... To Tahoe Joes for ruining mashed potatoes.
[SPEAKER_24]: They single-handedly ruined something that's so simple...
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to the lack of angst in the room tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate to be on the same page, but I really have a lot of the same FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to difficult situations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I just... I kind of... Like, there was like a... Somebody proposed something to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is going to sound dirty, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody kind of proposed something interesting out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, and it has to do with my professional career.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got an interesting proposal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm really torn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm just going to kind of put my...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, actually, if I can sneak something in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_16]: F you to my voice for deciding it doesn't want to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go on and move on with the rest of the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to regret this, but let's start with Explicit.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to ask you a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did any of my FUs get to the last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even remember what we touched on last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last week was last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I cut out most of your FUs that dealt with people in particular because we don't like those types of FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'd ask that you just try to pass those ones up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember which ones you can say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just what's new this week that pissed you off?
[SPEAKER_03]: Three hour show, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU for having a third crack in my fucking window over debris over a freaking storm again.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, three cracks in a window off in one whole month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ain't that a fucking bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you for school for starting next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: There goes packing up some of the books again.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you with everybody trying to make my tournament a joke again with the piss.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a tournament, just like everything else.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not something to take a piss on or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if YouTube people...
[SPEAKER_07]: who wants to start drama privately and sending their private messages to me privately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because you don't like somebody in this tournament does not mean you guys are not going to get along.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait till the tournament comes in.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it comes to people begging for the freaking song list for the tournament, goddammit, I told you the list is going to be 16 songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing else.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will not reveal it to the tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said on the rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just deal with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next person who... Next person who mentions this in private will be banned from my tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting a headache with all these people trying to complain and bitch about certain things that should not be bitched about.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Effie goes to a stroke that my grandmother just recently had.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty depressing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't really want to say this in the Effies, but yeah, strokes suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: And F.E.
[SPEAKER_07]: goes from misplanned, from plans being all mixed up on Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was supposed to go to, I was supposedly supposed to go to Canada's freestyle meetup, but things got mixed up so I had to go to Reno with a few people.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was planned earlier before the meetup.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Effie goes from the same people who are complaining about the religious issue over some games or censorship issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because something has explicit content or whatever or they think it's offensive like a puppet of Maria from Banya think it's too religiously offensive is a reason why the puppet was removed from the Paradise Island.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have got to be kidding me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I shit you not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is that game, why is that song offensive?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it says Ave Maria.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see how that, let me tell Mary, I don't see how that is offending a Christian group.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't say Ave Maria set your child on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: It doesn't even say that at all.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're probably thinking it's blasphemous or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God, you've got to be kidding me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I thought that I left Alabama.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck Christians!
[SPEAKER_24]: I hate the goddamn stupid super Christians out there that want to convert all the evils in the world.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's you people that ruin our TV and ruin our radio and music.
[SPEAKER_24]: Goddamn, if I want to see boobies flash by accident on TV, that's my God-given right.
[SPEAKER_24]: And if your children don't see, if happen to catch those boobies, it's time to tell them about life.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_24]: One day or another they're going to see them, and that's that.
[SPEAKER_16]: If your children catch sight of boobies or happen to hear shit, fuck, damn, no matter what on TV or the radio, it's your fault for not censoring them, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio are absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do your goddamn job and stop blaming the media for...
[SPEAKER_16]: Screwing up babysitting your children when it's not their responsibility.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you're going to get knocked up and have the kid, you need to take some goddamn responsibility, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's a little funny, though, about the religious issue?
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to point out, Loki was giving an F you to what we coined super Christians.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not all Christians, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can be religious and be one with God and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's your right as an American.
[SPEAKER_03]: Freedom of religion.
[SPEAKER_03]: But remember...
[SPEAKER_03]: Freedom of religion means I'm free to choose my religion as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's funny about the situation?
[SPEAKER_07]: Christians say they want to stand up to themselves, yet they commit a sin.
[SPEAKER_07]: A sin of wrath, of anger, saying this thing is offensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: They go outrageous to the management and patent vending themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now they're doing almost the same thing to DDR because Heysel Fuse says the word fuck in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they try to get rid of DDR and try to screw my tournament over.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they want to screw my tournament over... I'm not sure if that was... Finger on the cam, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously.
[SPEAKER_16]: I actually need to throw in an FU.
[SPEAKER_16]: FU to the majority of humanity for being stupid.
[SPEAKER_16]: And for sucking.
[SPEAKER_07]: and now I have to censor my props for this tournament so these don't go too far so I can't use my fuck you hat or I have to put a I have to put a white label so it doesn't show fuck you on this I can't bring vibrators on the tournament as a prop I can't bring barbed wire, I can't bring glass, I can't bring a tit cup that I have and etc etc etc that results in provoking the media
[SPEAKER_07]: because I don't want to get sued.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless I do a counter-loss and people stand up for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, since I don't know which FU's got into last week's show, I just have to say to be continued for now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh good, we'll finish this show in three hours after all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Arcadian, your turn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you, this cold is hanging around still.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you to the puddles of
[SPEAKER_09]: Angel!
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, F.U.
[SPEAKER_16]: to being sick earlier this week, seems like that's going around around here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, uh, yeah, I don't think, oh yeah, F.U.
[SPEAKER_16]: to school is starting on Tuesday because I don't want to go, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's my educational goals or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: and, uh, I don't want to, you know, work tomorrow, but I got to anyway, and whatever, so, that kind of sucks, and, um, I guess that's it, because I can't think of, uh, the FDs I was going to think of, so whatever!
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: With one notable exception, the room here is pretty not angsty tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a lack of angst tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to keep it as a three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up, exception.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's go and see if our chat room outdoes us tonight in the angst.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will have a look here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Misty!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkNight says, DarkNight says, DarkTetsuya says,
[SPEAKER_03]: in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_03]: MPQ says, F you to Sonic commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the Hedgehog, but the Burger Chain, I imagine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I see their commercials, I think, oh man, I want that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But wait!
[SPEAKER_03]: There aren't any around here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the same problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: They advertise Sonic all the time in Sacramento, and the nearest one is an hour drive away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a Sonic in Yuba City.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the closest one.
[SPEAKER_16]: When I lived in the Bay Area, that's all we got was Sonic commercials.
[SPEAKER_16]: And at least in the area that I was living in, we didn't even have one.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so we hear you there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, F you to my parents insisting on using AOL even though we have cable internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That coming from MPQ.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm canceling mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: VXChaseXV says F you once again to my manager.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you, F you, F you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Phoenix says, F you to DarkSakura for booting me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha, only kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a damn good thing he put that only kidding thing in there, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to the weather getting cold for tomorrow when I have to march.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he also says he apologized.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was him that called in and he apologizes for his microphone screwing up.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S says, That's no fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Big Red Pimp, Ohio Bomani says, F you to the lack of a Chinese food restaurant in my back-ass town.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dork says, one word, girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I don't know if he means the song or girls in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: You be the judge.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ 100 Matt, says FU of the week, General Grievous slash Derek, not holding up his end of the deal FU leaving hometown New York City to go back to school in Phoenix DarkSakura, oh it's Samir, hi DarkSakura I sent that on behalf of somebody I forgot, you sent that on behalf of a friend, and it comes from EarthDragonOnyx
[SPEAKER_03]: and the FU says I'm trying to decide on a new character so I have a poll going and someone said give it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck him.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Raichan says FU to the people that go through life believing they deserve something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't deserve anything in this life.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one owes you anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly Sephiroth 1215 says a big FU to General Grievous for telling on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know who this general grievance person is, but they're busted.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is that big bassy noise I'm hearing right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard like a big bass noise for a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Phoenix in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Sakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's spicy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to go to a quick break, then we're going to come back and wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you believe it's that time already?
[SPEAKER_03]: Got a couple more things we want to say to you guys, though, so stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Featuring a couple songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to do Rotel the Mercury, so we're going to do that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Bye-bye!
[SPEAKER_12]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio about ready to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Motion Picture Drama, The Aviator Best Motion Picture Musical or Comedy, Sideways Best Performance by an Actor or Drama, Leonardo DiCaprio
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Performance by an Actress for a Drama, Hilary Swank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Performance by an Actor, Comedy, Jamie Foxx for Ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Performance by an Actress, Comedy was Annette Bening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Supporting Actor, Clive Owen in Closer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Supporting Actress, the very foxy Natalie Portman in Closer.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_16]: She's well educated.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What'd you say, Jimmy?
[SPEAKER_03]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's very well-educated, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: She is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am a big homo, but honestly, Natalie Portman, I'd hit that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best Director, Clint Eastwood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Television, you guys watch TVs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you watch this one, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best TV Series, Drama, Nip Tuck was the winner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best TV Series, Comedy, Desperate Housewives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And best actor in a comedy, Jason Bateman in Arrested Development.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best actress, Terry Hatcher, Desperate Housewives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best drama, it was the guy in Deadwood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best actress drama, some chick from Law and Order Special Victims Unit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But look, here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the one I had to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best performance by an actor in a supporting role in a series, miniseries, or motion picture made for television.
[SPEAKER_03]: William Shatner in Boston Legal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: William Shatner, you guys.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what I have to say about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: KORN!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright guys, that's about going to wrap it up for us here tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys very much for tuning in and listening as always.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quick plugs, shoutouts on Tuesday nights, pump up the volume, listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monday night, yep, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's because my show is rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's better than mediocre.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want something that's strictly mediocre, Outside the Box is on Thursday, and it's better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's certainly funnier than Joey.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, tune in.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anything is funnier than Joey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_16]: The Flood is funnier than Joey.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else is there?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's... Whatever you're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's Thursdays.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mondays, Diversion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Diversion.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Friday's over on The Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wednesdays we have the oldie and moldy Orange Launch Radio reruns.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're still around.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to get some new episodes up in there, so I'll try to shuffle that around.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we're going to have new music coming to Bomani Music & More this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got some of the songs from Fusion, some new 2DX11 songs, some of the secret songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got some copies of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to put those in there, too, because there's some awesome songs in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are the secret songs?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a new Ryu song and a new Slake song, and I like them both.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the boss song for 2DX?
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got called out and I lost big time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll start it off with Explicit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since you were the tardiest, you have to go first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Being late sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Being the second tardiest, Angel gets her final thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: Need more game.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh wait, I have school this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arcadian, being prompt, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope I get broadband soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very soon, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki, having the least amount of seniority, you get your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomorrow's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my final thought is, I'm going to give Jamie her final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: My final thought is, well, my lap's pretty warm from this laptop.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go outside and do something, people!
[SPEAKER_16]: Except unless we're broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_03]: The final word of the show I'm going to give to Mr. Quiet Arcadian42 because he's got to say something, damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: One word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Leprechauns.
[SPEAKER_12]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_12]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm emailing Grandma, she's a hundred and two But now I'm set to inform ya Granddad's message won't pull through Wanna surf but I can hardly row The U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Postal Service ain't this slow I told AOL that I was totally screwed They said, we're sorry we boned ya But there's nothing we can do Yeah, yeah
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, no, I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: See ya!
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't forget about our podcast, by the way, because that's, you know, what we're going to go work on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, listen to the podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys very much for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a great one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And go back to our My Money Means More program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whore up our ratings!
[SPEAKER_03]: Rate us a five!
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell everybody you know