[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody and welcome to the very first Orange Lounge Radio Podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm your host, Rob Roberts, along with my other host.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm DarkSakura, the great and terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then of course we have one more host you guys have all come to know and love and I'm hungry no I'm Loki alright so Orange Lounge Radio this is going to be the first edition of our podcast so what is this all about the Orange Lounge Radio podcast the idea behind this is this great new technology that's out there on the internet that's basically you can kind of think of it as an audio blog
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's something that you can subscribe to.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're hearing this, you've figured out via our website how to subscribe to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now what you're going to be able to do is that you stay subscribed to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And about every week or so, you're going to get a brand new episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is not just rehashed, re-edited stuff that's on our normal three-hour live talk program.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is an all-new program that's made specifically for you to take with you in your pocket everywhere you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just promise to treat us gently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Beatmania, then we had Dance Dance Revolution, that's the one you guys have all heard about, certainly, and then we have other games that came out in that series, Guitar Freaks, Drum Mania, Para Para Paradise, all these types of games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then in the meantime, other folks notice what Konami's doing, and they come out with their own music games that are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got Amplitude, you've got Frequency, and then you've got Donkey Konga, Taiko Drum Master now, and then of course you had the granddaddies of them all,
[SPEAKER_02]: The very first games we saw like this, one of your favorites, right Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, my Busta Move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Busta Move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you get annoyed when people call this Busta Groove though, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, because Busta Move, the only reason why it's Busta Groove over here is because Taito has Busta Move licensed for Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which Puzzle Bobble is a lot cuter name for the little bubble game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it was Bubble Bobble and you had Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bust a move.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, how do you bust a groove?
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like fill it with something and then hit it with a jackhammer?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: How can you serve someone?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's just in the same category right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so of course we have this love for music video games because it's how we all kind of came together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you'll notice, if you visit huge websites dedicated to these games out there, things such as DDRFreak.com, things such as BomaniStyle, DDRSpot, and of course OrangeLaunchRadio.com, you notice that there's quite a little following to these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, OrangeLaunchRadio, we kind of want to expand.
[SPEAKER_02]: We noticed that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Video gaming, while it's addressed out there in the internet radio world, it's just not covered quite the way we think we can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we like to call ourselves also Video Game News About Games That Don't Suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which sometimes get fewer and fewer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's just so many great new games out there we want to talk about as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even when a game sometimes does suck, we've got to let you know about it so that you don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: and what they're talking about is that Konami is going to showcase over at the Consumer Electronics Show 2005 and Konami is going to actually feature Dance Dance Revolution at the show from January 6th through the 9th and they're going to be doing this thing called the Cardio Play Zone so now of course the Consumer Electronics Show this is something that takes place in America
[SPEAKER_02]: They're probably going to be selling games such as, you know, well, I mean, not literally selling there at the show, but they're going to be pushing games such as DDR Ultramix 2, DDR Extreme, things that came out this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what a really good time to be pushing this Get Fit envelope right at the beginning of the year, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because everyone's going to be making their New Year's resolutions.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, everyone's going to get in a big frenzy to buy it right there at the beginning of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So even if they lose their momentum later on, they've already made the purchase.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now you are somebody that actually goes to a gym on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You play DDR for a workout sometimes, but you get your real workout at the gym, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me about what happens in January versus what happens in June.
[SPEAKER_03]: The gym fills up with so many stupid people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, we're going to work out five million days a week, and we're going to get fit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, a month later, it's back to business as usual.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a couple of them will stay, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why for anyone, I say if anyone's ever going to make that resolution to get fit, start light because you will burn yourself out like just about all those other people do at the gym.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're going to play DDR to get fit, you know, we've talked a lot about on our three-hour program, we've talked a lot about how, you know, folks use DDR in their diet and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just remember to stick with it, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're going to play, play on a
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm speaking from experience here.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you stop playing for a while, you lose it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just the skill you lose, but you lose your stamina, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, I can attest to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, right now I'm working on the first stage of our coverage of the aerobic aspects of DDR.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm working on the fattening up stage, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then we'll get into actual gameplay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't say when, but at some point we'll start playing again, or at least I'll start playing again, and
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, what I want to talk about is going on in Bomani News right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has to do with DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome mix that's out there for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: They partnered up with a different drum.com, the label there, and just gave a whole new style of music to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, through the DDR Freak forums, we actually know some of the new songs that are going to be in Downloadable Song Pack 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you guys can look forward to these songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Cosmic Cowgirls going to be in Song Pack 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the song that was in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember that song?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my drum mania song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cosmic Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a remix of Kind Lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know exactly what the remix title is yet, but there will be a remix of Kind Lady in the song pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another remix of In My Eyes is going to be happening as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Togo Project featuring Sana, More Deep, version 2.1.
[SPEAKER_02]: This song, you might remember, was a hidden song in Max 2 USA, so now it's going to cross over to the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is a really interesting one, I thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: If I can even pronounce this right, it's a song from Guitar Freak 6th and Drum Mania 5th, and it's crossing over into DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Balalakia, Carried with the Wind.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know this one?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of an interesting one.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to hear those songs in their entirety, we'll be playing them on Orange Lounge Radio at some point a little bit of a later date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, as you know, on Orange Lounge Radio, the program which we have Sunday night, 630 Pacific Standard Time, we have this little segment we like to do called the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what we've decided to do for this portable version is, you know, Jamie still has a little bit of anger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the pain, the anger.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she's going to use that anger for the forces of good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's going to have her own... Is that what they're calling it now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's what they're calling it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now she's going to have her advice column.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Jamie, if you would, please tell us your advice column for this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My first piece of advice for this first podcast is...
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have to sign a contract, read the damn thing first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't just sign your name to it and then call customer service when you don't understand what you've just signed when they bill you for something or when something goes wrong because you were a big retard and didn't read it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Always read before you sign.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care how many damn pages it is or if it's in Swahili.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's a contract, they have to pay for you to read it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get a lawyer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just read it first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Understand what you are signing your name to, because a contract is binding and legal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you're under the age of majority within your state, and then that's another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Correct me if I'm wrong, though, but if everybody actually read their contracts, wouldn't customer service employees be without a job?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because people are still fundamentally retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just checking.
[SPEAKER_01]: And really now, why would you be signing a contract in Swahili?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: What if you're from Africa?
[SPEAKER_01]: But, ah, damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Still though, it should be English.
[SPEAKER_01]: English.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, tell us what's going on in the sim scene this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those guys that like to emulate their favorite music games on the computer, or, I'm sorry, emulate versus simulate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get yelled at by somebody for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Simulate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, really, one big thing, because a lot of websites are down because of different reasons.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyways, the big thing that came out this week would be Technofiend 3, which is the brand new Stepmania skin, for those who might not know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was just released, actually, on Bumaisel.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can find it in their downloadable sim file section.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technofiend 3.0 Stepmania 3.9 Release Candidate 2
[SPEAKER_01]: Release Candidate 2A, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the one that's on stepmania.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can download it there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just get the new upgrade, download that skin, and it's heaven right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And again, since this is the first podcast, there might be people listening to this that have no idea what you just said, which is possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, sometimes folks have taken the concept of DDR and built these simulators around it, and Loki...
[SPEAKER_02]: He's our man in the scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: He knows about what's going on, so he's always going to bring you those kinds of updates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, StepMania is the most popular Dance Dance Revolution simulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's available over at www.stepmania.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: But simulators being built for games other than DDR, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other types of simulators out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any popular recommendations?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some for Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's DTXMania.
[SPEAKER_01]: Step Mania is an all-in-one simulator game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Techno something or other.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's some 8-panel, 9-panel thing that there's like... Technomotion.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technomotion.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's like, what, three of those in the entire world or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think like two of them are in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, two of them are in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's those that are coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tons of, you know, games that no one really plays anymore, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to be coming to simulator stuff right now, though, if you want to play right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: DTX Mania, which would be one for Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can find tons of information on all these other simulator stuff on the Bomani Style forums.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually have whole sections dedicated to these simulators.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really play much Guitar Freaks because I don't have any good controllers for them or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as Beat Mania goes, Delight Delight, Reduplication, and there's Beemania DX is the other good one.
[SPEAKER_01]: So check those out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or BM98, that's another good one to find out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's pretty much all that's simulated out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know there's also Feeling Pomo, which is the popping music one, which is supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: But like I said, Stepmania 4.0 is supposed to have them all together, and it would be a lot easier than having six different programs.
[SPEAKER_01]: So look for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we'll see what happens there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's move on to what's going on in the rest of the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the gaming world's kind of quiet right now because it's the holidays.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just coming, you know, this is the first week of 2005, so we're just coming off the holidays.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's not a whole lot kind of new going on, exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sure we're going to start, as the new year comes back, we're going to start hearing a whole lot of stuff right up until E3 because they're going to start dropping little hints here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll do our best to keep you guys on top of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in the meantime, there's sometimes news that you can't control.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is the news, one of the oldest American ways of business, the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this one's kind of amusing, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys remember this game that came out this year called The Guy Game?
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was basically Girls Gone Wild in game form.
[SPEAKER_02]: You must love this concept, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, this has actually been done like Howard Stern and The Man Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's been done before.
[SPEAKER_01]: They basically kind of ripped it off and...
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack with Naked Chicks
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be a good idea, but unfortunately there was one little thing these guys forgot to check.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now what's happened is that Cox News Service last week reported that a young woman, and they're not giving out her name, they're calling her Jane Doe.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has filed suit against Take-Two, Sony, and Microsoft because this game was out on PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take two are the folks that made the game there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have filed suit because it has footage of her topless.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this was taken during the annual spring break on Texas South Padre Island.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, okay, that's where they get a lot of these girls to show their assets, so to speak, is at these events by getting them inebriated.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was one little teeny problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: The girl was only 17.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops-doe.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Jane-doe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, as a girl, a gamer girl, what do you think of this?
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, I think that showing your boobs for anybody is about the most retarded thing you can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Being from the South, from where Mardi Gras originated, I think that all those stupid tourists that go to New Orleans to flash their tits for, you know, boom pies, are retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so are all the ones who do the Girls Gone Wild thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're sluts.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think her parents should pay for this.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should, you know, make her parents pay for this kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: She was, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure there's laws against that, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know there's laws against that, and her parents should pay.
[SPEAKER_01]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ruining our entertainment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Always these stupid little hang-ups.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, any response to this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh... I actually agree with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: She knew where she was going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I told Dan to buy BMX XXX just because I wanted to see what all the crap was in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I did buy that game and that game is quite nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's my thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: With everything that has to do with putting people on film and everything, there's a little thing called a release agreement.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where was that in this, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: What, they just filmed it and didn't sign a release?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shame on Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure she signed a release, but the problem is, if you're under 18, you can't sign the contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she probably said she was 18.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just didn't check her ID.
[SPEAKER_02]: But of course, if all you're wearing is panties and nothing else, then you probably don't have your ID on you.
[SPEAKER_03]: There still is a thing, even if there was a contract, having taken business law,
[SPEAKER_03]: A contract against a minor is not a binding contract.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a voided contract.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, legally, yes, she does have the right to sue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, damn girl, just keep your clothes on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't be a slut!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that easy.
[SPEAKER_01]: All I gotta say is, we have the game already in so hot, nothing you can do from me seeing your boobies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will see them!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I will laugh at my victory.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a sick man, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly though, the interesting news that comes out of this in the end, this is going to be a collector's game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be that original version of Tetris that was on the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will be your first release of Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: This would be X-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you know the game I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where it looks like scissors in a maze except one of those is really his cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: On that note, that's going to do it for this edition, our very first edition of the Orange Lounge Radio podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys for downloading us, and we'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.