[SPEAKER_00]: Fox News ruffles the feathers of the gaming community Sega Master System games are poised to make a comeback and is the Gizmondo about to be revived?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm here!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, how are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am fine, how are you doing, Chris?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm now, I've had coffee with lots of sugar, and before that we had frozen yogurt with lots of sugar, so I'm getting ready to blow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're happy!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, if I'm not mistaking, this may very well be your last appearance on Orange Launch Radio for a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, not like ever, ever, but for a little while, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to desperately, desperately try to come back here because I've been in, for those of you who do not know, I've been going back and forth from L.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: to my home in the South Bay, Los Gatos, because my grandfather was diagnosed with...
[SPEAKER_05]: and I've been kind of being their chauffeur to whatever it is they need and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I've kind of been their little slave, which I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: But sorry to hear about the family circumstance.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's rough, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: People are old and that kind of stuff happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I've been going back and forth and I'm also moving to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Madison, Wisconsin, and March, if all goes according to plan, for school, and I have a girlfriend there, so, pluses.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's gotta be someone very special to get you to move from sunny, warm, wonderful California to, oh my fucking lord, it's cold, Wisconsin.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, the accent is kind of like this, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you gotta get yourself one of those, that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you kids have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you guys are going to have a lot of fun together.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm going to be trying to come back more and more.
[SPEAKER_03]: You better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, actually, we got a new addition to the family.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: My dad's girlfriend gave birth to a little girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 17th.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to come visit your little sister once in a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she's adorable and crying and driving her mother up the wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: That takes a whole lot, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going back to games and gaming type conventions for a little bit, are you going to be going to the Chicago convention this year, Asen?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going, Asen.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, actually, some of our listeners are really trying to get us to go, and I'm going to try to make it happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I definitely will come.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'll have an apartment, so you guys are willing to stay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have a pillow fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: The official OLR Battle Royale pillow fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually going to try and get a press pass to see if I can do some interviews for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a really cool idea, which I want to discuss with you later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for those of you who are going to ASUN, I will be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be at the art table with my girlfriend Megan and a bunch of other really awesome artists that are going to show up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so look for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'll have blue hair and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very easy to spot.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, let's go ahead and move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't introduced the one and only, let me switch mics with him so he has his normal back, the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finished the sandwich.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry I ignored you for a little bit there, but you know, lesbians cater a little more to our demographic than you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where would we be without Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki's a very important part of this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You having a good week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had an okay week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Perfect World
[SPEAKER_06]: Free play, free download, and according to her, it takes everything, and this is her perspective, took everything she hated about World of Warcraft and everything she hated about Guild Wars and removed them and combined the best parts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have any examples, like what types of things?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was really drunk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you'll know more about it when you're able to get in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was really nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, you get certain wear classes, get like pets and like flying pets.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you have to watch Torchwood.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the hottest show on TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you realize that this is a Doctor Who spinoff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I said.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, you know, it's like a Doctor Who spinoff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I said, I said, one of my friend girls is like obsessed with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're like, oh, yeah, we like Doctor Who, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you take Torchwood and rearrange it, it spells Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before we get to some more gaming weeks, I'm assuming you're all finished.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: All done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to read some comments from the chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
Africa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.orangemonstradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw asks, Sky, next week is the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will there be a show by then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn right there's going to be a show during the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could care less about the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: So absolutely we'll be doing a show because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think some folks out there would like to have some alternative programming to the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we do have the Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't they have the Kitty Bowl usually, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing a $25 sushi buffet at the place on that day, and I'm thinking about going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Other comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tiger Claw, just heard that Black Wolf is going to do his show on Saturday next week to the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's Black Wolf.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Bobby's project.
[SPEAKER_02]: He likes sports, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Bobby can watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like my roommate.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure my roommate's going to have some guys over here watching the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be out here doing our nerdy show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get back to games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week was pretty much just burnout paradise.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played countless hours of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it's not countless because I took a look at my stats there and I actually have ten and a half hours put into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You keep finding new things in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I found quite a bit of the hidden stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have almost all the jumps done and
[SPEAKER_02]: About half the billboards and half the smashes And I'm working to get my class A license And haven't played online yet Because the servers were giving me crap earlier this week So I just kind of avoided them But I may try some online stuff a little later Huh, it's fun though
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to play me online?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I got my copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll kill me, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of stuff you can do, like co-op, challenges and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that might be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I got a Vectrex.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, you won the Vectrex that you were talking about last week, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did that go?
[SPEAKER_02]: It went okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it on my desk now, and people are like, oh my god, I remember that!
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, to be honest, it's just kind of a desk piece, you know, I don't really play much on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did try, you know, some of the games that came with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Trek, the game, I understand it about as much as I understood it before, which is not very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like that game at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play Frenzy, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's called Frenzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Berserk, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same game, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Berserk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hyperchase Space Mines
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to leave it at my desk and people can come by and take a look at it and have some sort of demo loop.
[SPEAKER_02]: But none of those games ever had a demo loop and it also makes a really annoying buzzing sound.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, crap, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just turned it on when people wanted to take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, one of the controllers is broken so I had to fix that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I can get a new controller for like $10 if I really want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually make quite a few games.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are still making games for that system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: All homebrew stuff, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's new carts coming out
[SPEAKER_02]: as of last year still, so, I mean, that's kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: A complete waste of money, but it's neat, you know, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's nice to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, let's see, what else did I get?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't gotten it yet, but I have a copy of, God, I don't remember what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of the bit generation titles, but that one's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully I get to play that this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: and, uh, what else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I got, I'm actually planning on selling my Sega Saturns because I found an emulator that works perfectly on my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't even know you had a Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have two.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I bought them at a garage, or not a garage sale, at a Denios flea market because for some reason I wanted to play Panzer Dragoons Wii because I thought, oh my god, it was so awesome, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I went back and played it and I'm like, wow, this wasn't very good at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to get a stall and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But since now that I have something that will actually play them on the PC, I don't really need them anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's this local game shop, which I've been meaning to go to for weeks now, called Fair Game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They carry all the vintage stuff, everything from the Vectrex up through PlayStation 3 stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully they will...
[SPEAKER_02]: Be able to, uh, I don't know, buy that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I do have games with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember which games, so I have like two copies of Madden 97 for some reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Bug 2, a Knights demo, and like some other stuff, Machine Head, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, uh, I don't know, maybe I can put it on eBay though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, Saints Row, as usual.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and, I think I mentioned it, but not during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: My another 360 died.
[SPEAKER_02]: My another another one red ringed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently I had one that was starting to freeze up on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I figured, OK, I'm going to cut it off the pass and just put a new heat sink on it so that it'll work better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, put the new heat sink on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't really fix anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I tried pulling the heat sink off again and maybe applying a little more thermal grease on spots that may have missed some.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was a big empty spot on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went ahead and put some thermal grease on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reset it all back on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sure enough, it three rings on me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm like, crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I can't fix that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to hit it with blunt objects until it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or it won't work, and who gives a crap because I still have five.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I wanted six because my boss wants to play again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we had someone else join us up when he was busy doing something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now someone's taking his place.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he wants to play again.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, soon as you lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: You always have busy gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You manage to play a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we play at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: We play Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could play Xbox at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of Saints Row and lots of Burnout Paradise because that game, you know, it's really crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought this week I would have been playing some No More Heroes, but I haven't gotten around to that yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not yet, but soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't know if I'm going to get around to it anytime soon either because next week is Smash Bros.,
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the Japanese one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully we'll have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to give us your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go over to Chris.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, Chris, if you have anything you want to share about your gaming week, but let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, aside from playing WoW, which I seem to be doing on a regular basis now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I have no room to talk whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I heard you just got a 70, so... I wouldn't say just got, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I've been kind of out of it, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a character up to level 24 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, everybody start somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you're a Draenei, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm actually, I don't have.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've just now started getting into, because Megan is starting to play, and she's got all of her friends playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all of them have, like, epics.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm learning now what they're learning.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm, like, hearing all this shit, like, farm it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, oh, I'm farming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know for the longest time what that meant.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all, you gotta start somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I gotta, you know, because I was just a casual player.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't go, like, for hours on end, you know, just playing, and I'm like, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't need to look more like a noob than I already am, but it was, you know, so I just finally, you know, I'm starting to get more into it, but I don't have, like, a main.
[SPEAKER_03]: So wait, do you hoarder alliance now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Both.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a main, I just switch back and forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Horde is better.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to make your main a horde.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Megzi's main is a gnome, so to play with her... Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_05]: To play with her, I made a gnome, but the problem is that I'm like ten levels lower than her, so playing with her in that is kind of stupid, so I keep making more characters to try and play with her because she keeps making more characters and it's just not working.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, aside from that, I did a lot of D&D stuff, so that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I have to... Old school kind of gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've got like maybe four or five friends in LA that have always, have like, oh, we need to run a game, we need to run a game, and so I finally caved in and started making an adventure, because I don't like all the new, the pre-made ones, so I've been working on that a lot, and I freaking am annoyed at 4th edition that's coming out, but
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And people need to make me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm important.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you may, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week, I actually took a little bit of a break from WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I've been playing some, but I went back to another type of RPG that I just missed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't touched it in a while, and I decided to go back and play some Oblivion because I love that game because you can just run around and do nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Seinfeld of video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you want to ignore the main plot and just do whatever you want, you can.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I noticed you playing that this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I decided last time I did a fighter type, so this time I went like, I just went all out mage because I'm having a lot of fun summoning creatures to do my bidding and throwing fireballs at people.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I can't do damage for crap, so like if I get attacked, I'm screwed.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I create an army to go after people.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait for Elder Scrolls V. I never get past the towns because I'm too busy, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Violating the animals, punching the horses so they get pissed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the townsfolk don't look too kindly upon that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's pretty much just been that has taken up a lot of my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just had this random oblivion splurge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have been playing Burnout Paradise a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not enough to give a full review on just yet, but I do notice it's kind of like Test Drive and Burnout mixed together, which isn't necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little different.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of like the structure of the old Burnout games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure how I feel about this whole open world thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little weird, but I'm giving it a shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't taken it online either, which I hear is the best part, so we'll wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do find it interesting, though, that it interacts with the camera to, like, take your picture and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's talk a little bit about housekeeping, and then we are going to get into tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight in housekeeping, just a reminder, we are now broadcasting simulcasting on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a big hello to all the people who are watching us right now on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our Justin.TV channel is...
[SPEAKER_03]: www.justin.tv slash Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: But JustinTV is interesting because you can kind of see us even when the mics aren't hot, so it's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's that over at JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, next week on the show, an Orange Lounge Radio first.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually, what may be, I'm not sure, I don't want to stake the claim to this, but what may be a video game podcast first, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next week on the show, we are going to have...
[SPEAKER_03]: And killed me And tore me to pieces And threw every piece into a fire
[SPEAKER_03]: So we found out she was local to us, so we sent her an email and said, Hey, this might seem a little random, but do you want to come on our little podcast and sing the song for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: And she said, sure!
[SPEAKER_03]: So she's going to be here next week doing her cover of Still Alive, live here in studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's OLR first musical guest, and we're very excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's going to be a guinea pig for that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's cool, and we're very excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so she'll be here in studio next week, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: and as will the rest of us here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if we have any other guests scheduled for the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we going to get the chocolate rain guy at some point?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not going to get the chocolate rain guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's the YouTube celeb we're going to get in the studio and then we've got to look for people from other places.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, one day I want Dragon Force here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the ultimate dream.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll fly in from... Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be so complete.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like a
[SPEAKER_02]: See you at our Wayne's World right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: For real.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, why is the chat room saying they should get the Chocolate Rain guy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell does the Chocolate Rain guy have to do with video games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amixia sings about, you know, she does a cover of Still Alive.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's video game related.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chocolate Rain has nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it is funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will say this, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_03]: An old friend of Orange Lounge Radio is experiencing a little bit of internet fame of his own, I guess speaking of people who have said they will come on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did a remix of this guy from American Idol.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rinaldo LaPaz was his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did this song called We Are Brothers Forever, and it was kind of one of those things you laugh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this kid Justin, who we knew from like years ago playing DDR, he did a remix of it.
My father still be here.
[SPEAKER_03]: This has nothing to do with video games, but you can't help but admit that thing's got to be DDR inspired.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, he did that, and I emailed him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, dude, when are you going to come on the show again?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're, like, famous and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to come back.
[SPEAKER_03]: He said he would come back and talk games with us and maybe show us some more remixes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: I ran into him in a line for a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: A few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, like a couple months ago, but I don't remember what movie we were seeing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyhow, lots of things to look forward to on Orange Lounge Radio coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, please take us to video game chat, because obviously we're having problems with that tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, there's a big old stink this week having to do with Fox News and Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they aired a little segment called Sex Box, and they were talking about how Mass Effect featured full digital character nudity and had explicit sex and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone that's played Mass Effect knows that that's completely false.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nonetheless, though, they were on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually had a, I don't know, an expert, I'd say a psychology expert or something, who was kind of pimping out her book.
[SPEAKER_02]: And at the same time, also in defense, they had Jeff Knightley, who was basically from EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't it Jeff Keighley?
[SPEAKER_02]: Keighley, Knightley, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Knightley is Kira Knightley.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeff Keighley.
[SPEAKER_03]: Caribbean, Caribbean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio, we pronounce stuff good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I learned it how to read.
[SPEAKER_03]: I learned it on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so all you need to know is that basically they went back and forth for about 30 seconds talking about this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The psychologist and the host hadn't played the game, but yet they were still claiming all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyways, as the week progressed, I went kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, EA was saying they're pissed off that all this stuff was said.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is complete outright lies.
[SPEAKER_02]: They want a correction from Fox to basically fess up to not having played the game and just making up lies off the cuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: of course Fox said no we're not going to do a correction but hey you can come on to one of our shows again and to which basically they said fuck off
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, apparently the woman, of course, the psychologist, she has a book called The Cult of Perfection, and it happened to be on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, gamers got pissed off, and they, of course, realized, hey, her book's on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they left her a bunch of negative reviews, clearly stating that they had not read her book, but that it's inappropriate for minors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing that got me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that funny, Chris.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those negative reviews have been removed, the ones that gamers left.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's left, though, is still negative reviews.
[SPEAKER_02]: They weren't good to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually started reading some of the book, and as I'm reading it, I'm going, why was she invited to talk about video games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Her book has nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you're going to bring on someone to dog video games, fucking...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know which attention whore whose initials start with J and T will be there at the drop of the hat to come talk about video games and bash them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least call him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was too busy chasing an ambulance, you know, so... Apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so, you know, like I said...
[SPEAKER_02]: They trashed her book on Amazon, or all of her books.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently she has a few books, and they all suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Including, Ben there done that, kept the jewelry, and the fixer-upper man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is talking about how all men are fixer-uppers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, she's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta wonder, I mean, don't get me wrong, she is pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_05]: She is pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, she's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's got a fucked up nose, and she's got that pose that looks like it's post-metapause.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, whatever, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, she's a deranged woman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, so... She clearly sounds retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be fair, I don't know if you're going to cover this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'm cutting you off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: She retracted her statement.
[SPEAKER_03]: She retracted... I was just getting there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, the author, Cooper Lawrence, did retract her statement saying that
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, you know, I, she really regrets that, seeing that, and now seeing, seeing the game's, uh, sex scenes, seeing it's kind of a joke, you know, she's seeing more explicit sexual content on Lost than, um, you know, this game, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or other Fox programming, such as 24, Family Guy, which had a whole thing about side boob, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I, it's my side boob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all you see in Mass Effect is a little side boob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, not to be left out, Adam Sessler actually gave his opinion on the whole thing, and I thought he actually phrased it quite well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus one respect from me for him.
[SPEAKER_02]: From one nerdy white guy to another.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually I think he's kind of a tool, but actually, he wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he made his point quite nicely, and
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair and balanced, my big fat ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't even a political thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: This has nothing to do with Republican, Democrat, conservative, liberal.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is just about, that was the most piss-poorly researched thing I'd ever seen in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see the roundtable discussion?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chris, any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I don't know if you'd already heard about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I posted this in my LJ.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, I posted the entire interview.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just like the retardedness of these people just blew my head off.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's like they're like saying, God, I can't remember now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's just like, you know, I don't want my child to have to be subject to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like totally going off on, I don't remember what they said now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was just like.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just can't, I just, no, literally one of them was like, I just can't believe that we as parents have to monitor everything our children play.
Oh, God, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, I'll, I'll, I'll, I have this direct from my LJ, I'll just write, or I'll just read off kind of the part I said.
[SPEAKER_05]: As for the Blom, Bimbo, I know being a parent is hard, and you just magically get pregnant and are forced to care for a baby that you had no responsibility in creating at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there is all sorts of bad stuff coming from places like the interwebs and video games but do us all a favor and attempt to sound a little more mature when you say that simply monitoring what your child sees is a much harder job I know a lot of these adults are playing video games and stuff but you know when those adults are gone they're playing their parents' video games I'm like, why don't you fucking put the parental protection or codes and stuff on there
[SPEAKER_02]: to fix that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, since you're aware that they're going to be playing your games, why don't you, I don't know, solve the problem?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just one of the most journalistically irresponsible things I've ever seen in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they should all be ashamed of themselves for having their names attached to that piece, except for Jeff Keighley, which, you know, obviously was the only one that knew what he was talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only one that knew anything about games, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I laugh when he's like, have you played this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, but I've watched videos on... He knew going in, he knew, well, to his credit...
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, he's a smart guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's a well-respected journalist in the industry and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: He probably knew going into this, he's like, Fox News wants me to talk about video games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: He knew.
[SPEAKER_03]: He knew somebody was going to come on there that didn't know their shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: He had enough
[SPEAKER_03]: Smart's to have the foresight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you could tell that was his first question right out the gate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and then my favorite, they're all, well, they're all, you know, finding the ratings is so hard, you know, you have to look on the back of the box and it's not there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the front of the box and on the back of the box, so you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas on a movie poster, it's a tiny little thing at the very bottom of the poster.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: And the ratings... But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ratings on movies are all on the back of the box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not one rating is on the front of the box unless it's, of course, pimping out that it's an unrated director's cut or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's just disgusting and hypocritical when Fox Television runs all the stuff that's way more pornographic than Mass Effect could ever be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is actually kind of a shame because Mass Effect should have been a little more pornographic.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyhow, it's beside the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: But Fox TV, like, you know, you see way worse things on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God, everybody involved from Fox News with that little piece needs to come on the TV and apologize for being an asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will accept nothing less.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want that blondie to come out and say, I, blondie, apologize to the world for being an asshat.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that, Chris?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to start studying psychology.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what I want to do with my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I just love the psychologist that came on.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was discussing the psychologies of...
[SPEAKER_05]: All the, you know, children see this and they think it's real.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video games and any sort of entertainment, this does not count.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, if your child is going off and killing people because of video games, psychologically, that's not the video game's fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because your child is mentally unstable.
[SPEAKER_05]: And guess whose fucking fault that is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: The parents' fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: It all stems back from the parents.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they were probably going through the first stage of development and they fucked up majorly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I just love it when these people sit there and tell you, it's like, you know, video games and all this stuff, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hurting our children.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be fair, there are mental conditions that could be, but that's usually outside the norm.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of these kids on Maury Povich who are out of control and stuff, that's the parents.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's again, if it is a psychological disorder that requires medication, again, I give that back to, yeah, that's not the parent's fault that their child is like that because there's a chemical imbalance that's going on, but the parent needs to be responsible enough
[SPEAKER_05]: to understand that and take them to the proper doctors and explain to them the proper, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: It all stems back to your responsibility as a parent of what you want your child to see and do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we've got to stop giving Fox News so much attention here on this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I do want to respond to some stuff in chat here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.orangehauntradio.com, some comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ross DLUT says, Sky, you have to understand that Fox News is struggling to get beyond its little niche of right-wing shitheads.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're nothing more than a bottom-run cable networks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their ratings are probably lower than Lifetime and Spike.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Binary667 says, what do you have against Blondie?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's some quality music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously when I say Blondie, I'm not saying Debra Harry has to come apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: She didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Debra Harry has to apologize for anything, have her apologize for the Blondie Reunion album.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, that's besides the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know who I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not talking about Debra Harry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Portal Combat says, Fox News, you are not the father.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly enough, if there was an argument or something like on Springer or Moripovich or something like that, it would actually probably be more intelligent than what's on Fox News right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we got to get back to some happier topics, things that won't make us so damn angry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if we hadn't have done this right out the gate, we'd probably be doing the FUs right about now, but we'll have to save those for later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk about something happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get some happy news here to make us forget this whole Fox debacle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rez HD, that's a nice happy subject, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's even better?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that it is very possible this game is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially a lot of people seem to think so, are convinced.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said it's going to come out this month, and I think this is the last week left.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is that, and then also there was a quote from Q Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quote, the game is being prepped, and it's just waiting for the green light.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe next week?
[SPEAKER_03]: So in other words, basically, Q Entertainment is just saying, we're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's there, waiting to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just waiting for someone at Microsoft to push the button.
[SPEAKER_03]: that will be very happy when Rez HD I'll just, you know, I'll have that on my TV all the time and we'll never have a need to put my TV on Fox News ever again well I was reading, they had an interview with Mizuguchi about how to play it with the other controllers and stuff they said put one on your feet, put one on your back or something like that and I don't know what to do with the third one put it in a happy place put it in the spot that most suits you
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, some people are desperate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, there is a contest going on in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft is having some Halo fans to make videos about Master Chief in everyday situations that do not involve Halo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they win, then they will be accepted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they will get to go to a film school for a month in L.A.,
[SPEAKER_06]: for special lessons.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can use a video camera, you can use the game itself, animation, however you want to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just has to be Master Chief in a situation apart from the Halo universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for European gamers over 18.
[SPEAKER_06]: Submissions are to be in between January 31st and March 21st this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's an idea, kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you win with this idea, you only have to, you know, credit me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Master Chief responding to this Fox News story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, for anyone who's interested in it, it's Halo Recut is what the contest is called.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's at xbox.com slash en-gb slash halorecut, all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I hope somebody we know wins it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So good luck to all of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you win it, send us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll interview you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another first-person shooter game that's pretty fun, Team Fortress 2 is going to be getting some unlockable weapons and new game modes pretty soon, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the first earned weapons, I guess, is going to be for the medic, and it's an overhealer, which apparently I believe is a tool you can use to give a temporary boost to your other player's health up to 150%.
[SPEAKER_02]: and this is also part of the balancing that Valve is doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're also going to be talking about some other unlockable weapons, including a healing ray and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, they were going to be introducing a new map, Gold Rush, and there's going to be another one coming out as well called Badlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a remake, I guess, of an older map called Badlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically in Gold Rush the blue team must escort a mining cart through tunnels and the cart moves faster with the more blue team members nearby but stops completely if a red player gets near.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like how they're mixing it up and supporting the game well after it's come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's always good to see a game get a lot of love and
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't Laugh
[SPEAKER_03]: But so when you actually point at the skeleton, it says Bunny's Skeleton.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like almost like it was built so that at one point it was going to have a multiplayer environment.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like why would it need to say it's my skeleton?
[SPEAKER_03]: Couldn't it just say your skeleton or Conjured's skeleton?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, they could just re-release the game with multiplayer built into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They probably will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like how they do with like Twisted Metal, Black Online or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That might be how they try to hold us over for Elder Scrolls V. That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: www.ihalostats.com
[SPEAKER_02]: think of how awesome I'll be in bed think about it
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's a little disclaimer right there on the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: ihalostats.com is not affiliated with Bungie, LLC, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is something completely fan-made.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to their credit, you know what, even if I think this is a little, I don't know, useless, it's kind of cool in that, you know, hey, somebody had a weird idea and kind of built this whole thing, and it seems to run pretty well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So props to them for seeing their strange idea through to completion, if that makes any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, for more gaming news, for anyone who is a fan of Condemned, Condemned 2 comes out on March 11th, according to Sega, and it's gory and violent and weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which means I'm going to go pre-order down right now, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, the first one was kind of, it was just freaky.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a serial killer type game, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now that I think about it, we did start Condemned, but I don't think that after a little bit of it, I was too much into it afterwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: All you need to know about Condemned 2, and I can sell it to you in one sentence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meat hooks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has exploding babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: That might have done it, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exploding babies?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just looking at this picture of a guy with a meat hook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it a boom?
Why are they exploding?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody exploded them?
[SPEAKER_03]: How old are they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're babies, I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just came from a household where there was just a weak old infant in my arms holding these exploding babies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't judge me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at least it wasn't ticking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my advice, Chris.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't play Condemned 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's plenty of other video games out there for your enjoyment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't you play?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, Chris, I want you to go get a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have it in my backpack.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's nothing but happy babies, rainbows, diaper changing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all the glory of having babies.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the first time I changed a diaper in my life and I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a different type of exploding baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm breaking out the DS right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's not like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Condemned 2, now with exploding babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy, March 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's another game I'm looking forward to, far more than Condemned 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, that would be Grand Theft Auto 4, and the announcement that it was actually coming out this spring instead of the end of this year, or possibly not this year, that's just all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's dated now for April 29th.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it will be coming out of course on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 as well as a special edition which I already have pre-ordered and I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing though, Rockstar was commenting on why it's been delayed and they said of course one of the contributing factors was that they had some technical challenges with the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: and of course they wouldn't go into what the challenges were.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said it's not an issue anymore because both versions are now neck and neck in their development phases.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were just having problems getting the hookers just right in the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically said it's really no surprise to anyone that the PS3 was definitely a contributing factor to the delay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to go back to the last story because this is too good.
[SPEAKER_03]: In our chat room, Ekam, which is just Mike spelled backwards, says, Imagine Exploding Babies coming to a DS near you.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, Exploding Babies are in the trailer for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So watch the trailer for the game and you will see the Exploding Babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chris, don't watch the trailer for Condemned 2, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, this is too cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're actually playing Imagine Babies here in studio?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, get that filth out of my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to play Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: He gave it to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what you should be playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura is a wonderful game on Xbox Live called Every Extend to Extra Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game is pretty awesome, and it's on PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only gripe I have with the Xbox Live one is that the game doesn't get a whole lot of variety in it in the basic modes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have quite the same hypnotic backgrounds that the PSP one had in the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The skins don't change that much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to make up for that lack of variety, to Q Entertainment's credit, they have the custom tracks mode in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think a lot of people forget about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can actually play Every Extent Extra Extreme with your own custom tracks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, well, the problem with the mode this week is that it wasn't perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can either manually put in the BPM or you can tap it out to get the beats per second or beats per minute or what have you.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you couldn't exactly fine-tune it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until now, Q Entertainment has released a code that will allow you to make a fine adjustment to your custom music.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you better write this one down because it's very complicated.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a very complicated code to remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is the code.
[SPEAKER_03]: At the start menu, you're going to use the left and right triggers to put in this code.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get your pencils ready.
[SPEAKER_03]: Left, right, left, right, left, right, left, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think you can handle that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was after left?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can just have a Q Entertainment overload this week if you want to do this fine-tuning mode and then res HD and hell, you can play 99 Nights while you're at it if you want to play a bad Q Entertainment game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Night and Nights wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to stick to the puzzle music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not deviate from the puzzle music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, can you imagine if 99 Nights had some sort of musical beat thing to it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like, you know, Rez?
[SPEAKER_03]: All you had to do, yeah, seriously, to make 99 Nights cooler, all you had to do was be slashing people to techno music.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that would have been the coolest game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who wouldn't want to kill people to bad techno music?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something mixing Dynasty Warriors with Rez.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, I would totally play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exploding babies in time with the music?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of wrong, but you know, if you want to be abstract, then sure, go the space draft route, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could do weasel stomping mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Son of Dad says, Gunpei is god.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of the few Q Entertainment games I haven't played is Gunpei.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gunpei is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've heard it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gerardimo says, Rob, don't forget Meteos Disney Magic.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's worse than 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: I enjoyed the original Meteos actually quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play the Disney one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you play Disney Meteos?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen it been played before, but I thought it was cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm a Disney freak, so look at my online screen named Disney Punk 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about some release dates?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's travel the globe and find out what's coming soon to a retail store near you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll start with Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you need release, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how to answer that.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about on the 30th we get Chess Master Live on Xbox 360 and Rez HD given a date of the 30th in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first is Bomberman Land on Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try saying that three times fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: FlatOutHeadOn on PSP, Kingdom Under Fire, Circle of Doom, Yay, Lineage 2, The Camel on PC, PDC World Championship Darts 2008 on DS, which is really exciting, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Puzzle Quest, Challenge of the Warlords on Wii, Sims 2 Castaway Stories on PC, and Zoo Hospital on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zoo Hospital?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh boy!
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that exciting?
[SPEAKER_03]: Zoo Host-able.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to know how many people have pre-orders on Zoo Hospital.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got mine in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just making sure I don't want to miss out on Zoo Hospital.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I was hoping that Chess Master Live was actually Chess Master Live, you know, like a pornographic version of it or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be kind of cool, but no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, the...
[SPEAKER_02]: US isn't that busy this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty scarce.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's not going to be much that you're going to be interested in unless you love Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_02]: In which case, there's a couple games for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bomberman Land for the Wii and the PSP coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little mini-game with some adventure stuff in there as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's Bomberman, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bomberman Land Touch 2 for the DS is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pursuit Force Extreme Justice on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: and The Sims Cast Away Stories on the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of stories do they have to tell?
[SPEAKER_03]: Help, I'm trapped in a knockoff game of a once popular franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Help, I'm lost on an island.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else to note?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just seeing if there was anything else that's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pet Vet 3D Animal Hospital Down Under.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, say that one more time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have Zoo Hospital coming out in Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it the same game, which is a different name or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or is there really that big of a demand out there in the game marketplace for Zoo Hospital?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, there's a lot of freaking Pet Vet games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually one that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little different than your usual pet the animals and they are better type game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually have one that's done like Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a pet hospital game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it's cute because it's a good game for kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good game for kids, I'm sure, because how many... Objection!
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're fake eating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn, dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's tons of eight and nine-year-olds that want to be veterinarians when they grow up.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want, I can go even more obscure here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pacific Storm Allies, AGEODs, American Civil War, 1861-1865 Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome!
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, I don't want to go into any more details unless there's another tycoon game because, you know, every week there's got to be a tycoon game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, here's the one I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paws and Claws Pet Resort.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not for this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pet Resort?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pet Resort.
[SPEAKER_02]: It used to be Paws and Claws Pet Resort Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll have little hats and sunglasses on and shirts.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like really cute as in like a Scholastic Weekly type cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Highlights for children type queue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go to Japanese release dates because this is one of the fun parts of the show is getting to hear me horribly butcher the pronunciation of Japanese titles coming soon to Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll start with easy ones on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Devil May Cry 4 on January 31st.
[SPEAKER_03]: Need for Speed Pro Street also hitting January 31st as well as Sega Rally Revo also hitting as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, there is a Xbox 360 Plus release
[SPEAKER_03]: Devil May Cry 4
[SPEAKER_03]: as well as Assassin's Creed makes its way to the PlayStation 3 in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to the Nintendo Wii, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a game called Family Ski coming out from Namco Bandai on the 31st.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I believe that uses the Wii Fit balance board if you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming out on the PlayStation 2, another version of Need for Speed Pro Street.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Tales of Destiny, the director's cut, makes its way out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cyanide, with an X, I guess maybe that's Shyanide, is coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that on the PS2?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a pretty cool game, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a shoot-em-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game, Bullet Hill
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming out, Izumo 2 Double Tact comes out from GN Software on the PlayStation 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving to some of the handheld systems on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loopop Cube Loop Salad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not making that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loop Salad?
[SPEAKER_03]: Loop Salad comes out on the DS this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: Loopop Cube Loop Salad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a little penguin on the cover.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weird looking thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hero Michi Oni-san no Ayako Taisu Navi
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, yeah, I don't know, he's very happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like Richard Simmons happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should get a t-shirt with that on the front there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like the Japanese Ronald McDonald.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's 4chan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That picture is waiting to be 4chan'd into something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look this game up if you...
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're listening on the podcast and didn't get a chance to get the link in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lastly, let's go to the Sony PSP where there's a game called Patapon coming out on January 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have that on my PSP right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: You like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it good?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the eyeball one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, but not leastly, Sega Rally Revo also coming out on the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you what, I'll play it during break and then I'll tell you how it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you should tell us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to the gaming news!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, to move even further over to the UK, there was the drama going on regarding the release of Manhunt 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they had said that, yeah, it would be okay, there would be no harm in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the high court has said, nah, it's going to be harmful, so we don't want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: and there's no telling if it will be in any incarnation released.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, just a message to our friends over there in the UK who might be legally involved in all this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just release the damn game because seriously, it's not going to sell anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've all heard from us that the game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop wasting the dollars, you know, getting the court orders.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that good anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just let them sell it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one's going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good when, you know, we didn't know what the game was going to be like.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now that it's been out and we've seen the reviews and we've played it and we've kind of gotten over the, oh, wow, this was violent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, if the British board wants to look at something, I mean, Condemned 2, hello, exploding babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that might necessitate a ban or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, you don't understand, though, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exploding Babies, I mean, that has nothing to do with sexual stuff, so that's also another reason why we... Oh, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exploding Babies, that's not as offensive as ripping off someone's testicles with pliers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's keep moving with the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't really a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ubisoft has confirmed that there's going to be a new Prince of Persia franchise coming in their next fiscal year, which 2008, I guess that starts in March.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big whoop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we already knew this was kind of rumored to be coming out anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I see some, you know, artwork here that they were showing off.
[SPEAKER_02]: No word, though, on when exactly it's going to be out because their fiscal year runs from basically March of this year through April of 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: So somewhere in between there, we're going to get a new Prince of Persia game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And hopefully it looks like this, you know, piece of artwork that they have because it looks like Strider.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to the chat room and looking at some comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to go to chat.orangeloungeradio.com and leave some comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going back to the last story, Ross Steel UT says, No more Manhunt 2, angry face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee says, Come on guys, Manhunt 2 is not a game to get locked up in the government.
[SPEAKER_03]: SonOfDad says, Manhunt 2, no plastic knife attachment for the Wiimote yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a plastic knife, but it's a plastic sword, and then they've got stuff like that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says, I should maybe take a break from game politics.
[SPEAKER_03]: The story they've been running...
[SPEAKER_03]: make me want to stab random people, I guess, in response.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, see, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I see your displaced anger there is part of the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, video games making you want to stab random people.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that's just an expression.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure in Japan, though, they probably have a knife attachment for, you know, the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they have attachments for all the different weapons in Ghost Squad in there, so a knife, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people have a lot of free time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, I'm Tom Brady.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so excited to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, so no news yet on when this will be coming out for sure, but we imagine the delay is not going to be that long.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I imagine there's going to be third-party microphones and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's headsets already for some of the SOCOM games, which I imagine you can probably use those for Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand why they're delaying all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm probably guessing because everything that's Sony-related seems to be delayed one time or another.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's kind of funny because, you know, of course, all the Sony haters came out and said, here we go again, Delay Station 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like all the cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the Delay Station Portable, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really quick, some comments from chat, and then we'll get to the next story Jamie's going to do for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft says in chat, yes, if you sell something with the Skype name, you have to be certified by them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is, you know, part of the point is that, you know, the microphones are chatter juice.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get it, you know, Best Buy, Circuit City, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just some random mic technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: That happens to be a USB mic, but if you're going to sell something with a Skype name on it, like the PSP is going to do, it has to be Skype certified, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Tiger Claw says pretty soon the Skype calls on OLR are going to be done by people using Skype on their PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that's actually going to be a bad thing at all because, hey, if the mics are certified and everything's been tested, you know it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I look forward to that day, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about you guys, but I'll be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you cry?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because... Cry tears of joy or tears of pain?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cry tears of apathy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait to talk on my PSP out in public looking like a complete douche.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, what's up, man?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm totally on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the N-Gage all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have to side talk on it because it has a microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although the microphone that they're going to have plugs into the USB thing on the front.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think on the top of the actual system.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta say this.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's JustinTVChat and there's our chat at OrangeLaunchRadio.
[SPEAKER_03]: MacMan's making smart-ass comments in both.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says in the JustinTVChat, Echo123 is for wussies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Call in with no sure quality test.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell, don't even buy a microphone.
[SPEAKER_03]: You, sir, are part of the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he says in chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com, Yo, I'm on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wanna pick me up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I just
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't want to pick you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I do my story now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's about something that's even more retarded than Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, than that microphone anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone made an eye of judgment table to make up for the fact that the camera is easily bumped into poor lighting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he takes this little table and builds a custom hardwood replica of the mat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently it works just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I was like, people like this game enough to care.
[SPEAKER_02]: has that sold any more copies?
[SPEAKER_02]: oh no, I don't think it has what is the latest update on the Eye of Judgment numbers?
[SPEAKER_02]: still hasn't broke another 100,000 or even 10,000 can we count table sales as part of the million?
[SPEAKER_02]: honestly, if you want to, go right ahead before I mentioned it in that thread because I was egging on people in there I said I'd be surprised if it surpassed 300,000 units
[SPEAKER_02]: But like right now, it's really starting to flatten off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's sold 4,000 units in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: only in the last week or so.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, since now we are going to add table counts.
[SPEAKER_03]: What were we at, 160,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Adding the tables, we're now up to 160,001.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's how many of these tables we'll probably sell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's just this guy that made it.
[SPEAKER_06]: He doesn't say anything about it being retailed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a comment on there that it would be retail ready if they add a cup holder.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he just made this for himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where am I going to put my drink on this table?
[SPEAKER_03]: This guy's pretty hardcore to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to be a pretty hardcore Eye of Judgment fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy's name is Matt and he plays as Havoc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Watch out for Havoc.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm just still boggled.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, because like
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: It used to be the shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's the crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please, before we get into Magic the Gathering talk, please let us see the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, Sony's really trying to catch up with the whole Nintendo fad of releasing consoles in different colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now in Asia, you will be able to pick up a red PS2 system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, what's kind of neat is...
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am inching away from Loki slowly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, they could also use the Saturn argument, because the Japanese Saturn was white, and over here it was... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that was kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't get behind that argument.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're set to come out in Asia February 4th, so if you really need to get your hands on a red PS2... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other console sites out there that will sell colored...
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2 systems in almost any color of the rainbow that you want, so do you really need to wait for this shit to import it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And my god, seriously, it's the color of a console.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't have a PS2 already, it's like, oh damn, I was really hoping for a red one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now my dreams can be realized at the end of the console cycle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal Combat said a clear PS3 would be sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter how many colors of these consoles you're going to release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so the PS2's selling lots and lots and lots of consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS3, not so much, you know, but
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just going to confuse people even more with the white console now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yet another skew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why does it matter what it looks like as long as it's still the same piece of shit inside?
[SPEAKER_02]: This one's white, but guess what it won't do this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Play Blu-ray movies or do something that's important.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has no left.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never been more happy that we got our first day release than I am now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I was looking for the clip on YouTube of the kid from Wonder Shows and going, that's racist, but I couldn't find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you'll just have to imagine it in your head.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was able to find the white people song, but if you... White people having fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I love... Wonder Shows is so fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did they stop doing that show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nelly still sings the white people song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, she likes the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Dance
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Dance.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the one where they show the tour of the hot dog factory.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think this is the Wonder Shows and Podcast, is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not, but I couldn't resist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Patience!
[SPEAKER_03]: Patience!
[SPEAKER_02]: Patience!
[SPEAKER_06]: Patience!
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, insert, you know, train wrecks.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right!
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, I'll get to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll get to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need, like, an off-topic alarm.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need an off-topic alarm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at this picture that someone in the chatroom linked from, um, it was Actdeft that linked it in the chatroom, and it's from, um, Gakuten Saiban, which is, uh, you know, Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's,
[SPEAKER_06]: and two oranges with a banana sticking out of the middle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, DarkSakura, because you're so good at getting this show back on track.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see what's so funny about citrus roots.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's our chatroom that linked it, not me.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means we have pervs in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like pervs.
[SPEAKER_06]: There need to be more of them in the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pervs are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get back into some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I did not derail the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: They derailed it with Wonder Shows and whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look, Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll always save a day, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually the same old shit, but all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that is because, apparently, PlayAsia is taking pre-orders for a brand new Metal Gear Solid collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, it's the Metal Gear Solid Essential Collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll set you back...
[SPEAKER_03]: 34.90 and also $4 shipping and handling.
[SPEAKER_03]: You will get with it Metal Gear Solid, Metal Gear Solid 2 Substance, and Metal Gear Solid 3 Subsistence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you can just wait and get it at any retail store for $29.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you could just, you know, borrow your friend's copy that they're not playing anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does have new artwork.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the only difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course it all looks like the old artwork.
[SPEAKER_06]: because this style never changes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you were waiting all this time to get Metal Gear Solid, now's your chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now's your chance to get it in a couple months.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I really?
[SPEAKER_06]: And are you going to bring up things that have absolutely nothing to do with video games this time?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul Calibur 4!
[SPEAKER_06]: They're bringing back three characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We get Maxie.
[SPEAKER_06]: IceCave
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, YoungSong or whatever his name is, is a pirate.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So is Maxie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like playing with him.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maxie's also a pirate.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what else I have to say about this story, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_01]: Animal Dance, Animal Dance Look, everybody's doing the Animal Dance Animal Dance, Animal Dance Animal Dance That's the wonders of Wondershowsin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't even get the full slew of Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just get two.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Chris threw something at you for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we do another story now?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to apologize.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other news, Rob is random and he's red now.
[SPEAKER_03]: To everybody who's tuning in to Orange Launch Radio for the first time, I'd like to apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did my roommate bring us food?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I have to share it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have two of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want one because I'm full already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ate a whole sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then...
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, hello, we're on the air.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you had seen how off-topic we were, you would not be bored.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about animal dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, pass it over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, please, a video game subject, or nobody's ever going to listen to the show again.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the Final Fantasy XIII designer promises a demo for the game and promises that the game will be out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: which means that we'll have it sometime possibly before January 1st of 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless, of course, they're going to renege on the whole thing and say, you know what, yeah, we ran into some delays.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they can tell us whatever we want.
[SPEAKER_02]: And each copy is going to come in case with gold and free women.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never mind, I don't want it anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about just loose women?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, definitely don't want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free loose women.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be with the Fabula Nova Crystallis Collection, which has the dumbest name of the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we need to go crazier with the name?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's worked for Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's worked for Final Fantasy X. It's worked for Final Fantasy X-2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing is, even if this does come out in 2008, which I highly doubt a creator is promising it or not, it'll come out in 2008 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll take them nine months to translate it for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: What good is this going to do me?
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's okay, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure this is all the news that Sony needs to start playing it in their commercials for the PS3 to get people hyped up to buy their system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, to their credit though, they did remove Haze from there now, and they still have Metal Gear Solid, which doesn't look like it's coming out in the spring anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's move on so we can try and put this whole segment behind us and get out the last few stories here, including speaking of the PlayStation 3, Best Buy is clearing out the 80 gigabytes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, there is an internal memo going around, quote, the 80 gigabyte version of the PlayStation 3 is going close out and won't be replaced at this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will come off the planogram on January 28th.
[SPEAKER_03]: The 60 gigabyte version should already be gone from stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only the 40 gigabyte version of PS3 will be sold in Best Buy stores at this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: This means that there currently isn't a version that is PS2 compatible.
[SPEAKER_03]: At this time, Sony hasn't made any announcements about new products.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think as of this recording right now, they have sold out of the
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're phasing out the 8 gig systems for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, maybe they're going to stop offering Motorstorm for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even Microsoft's to blame for having a ton of different SKUs for their products.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, the PlayStation 3 has been very confusing with what's available.
[SPEAKER_02]: First it's the 60 and the 20.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the 20 goes away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it's the 60 and the 80.
[SPEAKER_06]: They show absolutely no confidence in their product.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the 60 goes away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it's the 80 and the 40.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the 80's going away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it's the 40 and God knows what.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So what game this week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: The game of the week is Akumajou Dracula X Chino Rondo, which is Dracula X Rondo of Blood.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: As a lot of people know, it was recently re-released for the PSP, but I'm not talking about PSP ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, the other clip that I liked had the better music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one loaded first.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: the other one in particular because it was new music that was for that game it was the theme Bloodlines which was the theme of Richter Belmont which is the character that they brought in this who was also in Symphony of the Night which came out in Japan as Nocturne and the Moonlight this is the predecessor to that game because you actually start off Symphony of the Night as Richter at what's supposed to be the end of this game when he fights Dracula so and of course the uh
[SPEAKER_06]: The music I have linked is from the PC Engine Duo disc, which was all Redbook audio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could actually put it in your CD player and listen to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, just the cool thing, because I don't know if anyone ever did this with Symphony of the Night, if you put it in your disc and try to listen to it, you get a warning.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a PlayStation Black disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you listen to the game track, it will block speakers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had the same thing on the Japanese one, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PC Engine one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I thought was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, the game had little animated cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should say poorly animated cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also the intro of it was done in German.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for old listeners of our show, I've actually brought in my TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you can play it on the US TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no country lockout.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is classic Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, if I do remember right, this is Super Castlevania 4, or the last traditional Castlevania games that have come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the rest of them have had that sort of Metroidvania format.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that term, Metroidvania.
[SPEAKER_06]: This particular one, because of how, I guess, relatively rare it was on PC Engine...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really hard to find it for less than $150.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I have an original.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had burdens for a long time because my friend had an original.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got ours because someone owed us $100 and came back from Japan with the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I thought was pretty freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It also had... And now this did have a version of it on the Super Nintendo that was not...
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of people said, oh, it wasn't all that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually enjoyed the Super Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not me, I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not compared to the TurboGrafx, or, you know what I mean, this first version, PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one, the cool thing about it is that as you went through, you had different routes that your story would take.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you rescued Maria, you can play as her.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um, this...
[SPEAKER_06]: As I understand, she was supposed to be playable in Symphony of the Night, as well as two other levels that they never completed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But on the Saturn version, you can play as her.
[SPEAKER_06]: And all of her attacks are there.
[SPEAKER_06]: She threw birds for her attack.
[SPEAKER_06]: And her special weapons were a dragon, a kitten, a turtle shell, and another type of bird that came out, which translated actually to the...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess four major gods in the Saturn version that came out later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, she gets this uber cutesy ending, and it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other funny thing about this is that because it had to run on the Arcade Card 3, if you didn't have an Arcade Card 3 in, it actually had Dracula X Stage X, which was done in really bad sort of rendered-looking bubble figures.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, um, I went through all this, um, that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, a lot of the, uh, enemies in this game were original for this one and showed up in a lot of the later series, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, we had, like, the Pikemen, which were, I think, the most single annoying characters ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're the ones who stay on the ledge and, like, drop a, a pike down on you and they were hard to get past.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, it was, this is, to me, this game right here, to me, is the top, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: To a point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Symphony of the Night exceeded it a little bit, but we wouldn't have Symphony of the Night if it weren't for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you have to respect the elders.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of all of the series, as far as I'm aware, well, these two are...
[SPEAKER_06]: LinkTogether.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one and Symphony of the Night are the only games to carry the actual Dracula X logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love this from Actdeft in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is a podcast?
[SPEAKER_03]: A miserable little pile of hosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: But enough of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have at you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was... What was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's actually... I dropped the mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Several remixes that were in this one from some of the previous games, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the little music clips carried over.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, this one, if you can find an original, good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: But other than that... This is probably... That's a scary little noise that thing makes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'd have to say of all of the... This is probably one of my top five games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Evar.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, there you have it, your classic game of the week for the PC Engine, Dracula X. I also think the bad guy is funny because his name is Shaft.
[SPEAKER_06]: What you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for sticking with us in the craziness.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back in a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.