[SPEAKER_08]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, our last show for January, because it is January the 27th of 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get right back into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you missed Part A, you missed a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: You missed a lot of randomness, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now we're going to get into some Nintendo news, because we had a substantial lack of Nintendo in Part A, so let's kick it off with some Nintendo news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the new things we learned this week about Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brawl is that it will have classic game demos included with it, including demos for The Legend of Zelda, Kid Icarus, Super Metroid, and Super Mario Bros., as well as Star Fox 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why the fuck don't they have demos on the Virtual Console if they're all available on Brawl?
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, if it's that easy to make demos for this stuff, then why isn't it available for the other stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it just me, or is this maybe a workaround?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they realize that tons and tons of Wii owners are going to be buying this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a, you know, AAA title of the highest kind for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's cool that they're doing that kind of stuff, but, I mean, seriously, though, if it's easy to implement, why aren't they doing, like, time demos on some of these, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gives this game even more value than it had already.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, God, we all knew this was going to be a powerhouse game anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the only thing that makes me kind of go like, are there really that many people who haven't played these games?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I just spoiled because I'm older so I kind of grew up with 8-bit Nintendo and stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: But are there a lot of people who have never played The Legend of Zelda?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who have never played original Mario Brothers?
[SPEAKER_05]: There may be some people, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, we grew up in the 80s and stuff, but there's a lot of people that have never played the original games.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, Chris is raising her hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You said during the break, though, you were denied video games when you were a child, so you didn't really have a lot of exposure to this.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, my parents refused to buy me anything that had to do with video games until I was finally in high school, and I got my Pokemon games back.
[SPEAKER_01]: My mom used to play with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, your mom was awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: My parents were retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just the different, well, I mean, obviously, you pretty much have two different extremes right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have, you know, the no video games in this house whatsoever, and then the family that plays together.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you literally have the two things in the spectrum here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, family I use loosely because it was me, my mom, and my brothers, you know, we weren't the typical family unit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, well, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it was just, it really was, my brothers ran outside and played in the neighborhood, and my mom was usually in my room playing my Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I had to, I didn't get to play my Nintendo as much as my mother played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also mentioned that there are other demos that are hidden in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My question is, why aren't there full games, kind of like Animal Crossing had?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because now there's the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_07]: So?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because a virtual console is a money-making machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I shouldn't say free money, but very, very low-cost money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, you know, obviously somebody is having to make those manuals and those kinds of things, you know, and QA the game and make sure it works in the emulator and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that, all things considered, is extremely low-cost.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have a demo for Mother 3 on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that would be kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would kind of hope they would do something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, give us a game that has only been seen in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, just a demo for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll never see the full game over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mother 3 came out in Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's evil.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ross Steel, UT, has a thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says in chat.orangesalmsradio.com, he says, Loki, Nintendo doesn't have many new games, so they have to sell this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mind them selling this stuff, but for some of these obscure games that are on Virtual Console, I'd like to be able to try them out before I spend $5 on them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course there's other people that are piping up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brad from PodCulture says, I've never played a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Actdeft says younger people maybe haven't played the games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And all very good points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, I guess maybe my perspective is spoiled because I really grew up on this shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some people were also primarily PC gamers or had like an Apple IIe or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a friend who never had a Nintendo, but she was the world's biggest Doom player that I knew.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I guess you guys make a good point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can admit when you guys make good points.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I mean, like I said in the beginning, this was never a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just kind of, wow, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess all you guys that never got to play these games will finally get your chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you like it, you can send Nintendo five bucks and get the full version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows, though, if there will be any Sega Master System games included in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not likely, since the only Sega character in the game that we know of is Sonic.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we did get news this week that Sega Master System games will be coming to the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: A whole resurgence of the Sega Master System.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the Sega Master System never really caught on here in America quite in the same way that Nintendo did.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was always kind of the cultish thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you where it caught on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Brazil.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true, and they still, you know, Genesis and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember reporting on the Genesis handheld that's still big in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dan was showing me a video file of Castle of Illusion for Master System, which looks oddly like DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no matter where you live, Sega Master System games, you are going to be able to get very soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually, where Sega popped in my mind, when I was like...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even know how old I was.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my uncle, I had to go stay over at his house.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he's like, oh, and don't worry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, at my house, I've got a lot of cool stuff like Sega and Sonic.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had no idea what the fuck that was.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then he showed it to me, and I just, my mind blew up because I didn't know, like, what to do with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was this little blue thing running in circles trying to get these little dancing ring things.
[SPEAKER_01]: And my perspective on that was, Satan!
[SPEAKER_07]: And here you are on this program now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And here I am years later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Life is funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: That reminded me of that because he was so excited to tell me about that when my mom forbid me to play video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is this, Satan?
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of early speculation that since the Game Gear pretty much ran off the same hardware as the Master System, it's only a matter of time before Game Gear follows on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is actually true.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were the same, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is why a lot of the games that did come out on Game Gear had Master System releases in other countries.
[SPEAKER_00]: And for the record, I have Fantasy Zone on Master System.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, look for those.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't have Fantasy Zone, maybe you ought to check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look for those to come to Japan in February.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure other regions will only be a little ways behind me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like we're talking about the MSX here.
[SPEAKER_07]: MSX is something the American and European audiences really don't know much about because all the games on the console were all in Japanese, so we're probably never going to see that, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the system they gave us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Guardic and Metal Gear, the old school Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the actual good sequel instead of the one we got over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Snake's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyhow, what other virtual console news do we have tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, this one makes me relatively happy is that Super Street Fighter 2 is going to be on the virtual console in the UK over on the PAL systems.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be 800 Wii Points, which is £5.60 or a €7...
[SPEAKER_00]: Ryu, Ken, Gael, Blanca, Zangief, Chun-Li, Honda, Dhalsim, Wu And the new challengers, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cammy, with her butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: She had camo legs, you couldn't see them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that game out here in the U.S., Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it came out last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then there you go, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're that excited, you can go grab it in the U.S., too, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I have the original...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well then, la-di-da.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm waiting for the Xbox One, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, why would I go buy this old one when there's going to be the new HD one?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's going to be sexy.
[SPEAKER_00]: When I moved out here, this is how big of a nerd I was.
[SPEAKER_00]: I shipped out a whole bunch of my stuff, but in my luggage I brought my Super Nintendo and all my games with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the first game that I had on the Super Nintendo that was mine was one that my boyfriend at the time bought me, which was Super Street Fighter II.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I still have the box everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's like my game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to this day that remains a pretty great port.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, it was really good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Street Fighter Alpha 2 had loading in a cartridge and I thought that was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo for the computer but the thing I remember about it on the PC is it had like remixed music and it was also the Redbook audio.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could put it in any CD player.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Random tidbit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, there's some other good news coming from Japan about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've surpassed 5 million units sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the Wii is the number one selling system in the world, but at least the new generation of systems, it is the number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, not in the U.S., but not for long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, right now they have sold, at least as of January 20th, 5,019,337 units.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is not bad, seeing as it's been out for 14 months already.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the US, their sales were 7.38 million as of the end of 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not unsurprising, but nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we all knew we were selling like crazy, no matter where you are, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brawl
[SPEAKER_07]: So some clips are already hitting YouTube, so pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's only a matter of time before we find out all the secrets that the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dojo has yet to reveal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I did look at some of the YouTube clips, and I have to admit, the game looks a lot like Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Melee, which isn't to be surprised, but it definitely feels like it has that next level to it, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: It definitely feels like the game is taken to the next level.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to play that level that's the old school Mario level that scrolls automatically while you're in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing about this game that I think is going to make it winner, and I realize fanboys everywhere are peeing their pants over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's the same reason why WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's variety.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is variety.
[SPEAKER_07]: This game sounds like, it's just like, really, they have thought of everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Variety.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's value.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really feel like you're getting your money's worth, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, you obviously have to withhold judgment until the game actually comes out, but certainly the hype, they're doing a wonderful job.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we'll see, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: We will soon see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, for our friends who are fortunate enough to have a Wii right now, it's been said that Okami Wii will be out in the UK, actually, by the summer.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're getting our version over here on 25th March, but there's not a specific date stated for the UK.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it will be coming out!
[SPEAKER_00]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad to see it's making its way out, finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: and there's you know I just real quick I want to say about Okami real quick I actually kind of missed it in the PS2 because when it came out I was too busy with ooh Xbox you know I was like too busy with all that as I think a lot of the late gen games from the PS2 were kind of like that so I'm kind of looking forward to being able to give this a real shot on the Wii and it looks like it's gonna be a lot of fun so I'm glad to hear it's on its way I'd like to see what they've done for controls on it me too
[SPEAKER_05]: From what I hear, it's not really changed that much from the PS2 version.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, no waggle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're going to have waggle in there, but it's pretty much a straight port.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't expect anything additional to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did hear there's widescreen support, though, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a new, I guess, handheld MP4 player capable of running old-school Nintendo emulators, and it's powered by the sun using solar power.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can also play MP3s, store e-books, and records audio, and of course displays images, all for $123.32.
[SPEAKER_05]: The cool part, though, is it also has a USB port to connect to other portable devices to share the solar energy it has collected, so you can power your other devices with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's kind of funny, though, because the whole thing looks very similar to the original Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those things that you probably only see in Korea or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: If nothing else, though, it makes for a great headline, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Console powered by sun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's... But then how do I play late at night?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the bummer.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was it, that one game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember... I have to go outside to play a game?
[SPEAKER_07]: This makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was that one game that came out on the Game Boy Advance, and I know I can't remember the title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Boktai!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Boktai.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the problem with the original Game Boy Advance is when you play it out in the sun, you can't see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: because it's very... It's not backlit, and it made it hard to see, so... Not a good plan, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was not a big Boktai fan.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one that came out after that, which I can't... Oh, it was kind of like a sequel, but it was on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it, I can't... But, like, they kind of took the sun part out of it, but it was still an element of the game, but you could just hit a button to charge it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was something that Hideo Kojima did.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like a sequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the name.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure someone in chat will...
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero on Tour
[SPEAKER_07]: and of course some news that spilled earlier this week from a French website that Guitar Hero On Tour was on the way to Nintendo DS eventually.
[SPEAKER_07]: So who knows what this game could be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably a spin-off game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would imagine there's not going to be a little guitar controller you actually plug in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I think there will be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because here's how they're going to probably do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have an attachment that plugs into the Game Boy Advance slot and there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can have your additional buttons like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to assume maybe it was a tapping game, kind of like Elite Beat Agents, where you have the guitar on the lower screen or something, and you can tap the beats or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it makes sense, but I think that they're actually going to have it where you can play the guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing I would think about that, though, is if they did have it where you play the guitar like that, there's no real easy way to see the screen and play the guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, no, I take that back, because you can hold it in your hand so that you look at the top screen and use your hand, I guess...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, your left hand could hit all the keys and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could work.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a weird idea, but it could work.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if it does come out, it'll be probably selling quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and regardless, we all know this is just a way to further milk a franchise that, you know, is prime.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not quite dead yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: The hot thing right now, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, I know you play a lot of games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Guitar Hero something you'd want to play on the DS?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd try it out, but otherwise, probably not.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be a nice diversion from Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_07]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_07]: by the way oh I totally forgot to say this during my gaming week but how could I forget like Thursday you know what I did I ran home I powered on the Xbox I put in Guitar Hero 3 and I downloaded me some Journey and it was awesome I just wanted to get that out there we were listening to the demo on that oh it was so hot
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: There were some.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of them is not going to be read because, honestly, it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's worthless.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because, clearly, if said person had been listening to the entirety of the thing, they wouldn't have taken it completely out of context.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, therefore, addressing Lucky Nuts, which just instantly indicates the quality of the person listening to this, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I mean that with
[SPEAKER_00]: None of the respect that you intended as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even see this email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: What was the comment about how I said I would be interested in physics if not for the math?
[SPEAKER_00]: You can be interested in a topic and not actually care to do anything with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fucking moron.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it tongue-in-cheek or what?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, DidYouLoseASock wrote in and sent a link to StarTropic's Wii decoder.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was on YouTube because we are broadcasting on those 22 seconds by linking in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently this is how it's supposed to work in StarTropic, so... Do we have more music?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's the end of that music.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did watch the video earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can kind of describe it for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Inside the manual, you know how when you download games on Virtual Console, you have the manual?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's cool is that they actually included a little hyperlink where it says in the story, you said you got a letter.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when you click on a letter, it actually brings up the original letter, the text, and then there's this little animation of...
[SPEAKER_07]: SilverChaos
[SPEAKER_00]: Last week, as of when I'm writing this, you all were talking about the Dusty PS3 with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry if I spelled it wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you did, but I won't point it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he brought up the fact that it might have been a setup.
[SPEAKER_00]: You were all discussing who might have done it, mentioning Microsoft's and Nintendo's possibilities, but you missed the most obvious answer, and I'm surprised no one in chat mentioned this.
[SPEAKER_00]: The makers of Dusty Cap 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you people thought that dust is this big problem, they would rush out and purchase one to protect their beloved PS3s.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for reading this.
[SPEAKER_00]: In need of a new screen name, Silver Chaos.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like your screen name.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lucky Nuts is clearly not all that lucky.
[SPEAKER_07]: The hate is spewing out of the mailbag this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oof.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drama.
[SPEAKER_00]: They can hate on me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can hate back.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am a PMSing female, goddammit!
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we have a happy email we can read?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Robert M., our good buddy, went to Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm going to read this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I paid to see video games live at Fox Theater in St.
[SPEAKER_00]: Louis and enjoyed the experience.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just a few minor FUs presented as wishes, such as it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: One, wish the mid-balcony seats were high enough to obscure the top part of the video screen behind the lighting structure, had I known that I would have paid more for the lower-level seating.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two, wish I had been in these lower-level seating at least to get better connections with other DS players.
[SPEAKER_00]: My attempts to start four-player Pac-Man vs. matches ended in connection failures.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fun to connect with that many gamers, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: I almost wish the Zelda section had featured more music than the iconic overworld theme.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something more along the lines of their medley of music from the Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And finally, one major F you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, absolutely not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ending the show with one winged angel.
[SPEAKER_00]: Enjoyable experience overall.
[SPEAKER_00]: Part of me wishes it had been longer.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the three hours at Ran plus pre-show and intermission.
[SPEAKER_00]: He also sent another email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, just about...
[SPEAKER_00]: To add one more, because we couldn't get the chat room for some reason.
[SPEAKER_00]: ObviousFE to Square Enix for not allowing use of their video in the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_00]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's because they have something to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't quote me on this, but I think they have something to do with the competing show, Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Play is a derivative of Dear Friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's put on by the same production company.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_07]: And GS68 says he went to Play in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spice Girls Spice Girls Spice Girls Spice Girls
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, he says he went to play in San Jose GS68 and says there were so many people in PictoChat that people were actually using Room B. Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't see that that often.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I remember doing PictoChat at E3 a couple years ago and realized that one of the people I was talking to was Melody.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were in the Nintendogs line.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: um anyway this last one um says hi OLR it's officially a year I've been listening to your show you rock and keep up the good work I listen to OLR on my iPod to keep my sanity while I do homework and then when I run out of recent episodes to listen to I tune into your radio station and listen to the music great job on everything and you have taught me important lessons after the ban I feel like I'm less immature now is DDR dead
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't seem to see much DDR action anymore, and when I used to play DDR, I'd get people to stop and watch me play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now people really don't care if someone's AAA-ing Mac songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, how do I deal with a kid at school who thinks I'm a nerd, yet he devoted all of his time and money to do World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I use the fact he plays World of Warcraft against him?
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you, Chris.
[SPEAKER_00]: She said yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: And was it a mistake using my $100 Dell gift card towards buying a widescreen computer monitor instead of buying an Xbox 360 with it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Too many questions, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is from Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I say this about DDR is dead?
[SPEAKER_07]: We kind of got into this in a previous episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me try to phrase this best I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, DDR is not dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: But DDR has evolved, and it hasn't evolved in the way I think most of us hardcore fans that grew up with DDR wanted it to.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't evolve for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: It evolved to where the money's at, which you can't blame them for doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they want to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when you look at the mixes, Disney Channel...
[SPEAKER_07]: Plugin to your TV, My First DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: DDR is kind of geared towards 12-year-old girls and their slumber parties, which, again, that's where the money's at.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's disappointing because you would think that there's two distinctly different audiences, the 12-year-old girls and the anime convention-going people that helped foster DDR in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: You would think we would get...
[SPEAKER_07]: A new mix that caters to us a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I suppose you could say Supernova 2 is that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But is it really anything new?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I always kind of said they needed to let the people responsible for the Xbox versions of DDR develop the next arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because the last time we ever saw any true innovation out of DDR was all done on the Xbox versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good and bad, but at least it was innovation.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I'm really going to say about DDR.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I finish reading the email?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, yes you may.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm going to give my, well, you know, with inflation, I guess it's $5 worth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I made Chris laugh.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember when we threw you into the fire and pretended that we were going to kill you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought somebody was going to be reading an email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, you can use the fact that that guy plays World of Warcraft against him.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually, if I had an option of getting a monitor or an Xbox 360 right now, I'd get a monitor.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then again, I already have an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, and he signs this, kid who likes Toho music on OLR station MMOs and Crysis.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's a PS on here that is addressed to Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki, if you haven't yet, go on Crymod.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has a bunch of Crysis mods and maps.
[SPEAKER_00]: Download the... I guess Physis?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's P-H-Y-S-I-S 3 map.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has random contractions that showcase the physics engines of Crysis.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll try that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I finally got my second graphics card in and running in SLI.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's tough because I... Overclocking one graphics card is easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Overclocking two graphics cards is not easy because you actually have to flash them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing around with that a little bit, trying to get it stable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Benchmarks now, I got 17,000 something in 3 Mark 06, which is supposedly pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have to try Crysis yet with my cards in SLI.
[SPEAKER_00]: He offers another description for that particular mod.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says you get to play bowling with a barrel with Korean soldiers as pins.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen videos of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Drop weights on a wedge to make a truck go flying and much more.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's the last email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want Harmonix to do a dance game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want them to make a dance game.
[SPEAKER_07]: that would use a similar DDR mat to what we've already bought.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would make me very happy for Harmonix to develop something like that, because honestly, I think Harmonix gets American audiences in a way Konami just never did, or when they did, they were never noticed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I think the Xbox versions of DDR were great, but even then, it didn't ever take DDR to the next, next level.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know, I think Harmonix would just kind of start from scratch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, they would have to.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I think DDR has needed that for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there needs to be a DDR mix that starts from scratch.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, say Konami will sue all you want, but if Konami, or I'm sorry, if Harmonix was able to innovate Guitar Freaks in a way that the game feels completely different, I'm sure the same can be done for a dance game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know if we have any people from Harmonix that listen to this program, but if we do, please be a known.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like you to make a dance game for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I would like, you know, I wouldn't mind if Konami would
[SPEAKER_07]: but if Konami is going to make a new one, they need to start over from scratch.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are starting over.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mean it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Throw out all your old code and start again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can get back to gaming news now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is a weird bit of news, but apparently the Gizmondo is coming back.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, apparently they had a Gizmondo teaser site stating that the legend is reborn and exciting physic worlds and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently it will be back according to, at least in some form, Plex technical director Ian Murphy and says that the product has been recovered from liquidators
[SPEAKER_05]: and PlexTech is bringing it back to the market.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now some folks are asking in chat, wasn't this then retracted a little later?
[SPEAKER_07]: Was this story ended up being retracted?
[SPEAKER_07]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if it's been retracted or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least this article doesn't really say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he basically said that the device's second coming is happening as soon as May 2008.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be honest, if it was retracted, great, because I don't think it was too good to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is not being retracted, and actually, I think this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not realize this franchise was set to make a comeback.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game called Populous.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you guys ever played this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was on Super Nintendo, but it was more of a computer game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's more best remembered as a computer game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's going to have a resurgence on the DS, and Electronic Arts is bringing Populous out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's what's really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing about Populous was that basically the game had, I would call it, different skins.
[SPEAKER_07]: There were many different skins the game had.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you would build these cities that were human cities or Martian cities or it was more like, I shouldn't say human cities, it was like a medieval city or a, you know, new age city or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the DS version of Populous, a new type of skin is going to be added.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a Nintendo civilization.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: The small cities start off as a little game and watch system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then they grow into NESs.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What does that even mean, the retraction was retracted?
[SPEAKER_07]: The first retraction was a mistake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make up your goddamn mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the first retraction was a mistake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is actually coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scary enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: DM ends in chat and trying to make kind of a joke about OLR, is that you can evolve your crappy guys on a show to a Sunday show, like there should be an OLR skin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I think that's kind of a cool idea, not so much what you're suggesting, but a version of Populous where you can make your own skins.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little silly, but fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am definitely looking forward to Populous DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be a good chance to revisit a series I haven't played in a long time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm glad you'll have that opportunity.
[SPEAKER_00]: For people who like games on their iPod, Pole Position is coming out to iPod.
[SPEAKER_00]: So Namco is releasing Pole Position Remix.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's available through iTunes.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you drive with the iPod wheel.
[SPEAKER_00]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope that it comes out okay, but they're actually saying that it's the worst of all iPod games that are available now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_00]: But another reviewer said that it's the best one out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's five bucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you've got five bucks, you know, and don't have to spend it on kitty litter, give it a try.
[SPEAKER_05]: Worse or better?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it makes sense, though, a driving game with the iPod wheel.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it is kind of a logical step, so I would think it would be okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, pole position's a little bit
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, old?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Pole Position is definitely one of those games that was way cooler when you were playing it at Chuck E. Cheese when you were six, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, you go back and play it now, you're like... I had a Pole Position cabinet in my house for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, that's pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we put the MAME in it, and we had actually... Dan found an identical one.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, you had a stand-up cabinet for Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had a stand-up cabinet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember Chuck E. Cheese, they had the sit-in-the-thing Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, those were great!
[SPEAKER_07]: Those were awesome, but, like, it was better when you were six.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember Hard Drivin'?
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hard Drivin' was good because I worked at a Namco arcade when I was out of high school.
[SPEAKER_00]: And one day I was there and we had no customers and I had been up all night and I took a nap in one.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were dark.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a game that was on the PC that was very similar to Hard Drivin' and it was called Stunts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you made your own stunt tracks but the graphics were pretty much the same as Hard Drivin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great though because if you made a bunch of little 45 degree ramps...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was similar to that, but if you made a bunch of 45 degree ramps and just drove on it really fast, your car would get up to like 500 miles an hour and it would fly into the air like a tornado.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you think about it, games like Burnout, you can trace their roots back to hard driving.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember playing Test Drive 3 on the PC with the really crappy graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, screw you, I had Test Drive on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this might as well have been on the Commodore 64 because the graphics were crap, but
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to drive and run over chickens in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, when I was eight, Test Drive had like the best graphics ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this game may not be as good of an idea as, say, you know, Pole Position on the iPod, but there is a fan-made, and I don't even know where this came from, because I think it was a joke at one time, or they had a demo for it a while back,
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's Charles Barkley's Shut Up and Jam Gaten.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a fan-made game made with RPG Maker.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it basically tells an epic story of post-cyberpocalypse Neo-New York in the wake of the great b-ball purge of 2041 that threatens to own the entirety of your existence for some time.
[SPEAKER_05]: and well they actually have a bunch of weird stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cool though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically an RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have like your basketball moves you do and little mini games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is free to download and free is the magic word of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free is a good price for this story.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're interested there's I'm sure you can find it out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are a bunch of different links and stuff hosting it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The website that actually has the info is from a gaming forum.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like a
[SPEAKER_05]: GamingW.net and just check their forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got the full game from Tales of Games Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: Presents Barkley Shut Up and Jam Gaten.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: To put that in perspective, and a lot of sites have been putting it this way, that's half the size of Australia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Australia's population is like 20 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now granted, you have to think about like Australia is like mostly desert in the middle, in the outback.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most of the people kind of live on the coast, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's still a pretty staggering number there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chris, I know you missed that.
[SPEAKER_07]: 10 million subscribers in World of Warcraft announced this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not surprising.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they all live in China.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no, that's no joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, there are 5.5 million of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Over half of those subscribers are in Asia.
[SPEAKER_07]: So not just China, but the Asian region.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2.5 here in North America and 2 million subscribers in Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, some of those people from North America are kind of... Wait, I'm sorry, Chris.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a mic, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you got... Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see... I got a mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see you stole one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I stole it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of those people in America are not that bright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like...
[SPEAKER_01]: I surf the forums.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not active on the forums because I just can't deal with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, World of Warcraft forums, home of some serious lulz.
[SPEAKER_07]: Serious lulz.
[SPEAKER_01]: Best one today, server crash was deliberate hack by horde.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, it was the horde crashed by server.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the funny thing is, this wasn't a joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: This chick, or it could be a guy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: This person actually... Wait, is it a blood elf female?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: This person... It's a level 7, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: This person actually, like, was damn serious, and everyone was, like, going, Oh, lols, broke the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or is it the horde?
[SPEAKER_01]: Insert...
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't never seen it so, like, plainly put, but that is a very good point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, um, let's
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on from the internet lulls to something a little more newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it says for PlayStation 2 release in March, Ratchet & Clank Size Matters will be coming from PSP to the PS2.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also mentioned is... Oh, I'm trying to... I thought there was another game mentioned in this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it not loading?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, given that it's completely crashed my browser before.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Silent Hill Origins is the other game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, Silent Hill Origins.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't particularly mentioned here.
[SPEAKER_05]: But basically, Ratchet & Clank, Size Matters, was officially announced on Sony's site.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, both these games that everybody kind of knew was coming, but nobody wanted to announce, finally they're like, oh yeah, since the entire internet found out, the horde ruined it for everybody, these games are coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Surprise, I'm sure you're shocked.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about you, Jamie, but I'm actually excited about Silent Hill Zero on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Silent Hill wasn't really a game I wanted to play on the PSP, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually thinking of getting a light just so I could hook it up to the TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Silent Hill is a scary game.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little screen is not that scary.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like scary.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like scary too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the kind of scary that fucks with your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if Silent Hill isn't your cup of tea, then maybe some old Sega arcade games are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, the Naomi BIOS has been cracked and now will be... Finally?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, finally.
[SPEAKER_00]: That means Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that means that this brand new emulator, well actually it's an emulator for the Dreamcast, will be able to run wonderful games such as Marvel vs. Capcom 2, Ferrari F-355 Challenge, and Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also known as The Good Stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, so the Naomi games are going to be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: More news as soon as we get some.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I want to go back to World of Warcraft for a minute, but not to talk about some internet lulls.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually want to talk about something kind of a little bit sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has to do with a Virginia Tech student.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is not related to the tragedy that happened last year, but it was just another unfortunate tragedy.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a student there, a 21-year-old senior named Daniel Kim, who actually killed himself in a Target parking lot in Virginia.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, what was the first thing that was blamed in the death?
[SPEAKER_07]: Gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the horde!
[SPEAKER_07]: Individuals...
[SPEAKER_07]: Not okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Individuals were automatically making assumptions about his death.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it makes me angry that people always jump to these conclusions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, you know, you say Virginia Tech, you think about that horrible, horrible tragedy that happened there last year.
[SPEAKER_07]: And who is the very first guy to come out and start blaming video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Lord Voldemort.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you've listened to this show enough, you know who I'm referencing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lord Voldemort comes right out and blames the video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turns out,
[SPEAKER_07]: Guy never played, he didn't own a single video game thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: He just, there were mental problems that went beyond, you know, anything entertainment based.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it just, it pisses me off that people jump to conclusions.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay, he's a lawyer, he can say whatever he wants.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: No repercussions.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there is repercussions because there's angry people like us get on the internet and yell at them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, serious stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Regardless, this kind of stuff makes me very angsty when I hear people jumping to conclusions about the video games made me do it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what better time for us to bring on the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_00]: My FU of the week goes to my fingerprint.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's been catching a lot more lately, and I'm going to have to go to the doctor next week, and it's also starting in my index finger now, so it's looking like I'm going to have to have surgery on my hand.
[SPEAKER_00]: But maybe I'll get disability and not have to go to work.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: The thing is that if I had that much time off of work, I wouldn't know what to do with myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if I couldn't use my hand, I really wouldn't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would be so bored.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I haven't been able to draw anything in like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been really a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever you do, don't let the evil get into your hand, otherwise you're going to have to chop it off with a chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then I can have a shotgun hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the plus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can replace it with a machine gun hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I thought the Wonder Shows and stuff was bad, but you guys are... This is not Boomstick!
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are taking it to a whole new level.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some folks in chat are giving you the finger, but only so you can type.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to another one of my 360s crapping out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Luckily, though, I found out there is another way to fix it, which involves heating up the motherboard with either a heat gun or, in this case, since I don't own a heat gun, a blow dryer until it gets really hot and then hopefully fixes everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about as effective as, I don't know, throwing your console at a wall and hopefully fixing it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm going to give it a shot because, hey, what's the worst that can happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's already broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm knocking on wood.
[SPEAKER_07]: My turn?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU of the week goes to this A&W float, which I saw at the grocery store.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, like, who doesn't like root beer floats, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love root beer floats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: But have you tried this?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's just like cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to try some of this?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's just like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here, try it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try it on there.
It's.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like it.
Here is just.
Ooh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, F you to A&W for this thing that is no substitute for the real thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to you guys for disagreeing with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how hard is it seriously to make Rupir float?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I do... No, they should have.
[SPEAKER_07]: The concept of it all being in one bottle is... You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if this would work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rupir with the vanilla Dippin' Dots dropped in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can say at the store they not only have the A&W float, but they have Sunkissed floats too, but I don't think I'll be trying those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, like orange cream soda is actually really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Saint Delight floats?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Saint Delight would be nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chris, do you have any FUs of the week you want to give out?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, an FU to my dad's girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_01]: The woman's driving me absolutely fucking nuts because she's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, I've been saying on air all night, she's a new mom, and she's hormonal, and I get that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, but keep the baby away from things that are going to kill her!
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, for instance, Baby 101, for those of you who do not have children, I would assume that all of you are intelligent to know that blankets are a potential hazard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, you put the baby in baby blankets, but you keep it so that they're not, you know, in the way of the face.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: She's driving me nuts!
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, just the, like, I get, you're a new mom, I get that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone makes mistakes.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you're making, like, 101 mistakes.
[SPEAKER_01]: You should have learned.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've met your quota.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've met your quota of mistakes, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, no, it's like, you're allowed to make mistakes, but you're not allowed to make mistakes that are this big.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is, like, stuff you should have learned when you learned you were pregnant.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know?
[SPEAKER_01]: Baby wipes, they're supposed to be cold and fucking cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope things get better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry to hear about the discomfort there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, F you to you for leaving us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know I love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't say F you to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you would, but it would be kinky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we just have a couple more gaming stories, and then we're going to open up the Skype line for your phone calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_00]: Choo, choo, choo.
[SPEAKER_00]: I couldn't pass that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a rumor that Space Channel 5 is coming to Wii and other systems.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, we're getting Knights and Samba D'Amico, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a mention saying that there was going to be Space Channel 5.0 that was reported on Japanese news site The Magic Box.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sega denied it on IGN, but it could happen because they've done this before.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was even stated by Mizuguchi that he'd be interested in bringing it as a downloadable game like a Res HD is.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be cool if they made a new game
[SPEAKER_05]: It's from what I heard when they were licensing some of the old Michael Jackson music.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I know that in the second Space Channel 5, the dances were in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: In one of the dance battle ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I got some last minute stories here real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then after that, we'll be taking some calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, of course, who doesn't like a good drinking game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently...
[SPEAKER_05]: Sexy Video Game Land's blog has come up with a few different drinking games, one of which is familiar solid, and it requires a bunch of different concoctions to make up, including, I guess, American beer, bottle of Russian vodka, six-pack of Red Bull, and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, coarse salt, lemon-lime juice, and... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_05]: Real quickly, I'll just go over some of these.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you trigger alert, drink Red Bull.
[SPEAKER_05]: When an enemy shows inappropriate sexual attraction to Snake, you take a vodka shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whenever your commander reminds you via the codec that you're on a stealth slash sneaking mission, that's when you take a beer shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's kind of complicated and they have a big long list of stuff that you do so you probably can get pretty wasted from that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other drinking games that they had available though, one was for Final Fantasy X2 or X2, my mistake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, this one's a lot simpler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically four different things to take a shot to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every time you see YRP, you take a shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every time you see a clumsy-framed Yuna fanservice upskirt, take a shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And whenever you notice or re-notice LeBlanc's impossible simultaneous side and underboob dress setup, take a shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the idea, to get drunk in like five seconds?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And whenever Brother's antics become completely insufferable, take a shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to see the OLR drinking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure they've got one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other stuff real quick, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Skyplane's open, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Use name on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some screenshots showing a car in No More Heroes, and apparently it has a New Jersey plate on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So people are thinking, hey, Santa destroys in New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: One cool thing, if you haven't played it yet, I was playing a little bit during break, Patapon, the demo is available in the US, and one of the cool things about playing the demo is it will unlock an exclusive weapon when you buy the full game.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you buy the full game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, when I said the whole OLR drinking game, SSJ100Matt and Actdeft, like in unison, said, OLR drinking game, every time Loki says anyway, you take a shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love it!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's go to the phones real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll let Loki finish the stories in a little bit, but we want to hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, GS68.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I've been playing Super Metroid lately, and several weeks ago I decided to try Metroid Prime 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: You were playing Metroid Prime 3, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and I found it pretty disorienting, and
[SPEAKER_11]: and at some point I got stuck and I started going around in circles and getting dizzy and that's when I just realized that
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not for first-person games, and I'm not a big fan of 3D games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to take Metroid to a 3D space is tough because you really have to, you know, when you've played 2D games for a long time to then suddenly have to conceptualize things in 3D takes some getting used to.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really does.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think a lot of people don't give some of us enough credit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I partially blame it for why I suck so bad at Halo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm always getting lost just because I'm, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like to think I'm not stupid or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just am not used to gaming in a 3D space for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I just started playing Super Metroid over the summer, and I think it's more with me and first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, on paper, first-person shooter on the Wii sounds really cool, but when I try it, I get dizzy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, maybe you're just...
[SPEAKER_07]: You might have a little bit of the motion sickness, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to make sure you look away once in a while and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, certainly, I know DarkSakura has talked about that she doesn't like to play a whole lot of first-person shooters because she, on a big old TV, can make you feel a little nauseous, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mostly, it's probably, I'm assuming, and Jamie, feel free to correct me if I'm wrong, I'm assuming it's kind of a lot of the same triggers that make people motion sick in cars come into play in video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: because it's like, it's like, you know, like that whole thing where like if you're sitting in the back of a car around a windy road.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there was like this cutscene in Final Fantasy 7 where Cloud says never to read while in a car or truck, which I thought was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's interesting you bring up Final Fantasy VII because remember that was a big shock when it came out because it was like, OMG, it's taking a 2D game and putting it in a 3D space.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was kind of different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy VII still felt pretty 2D to me, just with a 3D twist to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like two and a half dimensions, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the point is, overall, I guess I'm just more into side scores and first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think that's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think people are into whatever they're into, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no particular type of game you have to like.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, GS68, any other final thoughts for our listeners before we keep moving on?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you for your input tonight, and I hope Metroid Prime 3 is a great game once you can kind of get used to the first-person-ness, so I hope the sickness doesn't bog you down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it another go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you'll find this a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll try sometime in the future.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though I'm not a big fan of the first-person games, I freaking love Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about punching the animals.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is RossDLUT.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, RossDLUT, my friend.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: A few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, you're talking about the whole idea of conceptualizing 3D games when you've been used to 2D games just now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think what's helped is
[SPEAKER_02]: You have environments that are more detailed to where you can associate landmarks.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you remember the old 3D games, like in the early PS1,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, all the walls look the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it made Doom damn near impossible for me, because everything, you know, one wall was the same as the other, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you've got a damn good point here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one thing that always kind of frustrated me about the Mega Man Legends games, especially the early ones, is that, you know, everything kind of looked the same, so it was very hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there were only two Mega Man Legends games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but... But yeah, I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't do a 3D game and have everything look the same, because you're just going to get horribly lost, and it doesn't matter...
[SPEAKER_02]: but then again the same thing happens with a lot of 2D games the original Metroid was a pain in the ass because all you had was the
[SPEAKER_02]: The Black Background, and the different colors of the floors, so it took me a little while.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, you bring up a damn good point, because it's not like in the real world I have a problem conceptualizing 3D space.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think many of us do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, maybe there's a condition out there, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But most people don't have a problem conceptualizing 3D space in the real world.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think you're right, a lot of that is landmarks, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: How do we give directions out?
[SPEAKER_07]: We say, okay, go straight down the street, and when you see the McDonald's, turn right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need those recognizable landmarks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you need a McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_07]: For lack of a better term, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: maps, instant maps, one-button maps, a little mini-map in the corner, a way to conceptualize the 3D and 2D very quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one reason I way prefer Kingdom Hearts 2 to Kingdom Hearts 1 is the mini-map.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a huge... Yeah, I hear you.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the games have the mini-maps.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even the really late ones, like Call of Duty 4 has a mini-map when you pause.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there are a lot of aids today.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is that, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said, 3D is a lot easier today than it used to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what else did you want to say, RustyLUT?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we're trying to move through a lot of calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go back to the whole idiots on Mass Effect thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we've been seeing for the better part of a decade and a half idiots attacking video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm going to call them idiots because, you know, ignorant means you don't know better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid means you don't want to learn.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: Drew, your words have not been spoken on this show tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is, I always wonder what sort of impact they really have, aside from the whole soundbite culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when you look at it, in that time when the anti-gaming attacks have been so intense...
[SPEAKER_02]: The industry has just grown and blossomed enormously.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just had this epic year last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: $18 billion for the industry last year?
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to really wonder how important these Jack Thompson, how many people they actually reach out to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think what we lose sight of is that the United States is a country of 300 million people.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's...
[SPEAKER_02]: A ton of cable networks, literally, a ton of cable networks and satellite and everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's so many options out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you're kind of right, Ross.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think one thing we kind of don't consider about this Fox News piece is that they were probably preaching to the choir in a sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a lot of the people that watch Fox News were probably already the crowd that bans their children from playing video games altogether and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it doesn't excuse the ignorance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, nothing excuses the ignorance.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think originally these guys were probably preaching to the choir, but at the same time it doesn't give them the right to lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, and I'm angry about the lie, but at the same time, compared to other times in history, other media's attacks, video games have had a pretty damn light.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I've gone through it pretty damn quickly in comparison.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took the movie industry 40 years to get over the Hays Code, for example.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the comic book industry only recently got out of the shadow of the comic book.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video games have had it very light.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ross Dill, UT, we've got to wrap up but I've got to say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be very interesting to see what happens especially as this Hollywood writer's strike continues where video games are going to become... You watch this happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: The longer this strike goes on, the more of these writers are going to start writing for video games and we're going to have very Hollywood-ish type of video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're already seeing that happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're already seeing video games
[SPEAKER_02]: taking audience from television, which is part of why you see all this anti-gaming stuff on TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're trying to get rid of that market.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I know you're tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was another story about this this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how they say that video game plots are always so thin they never make good movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you're going to start seeing a lot more games.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't make good movies because the directors suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true a lot of the time, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uwe Ball anyone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Silent Hill some of them were passable some of them were even Mortal Kombat was passable passable I liked the first Mortal Kombat I liked the first Resident Evil but then you look into shit those were good movies you look at shit like Blood Rain and you're just like this is why I get better okay one sex scene we're not gonna be alright Rusty or UT I'm so sorry we gotta let you go but have a good one buddy it's always good to hear from you bye bye you do the same bye bye
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft from chat
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, three things on mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one is the DVR is dead thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree with you on the Konami should definitely hire or commission harmonics on the whole renewal of DVR.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're having so much success with Guitar Hero and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, you're from Mexico, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I remember right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's one question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear that Pump It Up has a huge fan base in Mexico.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that true in your neck?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, obviously, Mexico is a very big place, but is that true in your neck of the woods?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Pump It Up is more popular on the center of the country, more on the south side.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the north, DVR has more popularity.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that might just be because a lot of American culture kind of seeps through because the closer you get to the border and everything?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that might be a part of it or just
[SPEAKER_07]: Coincidence.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's most part of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I was thinking, yeah, and somebody brought it up in chat too, ColorSakura said it in chat, and I was thinking of this too, that the World Pump Festival was happening in Mexico City.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, Mexico City is much further south in Mexico than, you know, other places.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I wanted to comment on what you said a week ago about Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: That it's coming to Mexico and it's coming to Mexicali, that's my hometown.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty damn excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: That has got to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to be easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet it's not every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, a lot of big tours and things don't always think to go to Mexico or other countries.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hear a lot from Footy Monster, who's in Argentina, and not a lot of stuff comes to his neck of the woods either.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet that's got to be pretty awesome to see something like this actually kind of recognized.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, hey, let's go to some places a little bit outside the North.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go somewhere besides L.A.
[SPEAKER_07]: and New York, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's pretty exciting because here in my town doesn't happen anything like this huge, like, video game slide, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe for some people, it would be like, oh, video games, oh yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for me, it's a great experience that's going to happen, going to the bullring that's going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hearing all the music I know and recognize from old video games, and also with my friends that also are video game fans,
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, let me ask you just one last question, then we've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think it will succeed in a non-traditional place like Mexicali?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think the show has the potential to do very well there?
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a pretty big community of gamers, and also people who like anime, otakus, and pretty much geeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I... It would be a success, though not as great as in the big city.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another thing I wanted to add before ending the call.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the Fox News thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a little opinion on my part.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be not us attacking them also or ignore them.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should acknowledge their opinions and maybe make a debate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the PAX Expo tried to do last year with Jack Thompson, a debate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very interesting perspective that maybe instead of getting on the offensive, like things that you see on Amazon.com, everybody attacking this lady who said this, maybe the video game community can kind of look at how can we stop this from happening in the future?
[SPEAKER_07]: If this is what people really think, how can we educate them otherwise?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very interesting way of looking at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I appreciate your opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, we're out of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to let you go, but thanks so much for your call.
[SPEAKER_03]: You too.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But if they have an agenda, like, you know, trying to be sensationalists and stuff like that, and really rile up people about video games, they're just gonna do these stories anyway, since, obviously, they don't really care about apologizing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised we don't see more crazy shit on there, like, you know, Grand Theft Auto literally reaches out at the TV and murders your children and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean... The Horde is after your children?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the Horde is after your children.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a satanic cult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cultivated by a video game, it has 10 million followers, and it will destroy the Christian race.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how we can go from that into another call, but we're going to try.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to that, because sometimes I pick up calls and don't acknowledge for a little bit, just to get them on the line.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to that for 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how you held the laughter in, so we couldn't hear you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ramma, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there was a couple things I wanted to discuss, but I'm putting that aside because I'm very pissed off right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one thing to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I please say it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: People, shut the fuck up about DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's
[SPEAKER_09]: Done.
[SPEAKER_09]: God forbid Konami ignores its other franchises to please you drooling fanboys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't say they're really ignoring their franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're still releasing more than two games a year for the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I wouldn't say it's dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, pretty much, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, be thankful you're getting something, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all the people who play DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all their fault because they're not the ones playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's releasing plenty of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just you guys, you all suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma, I agree and I disagree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree to a point that at some point you have to let DDR go.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just have to let it go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's past its prime, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same part, it sucks because without DDR, I would never have met Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have never met Matt.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would have never met you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Chris was talking about a fundraiser going on on DeviantArt to help one of the artists in need.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was talking about that's a really great example of community.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I bet if something like that happened in the DDR world, the DDR community would have done something similar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen, Thomas Howard, he's hungry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every community has done something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some conventions, when they have the auctions for artwork and stuff like that, they will say a portion of this will go to this charitable organization, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've heard all sides of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's not continue to indulge the DDR discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else did you want to say, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I do know a few episodes back it was talking about the Wii and the Wii Remote, and it's something I thought about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me ask all of you guys this, and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: If the Wii came loaded with the Wii Remote and a classic controller, would the console still be considered a gimmick system?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do see how Nintendo wanted to get away from that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played some of the Wii games on launch, and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played Dragon Ball Z, Budokai 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, I need a regular controller in order to play the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: At first, everyone was like, oh, this is so cool, this is so great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, developers are like saying, this ain't a joke, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go on to other things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think a very realistic possibility in the future, Ranma, is that when the Wii start coming out in other colors, and again, this is all speculation, why not throw in a matching classic controller of another color?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii is an established thing now.
[SPEAKER_07]: The waggling and the motions, it's established now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Developers will buy into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's okay to start putting in classic controllers and kind of see what can happen with a good mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll definitely work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, like, you got, like, a game where one person uses a controller to, like, drive a car.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other person can use the remote, the control, like, the little guns or the lasers.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, lots of ideas.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, I think back to that YouTube that came out a little while ago with the whole reverse thing where the guy had the whole conceptualized space thing, but he was, like, wearing the sensor bar on his head.
[SPEAKER_07]: That thing was amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you saw it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure someone in chat has a link to the YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's freaking amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma, really quickly, any last thoughts and we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm tired of 3D games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want more 2D games and 3D environments.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Real quickly, how do you feel about the Bionic Commando remake?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that seems to be exactly the kind of thing you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll buy that for $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks so much for your call, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, like, I had the biggest nerdgasm when I saw that Bionic Commando thing last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I can even say that.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, any other... Any other... Yes, I fangasmed all over myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got another call.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the last one, I promise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Let's Have Tea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, Let's Have Tea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Real quick, because we're trying to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you want to say?
[SPEAKER_12]: I know you didn't really want any more comments on the whole DDR thing, but there are communities out there working together using DDR for charities.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know there's an organization in Indiana that they've been doing annual charities for seven years now, using DDR as a...
[SPEAKER_12]: away to raise money.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this year, they raised just over $2,800 a weekend for a children's hospital.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you happen to have a website link or anything?
[SPEAKER_12]: The community for that is over at NDDDR.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's called the DDR-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's have T. We've got to let you go because I swore we were going to wrap up, but thank you so much for sharing that with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love that nickname too I forgot to compliment him when he was on the line but Let's Have Tea is like one of my favorite nicknames of anybody in chat alright I promised we could wrap up we're gonna do a couple quick last minute stories but I did want to say this real quick because he's talking about charity and I think it's really interesting this has kind of become a fad lately I don't know if that's the right word to use because that has kind of a negative context with it but I've noticed it seems like I've seen a lot of these 48 hour gaming sessions for charity lately like you know I want to say
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody sent me an email, I think it was one of our listeners, that they were going to play through the Banjo-Kazooie games in one weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course we saw the Mario-a-thon, the Sonic-a-thon, the Zelda-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a very interesting trend right now that people are doing these marathons for different charities.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a great example of...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: To kind of go back to some of the stuff we talked about earlier, there is a rumor, I guess now, apparently a tipster who tipped off QJNet about the phasing out of the 20 gig PS3s is also saying that now he has information about the phase out of the 80 gig PS3s for GameStop and EB.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they're also phasing them out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: and he says I went ahead and looked in our back office inventory screen and found that only SKU listed as active for the PS3 console was the 40 gig system the 2060 and 80 SKUs were deleted so that's kind of interesting and of course Sony has come out and said no comment regarding the phased out rumors most likely though if we're hearing that a lot of these retailers are phasing out that something's going to happen so not a big surprise there
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone else apparently found another hack into the Wii to run their own code.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's an exploit using a game save for Zelda Twilight Princess where you can crash it and run a code using a buffer overflow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the Surfer Girl, of course, she's had a lot of rumors that have come true here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of our newest ones include Slalom, I guess, a rare
[SPEAKER_05]: and Dead Rising 2 and Lost Planet 2 not too far behind.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PSP will also be getting a follow-up title coming in the form of another Syphon Filter game.
[SPEAKER_05]: and we'll have the story tied into a PS3 version as well, also set for 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: And finally, there is some stuff coming from EA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they are rumored to be working on another Wing Commander title, an actual Wing Commander title, not some crappy Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, there is also another Xbox Live Arcade game coming from Rare, and that game is Mr. Pants, which I don't know if you've played Mr. Pants, but it's a weird game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mr. Pants.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is a game called Mr. Pants?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember, but it looked weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're way over for time tonight, so we definitely have to wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other last minute stories quickly, though?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to make sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then let's go ahead and wrap it up with our final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: as long as I drink it in moderation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't live off vitamin water, but it's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lastly, but certainly not leastly, thank you so much, Chris, for coming over tonight and lending your moral support and your shining face to our show and a very good bonus segment all thanks to you tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Chris, any final thoughts from you?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Horde is after your server.
[SPEAKER_07]: And please call in once in a while and let us know you're doing okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I plan to.
[SPEAKER_07]: You better.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're still going to be our roving reporter in Wisconsin.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll find something gaming-related up there for you to cover.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I've got something that I want to plug later, but I'll do that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to plug it now?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm losing my memory already.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just wouldn't happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: We wouldn't be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We wouldn't be able to do this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we do it for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do it because we love getting to hang out with y'all on a Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_07]: And even for those guys that can't make it live, we love the feedback and the stuff we get.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are awesome, and thank you so much for your support of us.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like what we do, all we ask, help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell a couple friends about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Post a positive review on iTunes, which, by the way, we got a couple of those this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to really thank those new entries on iTunes this week, some really nice reviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: or wherever you think would be best.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know not everyone uses iTunes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dig, Yahoo, Podcast, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: And until next week when we will be joined with our first ever musical guest, which is going to be all kinds of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you then here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_04]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!