[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_07]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, January the 6th of 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: Feels a little weird to be saying that, 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they just kind of, they briefly went over everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were talking a little bit about some mobile platforms and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, actually, that's what they're talking about a new telephone service right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently, I guess their sync service, you know, the one that you keep seeing the commercials for, is basically going to be ripping off OnStar, including, you know, if you get in an accident, sync will call, you know, 911, you know, and then play them a song or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they'll tell them that you've been in an accident and get...
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming-related stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've announced a whole lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: A couple things they announced, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've sold 17.7 million units worldwide so far to date.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did $3.5 billion in business through November.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, of course, past the 10 million member mark on live.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did announce that their Xbox Live video marketplace is going to have some new additions, including ABC and Disney are going to be bringing their TV shows to live.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you're going to get Lost and Desperate Housewives.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lost, Desperate Housewives, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, they're saying that they're going to be adding MGM movies as well that are going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the UK, they're going to be offering their medium room service, which is like their IPTV and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, though, there's going to be a company, British Telecommunication, I think, BT.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be partnering with them to use the 360 as a set-top box.
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically, you'll be able to watch TV, I guess, through that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they have no...
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox 360 Ultimate or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now they're doing some phone service and they're showing... What was the thing you were talking about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right when we were doing the music break between Part A and B here live, you were mentioning something about a Zune MySpace type thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they have the Zune Social.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be basically a part of their website.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can create your own page.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll have your
[SPEAKER_09]: Zune pick and your Zune tag and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll basically show all your stats, kind of what you're listening to, your top three songs, songs that you've flagged as your favorites, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Customers will be able to go through there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's last FM for your Zune.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sort of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can listen to songs that other people are listening to.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can buy those songs and you can visit their friends and listen to songs and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Talking about being able to hook everything up between the TV, your Windows PC, your mobile PC, your Zoom, etc.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Sakuramax is in our chat right now at chat.orangeonline.com and really doesn't give a shit about anything you're saying, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: What Sakuramax wants to know is how many copies of Eye of Judgment have moved?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we really want the update on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't gotten the new MPD numbers yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're not close to a million yet, are we?
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't even broke 100,000 yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go ahead and go back to the gaming news then.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Loki will keep one eye on the Consumer Electronics Show speech and let us know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just break in.
[SPEAKER_06]: If anything really big is announced, just break in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, let's start things off.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is a little bit surprising.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, Nintendo is no longer shipping the Wavebird to stores right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have kind of phased out that system.
[SPEAKER_09]: No word, though, if, you know, I guess... I really wish that they would just allow the classic controller to play GameCube games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that would make things a lot easier, because it's a pain in the ass to have to have a GameCube controller to play GameCube games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um, right now, apparently there's no other way, you know, to play your classic games on the virtual console if you don't have a GameCube controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess you could buy a wired controller, but, um, or one of those third-party...
[SPEAKER_09]: controllers that's like a WaveBird, like I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: The WaveBird is an amazing piece of hardware, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, everybody knows that it's like a really great game controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it was obviously, you know, it was wireless, kind of before you had the Xbox 360 wireless and PS3, you know, 6-axis or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a great peripheral.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of weird that it's going away now before Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Melee is out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you were hoping to control Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Melee with a WaveBird, you better get your hands on it if you don't already have one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have one, sadly.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the things I was talking about, real quick, just to break in with the CES stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were talking about how, I guess, this new phone service that they're doing, I think it's called Tell Me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will actually allow you to use your phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, say, for example, it has GPS and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: You walk up to a theater, it will show you on the phone what's playing there and that kind of stuff and all the information.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can buy tickets.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the other things that they're showing is you can actually use your phone's camera to point in that building and get directions to how to get to the building, what the building is, and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will know, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Freaky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of freaky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty soon it's going to be the Jetsons, flying cars, video phones, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We already have video phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we kind of do.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have to do teleconferencing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you know, actually, I'll say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't mention this during my gaming week, but I gotta say, this is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I mentioned this last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I couldn't have, because the New Year's thing happened after last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a little New Year's get-together here at the place.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shane is obviously a good friend of mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meek Latavi's been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_06]: He doesn't live here anymore because Konami folded in the Bay Area, so he went back to Kansas.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's back there, and he couldn't come to the party.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we got on the Xbox 360 cam, and I hooked up the cam, and so we could all wave at him through the camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was talking on the phone with him at the same time because he doesn't have a headset or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, it's kind of like a way for him to kind of see everybody without actually being here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought that was really neat, you know, and that's kind of a video phone in that regard.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's sort of what I was thinking because even now a lot of cameras like, you know, that one's got, doesn't that one have a microphone on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, EyeSight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, really all you need is a camera with a microphone and speaker and there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was the equivalent you had with the Xbox camera and being on the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not too far off to being an everyday thing available in the home, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of surprising we're not already there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I remember that was a big thing they always talked about in the 80s and 90s was the video phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more, I think, something that they've put more in a business-oriented type market, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've worked at places that had video teleconferencing, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Tetsuya was asking if we were playing Strip Uno.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perv.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you do bring up a good point because I have joked on this program that Strip Uno is really the only reason to have an Xbox 360 cam right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I found another decent use for it, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the smacketh was laid downeth, and you cannot actually download full DS games coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is not in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is in the future, however, is what Japan already has, the DS demos being downloaded from your Wii to the Nintendo DS, which I think we all saw coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: That functionality is almost already there to an extent.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't download them yet, but if you own a copy of Geometry Wars Galaxies, you can actually beam a copy of Geometry Wars DS version to your DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that functionality is already there in some games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no full DS games at this time, which is fine because that would mean there would have to be a whole other memory unit, which means they would probably unleash a... I'll bet you anything if they do remodel the DS, a new DS remodel is going to come out with some type of onboard memory so they can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, someone decided to be original, as I say this in humongous quote fingers, and bring out a peripheral for the cell phone to play different games on that is called a Z-Mote, put out by the company called Z2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Bluetooth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks just like the Wiimote, only smaller.
[SPEAKER_04]: It fits directly in your palm.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Nintendo Wiimote, isn't the button on the Wiimote referred to as the Z button?
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that the Z button in games?
[SPEAKER_09]: On the Nunchuck, it's the Z button.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you do a little ground pound in Mario Galaxy, that's the Z button you're hitting, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, this isn't going to be a lawsuit at all or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but it's black.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well then that makes all the difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it looks like it's matte.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not shiny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That just means the parts are cheaper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, seriously, what games are you going to play on your cell phone with this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe if you're trying to play Pac-Man, because I can tell you from experience that Super Pac-Man on a cell phone is damn near impossible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing that's damn near impossible is to get a damn game that's not censored in some way.
[SPEAKER_09]: And unfortunately, Metal Slug 3 has been censored in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of spewing streams of blood in the zombie stage,
[SPEAKER_09]: You spew streaming something, some white substance.
[SPEAKER_09]: White substance, that's even worse, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Semen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you shoot streams of semen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways... That's even grosser than blood.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you want to fix it so that there's blood again, all you have to do is just...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Slug 3 Metal Gear 3
[SPEAKER_04]: The zombie stage is like my freaking favorite in the whole game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But nevertheless, the news about a desensitized version of Metal Slug and the fact that things have to be toned down for us here in America because we can't handle the blood, that just incites rage within us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about you guys, but it motivates us to do a little segment here we call the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um, my FUs are multiple fold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, first is, uh, to being sick because I lost two days of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I got sick pay forms, that's okay, but... I just, I turn into a big emo mess whenever I'm really, really sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm just so tired all the time, so I was really just crabby and upset and I hated it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm feeling better today, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to go back to work tomorrow and on top of that I have to go in early but it's a good reason why I'm going in early because I'm going to my school tomorrow to see how close I am to graduating I might actually qualify for yet my ninth change of major since starting my college career ten years ago and also an F you goes to my right hand middle finger because I've started developing the symptoms of trigger finger in that one as well
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that I might have actually injured something instead of it being some sort of naturally causing thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because normally Sugarfinger sets in if you're older or do a lot of heavy pulling with your hands and I don't do either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I push and I type and that's about it and that's not what causes Sugarfinger.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I get to go back and get another shot in my hand which is going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, do you have anything you want to F you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not really mad at much of anything other than the really crappy drivers for the NVIDIA cards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently the latest graphics driver that they have now, for whatever reason, when my system boots up, it keeps flashing black every now and then, and I basically have to switch my resolution down to something lower than switch back up to normal, and it stops.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know why it's doing that, because the older drivers didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other thing that kind of really sucks...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there wasn't really much more announcements, I guess, at CES.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least the Microsoft thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No Xbox 360 Ultimate or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're done.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just basically had Slash come on stage and they played some Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that the way an episode of Scooby-Doo would end?
[SPEAKER_06]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slash just comes out and everybody rocks out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a big party.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to whoever stole our garbage can.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no fucking garbage can now, thanks to the storm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if God stole it, Mother Nature, or one of the neighbors.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are missing a fucking garbage can.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's freaky, because, like, where are we going to put the trash?
[SPEAKER_06]: Call them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm going to do tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a scary notion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still give an FU to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Robert M. would like to point out the irony in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Dark Sakura gave the finger to her finger.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says, Sky, perhaps it was stolen by a bum?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that's the scary thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, maybe it was stolen by a bum, but seriously, why does a bum need a fucking trash can?
[SPEAKER_09]: And seriously, why would he hike this far into this, like, development here to steal a trash can?
[SPEAKER_06]: And why not steal the recycle bin?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's bigger.
[SPEAKER_09]: My guess is it blew away.
[SPEAKER_04]: It blew away in the storm, and someone said, hey, free trash can!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what day, was it the day when he had all the trash cans out the curb?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it wasn't the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We brought them back up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well that's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it is very weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we have no idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the weirdest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you store your trash cans behind the fence.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, we'll be doing that from now on, but still, kind of weird, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: If a bum took it because they wanted to, I don't know, live in it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would you live in a trash can?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did Oscar the Grouch steal my can?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did Oscar the Grouch need a new home?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did he not take the... There's three cans.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a recycle, there's a lawn, and a garbage.
[SPEAKER_06]: The garbage one is the smallest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because he lives in a garbage can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fuck you, Oscar the Grouch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: ACTION GENRAS
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually announced in Game for Windows Magazine, so this is something for PC gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's being created by Chris Taylor, or I guess he's spearheading it or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently it's supposed to be inspired in part by Warcraft 3's modification, Defense of the Ancients.
[SPEAKER_09]: From the screenshots, it looked almost like an RTS version of Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they have like these Titan things that look like, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always like hearing about these games that combine these very interesting types of genres, like RPGs and action.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, almost every game's an action game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it kind of makes me think of Kingdom Hearts as like RPG mixed with action, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm just kind of interested to see what this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, just think more of an RTS game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it basically looked like.
[SPEAKER_09]: RTS game, I guess, where you're,
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, no release date announced yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: All we know is that Demigod is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the almighty soon, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Rockstar is going to be...
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_06]: And what is it, like the original Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they're Grand Theft Auto 3, Vice City, and San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll take it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first Grand Theft Auto game, and the second I believe, are available free on their website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's right, they did that some time ago, I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, if you want to play those, because I remember the original Grand Theft Auto, that game was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing like what it is today.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very, very different.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, anyways, uh, let's see here, Just Cause 2 was announced, released some details about it, uh, they're gonna be, I don't know, getting rid of some of the side quests, I guess, in the game, to kind of simplify it a little bit more, make it more, um, I don't know, straightforward.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now they're saying that they've identified the key areas that they want to improve for Just Cause 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just want to make better use of the huge game world, enhance the stunts, improve the combat, and reward exploration.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I don't understand how you can reward exploration but get rid of some of the side quests.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of counterintuitive.
[SPEAKER_09]: but apparently the game is not going to be set on the island of San Espirito anymore it's going to be a tropical paradise in Southeast Asia but it will still have Rico Rodriguez as the lead character I don't know, I didn't really play Just Cause I played the demo a lot, that was fun
[SPEAKER_09]: And I know that game had a few glitches where you can fly a plane underwater, but, you know, other than that, it looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sold pretty good for a first, you know, a new IP, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it might be one I might pick up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually might pick up the original, because I think it's dirt cheap right about now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it is dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I saw it in a bargain bin the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this isn't coming to a bargain bin anytime soon because the latest and greatest piece of technology for you PC gamers is a brand new video card, NVIDIA's GeForce 9800GX2.
[SPEAKER_06]: A blog called HardOCP has gotten a peek at the new card.
[SPEAKER_06]: This card is coming out in late February, early March-ish, and it's basically going to replace NVIDIA's
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: are nowhere near what Nvidia's are, and because of that, Nvidia doesn't really have any competition, so they keep re-releasing their old cards with slightly better processors and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this, essentially, is just two graphics cards shoved on the one card, is what it basically is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like your Core 2, or the quads that they have, the Intel chips, they're not really a quad-core processor, it's just two Core 2 Duos on one processor.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear that I've got one that's 13 inches?
[SPEAKER_06]: I paid good money for it, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure you did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what I want to know, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it make WoW run better?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, WoW will run on pretty much anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really will, but it's kind of choppy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it make freaking Tabula Rasa run better?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I tried playing a demo of that, and it did not run very well on my computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is strange, because it's not like my computer is that old.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game's a memory hog.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about we do something else, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about we do some emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to get to the mailbag, but something you kids should be thinking about, because it's coming up very soon, not too far after the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to bring back a game we haven't done in a long time tonight on the program, and that is Listless.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're actually going to be looking for a caller in a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not yet, but we're going to be looking for a caller to play with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Listless, and tonight's topic, so you can start thinking about... Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll save that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep that a secret.
[SPEAKER_04]: Save it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you call in right now, Rob will tell us who it is and we'll laugh.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not going to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I am kind of wondering.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should get someone to participate in Listless with us so I can tell them the topics so they can start thinking of their list because we don't want to have to come up with it on the spot.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to participate in Listless tonight and you're available on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about a trivia question to answer by private message?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: A trivia question to answer by private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you gotta do mails.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should probably send it to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, send it to Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, send it to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll work for Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the trivia question?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything I want?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about... I hope you pick something I know the answer to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, if you don't know the answer to, I'll tell you anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't make it too hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want somebody to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's my favorite color?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's DarkSakura's favorite color?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, send me a private message with what you think DarkSakura's favorite color is.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the first person to get it will play listless with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'll tell them the topics they can think of their list.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so send a private message to Skye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, DarkSakura's going to open up the old mailbag and get to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just four.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a fifth one was a thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Rob, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did I do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one comes from...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to say Ryan, who put his full name on here, and I don't read out everybody's full names.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it says, Hey guys, I was wondering if the Operator 11 feeds on OLR can be downloaded to a computer or a PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock on, Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, not right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, as we have... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: As we've stated earlier, Operator 11 is having mental retardation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, technical difficulties, so we're not going to say much more about them, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So moving forward, the next email comes from Martin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Martin?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, OLR Crew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to ask your opinion about a gaming cliché that I think is really, really outdated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I constantly hear many game reviewers and game podcasters talk about how kids are always trying to explain game systems and gaming to parents buying the current-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that it really must be pointed out that these supposed naive parents grew up with gaming in their lives, starting with the Atari 2600 and Nintendo NES,
[SPEAKER_04]: and many kept gaming since they started, myself including.
[SPEAKER_04]: Growing up in the 80s, yes, it was sometimes a challenge to teach a parent about what a gaming system could do and their relevance, but gaming has been well established in almost every living room since the 1980s.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really think that this need to explain to a parent about what a PlayStation or Nintendo Wii is
[SPEAKER_04]: is really outdated and just plain foolish to think.
[SPEAKER_04]: A good portion of all of us oldsters have and continue to game and in some cases know more than their kids about gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't buy into the hype.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only parents that do not know what video games are will never get it because they choose not to know about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Martin and all your friends at bunchofdorks.com Nice name for a website, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have anything to say about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I was monitoring the trivia question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Summarize for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, basically saying that, you know, since there have been video games for as long as many of the people out there have, I guess, grown up and are now parents themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there shouldn't be any excuse for a parent not to be aware of what a system is or what it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I also do think that
[SPEAKER_04]: and I actually do agree that they don't know what it is because they choose not to know about it but I think that it's not really the system so much themselves as the content that they need to be informed about because when we were little you know games didn't look that major you know what I mean we you know true we had Metal Gear and we had Splatterhouse and but they still it was all cartoony looking you know and now it's so realistic that I think that
[SPEAKER_04]: There does need to be a degree of caution on the part of the parents.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in that case, I can see how they might be naive or misinformed or uninformed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't think it's the system so much that people really need a lot of education on.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, we finally got a winner of our stupid trivia thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could not guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my God, it took forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I've made any
[SPEAKER_04]: Secret about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, next email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, which person sent in that last email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was... I closed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Martin from a bunch of dorks dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I read this email earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear I was paying attention to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyhow, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's funny about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was reading this, I kind of thought to myself, I was like, okay, as far as the Atari 2600 generation goes,
[SPEAKER_06]: Not everybody had that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of us were lucky enough to experience that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even, I think, Atari 2600, not everybody in our generation necessarily experienced.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was still kind of something that only certain kids on the block had.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in some parts of the country, you weren't as able to find these as easily.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was still kind of a luxury item.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: As video games are in general today.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even when I say luxury item, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: places in your generation where you were able to have this luxury item, where I think a lot of parents, or people that are now parents, weren't exposed to this when they were young.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nevertheless, even if they were, they remember video games as being Pac-Man, Combat, and not Grand Theft Auto or Manhunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was much different back then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that the case with a lot of them is that
[SPEAKER_04]: Not everyone has been, you know, the hardcore gamer type that, you know, like me and my husband and our person who emailed us or any of us in this room that, you know, once we, you know, grew up and started working, you know, oh, well, that's child stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We put it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we are more enlightened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's as, you know, fine as a recreation item as any.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's always been, I think, when they were growing up with that type of thing, oh, well, you're still doing that?
[SPEAKER_04]: My mom still says that to me, and I'm like, okay, you sat and played my Nintendo as much as I did when I had it, so what's your excuse?
[SPEAKER_04]: And now she wants a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mom wants a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at any rate, that's where I think the difference comes in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that it's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those who don't know, it's because they choose not to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't educated themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're all surprised, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they don't have a right to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can move on now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry I was not paying attention fully the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this makes me feel slightly better.
[SPEAKER_04]: J-Rod emailed.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one who has a really cool quote about Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, DarkSakura, I know this isn't exactly a gaming question, but you said you get a sinus infection every single year for New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm in the same boat as you, except whenever I have something like a concert to go to, I'll get a sinus infection without question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone could ask me to go see a concert tomorrow and I'll develop a sinus infection overnight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woe is us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, for me, I always get...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, the Olive Garden is the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget never-ending breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should just go for salad one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to, you know, because you want to come over for movie night because I have to show you Stardust because I love that movie so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's do Olive Garden that night.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I'm not completely broke.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do dinner at the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeehaw!
[SPEAKER_04]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can't pay, it'll be my treat because I want never-ending breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll get you after my payday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go to Indian again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the whole time I was sick, all I wanted was Indian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, Ross Steele?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dammit, I need to have it out with him for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Ross Steele, goddammit, you criticize Loki and his, you know, ways, which I, you know, to some extent I agree with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You criticize me playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I do play too much WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I draw the line at you criticizing our love of the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Olive Garden is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Olive Garden is wonderful, and damn you for thinking otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, although, although, one of these days I'm going to have to take you to Pasquale's.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're closed on Monday, but they're open on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope you get smited with Zuppa Toscana.
[SPEAKER_04]: He should get sangria'd in the eye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: May a deep fried ravioli fall from heaven onto your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds good too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, this email is titled Yaris made better by Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey OLR, I made this video on YouTube and got the inspiration from you guys and girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you should actually start that segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are a lot of crappy games out there and someone needs to make them watchable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I think you guys are great and I will keep saying that because you are and keep going strong.
[SPEAKER_04]: To get the video, search for PKJR92 and I'm saying it out loud so that they know what to look up on YouTube or Yaris or Dragon Force or even OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sincerely, PKJR92.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Change is inevitable except from a vending machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: is the quote on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard that quote before.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the way, I did watch the video, and basically he took the trailer for Yaris, the 30-second trailer for Yaris, and put Dragon Force's music behind it, and it's surprisingly effective.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do approve.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I will find the link to that YouTube and post it in chat for you all to look at right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not right right now, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got one last email in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can hear Loki watching it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't it make the game better?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got one last email in.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be a lot better with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Sakura Maxx.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, OLR, just mailing to say Happy New Year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was running a little late since I didn't have computer access while the New Year special was running.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is from Sakuramax, the one who hasn't annoyed you people in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: You happy?
[SPEAKER_04]: And a person with MassGamerADD, what to play next.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there we have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No more emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops, sorry, I haven't watched the video.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was just going to add a little thing that says I approve.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, see, now everybody in the chat room is like, you need to go have real Italian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have had real Italian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually went to a little place in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know if you guys have heard of this, but I always thought I got a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Español, which means Spain, but it has really good Italian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's real Italian places all over.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet there are really, really good places in New York, though, and that's where they're offering to take me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm not going to say no, especially if you're buying.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send emails, maybe profess your love for the Olive Garden here on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if we're not the weather podcast, we're the food podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything but games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That should be our new tagline.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're tired of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've been doing games for like six years.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time for something new, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a couple more stories for you guys, and then we're going to get into tonight's listless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I'll let you go first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, if you've been playing Team Fortress 2, you may have been noticing that there are some achievements missing for one of the classes you can play, and that would be the Medic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's going to be fixed, hopefully pretty soon, because a German site was listing some brand new achievements, 36 new ones, actually, for the Medic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the other ones here, they had Heal Under Fire, which is healing somebody while on fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here, they have one for healing an engineer, healing teammates who've called for a medic, Ubering a friend, and they have some other fun stuff like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Bone Saw Spy Caller, or I'm assuming that's Killer, killing an enemy spy with a bone saw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I'm going to interrupt this story to show you the fly swimming for his life in my coffee right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That fly is going to be totally hyped up on caffeine.
[SPEAKER_06]: The more he swims, the more hyper he gets.
[SPEAKER_06]: But goddammit, that just ruined a perfectly good cup of coffee.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go flies!
[SPEAKER_06]: Asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Asshole fly.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, hopefully we'll see some of those soon, maybe in an update or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even the chatroom is like, Rob's derailing the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do want to say this, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: The native Spanish speakers in chatroom are yelling at me and screaming at me, and I should know better, but I only had two years of high school Spanish.
[SPEAKER_06]: España is Spain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Español is a Spaniard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Spanish.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know any Spanish.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I knew that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Donde Esta El Bano.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody on Ragnarok last night was spamming with Donde Esta La Biblioteca.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew, they're telling me to drink the coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fucking gross.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is wrong with you people?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just say that you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have a camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm, I'm drinking it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's so gross!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, why are you doing that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel that fly in my throat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, he's turning into a fly now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's so crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is how we're starting off 2008, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear everybody, Rob is crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The end.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can get away with much more when Op 11 isn't running.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we'll never have a webcam again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get away with a lot of stuff over here because the camera's never on me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, one week I'm going to just surprise you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it'll be Jamie Cam.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll put that camera up there and put another camera hidden somewhere that's actually the real camera.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's elaborate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Candid camera.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll make that the day I throw up on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, a lot of folks have been saying this week with all the Xbox Live downtime, I'm just going to go play PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony's network is free.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to go play that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Sony has been polling customers in some of their Asian regions on ways that they can improve the PC and PSP PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the things that they're polling about?
[SPEAKER_06]: A monthly subscription plan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, possibly is Sony looking into charging a monthly fee for the PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_06]: But, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Loki, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're wanting to jump at the bit here to say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're possibly going to be offering a monthly subscription for unlimited download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game tap for your PSP, basically, but with Sony's games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: That actually isn't a bad idea at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would hand it to Sony if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, the trump on that, I guess, is that there isn't really a whole lot of download content on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be a definite way, though, to ensure income from the service on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd pay for that for a month, download everything, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just wait a few months.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if it's contractual?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think services like that are usually contractual, are they?
[SPEAKER_01]: Some are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, like GameTap is, and it's month to month.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well anyhow, I think it's about time for us to have a list list.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it list list time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, list list is the game where we're going to create the definitive list for something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, lists are big, especially around this time of year as one year has ended and another begins.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lists are big, so we're going to make our own list tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we have a lot of new listeners since the last time we've done this because we used to do this game a lot and we probably haven't played it in like four months.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the way listless works is that we're going to have four panelists, myself, Loki, DarkSakura, and our mystery caller.
[SPEAKER_06]: And each of us are going to give you our top three things that will match the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then here's the twist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Each one of us takes one thing off the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have 12 that gets taken down to eight.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so once we're down to eight, then the chat room votes on the top three things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that will bring us the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_06]: And tonight's topic for the list, if you'd like to start posting your suggestions in chat, here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gadget I'd like to see them announce at Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't have to be gaming related, just any type of tech gadget.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the gadget you would like to see them announce at the Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can be real, it can be crazy, anything you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's it right here, tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let us call the person who correctly guessed...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's favorite color.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I can find them in the list, I suddenly can't find them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm making them call us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little bit about your favorite color.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite color is very, very dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's favorite color was black.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't check out the keynotes or anything, but I like to watch what they got showing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about what I said earlier in the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it true that most game nerds are somewhat of tech nerds too?
[SPEAKER_06]: They like to see the latest tech stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you kind of have to be, to tell you the truth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially with the whole next gen that's going on now.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: My number three pick is the Rez Trans Vibrator 2.0.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why a Rez Trans Vibrator 2.0?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, it would come out just in time for Rez HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rez HD is just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who wants to go next?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can go.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what is your number three pick?
[SPEAKER_04]: My number three pick is a remote-directed EMP gun for jamming other people's cell phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why, pray tell, do you need an EMP gun to jam people's cell phones?
[SPEAKER_04]: For people driving like fucking retards on the road while talking with their phone glued to their face, or people in front of me in line at the grocery store too busy talking on their phone to pay attention to what the hell they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those people need to either die in a fire or hang up the phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Preferably.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's actually a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I'll go next.
[SPEAKER_06]: My number three pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I don't know if you've ever seen these.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever seen those guns at, like, Target or things that shoot the big blast of air at people?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the air cannons.
[SPEAKER_06]: Air zookas.
[SPEAKER_01]: Air zookas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, air zookas are so awesome, but I want them to introduce, like, an air zooka that will actually blow somebody over because it has so much power in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to just call it the supreme air zooka.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how electronic that gadget is, but I would imagine you'd need a little battery power to make that thing work.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Loki, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number three pick would be kind of a sequel to the AIBO.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the AIPER, and it would be a robotic cat.
[SPEAKER_01]: They already have those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I want one from Sony because I need my cat to be able to spy on my other cat so I can see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony does have an AIBO cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a gray one and a white one and a black one.
[SPEAKER_06]: He can put anything he wants on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: You take it off if you don't like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I sloth?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ferret.
[SPEAKER_09]: I ferret.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, I ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I go with I ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to change it to I ferret.
[SPEAKER_09]: I ferret.
[SPEAKER_09]: So AI ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're back to you, SSJ100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Matt, what is your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_03]: My number two pick is...
[SPEAKER_03]: An Apple handheld gaming system.
[SPEAKER_06]: As is the device of many fanboys' dreams.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you an Apple fanboy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, why then, especially from non-fanboys, should Apple announce a handheld gaming system?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there should be another handheld gaming system in general that's not the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_06]: As RawSteelUT says, the Pippin Boy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what it would be?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, DarkSakura, what's your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_04]: A streaming TV for iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the YouTube channel, but like actual episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was gonna say, YouTube's not good enough for you, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because you can't really find full episodes of stuff on YouTube, and it's like a limited YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they need to have like a show service.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like for me, because I don't like to sit in front of the TV because that's just boring to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I have to have other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So having it on my iPhone...
[SPEAKER_04]: and I could, you know, watch for a little bit and then go do other crap and then come back and finish watching it when I'm done would be perfect for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I'm actually going to take my number two pick from the chat room because this is a darn good pick and we can be as silly as we want, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to suggest that a portal gun be unveiled as CES so I can have my very own portal gun because seriously, who couldn't use a portal gun?
[SPEAKER_04]: I could use one all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so portal gun, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what would be the number two pick for you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, my number two pick also happens to come from Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like the Aperture Science Sentry Bot.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the ones that say, hello, and then turn the chute at you.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're perfect for the neighbors.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, those things are such assholes, but okay, yeah, those would be good guard dogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised no one said a companion queue, but I guess we haven't gotten to the number ones yet, so let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt, what is the number one thing you would like to see them debut at CES?
[SPEAKER_06]: New Gadget.
[SPEAKER_03]: My number one pick is the Dreamcast 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sega fanboy, eh?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, I just want to see another Sega system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not really a fanboy, I just think, you know... Don't you think, though, it's about time to let go?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, DarkSakura, what would be your number one thing you would like to see them announce at CES?
[SPEAKER_04]: Portable Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portable Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a bad choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: What made you decide to go with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
[SPEAKER_04]: We were playing that the other night too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because seriously, holodecks are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Loki, what would be your number one pick?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gadget, you'd like to see them unveil at CES.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number one pick has already been said, which was a portal gun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right, because I didn't really have anything that I thought of.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it's not practical in any sense whatsoever, but we haven't seen anything come from George Foreman in a while, so I want a George Foreman grill that I can cook an entire cow on.
[SPEAKER_09]: at one time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it needs to clean the cow's guts out for you and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Self-cleaning.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, pray tell, would the George Foreman entire cow grill be called?
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be George Foreman's self-cleaning cow grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to be very hard because this is a very good list of items that we've built tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Lab says the mean lean fat reducing cow machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would certainly reduce the size of those cows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: We said anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very few of these items are actually gaming related, I'd like to point out, but it fits the theme of our podcast tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, SJ100 Matt, I posted the list there in private message for your reference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me go ahead and read it as it stands now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to kill the music because this is the serious round because we have 12 items on the list but four of these things are not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Rez Trans Vibrator 2.0, Remote EMP Gun for jamming people's cell phones, Supreme Air Zooka, iFerret, Apple Handheld Gaming System, Streaming TV for iPhone, Portal Gun, Aperture Science Sentry Bot, Dreamcast 2, Portable Xbox Live Arcade, Holodeck, and George Foreman Self-Cleaning Cow Grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: But four of these things are not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: SJ100, Matt, what is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go with the Airzooka.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a bastard, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's not that electronic, is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Supreme Airzooka is not worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but it isn't really an electronic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I guess you would need electronics in order to build an Agraver person.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how awesome would that be?
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, DarkSakura, which of these things is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to say the Apple handheld gaming system.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was expecting Loki to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because I think that Microsoft would do it better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's also the iPhone, which in a way they'll probably turn into a gaming system.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know there's going to be stuff coming out on that eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love my iPhone, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that when we have a company that's already established for having quality games out now, I think that's only inevitable.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I've got to get rid of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so sorry, SSJ100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Matt, we're picking on you tonight, but Dreamcast 2 is not worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not going to happen, kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: None of the things I listed were never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: A holodeck has a better chance of happening at a future consumer electronics show or Loki's fucking cow grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: S.S.J.
[SPEAKER_06]: 100's list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your Airsuka got taken off?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I know, but the other three, we eliminated SSJ's entire list.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the way the cookie crumbles.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100, Matt, I'm very sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently your choices just weren't worthy tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to cry about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm going to go cut myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm sorry that things didn't go your way tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, because you don't have any items on the list, we'll still let you vote for the winner.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anything you want to plug before we hang up on you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I like it when they don't have anything to plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He got his whole list eliminated by us three bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't happen, it hasn't happened very often.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can only think of one other time in ListList where somebody's entire list got eliminated.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were mad that I took off the ResTrans by Rear 2.0.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you improve something that vibrates?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that complicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poor power.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are left with eight choices that have been deemed worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: The remote EMP gun for jamming people's cell phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: An iFerret.
[SPEAKER_06]: A streaming TV for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: A portal gun.
[SPEAKER_06]: An Aperture Science Sentry Bot.
[SPEAKER_06]: A portable Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: A holodeck.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a George Foreman self-cleaning cow grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please send in your votes via private message for your number one and number two picks.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't label them one and two, I will assume that the first one is your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have about ten minutes while we go over these next few stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: So place your votes now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, we get back into the gaming news with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have our dear friend who is the...
[SPEAKER_04]: God of third party peripherals, Mad Catz, making instruments for Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a multi-year licensing agreement with MTV Games to do wired and wireless bass guitars and a percussion set that's got drumsticks and a microphone and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it looks like we're going to be seeing those come out eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the first half of 2008.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, one place you probably won't be able to get a good deal on those would be at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently they had a coupon that was in, I guess, one of the local papers.
[SPEAKER_09]: For 20% off of three toys, you basically buy one toy, save 10%, buy two, save 15%, buy three, save 25%.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, um, oddly enough, um, you know, games are listed as, you know, under the toy section on the website.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, if you went into, um, a Best Buy and tried to use that coupon, um, they would not let you because they said that games are not a toy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says, um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, um, a employee at Best Buy, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: So the games and game systems do not apply to that coupon because they're not toys.
[SPEAKER_09]: A toy would be like a doll.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, Best Buy ripping people off yet again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is video games a toy or not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's
[SPEAKER_09]: If they're listed under their website as a toy, then yes, I think it would apply as a toy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you've got to be more clear on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're just saying toy does not apply to video games, that's what they should have had the fine print on the coupon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they should honor it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's their own fault.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the fact that they're saying, oh, I'm sorry, that's not a toy, well...
[SPEAKER_09]: Bait and Switch Gotta love it
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well we're going to give just a couple more minutes for listless votes, so get those votes in now, we will announce the winners shortly, and we're going to be taking your Skype calls on our Skype line, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio, and pretty soon you'll be able to call in from your PSP apparently, but I'm going to ask first, while we wait for any last minute votes, if there's any last minute stories that any of the hosts would like to cover tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony, of course, introduced the 16 gigabyte memory stick duo for, you know, obviously cameras and PSP and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a whole lot of movies on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or a whole lot of games, depending on how you look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been pretty dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: H.D.V.D.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what can you do?
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, it's the ramifications.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you think about it, Warner Brothers also owns New Line, which is a huge studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did Lord of the Rings, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just a huge blow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're saying that this could single-handedly turn things in Blu-ray's favor.
[SPEAKER_06]: But something to keep in mind, Paramount is still HD DVD exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I believe there's one other studio that's still... Universal?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, HD DVD exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it isn't necessarily over yet, but that is a very big blow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even I'll admit that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that means, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Batman movies and stuff are going to be Blu-ray exclusive, which kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also the thing Kmart did too, saying they weren't going to carry Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just one more last minute story, and this is kind of stupid, but apparently some guy shot his son over an Xbox 360 argument.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently a 17-year-old in Pennsylvania
[SPEAKER_09]: Talk about asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the kid doing with a rifle?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one of many questions I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: This means we need to fire up something for 2008 here.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the inaugural stupid award of 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard these arguments before where somebody is yelling at somebody else and goes, I'm sure it's just like, why don't you just shoot me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't you just kill me?
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't mean you actually shoot them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever heard of, like, a metaphor?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, so stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's this guy's name?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, they didn't have his name.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Unknown... Wait, I saw it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I gotta look at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I saw this somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to go to the original site that ran it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I want to say this happened not that far from where I've been in Pennsylvania before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, where the hell was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, person in the... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: 60-year-old James Stanley Nidasik shot his 17-year-old son.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, congratulations, James Stanley.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't pronounce your last name.
[SPEAKER_06]: You win the first Stupid Award of 2008, courtesy of Orange Lounge Radio, for shooting your son in an argument.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a release date for the Xbox 360 and Wii versions of Bully out in the U.K.,
[SPEAKER_04]: March 7th.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're getting that here too, I believe, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's around March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet-ish.
[SPEAKER_04]: This should be the scholarship edition over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to be very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, shall we get to tonight's listless winners?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was neck and neck tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only one vote separated number one and two.
[SPEAKER_06]: But everything got a vote tonight, which doesn't happen very often in Listless, but somebody in chat wanted a little bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the end, there could be only three.
[SPEAKER_06]: So here it is, your top three gadgets you would like to see them unveil at CES.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_06]: No arguing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a very scientific method we use here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: The number three thing you'd like to see them debut at CES is the holodeck.
[SPEAKER_06]: The number two thing you would like to see them debut at CES is a portal gun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meaning the number one thing you would like to see at CES either this year or 2009, the George Foreman self-cleaning cow grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It bakes the whole fucking cow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not bad for a last minute pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now your only trouble is where do you get a cow?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the only downside.
[SPEAKER_09]: You tip it over and then put it in a bag?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You tip it over into the grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go ahead and open up the Skype line of calls then.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to go ahead and give us a call, we'll take your calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll take a few of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross Deal UT says, Loki, you can get a cow carcass at Publix Easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here in Florida.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know what that is, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know what that is?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea what that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to give this to me now while we're trying to take calls on Skype?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I had to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, this is Ross Deal UT.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, Ross Deal UT.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Friend, buddy, pal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey there.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm nothing much.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, Publix is a supermarket chain over here in the southeast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very big supermarket chain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I've seen people, I used to work at a Publix once, and yeah, I used to see people getting the cow carcasses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's what they do for Thanksgiving instead of the turkey, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You put it in your shopping cart.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's something I'd like to see them doing on Supermarket Sweep, putting five of those cow carcasses right in the car.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you'd need more than one cart, man, those things are fucking huge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's how they did it on the show, they'd fill up one cart and throw it to their partner and they'd get another cart, alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, would Supermarket Sweep not be the best video game ever?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would Supermarket Sweep not be one of the best video games ever?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, that's the kind of shit they need to be doing for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be a good Xbox Live arcade game, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope Microsoft's listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you guys are listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what else is on your mind, Rusty?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: In reaction, a couple of things, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: In reaction to the whole Warner Brothers New Line thing, the CES
[SPEAKER_08]: HD DVD press conference got cancelled I heard, it's like they've got their tail between their legs going Well, it's pretty big when you think about it There's only like three exclusive HD DVD studios left And Paramount, like I said in the chat, they're only exclusive because Microsoft paid them a boatload of money
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen pornographic Blu-rays on offer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could have sworn on this program last year we had a story about that the porn industry had gone with HD DVD for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember the reason, but they went with HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did they go back on that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I always said whoever gets porn wins the war.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now that porn is going to Blu-ray, I'm like, it's over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the problem with porn really is that it's not like back in DVD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now you see porn really moving into the downloadable space.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox Live Marketplace is going to suddenly offer porn, although they ought to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could say the same thing about Walmart.
[SPEAKER_08]: They carry those movies and they don't carry porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Microsoft has an image to protect, but what I was about to say is that you can't go five steps in either direction online without dipping into a pay site.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where I see a lot of the pornographic market going, is online.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't have to worry about people picketing in front of porn shops or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the problem is they already did that with the Wii, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: They already did... Yeah, you remember that, like, a few months back.
[SPEAKER_06]: My child went to X-Tube on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, anything with any sort of internet capability is gonna have pornography.
[SPEAKER_08]: My concern is if it ever went to Xbox Live Arcade, you'd have a bunch of people, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch some porn and go play Halo or Uno with their cameras and you'll see them all.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can put porn, stream it off of your 80 gig hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet anything you're only going to get to put pre-selected video clips that just happen to be clips from Sony's latest movies and TV shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's going to be stuff that's off your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be anything, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything on your hard drive, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's Porn Palace, only available at home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to have a virtual porn house at home?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, what I want to know is, you know, are they going to be...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'm going to let you throw cocks at people in home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are they going to throw cocks at people?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Second Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, did you have something you wanted to say to this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything else was Second Life.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was just going to say Walmart wasn't exactly the best thing to bring up since they actually sold censored versions of movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I totally agree with the point that Walmart's just as bigoted as everybody else in this sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to sell the violent movies, but heaven forbid our children see titties.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heaven forbid we teach them responsible sex at a young age.
[SPEAKER_08]: Walmart is a huge contradiction.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll sell the unrated movies gladly.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll sell the M-rated games gladly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they won't sell porn and they won't sell music with explicit lyrics.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never understood that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will never forget that fucking Sheryl Crow, of all people, got banned from Walmart because she said in one of her songs, she had a lyric about somebody buying a gun at a Walmart store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can, in fact, buy guns at Walmart stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a hunting section.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Walmart fucking banned Sheryl Crow because Sheryl Crow poses this huge threat to society.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, what's going to happen, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: She does, however, pose a huge threat to good music.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, when I think of hard fucking core music, I think of Sheryl Crow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, last thing before I go.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll be happy to know that long after it's been released, they're releasing a Stranglehold map pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd actually heard about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got the email from Midway, except I never played Stranglehold in the first place, so I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was about to say, I mean, it wasn't exactly a best-selling game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why would anyone care at this point?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably they were already making it, thinking the game was going to be huge, and now it's just kind of one of those wah-wah kind of releases, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they kind of have to at this point, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can make $50 off it, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, how are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm calling from Sweden, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're calling from Sweden?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got to be like four in the morning over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'm the first one to actually call from Sweden, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had people in England, and I want to say we've had South America, definitely, Mexico.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say we've had another... We've had Denmark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Denmark was it, but we haven't had Sweden.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, good evening, so to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a bit pissed last year since, in your years of, your best of year, since never ever spoke about that the expansion for World of Warcraft, Burning Crusade, actually came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was, but then again, I just was like, wait, did that actually get released?
[SPEAKER_06]: Last year?
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like it was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That did come out in January, and as far as PC games go, that was a huge title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, in all fairness, and to cover our rears a little bit, we did talk about BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked about The Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been actually... I don't know actually when I got hooked on your show for some reason, but I've been listening to your show like I would say maybe a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, I had some, what is it, since I've upgraded platform from going from Macintosh to PC nowadays, so I've had, what is it, only a half year that didn't go that well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, are you a big, do you play WoW yourself?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you really big into Burning Crusade?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm, yeah, I'm like, I would say that I'm a huge WoW fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, players, since that's basically almost the only thing I've played.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did I buy games last year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was Burning Crusade, and, well, I tried out EVE Online this summer, the summer bit, and then I bought the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good taste.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that I share with games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my question, though, to you, because I notice you're mentioning a lot of PC games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we always like to ask our callers who call in from other countries, because I know a lot of times here on this program we focus on, here's what's happening in Japan, here's what's happening in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: We try to cover the overseas stuff, but sometimes it's best to kind of hear it firsthand, what the gaming scene's like overseas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, for instance, we've kind of heard from callers that have called from Latin and South American countries talk about that
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the scene is very expensive there.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you say the gaming scene is like in Sweden?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it easy to walk into a store and pick up the latest and greatest game or console?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or is it a challenge?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like a piece of cake.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only problem is that, well, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Games are currently quite fun in one way, since the PS3 is...
[SPEAKER_02]: For the cost of a PS3, you can actually get a decent computer and start playing WoW or Orange Box, whatever you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they do say the PS3 is supposed to be a computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least they keep going back and forth on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's a computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And still, what is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was an argument that really the cell engine, which is in the PS3, is not even made for games, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm assuming that the PlayStation 3 sales in Sweden are similar to that they are here, where there's quite still a big pile of them at the store waiting to be moved.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it really is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess maybe we aren't so different after all.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you want to cut me off right now, but anyway, I just want to say, Skype,
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a 70 Druid, which I'm quite impressed in one way, since, well, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: In a way, just well-related.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played World of Warcraft on US servers for one year, and I never even got to level 40.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you playing on a PvP server?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's probably why.
[SPEAKER_02]: PvP server was
[SPEAKER_02]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Warsong.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've developed the infamous altaholic disease, which is that you made one character, and then you get a character like 35 or something, and then you play another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you repeat that for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically you have WoW ADD is what we would call it, where you can't focus on one character.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have plenty of friends who do that same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't got a character pass level 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, really, I actually have 63 mage nowadays.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: When...
[SPEAKER_02]: When the Burning Crusade came out, I switched to European servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, well, they made it a lot easier to level.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, when the 2.3 patch later that came out just a few months, one month ago or something, not even that, made it a lot easier to level.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I don't know what it is, and I do have to wrap up and get going soon, but I will say this about Druid, is that what's amazing about that class is it's one of the last classes I tried playing in WoW, and I think the reason I've stuck with it so long is that you really can do, like, a little bit of everything as a Druid, and that's why I have so much fun with it, because, you know, I can do spam, you know, Moonfire or whatever, but then I can heal, or in a pinch, I can flip in a bear form and, you know, tank, even though I'm not very good at it, because I'm specced for balance, but, you know, it's kind of interesting, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I know how fun Druids is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got one at level 45 at the current stage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you need to take it a little higher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were speaking about, well, what was the New Year's promises or stuff, and my problem is that I was saying that I will get one character level standing, but then I just realized that
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this new MMO that's been announced called Warhammer Age of Reckoning, which is highly anticipated in my ranks, which is Weehoo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it sounds like it could be a big year into 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully we don't neglect to mention that at this year's end special, or we might get another call berating us.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, we've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mind letting the international calls go on a long time, though, because I know you've got to stay up very, very late to listen to our program, and we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any other quick final thoughts, things you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, just keep on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really one of the greatest I have heard so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hats off for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate it very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you so much for staying up and listening to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: A true fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is actually my second attempt in...
[SPEAKER_02]: and listen to your live since I'm usually not well since it's the hour difference is such a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of these days we're going to have to do a show at noon to give our British and not just British but overseas listeners a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody over in those time zones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweden, Denmark, all of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks so much for the call though.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love hearing from the international folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do one more call if you've got any other calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up, everybody?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how you doing, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm finally recovering from my holidays.
[SPEAKER_11]: So how about you guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for the card, by the way, on a personal note.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, no problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, did you get your card yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to check the mail.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a pile of it, and I've been sort of too sick to look at anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's hilarious, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_06]: Your car actually got wet because of the storms.
[SPEAKER_06]: The rain got in my mailbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that crazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that happened to Dan's friend Will.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was expecting the title to his truck, and he found it floating in the gutter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just that the wind actually blew open the little flap, and water got in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, sorry Ranma, enough about me boohooing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll make this brief.
[SPEAKER_11]: I finally got a chance to play Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, what'd you think of Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_11]: It is great.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's got to be one of the greatest games I've played all year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am probably one of the only people on the planet that thinks that Guitar Hero 3 has a better song list than Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just not as into the songs in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I will say, Rock Band has some great download songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I actually like that Attack song a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one you told me to get.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually really like that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock band's growing on me, but here's my question, because I was just thinking about this earlier today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's your call and everything, but I'm deflecting.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think they could do for a rock band 2?
[SPEAKER_11]: Add more instruments.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, a keyboard would be nice for rock band 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: That I would like to see happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I think they should do for rock band 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not have a Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they should come out with Pop Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think in Pop Band they should get rid of maybe the guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lose the guitar and put the keyboard in instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or lose the bass and put in the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would love to see them do a Pop Band game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I don't know how that would go over.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if they do a Rock Band 2, maybe one of the controls could be a double axe handle controller.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that would be badass.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be pretty rad to have because that's what my character has.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a giant double axe controller with a big unicorn on it because you can put stickers on a guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I put a big unicorn on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan has the tattoo of the snake coming out of the pants.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every time he shows it off, he goes, what's a trouser snake?
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100 Matt says, polka band.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dark Knight says, I got to have cowbells?
[SPEAKER_11]: If there's a polka band, it's got to be Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I was telling you about this the other day, but our friend was, while she was highly intoxicated, by the way, walking around with a cup and a pencil playing cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: So as a long time, because I know you've been a long time fan of Konami's Bimani series and DDR and all that stuff, and I know that's how you kind of first came to our station.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think Konami could do to kind of step it up and give Harmonix a little competition?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually bring over more of the Bimani games and fine-tune it more for American audiences instead of... Did we lose him?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm right here, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine-tune it for American audiences instead of... Instead of putting in rehashes of some of the Japanese songs, like with DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: As much as I enjoy DDR...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: as the buttons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looked like a funky version of Whack-A-Mole to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that kind of what it looked like?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like Whack-A-Mole to music.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like touchscreen or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be friggin' awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except how can you play that on a home console?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's something that's only going to be in arcades, if anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, one thing I've noticed is that when me and my roommate, when we play Guitar Hero, it's like, eh, eh, we have to trade off controllers back and forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's just more than one person here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, with Rock Band, I mean, my friend brought it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like for the Christmas party.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like the ultimate party game, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, like, you have a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: You got, like, WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_11]: You got the Mario parties.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you break out of Rock Band, everybody will just show up and just start playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, you're switching off controllers back and forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're just getting together, having a good time.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, well...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkTetsuya DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Two quick things.
[SPEAKER_11]: My game of the year was Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Worst game of the year, Rover vs. Smackdown 08.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why those two?
[SPEAKER_11]: For me to get into a game, you've got to take my full attention.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any game that can help me kill a 45-minute train ride from homework vice versa is definitely up in my book.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Phantom Hourglass was one of the few DS games that were actually able to have me do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And as for Raw vs. SmackDown 08, I'm an average wrestling fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just didn't like the fact that they took so much out of the Wii version compared to the other versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, the Wii got the gimped version of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why it gets worst game of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just had to ask because you know you're one of like the two people who didn't say Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just had to ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have a 360 yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, DJ Rama S, we got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thank you so much for calling us always.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I'm going to get a bug lamp for this room and every time it goes bzzz I'm going to laugh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big rigs over the road.
[SPEAKER_09]: Racing is really, really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I am not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although not as bad as I thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's some where those Wii conspiracy games are even worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys very much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting and independent radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We would be nowhere without you guys and your word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you like what you've heard, please tell two people about our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spread the word about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you tell two people, then slowly we'll take over the world because we don't have any magazines or websites to get million views a month that we can advertise on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We literally broadcast out of my garage.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's independent radio at its finest.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't feel so inclined to tell people, you can always leave us a nice review on iTunes or Dig or Yahoo Podcasts or any of those sites because that works too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, thank you guys so much for tuning in this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next week we will be back and we'll have more gaming news and more stuff to come in the year 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully some surprises here on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to book some guests for the upcoming shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hopefully we'll have some of those in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So more to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until then, I'm Rob Roberts, she's DarkSakura, he's Loki, and we're out.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!