[SPEAKER_01]: All right, anything else you want to add to your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then let's go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week was fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a little bit of Nitro Bike this week because I was anticipating it was going to be awesome and all that stuff for the Wii because they're kind of comparing it to Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not even close to Excite Truck, and it's also not even close to being good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, unfortunately, it sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: In what ways did it suck?
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucked because the tracks weren't really open enough like Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game itself wasn't very fun because you can do tricks in the air and stuff, but really there's no need to be doing any sort of variety of tricks because you can do the same trick over and over and get the same kind of bonus for it, which is more Nitro.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the fact is the tracks aren't really straight enough anyways to where you would need the Nitro, so it was kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: They tried, and they failed.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing, though, that I do not like about a lot of these racing games is that unlike Excite Truck, which you hold the Wii Remote kind of parallel to the ground, a lot of these games will have it where you're holding it on its side so that you can use those really crappy plastic steering wheel controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I really hate having to hold it like that because it makes it really uncomfortable for...
[SPEAKER_03]: for your hands because you have to twist your whole wrist back and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sight Trucker is just awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, on purpose, I played Offroad Extreme Special Edition, which is a game that got reviewed on IGN, giving it a 1.5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's deserving of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, your vehicles in the game kind of control like crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very sluggish.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I had trouble staying on the track because of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was fun to get to play it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, not so crappy games, I got to play Burnout Paradise, which I'm very surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game, I didn't think it was going to be that good when I played the demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't seem like something I would like, but playing the full version of the game, I was completely wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and in fact usually I notice a car will zoom past me and start driving crazy and I'm like okay that's one of the cars and so I'll chase after it and stuff but uh it's just pretty awesome and the races are pretty cool also the music in the game they have a great soundtrack in it although the only flaw they put Avril Lavigne's girlfriend in there so I guess there's gotta be something for everybody but it was a little weird driving and all of a sudden your girlfriend comes on it just felt strange but uh
[SPEAKER_03]: I highly recommend the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be playing this for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually looking forward to picking up this game, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the Burnout games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not huge on a lot of racing games, but I like Burnout quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to try the online, but the servers, I guess, are not up right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, seeing as the game isn't totally out yet, that might make sense why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and then product placement, there's a ton of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's vans driving around with, like, axe and, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: and all sorts of weird shit on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like manly ads.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but you can crash into them, which is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, it's like, oh, product placement, destroy!
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be funnier if you got more points if you destroyed a Tampax billboard or something, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, you drive really fast through the game, they'll have like stunt mode and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just like, it's like, you know, just crashing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you try doing, like, your own custom soundtracks?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you said you don't like Avril Lavigne or whatever that's in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, like, when I played the last Burnout game on 360, I just used custom soundtracks all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would basically use the music from Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune to Burnout, and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually, I just, they have, you know, the EA tracks or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go in there and shut off which songs you don't like.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you don't like Avril Lavigne, you can just turn the track off and you'll never hear it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good function.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, actually what I did is I kept, and I make,
[SPEAKER_03]: If I had to find it from a cage match, but I may pick this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a song in there remixed by Jason Nevins that I've been having on repeat because it was the song that they had in the trailer for, what was it, I want to say it was Taxi or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That really crappy movie with...
[SPEAKER_03]: Queen Latifah, and what's his name?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a cool song, though, but they had it in the trailer, and just racing to that song is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm looking at our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually have two chat rooms now because we have the Justin TV chat, too, but I'm a little worse at being able to stay on top of that one, so we'll try to read both chats, but I'm looking at our main chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com, and some predictions from Son of Dad for the next Burnout game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Britney, bitch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe that'll be on the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: And that will be turned off as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some Britney songs are actually kind of fun to drive to.
[SPEAKER_01]: They do incite a lot of rage and the ability to crash into other cars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the online mode's going to be pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I guess you can just turn it on where people are just racing around with you and stuff, which would be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the game itself, I mean, just driving around is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rice Princess Alien Crush Good Taste Actraiser
[SPEAKER_04]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_00]: I love Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, Actraiser's so good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Doesn't it have, like, the best music ever?
[SPEAKER_00]: It does!
[SPEAKER_00]: Yuzo Koshiro is the man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, we have to get Devil's Crush, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right, that's up there now, too, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I just remembered that we played a bit of Alien Crush at my house, and then we had to hook up the TurboGrafx and play Devil's Crush, but now that it's there, it's like, oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, seriously, like, because Alien Crush is addictive, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got to 64 on my Orc Hunter, and wow, and whoop-de-doo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing super exciting, nothing new.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you are wearing a Silent Hill shirt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you excited for Silent Hill 5?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rumor is it's going to be out by summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it is, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you check out Silent Hill Origins on PSP at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't have a PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but I figured maybe you stole someone else's.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ask William.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought him one for his birthday.
[SPEAKER_01]: He never plays it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But also take note that Silent Hill Origins is coming out on the PlayStation 2 very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you can just play it on PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone needs to play the other Silent Hill games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that Nathan you're looking at?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Nathan, care to defend yourself?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe tell us a little bit about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have never played a Silent Hill in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you played Resident Evil?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't say played so much as died a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, what kind of games have you been playing this week, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alien Crush, a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what the point of the game is besides points, but that's all that I care about is more points.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just want to keep your ball alive is what you want to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I try to keep as many balls as possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: In play at the same time?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else you've been up to this week in the gaming world?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just today, my level 58...
[SPEAKER_01]: Torrin Warrior went to Outlands
[SPEAKER_01]: You're right, I don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and Pirates Pinball and Spider-Man Pinball that just came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember you talking about this at one of the pinball shows you went to and I'm just curious if it ever came out but something I heard about
[SPEAKER_01]: They were going to take a high-def TV and put it on its side and lay it down so it was like a pinball table.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had six of them there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their Ultracade pinball is what they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're very, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have to say, because what I did is I went and played the virtual tables.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I went back to play the actual pins because a lot of them were there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're pretty close.
[SPEAKER_05]: The physics in them are very, very good, but there's just something not right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But each of them I think held like six tables, and I think there's a capacity for more.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was very interesting, but you couldn't get like, you'd only be able to do like certain pins, like there's the standard two flipper, you know, start button, whatever, unless you had something equipped that had the other buttons mapped, like for things with double flippers, where you have to have two sets of flippers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two controls for it, or like a special, like the Magna Ball, for example, on... One of those tables that we can't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like one that you hit the button and it catches the ball before it drains.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want to say, I know it's not on... I want to say that it was on... Whodunit had one.
[SPEAKER_05]: But like...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be a little bit more difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'd have to find a way to map it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the cannon button on Black Rose.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to read some other things in chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not related to pinball, unfortunately, but something about the burnout.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were talking about the custom soundtracks and SSJ100 Matt said, I'm waiting for the next OLR listener to suggest Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be an amazing soundtrack to put as a custom soundtrack to a burnout.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, we're about to get into the gaming news for the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: But first, a quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_01]: As many of the folks in our live chat are noticing, we have moved from Operator 11 to a new service called Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_01]: So hello to all the Justin.TV people.
[SPEAKER_01]: The cool thing about Justin.TV is that we now are no longer limited to 40 minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: So JustinTV, and our username on JustinTV, of course, is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you want to check out the cam right now, you just go to www.justin.tv slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, that's going to do it for housekeeping, so let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll start off tonight with Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, I'm sure this is going to come as a big shock to you, but there's a certain game out there that's going to be delayed one month.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, Nintendo finally came out and said that, guess what, Smash Brothers is delayed to March 9th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure that's the first time that you've ever heard of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky for the people in Japan, though, it is coming out the 31st of this month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also lucky for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: So for all those people that import their games, they're...
[SPEAKER_01]: They are A-OK.
[SPEAKER_01]: But isn't it going to be very heavy on the Japanese?
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you going to be able to navigate through the game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you'd be able to navigate through the game just fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not going to be that complex.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's so many different modes.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you've been watching what's going on on the dojo, there's so many different modes.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes it even easier, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's going to even matter as much with that because...
[SPEAKER_05]: First of all, half the time they put up the text, it's going to be in Hiragana.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, either Hiragana or Katakana.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's usually a language select anyway for different regions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, their excuse for it is they said that development is taking slightly longer than expected, which is bullshit since it's coming out in Japan already.
[SPEAKER_03]: So obviously development's done on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's localization.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's either taking a long time or they can't press enough copies fast enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: So one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, is it possible that maybe, well, I guess that's localization, I was thinking maybe translation and all that stuff, but people shouldn't read into this like, OMG, they went back and added a new character or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they're not adding a new character.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think there might be any secret characters that they've been sitting on that they haven't announced yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope the Eggplant Wizard's in it, because I love Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, look at, they didn't announce all the new characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are you laughing at the Eggplant Wizard, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking of Captain N.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, like, you know, Captain N Captain N should be in it Game & Watch, or Mr. Game & Watch He was a secret character that they never talked about Yes, that's true You never know Mr. Game & Watch is awesome
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, if Eggplant Wizard doesn't make it to Super Smash Bros., perhaps it will make it to the rumored, emphasis on rumored, Kid Icarus game that is being worked on by Factor 5 for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rumors are abounding this week, and GoNintendo is reporting that Factor 5 has been offered up the license from Nintendo to make a Kid Icarus game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or Kid Icarus, however you want to pronounce it, because that was always a point of contention.
[SPEAKER_01]: People never knew exactly how to pronounce the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Icarus?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, regardless, Factor 5 made some previous games on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe they did Star Fox, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't they do the Star Fox game on GameCube?
[SPEAKER_01]: They may have.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, anyhow, that would be very exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't they do Fire Emblem?
[SPEAKER_00]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, well, Factor 5... No, not Fire... No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Fire Emblem wasn't Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Breath of Fire was Capcom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, so anyhow, regardless, I am very excited at the potential of having a new Kid Icarus game out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just hope they don't kind of like screw it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, I don't want it to be 3D or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just kind of know that things are going to be inevitable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, chatroom saves the day when we forget things.
[SPEAKER_01]: ShadowNextGen says, Factor 5 did the Rogue Squadron games.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in other news, for anybody who keeps up with the results of video game system sales, it has been pretty clear that the Wii and DS are outselling the Xbox 360 as far as units, but Microsoft is like, uh-uh, we made more money, so we win.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, in fact, they've made $4.8 billion compared to $3.5 billion on the Wii and $2.2 billion on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, if you're just looking at money, yeah, PS3 does not have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also, for the Xbox 360, they've sold 4.62 million units.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: PS2 sold 3.97 million, PSP 3.82 million, and the PS3 sold 2.56 million for its first year.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of that money stuff has to do with the fact, though, that the Nintendo Wii, they make quite a bit of money off every sales of those, whereas Microsoft and Sony still lose money on every one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think that, yeah, so I think that for...
[SPEAKER_05]: If Microsoft is saying that they've made more money with what they lose in production, then overall, yeah, I'd have to say they're definitely having to move a lot more units.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't see where the... But the Wii is clearly selling like crazy if they're having trouble stocking them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is only the numbers for 2007, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, Xbox 360 is still number one in the U.S., although...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, maybe it gave them a little bit more attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that they got any more than they would have normally gotten anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a little bit, because I know that distribution didn't get as many Wii systems in January because of this whole rain check program, but
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how many people that affected, but I'm just kind of curious, because I remember throwing that story out there, and it was kind of like, well, what if Wiis are still really hard to come by in January, which it seems like they are.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's still hard to find, and it probably will be for a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chat room to the rescue yet again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jvmon is in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chat on orangelaunchradio.com and says, Rob, I work at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_01]: We filled all the pre-orders already and already got extras to sell to people.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got the same amount we did November to December.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're still cranking them out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, as far as what the games did themselves, Halo 3 was at the top.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had 4.82 million, and Wii Play was right behind it.
[SPEAKER_05]: which I think was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call of Duty 4 followed that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero 3 on PS2 was behind that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the only reason Wii Play did so well is because it was like controller plus cheap games and that made it stand out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like Wii Sports and people love Wii Sports and for a while there it was hard to find remotes and that was the only way you could find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, win, win, win.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sneaky.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually were at Fry's last week when I was having my computer drama
[SPEAKER_05]: and there was a lady there trying to decide whether or not to buy Trauma Center or buy Wii Play and she's like, wait, this has a controller with it and put it down Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Trauma Center is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about the lowest common denominator.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: For real.
[SPEAKER_01]: There it is right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo's secret to success.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all about the lowest common denominator.
[SPEAKER_01]: For real.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo deer hunting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll win.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo came out and announced a few dates of titles coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is first and third party stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the first half of 2008, some of which we probably already knew about, some I guess were surprising, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, one game that was rumored to be coming out soon was Okami on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's been dated for the 25th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii Fit scheduled for quarter two, which that would coincide with the supposed rumor from 1UP that Wii Fit is supposed to come out May 2nd, or not 2nd, the 20th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see, Pokemon Mystery Dungeon, they're going to have some sequels coming out for that in quarter two as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crossword DS, Nintendo Crosswords, coming out May 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Professor Layton and the Curious Village, the current number one selling DS title in Japan right now, coming out in the United States on February 10th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see, some other fun stuff for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: February 26th, The Masked Queen and the Tower of Mirrors, the Dragon Quest Swords game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Karaoke Revolution Presents American Idol Encore.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's coming out the early part of February as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks like Apuna is scheduled to be coming out from Koei.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's supposed to be a pretty good role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm laughing over here like a three-year-old, but... Apunani.
[SPEAKER_01]: She can't contain herself either.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ironically... It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strangely enough, though, in here, they have Nitro Bike from Ubisoft listed as March...
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they didn't realize it's already come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't get the memo on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, April, we cannot forget Wild Earth African Safari from Majesco, the ripoff of Africa.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Cooking Mama Cook-Off 2 in June.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I know the first one controlled so well.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Cooking Mama on Wii was horrific.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the DS one's still cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I say.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another cool game that's on the Nintendo DS is Castlevania Portrait of Ruin.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game was pretty awesome on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: And some screenshots, some rumored screenshots have leaked from a new Castlevania game, although we kind of emphasize this is only a rumor at this time.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, it would really not be a surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of a no-brainer that Konami would probably make a follow-up game to this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Portrait of Ruin
[SPEAKER_01]: It's unknown at this time.
[SPEAKER_01]: But apparently there's some type of Wii menu item that's being seen in the screenshots on the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would that imply that there's going to be a Wii Castlevania game coming out soon as well then?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Castlevania is a good franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: But isn't that, I mean, that would be cheesy, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't have to have, like, you can actually whip.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one says that you... It's not cheesy at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one says you can't have just a traditional game on the Wii system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, people just, for some reason, get it stuck in their heads that they've got to make some, you know, motion control crap and stuff to go along with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at, uh, what is it, you know, Super Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that didn't have too... I mean, it had some stuff, but it was pretty much a traditional game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Macman says in chatroom, Castlevania whip carnival games.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't applaud that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Simon Belmont or whatever one of the Belmont crew has to tame lions or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: GS68 in our chatroom speculates it's probably going to be Castlevania W of I because it has to say we.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he's suggesting Castlevania Wind of Illness.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that sound Castlevania-esque to you?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very Castlevania-y.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very Castlevania-esque.
[SPEAKER_01]: But does it have to be like a music, like Symphony, Rondo, Wind of Incontinence?
[SPEAKER_05]: The ones with the... Well... Sorry, JVS.
[SPEAKER_05]: That really only applied to... Well, only applied to Dracula X. Because to be technical, Symphony of the Night slash Nocturne in the Moonlight
[SPEAKER_05]: and all the other ones after that were just Castlevania
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you're talking!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd buy that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I'd buy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sure we're going to get into this a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's probably something Itagaki would be into as well, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: He'd have to whip the cowboy hat off his head.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew, this is a crappy game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: From Namco.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's listed as a game coming out in the summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Active Life, Outdoor Challenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I don't want to be active.
[SPEAKER_03]: I refuse to buy that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like being active.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you need it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They should have different types of interactive games like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, for our friends in the UK, there are a couple of things out for Virtual Console, and I'm very sorry for you all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, one of them was okay, but there's better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like 1080 snowboarding from the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Riot Zone for TurboDuo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really sorry because it's not very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, you know, if you're feeling adventurous, you could just say, you know what, forget Jamie's opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to download it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to download it and throw up, be my guest.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, enjoy or don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is one game that's coming out on the WiiWare service at some point here
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually being scheduled for the second quarter of 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game called Platinum, and it's kind of a mix between a shooter and a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what I thought was interesting is they were talking about some of the stuff that it will support.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing, they have a price point on it, which is going to be 1,500 Wii points, so you can kind of expect a lot of these games to be around the $10, $20 range.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or $15 in that case.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's why that's a range, Robb.
[SPEAKER_01]: You see, it falls right in the middle of that range.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, I understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basic math.
[SPEAKER_01]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: You say 10 and 20, yet this game's going to be 15.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just clarifying for our listeners who may not be following because they fell asleep during your report because they can't understand simple math.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you insulting our listeners like that?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I would never.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, it's Nintendo strategy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lowest common denominator, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got some interesting stuff though in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play it with the Wii Zapper, although I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play it offline with up to 12 people at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess that would be one person uses a nunchuck, one person uses a remote, and then also the four, that's four controllers, and then four GameCube controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's craziness.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't even fit that many people in my living room.
[SPEAKER_01]: We did that once, remember WarioWare?
[SPEAKER_01]: 11 people.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, but that was crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was like a workout because you had to run around.
[SPEAKER_03]: There wasn't enough room in that room for people.
[SPEAKER_03]: It supports DK Bongos.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have finally another game that can utilize the DK Bongos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they're also planning a version Can you use the Guitar Hero 3 controller too?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you can use everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Armat?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I'm sure you probably could, since, you know, it's... That could be like the ultimate showdown.
[SPEAKER_01]: Twelve people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Twelve peripherals.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the ultimate WiiWare showdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep in mind, I think that it's actually pretty funny, because for me, who likes to find however many different controllers will work on a different game...
[SPEAKER_05]: My friend was the one who invented Rod Caliber.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will have a ton of different multiplayer options and peripheral options, but what if the game sucks?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, oh, great, I can use all these controllers, but do we really want to play this game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, are you sure it's a 12-player game, or is it somewhere in the range of 10 to 14 players?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's 12 players.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, for support for 12 people.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does not say a range of...
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Developers Conference
[SPEAKER_01]: That would actually be a really smart place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would make lots of sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually, now that I remember seeing this before, this was the first game that was announced for WiiWare at one time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it doesn't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of weird looking, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, I don't know, how would you describe that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Abstract.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is great radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob, describe this screenshot for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's in space.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's got bejeweled stuff and a sun.
[SPEAKER_05]: From over here, it looked like pizza.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're just hungry.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just want to eat it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's a good idea, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to do the whole 12 people, 12 peripherals, one game, and have a showdown, and then laugh at how stupid we are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Power Glove wins.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you?
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess they've taken Mario and combined it with, what the hell else?
[SPEAKER_01]: They've got this game Fusion, and they've got, I guess, Kingdom Hearts all worked into one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically a game called Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fusion, but it combines Mega Man, Halo, they've got Ghosts and Goblins, Sonic the Hedgehog,
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's all made in this one GameMaker 7 program or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it plays like Super Mario World or Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, that's like a Halo stage and we had a Mega Man stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else is there here?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's more Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they have the whole entire Bubble Man stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is craziness.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody was really bored.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I think that's all we see is the Bubble Man stage now.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you can actually play the demo for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can throw the bubbles.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very creative.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody's got a lot of free time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually cooler than Asshole Mario.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's quite a compliment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because Asshole Mario is really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Macman asks the question, Mario plus Kingdom Hearts plus Mega Man plus Halo plus Sonic equals Will It Blend?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pirates of the Burning Sea on the 22nd
[SPEAKER_05]: Advance Wars Dark Conflict and Burnout Paradise Cruisin' for Wii Donkey Kong Jet Race, Ferrari Challenge on Wii and DS Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends Imagination Invades on DS FDC World Darts Championship 2008 Fantasy Star Universe Ambition of Illuminus Pro Evolution Soccer 2008 Universe at War Earth Assault for PC
[SPEAKER_01]: That it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doesn't seem like that busy of a week over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I guess it is January.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess all the people who are addicted to PSU will be happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's not a very busy week over in Japan either, but I'm going out of turn.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually supposed to be the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: states next.
[SPEAKER_01]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, in the U.S., we have a pretty good week of stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: My personal favorite, No More Heroes, is coming out for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely worth picking up.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you don't have a Wii, maybe you'll like this for the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Advance Wars Days of Ruin looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pirates of the Burning Sea for the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Burnout Paradise coming out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're looking for more of a casual game, Endless Ocean on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario and Sonic at the Olympic Games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: One Piece Unlimited Adventure on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Iridium Runners on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rainbow Islands Evolution on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: And hopefully you'll be able to get past... Hooray!
[SPEAKER_03]: And exclusive to GameStop, I think it's hooray, Kawasaki Jetski, which is actually supposed to be like Wave Race.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wave Race is cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But probably not going to be because it's put out by Destineer and every game that they make sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: Cross our fingers, maybe someday their games won't suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just going to say this about Rainbow Islands on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do love Rainbow Islands, the original Rainbow Islands game, and that is where my love for the series ends.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because none of the games after that were really worth getting excited about.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now we'll go over to Japanese... What about Parasol Stars?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you could say all those games are in the Bubble Bobble universe, I suppose, but... Parasol Stars was great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Parasol Stars was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, going over to Japanese release dates, not a lot on the Xbox 360, but you do have on the PlayStation 3 this week, Juice 2, which I think was delayed from last week, because it came out on all the other systems last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: There really isn't a lot to speak of otherwise on the next-gen systems, but on the current-gen systems, such as PlayStation 2, or I don't know, is it high time for us to start calling it last-gen now?
[SPEAKER_01]: PlayStation 2 is really last-gen, and current-gen is, I guess, last-gen, who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: How about we just call it PS2?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's another Mahjong game coming out on the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Sims 2 Cast Away also comes out on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: And The Prince of Tennis, Driving Smash Side King.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an interesting anime.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: You too can be the Prince of Tennis in the privacy of your own home.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd rather be the Prince of the Cosmos.
[SPEAKER_01]: On the Sony PSP, not a whole lot of stuff, but you do have Winning Eleven, Ubiquitous Evolution 2008 coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: A couple other games getting price reductions, such as Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to do it for your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all happy and good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, speaking of things that are happy and good, there was a... Well, I'm sure that people have heard about this by now, but there was a guy named Paxton Galvanek who rescued two victims from an overturned SUV in North Carolina.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this guy's supposed to be pretty cool because he, you know, assessed the situation, treated their wounds like with perfect first aid, kept them alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: and his medical background consists of playing America's Army.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's a classroom in there and part of the classroom area is basically all the stuff they go through in BASIC which is including a medic class so that you learn BASIC first aid and when he witnessed the accident he basically went right into that mode and the first person he treated was someone who had lost two fingers and so he
[SPEAKER_05]: Used a towel to stop the bleeding and held their hand over their head.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got a full first aid certification because I have to as a massage therapist.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the first thing that you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: You see who's more injured and if they're bleeding, you hold their hand over their head and have them do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you also treated somebody for a head wound too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that by the time someone arrived, which I think is kind of funny because it said it was a soldier that showed up to help them out, everybody was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: and he actually, uh... I think it's pretty cool, though, if they're putting in, like, actual real first aid techniques in that game, then that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: By chance, did he play Trauma Center as well?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you can learn a little bit from playing Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we're not to cut people?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can stitch up somebody by, you know, waving furiously.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you can also stop time, slow down time if you use your psychic powers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Star, you can totally, like, heal them completely.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so maybe America's Army is a little more practical.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, that was the whole point of that game, though, is to show, you know, what it's supposed to be like to go through, you know, basic and be out, you know, on the field and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I actually think that's kind of cool that someone could just...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to be the medic!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, they do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's more of the be all you can be and going into the army can strengthen yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's like when people are playing an MMO and they pick their class, it's like the same people who would pick a priest because they like to assist and heal people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my theory.
[SPEAKER_01]: And of course our chat room is breaking out into a chorus of heal please, heal please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you ever played America's Army?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a rigorous training process just to start the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They make you take tests before you get your gun, and then it jams.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: LF-10000M, Iraq Instance, tank and healer needed, please send tell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if people are, you know, buying the game for the purpose of what it is, as a simulation, then it needs to be that in-depth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, I mean, really the game is just a marketing tool for the army anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is, but... And now this kid is going to be the poster child of that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look, see what America's Army can do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now imagine what would happen if you joined the real military.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just reading the thing over and saying, you know, when he was talking about what he did, and I was like, that is proper first aid.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you're supposed to do, so pay attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kudos to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I guess you really can't stitch up somebody by going like this and flailing your arm about.
[SPEAKER_01]: I refuse to believe it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something along the same lines as America's Army.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently the porn industry has dropped their backing for HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: And dozens of Xbox 360 owners cry out in pain all at once.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to put my HD DVD player on Craigslist tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't know if it's everybody, but one studio in particular, Digital Playground, has decided to abandon HDTV and stick solely with Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good for them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not every studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not every studio, as a lot of people are reporting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just Digital Playground.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't... Never mind, I'm not going to say it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest, I... Let's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, Irene and I are giggling like three-year-olds over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Irene's all, you're just hoping it's not Falcon or Colt, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I mean, it's one studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how many porn studios are out there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, there's a ton of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But let's see what Digital Playground has to offer us, you know, because... Okay, I mean, seriously, let's see here...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're top-selling titles that you may be missing if you have an HD DVD and you want it in HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jack's Teen America 19, Mrs. Bee Haven, Jesse's Juice, Janikova and Blue, Forbidden Tales, Jack's Big Tits Show 4, Hush, and Jesse Jane's Scream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although...
[SPEAKER_03]: To their credit though, they did produce the Pirates film, and Pirates was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hilariously bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Macman suggested the PlayStation 3's newest games, Drake's Penis, Ratchet and Dick, and Heavenly Sword.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing though, they may have stopped making HD DVDs, but they still sell them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They still have quite a bit of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And besides, anyone that actually watches a lot of porn anyways, they don't buy their porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on, this is the internet revolution, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who actually buys porn nowadays?
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can find plenty of it in DivX out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And remember, your PlayStation 3 also plays DivX, and hopefully Xbox 360 will at some point soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where you can stream stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe Xbox 360 is already playing DivX now after their last patch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: So SingStar does not appear to be doing quite as well as people originally thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad they can under-deliver like normal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, however, to be fair, Sony did make a response a little later in the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: SingStar Studios said that downloadable songs for SingStore are on the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: The original vision was supposed to be 350, but they missed the mark.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, they are going to put out 18 new tracks on January 18th, which should have already passed.
[SPEAKER_01]: 15 English songs and 3 Spanish ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: Including David Bowie and Blur.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: And February 4th is supposed to see the launch of even more songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They only missed the mark by 200 songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and 15 of those are in English.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're supposed to be updating it now twice a week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, not twice a week, twice a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one needs to be playing SingStar anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a horrible, horrible, horrible game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Karaoke is a horrible, horrible, horrible piece of entertainment, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you really feel?
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus they have the ability to upload videos of yourself singing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who would do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we do have a situation.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do I have to call out the troops?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do I have to get a medic?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry for all of our European listeners who are excited about Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not in 1080i.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was only added to the US version later in development, and the PAL version is not going to have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank God, I thought there was a real problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that it would delay the game's release because they have to test it for QA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry!
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait a minute, game developers are QA-ing their games again?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's good news.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be 480p.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you really have been out of shape about that, remember, PlayStation 3 games are region-free.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you really need your 1080i, to be honest, you're not going to tell the difference between... If you've got an HDTV...
[SPEAKER_05]: Then it doesn't matter if it's PAL or NTSC.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: So get it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Import it!
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's your workaround.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_03]: Workaround!
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of workaround, they finally released the custom firmware from DarkAlex, the guy behind all those wonderful PSP custom firmwares, or at least all the popular ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: He has just released 3.80 M33
[SPEAKER_03]: and it will give you all the wonderful features of 3.8 including the streaming internet radio and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus a bunch of new features as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the cool things I liked about this actually is you can, once you've loaded 3.8 in there, any additional firmware updates that happen to come along from the custom firmware scene, you can actually update them over the internet just like you would your normal PSP firmwares.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can just, you know, download an update and update it right there, just like you would any official firmware.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I did, and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's available right now for PSP Slims, and they also have one for the PSP Fat, I guess, that also has some of the stuff for the 1.5 firmware, so you can run your homebrew crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: But try as they may,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: One thing that perhaps Dark Alex maybe wants to work on soon is solving the Dust problem on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, no, I'm not trying to make a joke that nobody's playing their PlayStation 3, so they're getting dusty.
[SPEAKER_01]: But remember, remember, like, Dust killed somebody's PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, Sony refused to do anything about it or something like that?
[SPEAKER_01]: The guy ended up getting a refund from the credit card company or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dust is obviously a huge issue for PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, that PS3 right there looks like someone put it under their sawhorse when they were cutting some wood or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do collect dust, though, really easily.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're dust magnets.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: So insert your dust cap joke here, but there is officially a dust cap coming for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That company makes really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got a couple of controllers that they put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: The GameCube ones back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a mod that makes my PS3 smoke a cigarette.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would make it even cooler.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or you could just not smoke next to your PlayStation 3 or put it in a well-fitting...
[SPEAKER_01]: Take a hit off this PS3, you'll love it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Suddenly your PlayStation 3 is glowing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wanna get high?
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at the website though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you look at the ad for it?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking at how all of this fits in, I think it's a very good idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: How it all pieces together?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they said that it's charged with static to attract the dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know like those static wipes?
[SPEAKER_05]: for dusting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same theory on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll link the ad in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the ad is available at Hori.jp.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just browse to their products for the Dusk Guard Kit 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, um, I think that GameStop still carries a lot of Hori products.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, shouldn't have any problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dusk Cap 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was always hoping it would come to the US.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in other news.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, we said we weren't going to talk about this guy again.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he, who shall not be named, keeps reappearing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has he opened the Chamber of Secrets this time?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's trying.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's trying to open up a can of drama is what he's doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Jack Thompson, The Butthead, Lord Voldemort
[SPEAKER_05]: and he's quoted saying I was never interviewed about Buzz I never heard about it until I was quoted having allegedly said this about it and what he was quoted as saying is that video games have hurt far more people than they have helped and he said that what he would say well I'm just going to read his quote because he speaks in circles I would never say what I am quoted as saying in any context as the quotation regardless of what it is applied to is absurd on its face
[SPEAKER_05]: How in the world could anyone prove and or quantify that games have hurt more people than they have helped?
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds to me like he's lying.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, every time this guy opens his mouth, I don't know about you, but I get a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you get a little angsty?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Real quick, I was just going to mention that Take-Two actually proactively sued him, so that's also going on right now, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, Loki cut me off, and that makes me even more angsty, so you know it's time to bring on the FUs of the week!
[SPEAKER_05]: An FU to my washing machine for not wanting to wash my hoodie by itself and imbalancing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I really wanted to wear my Jack hoodie tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Nightmare Before Christmas one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I couldn't because it's still wet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really not very instant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to my cat for throwing up a hairball on my massage diploma.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now I have to go get a reprint of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my transcripts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I have to get reprints of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you...
[SPEAKER_05]: to my folder from when I first started school because it has all my massage school receipts in it so that I can have myself one big fat tax write-off.
[SPEAKER_01]: All done.
[SPEAKER_01]: And?
[SPEAKER_05]: An FU to the company I work for for not claiming my W-2 yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: For real?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want money!
[SPEAKER_01]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, your FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, FU to the theater that I went and saw Cloverfield in.
[SPEAKER_03]: because the entire time the front left speaker was making a noise so it was really annoying the entire movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you sure it wasn't just the monster?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we went and complained to management and they're like, you know, a bunch of little kids running around trying to figure out how to fix the speaker.
[SPEAKER_01]: The monster didn't go have some fourth meal at Taco Bell?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: My FU of the week goes to the damn flies in here
[SPEAKER_01]: Who have not been served yet with the swatter of justice Are they hiding right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they are I haven't seen one in a little while F you to the fact that the flies hide all week long And then they come out on Sunday, I hate that Anyhow, Rice Princess, Nathan, you guys have anything you want to add?
[SPEAKER_04]: Flies just like listening to the show, jeez F you to being sick and not being able to hear out of my left ear So I sound like an old woman like, eh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why'd you say that again, Shani?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, yeah, it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also second the FU to Cloverfield audiences.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, no, you just said the theater, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: The audio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I say FU to the audience, because they're stupid and immature.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're, like, yelling out what they thought of the movie at the end.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I don't go see movies on opening weekend ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because of kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there were a bunch of kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like I went out and said, you know, my opinion on the movie, because I don't care to do that, but people do, and they're stupid, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: F.U.!
[SPEAKER_02]: My only F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: is for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love you guys, but you gotta really hurry up and make available on the virtual console Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Mario RPG
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people haven't played it and don't know how great it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: My games look better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you to know Guardian Legend either?
[SPEAKER_01]: Greatest 8-bit game of all time.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've been saying that for a long time on this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I do agree, Super Mario RPG would make a fine addition to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_01]: But don't keep holding your breath.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, Loki, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, this is kind of exciting, and hopefully this comes out in the Wii, because this would be one of those games that could utilize that whipping motion from the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Leisure Suit Larry, box office bust, is coming to consoles and the PC fall of 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yes, if you don't remember Leisure Suit Larry, well...
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX 360, PlayStation 3, PC, and Mobile Phones Team 17, The Worms Games
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the script, I guess, is being penned by Happy Madison Productions' Alan Covert.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that Happy Gilmore and Billy Madison or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Happy Madison is Adam Sandler's production group.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Alan Covert, he's done such wonderful movies as... I now pronounce you Chuck and Larry, Grandma's Boy, Eight Crazy Nights...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Deeds, Little Nicky, Big Daddy, Deuce Bigelow, Male Gigolo, Waterboy, pretty much every other Adam Sandler movie that's been out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy Gilmore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If only that game had Adam Sandler and the whole Happy Madison group doing the voices in there, that might be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Rob Schneider in that game, that could be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do it!
[SPEAKER_03]: All night long.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should make a Leisure Suit Larry movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Happy Madison.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the games I actually, one of my favorite games is Burning Rangers, which is also put out by Sonic Team, who can do no wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Sonic Team.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, the game is basically set in the future where...
[SPEAKER_05]: The only few hazards remaining is one of them is fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: So these are futuristic firefighters who use their super sentai powers to extinguish flames and rescue people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And after you beat the game once, you actually have a random level generator that you can use to change the game each time you go play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as the technical side of it, for people who were Saturn fans, you know that the Saturn was...
[SPEAKER_05]: ADX Audio Compression Fantasy Star Online
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a central dome fire swirl level where one of the main characters from Burning Rangers asked you to help them put out fires and help people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And had the music from the Japanese version of Burning Rangers, which was Angels with Burning Hearts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two of the vocal songs were in Sonic Pinball Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the theme song was in Samba de Amigo, if you remember, as one of the downloadable songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Samba de Amigo
[SPEAKER_05]: Burning Rangers is cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you have it, your classic game of the week, Burning Rangers.
[SPEAKER_01]: A game I never played, but maybe I ought to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I will bring that to the Saturn over one day.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you should.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's funny that it goes for bucks on eBay, and I got mine at a convention swap meet for 30 bucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes you find little gems there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, that's going to do it here for Part A of our show.
[SPEAKER_01]: But as you know, Orange Lounge Radio is divvied up into two parts every week, so we will be right back after just a little bit with Orange Lounge Radio Part B. Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.