[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, October 14th, 2012, an upcoming holiday game is leaked a month early, Valve is looking for some hardware testers, and could you soon feel temperature in your PlayStation controller?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: which I know a lot of you in the chat room might be going, wait a minute, she's right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's the magic of the internet, you see.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's sick today.
[SPEAKER_03]: She caught Disneyland plague or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: She caught the gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: She went to gay days at Disneyland and wouldn't you know it, she walked away with a horrific case of the gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so she will not be here tonight, but she is in chat if you wish to say hello and feel better and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, with us tonight in studio, we do have Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a cold.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a cold, but it's not the gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gay doesn't make you all stuffed up, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I sound, I definitely have the gay because I'm sounding a little sick today, but I just blew out my voice over on Friday, but I'll talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, also say hello to, we have a guest host here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love it when he's available and on standby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Alan.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's me again.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you again?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's new with you?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the last time we talked to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not much, working, working a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to pinch hit last week, but I had to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: My amazing boss got me the day off.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta make the money.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it looks like you're a horrible, terrible boss is in chat right now if you want to say a few words.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm giving him a hard time on purpose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else do I need to plug here at the top of the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be sure you listen to us live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Bobby Blackwolf Show at the Voice of Geeks Network or vognetwork.com Home to a variety of great geek shows, not just video game shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's important to point out is that, you know, we do have some awesome video game shows, obviously, with this one and Bobby and Girls Gone Wow and Hard House.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have some non-video game shows, things like Under Station Live, Pod Culture, Critical Myth, British Invaders, Anime Jam Session, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it all goes down at vognetwork.com
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to come with a kickoff topic tonight but I neglected to think of something because I'm a little bit my voice is shot tonight because and I think a lot of other shows in the network have been talking about this understation live and I just mentioned this on Bobby's show before and I think I've mentioned on here too I was asked I was fortunate enough to be asked to be the director of the return of the Rocky Horror Picture Show here in Sacramento and
[SPEAKER_03]: and while it went marvelous on Friday, it was very exhausting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also emceed the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm basically screaming obscenities into a mic in front of a crowd of 400 people and it felt really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like what I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of, kind of.
[SPEAKER_03]: On this show every week, except I could see them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't hide from them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could see them too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew you were going to lose your voice or get damn close to it because when you were shouting your intro, there was a part where you literally blew your voice out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could hear that sound wasn't like...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So, we know that this is the season for video games to become movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I don't know what it is, but every October, well I do know what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the fact that October is kind of the month for Hollywood to release their crap films.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which usually includes the video game movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, all the Resident Evil movies come out late September, October.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm not saying these movies are crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hollywood kind of views them as crap because they're kind of in between this summer blockbuster and Oscar nominee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oscar season starts at Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So most video game movies end up coming out in the October season.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if they were actually supposed to be crap, they'd be coming out in January.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the two movies that came out video game-wise this year are both kind of monster Halloween-y movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Resident Evil is more of an action movie, but
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's the Transylvania Hotel or whatever and the Frankenweenie and all that stuff's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wreck-It Ralph very soon, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although technically it's a November movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think they're just... Wreck-It Ralph, I mean... Here's the thing about Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we're all excited about Wreck-It Ralph, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's Disney and it's video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So obviously there's a great cross-section here that this show represents very well that is very excited for Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think for...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure how it's going to do in the mainstream.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it is still kind of a risky thing for Disney.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that's why it's not their Thanksgiving movie or their Christmas movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's kind of that odd little place.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in a place where it will either flop horribly and disappear.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that'll actually happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's going to do better than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The funny thing is, I think it's going to be a lot of parents who are actually into it because of all the Nintendo references and things they remember taking their kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's truly a movie that's geared towards both and there's a lot of people that are excited about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I got on a tangent talking about Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I really wanted to ask about was since we're in this time of year where we talk about video game, movies, and so forth, I just finished doing a stage show
[SPEAKER_03]: So what video game do you think deserves a stage show?
[SPEAKER_03]: What video game deserves an adaptation?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have to be a musical, but think Broadway style.
[SPEAKER_03]: What video game do you think should become a full-fledged on or off Broadway production?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I... Well, they've already kind of done this as a music... Like a video, but... Buggy Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that video was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it was done Broadway style.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'd go for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, have a bunch of people doing, like, you know, the artistic dancing and singing and stuff like that and have video of Saints Row being Buggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can even, you know, do Buggy Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Driver 3 is probably very, very, very, very buggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want new music for that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, what would you want to see on Broadway?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maniac Mansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maniac Mansion?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's probably almost too easy of an answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a TV show at one point, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or my troll answer is Echo the Dolphin.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wouldn't be a Broadway production so much as it would be like the tank show at SeaWorld.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be like ice capades.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, someone comes out in a dolphin suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're swimming through rain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you saying that dolphins can't ice skate?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, they don't have to ice skate, but they can hop up and slide across the ice and then slip back into the water.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect Halloween
[SPEAKER_03]: Should Mass Effect be a musical?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't do those effects on a stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: That needs a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you could, it would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would not be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's look at some of the answers from our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wicked says, Final Fantasy VI, the opera scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's a very, you know... Well, I mean, technically it was an opera.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like, now you're talking about the play that became the video game that became the play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like Street Fighter 2, the movie, the game type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura is in our chat tonight saying Clu Clu Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: How would that work?
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody would just pole dance on stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clu Clu Land would be a showgirls type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Irritating stick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wow, that would be a hell of a stage show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like Lion King right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like some crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone's going to come out of there and be like, did I just drop acid or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened to that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stan in our chatroom says, Space Channel 5 should be on Broadway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now there you go, there's a great musical idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could actually work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is kind of sad That could work Sad in an awesome way though Let's see SSJ100Matt says Parappa the Rappa Let's see Stan says in Chicago they've done a Mario burlesque show Same with Zelda I think
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just cosplay strippers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burlesque show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just add some class to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fucking cosplay person stripping.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, now, I have friends that do burlesque that would take a lot of offense to what you're saying right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I aim to offend everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are so rude.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least you can say this.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the burlesque community has done it, you know what other communities probably done it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Drag queens.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my question is, has there been a Mario or Zelda drag queen show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, you used to live in the city and go to these shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the craziest drag queen show you saw in the city?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, they were all really amazing, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: One time I went and they did Ziggy Stardust album from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smashing Pumpkins, Drag Tribute Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, when I think of drag queens, I don't think of Smashing Pumpkins, so that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's why San Francisco's more alternative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: San Francisco's hipster drag, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole cabaret, you know, the greatest level of all, you're not going to find that there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma in the chat says, Loki, I know people that do cosplay burlesque, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burlesque stripping, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we really just going to like... Are you telling me that the end of the... And it's happening in Ranma's room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, are you telling me that the end of the show that they don't end up with less clothing on, therefore they are stripping off clothing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Out of this world
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Morpheus in chat says, I saw a peach drag queen at New York Comic Con.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I gotta say, the peach drag queen thing has been done at several conventions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Mass Effect 3, the DLC that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Been playing the hell out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They added, you know, we talked about, or you guys talked about it a little bit last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Collectors, which were the antagonists in 2, are now an enemy class that you can roll into in the multiplayer matches.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I unlocked the Volus Adept, which is an ultra rare and 7 unlockable character.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure saying Volus Adept is the same as saying, like, Pineapple Toaster Oven to most people in our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pineapple Toaster Oven?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: I like pineapple and I like toaster ovens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I unlocked one of the new coveted secret characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about a toaster oven that cuts the pineapple for you?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played some Black Mesa Source a little bit but not as much as I have been because I already went through and beat it and I'm waiting for them to patch in the end of the game Mass Effect Infiltrator because about three weeks ago I upgraded my phone I now have a Galaxy S3 I believe Bobby Blackwolf got one about a month ago so I downloaded the Infiltrator Mass Effect game for it
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks gorgeous, but it controls so bad that it makes me angry that I spent the four bucks on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It controls so poorly for me that it makes me feel like... Have you ever had someone...
[SPEAKER_05]: You show them a game like Saints Row or Grand Theft Auto, and it's someone who does not play video games, and you hand them the controller, and you're like, okay, here's how you move, and here's how you get in a car, and they just drive off a cliff.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first thing they do is they just die because they don't know how to play games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Infiltrator controls so poorly that it makes me feel like I'm one of those people.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I told James about it and he has it on iPad and he said he made himself beat it just because he has a boner for Mass Effect and he's like, oh yeah, the game's a total piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe I beat it all the way through.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucks for some of these hardcore franchises.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fruit Ninja, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: For whatever they're doing in that game, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really it, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how to play Tiny Tower, which is like a two-year-old iPhone game, but
[SPEAKER_03]: But since you're coming off having the phone that doesn't even have a QWERTY keyboard on it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had the BlackBerry equivalent of the Nokia brick.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the classic, you know, you throw the Nokia brick at a car and the car explodes and the brick is fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had the BlackBerry equivalent of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now, so going from that to this...
[SPEAKER_05]: Android, Ice Cream Sandwich, ooh, you know, little laptop in your pocket is quite a change.
[SPEAKER_05]: In Tiny Tower, I give all of my stores perverted names.
[SPEAKER_05]: The laundromat is called the Stank Panties.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got, the TV studio is named after a porn website, which I'm not going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's actually, it's Porn Studio because of the name I gave it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, it's good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times, killer game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, just to fan the flames of this, what made you decide to go with the Galaxy S3 on the day the iPhone 5 came out?
[SPEAKER_05]: to be pragmatic about it you represent the Apple portion of this household which is fine I'm not hating on that but it's like if we want to be you know the ultimate geek duo we need Android representation up in here so that people can come to us and they will ask Rob the Apple questions they can ask me the Android questions if I want to be pragmatic about it make sure all of our braces are covered that is the best possible answer you could have given good job this is why I keep I will investigate whatever it is you don't like
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: So when they ask you about the Apple stuff, like, why should I get an iPhone 5?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's new!
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta get the new thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this week I've actually been trying to catch up on a lot of stuff that I haven't been playing because I've been playing a lot of Minecraft or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's see, this week I played some Vita stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was also another thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to play games on the Vita because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been and it was sorely neglected so I tried out a couple demos I had first Gravity Rush which was pretty cool just not really something I mean it's a good game but it's not something I'm going to be playing because I just don't want to play a lot of different games right now I've already got plenty of my play right now but it's a it's a unique looking game it's fun
[SPEAKER_04]: So I played that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played LittleBigPlanet Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that was something I was like, oh, I'm probably going to get this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then I played it, and it's LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great, but it's got the Vita gimmicks that you kind of expect in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just kind of like, eh, it's another LittleBigPlanet game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably won't play this, so I'm not going to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, it's not that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have LittleBigPlanet 2 that I haven't played.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why am I going to buy another LittleBigPlanet game that I probably won't play?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to finish other games first before... I'm just trying not to get into that mode of, like, I need to get all these games because they're good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I'm going to be sitting on all these games that are good and not have time to play them and then more good stuff's going to come out and I'm not going to have time to play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ended up... There's a ton of games I have that are really old that I haven't played yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: and 3D.GameHeroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've lent that out to so many people and I have yet to play that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that game came out around the same time as Red Dead Redemption or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was just like, ooh, Red Dead Redemption.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just kind of lost track of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a new story coming up later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'll mention it then, but there's this really good sale going on right now on a bundle of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're like all things that people tell me I should play and I've missed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like, wow, for a very, very, very small amount of money, I could catch up on three years worth of gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for that amount of money, I think it's a good deal, even if you don't play them, because that amount of money for one of those games... We're getting ahead of ourselves, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game I actually did want to play, and I bought it mainly because it came out on this platform first, was Retro City Rampage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been looking forward to this game forever now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have the whole cross-buy thing on the PlayStation Network so you can get it for your PS3 and Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I bought it for my Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's fantastic if I didn't have a cold at the point when I was playing it my body was aching and my eyes were just like burning if it wasn't for that I would probably have played a lot more of it but it's a fantastic game and there's just so many homages to everything it's just crammed full of just so much fan service and just like oh my god I remember that and even stuff that will probably fly over your head but
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fantastic game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just basically the best description I read for it was someone says it's a developer's love letter to the industry for all the 8-bit games that he played.
[SPEAKER_04]: It even has modern references and stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The story is just throwaway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes no sense whatsoever, but it's got everything, and it's seriously a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I am looking forward to playing that on my PlayStation 3, hopefully, but on the Vita, it's still pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, the game does tend to make the screen a lot smaller, like in different sections of the map and stuff like that, and so playing on a Vita, I'm sure it's not so bad on a TV, but on the Vita, the screen gets really small, so that might be something that might turn people off from it, but
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fun game, especially if you like, you know, Grand Theft Auto 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very much like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But even if you don't like Grand Theft Auto, it's still a great, you know, action game with just all sorts of crazy stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, from Bionic Commando to Bill and Ted to Back to the Future.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, more Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played a lot more Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fished up my castle, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, come join the server if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Call of Duty, we bought Map Pack 2, so we're going to start playing some new maps because we're just kind of getting bored of the ones we're playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, tried doing another Streak Week, missed it by another game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting close, getting close.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was it, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was all the games I played.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Alan, you'll get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how, and the live listeners will understand this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Podcast listeners, I apologize for a minute, but we're having these stream dropouts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like it's happened twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, we, just so you guys know, we actually purposely left the internet off for an hour today while we went to go run errands.
[SPEAKER_05]: The cable modem and the router off for an hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do a complete power cycle of every damn technological thing in this house so OLR can stay up with no downtime tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're on two.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not in this house.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is not in this house.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is on their end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, why do you guys keep dropping our stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if it's not because sometimes I see that we're still sending data
[SPEAKER_03]: and they start complaining in chat that it dropped and I'm like, it didn't drop because I see that we're still sending data because if Comcast goes down, then our net should stop working, I should get booted from IRC, all of that should happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that makes me wonder, is it our stream provider that's really having the issue?
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't happen to Bobby.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, it doesn't happen to Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's done it for an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what the hell's the problem?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could be our, is he, where is, sorry, forgetting all, where's it located?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are we piping to right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, that's a good question that I don't know the answer to, that maybe Bobby does Cause if it's in the Midwest or the South, it could be our connection to there, and he's in Atlanta It very well could be, let me see if this tells me where we beam the show to, because I'm actually not sure Such great radio right now I know, but you know what, deal with it Um, it says New Jersey, so it would be infinitely closer Oh yeah, so for us, if we're piping to New Jersey then, there's, yeah, it's probably the stream Weird To us
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mean, it is New Jersey, so no wonder the stream's getting late.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who else do you want to offend tonight while we're at it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're still early.
[SPEAKER_04]: We haven't even started story yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've done burlesque people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've done New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not saying there's anything wrong with burlesque.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burlesque is awesome because it's, once again, women stripping off their clothes, which is, you know, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think really the only difference between burlesque and strippers is strippers kind of go all the way, whereas burlesque is more of the tease and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're still stripping off their clothes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just like, you know, Skinemex strippers versus, you know, the stripper strippers, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh boy, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who spilled Jaeger and spray tan on the server rack?
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a very DarkSakura week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week was very DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does everybody know what that means?
[SPEAKER_03]: Aspect and WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sims?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's DarkSakura circa 2009 gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week this week was I played a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did some dailies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I shouldn't say a lot of WoW because I didn't play a lot of WoW because I've had weeks where I've played a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is not one of those weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I played enough WoW to do a few dailies here and there and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I played Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: because, as Alan mentioned, the new DLC went up, the multiplayer DLC, and it's very well-rounded.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got a whole new class of aliens that you can fight, the collectors from Part 2, so that breathes new life into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has some new classes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter because I won't be seeing them anyway because I never get that stuff in my...
[SPEAKER_03]: Premium Spectre packs, but I did finally get one of the ones I really wanted.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got the Cerberus Adept, and I've been playing that class a lot because he's the guy with the whips, and you're just like, Hulk smash!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hulk smash!
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything, and it's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vanguard's like that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, we were doing a multiplayer match earlier with some friends, and one of my friends was like, who sent the body flying out the window?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, Mass Effect 3 multiplayer is still really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like that they've staggered this content a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, what is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every Tuesday, we're going to get just a handful of new things, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every Tuesday for a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if they're doing it because there are 16 new kits where a kit is a...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, maybe that's what they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Street Fighter IV Street Fighter IV, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've probably got all the other achievements by now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's not a lot else to work towards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, heck, you haven't even been playing since launch, but your N7 score is what?
[SPEAKER_03]: 800 and something now?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like 820 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be higher, but when I do golds and silvers, I'm usually on a level 20 and they don't gain XP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's move into some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe today or tomorrow, I think it's tomorrow, is the last day to nominate us for the podcast awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please, for your consideration, Best Gaming Podcast and the Stitcher Awards also going on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think they end either tomorrow or Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please...
[SPEAKER_03]: Consider a nomination for us there as well for Best Gaming Podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: If for whatever reason you don't want to vote for us, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please support one of the other shows on the VOG Network or at least, bare minimum, support Indie Podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Stitcher, I believe it's every day or every day you can vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can nominate for Stitcher every day.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Podcast Award is just one nomination.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll keep our fingers and toes crossed and let you know what happens either next week or in a couple weeks when those nominations are announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember,
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually, I hate the whole begging for votes thing, but it really is good exposure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these guys, as much as some of these big podcasts are fine, the NPR podcasts are great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, wait, wait, don't tell me it's a great show.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Adam Carolla show is a fine show if you like him and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they don't need the additional exposure.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have plenty of corporate exposure and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we really want to see the indies succeed in these shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's a lot of really good indie programs too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like there's good indie games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's move on to the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, no, one other thing I gotta plug.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very important.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always like to plug the shows that are kind enough to invite me on as a guest.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was a guest this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how I fit this in this week, but I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a guest on Nerdgasm Network, their gaming show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's episode 54 of...
[SPEAKER_03]: NerdgasmNetwork.com
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll hear more about putting it all out on the table, and I'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some more burlesque talk, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, very similar to burlesque, but in a different way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's another year, so another Microsoft game has been leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hurrah!
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Microsoft is investigating a report of Halo 4 being leaked, and they're working with law enforcement to address the issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's images being surfaced on social networking sites depicting retail discs and a dashboard featuring the game ready to play, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it's absolutely 100% been leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, you know, they're like, well, we're clarified with that's actually it's been leaked 100%.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has it been leaked?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know that much more you can say other than it's pretty good and also I guess some other information apparently the game is going to be on two discs the second disc is going to contain installation data for the multiplayer stuff and once you've installed that then you can actually play the game with the first disc kind of like Forza 4
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Loki, help me understand something.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are people able to play this game before the release date?
[SPEAKER_03]: Piracy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But piracy's bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is bad, and they will get banned if they go online.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Microsoft called the po-po.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they're really investigating.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, look, obviously...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're gonna say, you know, they're gonna invoke the police because, and you know, it is a crime.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can poo-poo it all you want, but stealing shit is a crime, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but what will the police really do to investigate, you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think the police is coming after little Johnny Pirate that went on the Pirate Bay and downloaded the program?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or do you think the police are looking more into how the leak happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're trying to find out how it got leaked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then the police aren't doing a very good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate to say it, but let's see, Gears of War 3 leaked, Halo 3 leaked, like every big Microsoft title leaks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did Fable the Journey leak or did that just slip off the radar?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, any title out there, any title that's being released is leaked usually a week before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reason that happens is because that's how the shipment schedule is for retailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: They usually get stuff Monday prior, or if it's direct retail partners like, say, GameStop and BestFies and stuff like that, they're getting their product probably the week before on a Wednesday or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now here's how I think this happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is totally speculative.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not the week before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo is not supposed to be out for like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's how I think it happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a couple of ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, someone nabbed a copy when they were pressing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, an actual copy out of the duplicator.
[SPEAKER_04]: or, and this happens occasionally, the warehouse that ships the product, the Microsoft product, will misship something and accidentally send something early, like way earlier than they're supposed to receive it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, personally, we had some Skylanders stuff for the new Skylanders Giants that they accidentally shipped us earlier than it should have been, like about a week earlier, which is usually unusual.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, lucky you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some lucky asshole got Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not doing anything with Skylanders, but I'm just saying it happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been Microsoft-released games in the last few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had Fable, and then next week we've got...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Central 3, Forza, Horizon
[SPEAKER_04]: or who knows it could have just been somewhere else an employee you never know I mean because it's one of the biggest games this and probably Call of Duty Black Ops 2 are gonna be like the ones the scene groups out there fight each other who's gonna be able to release it first and you know it's it's all bragging all EPing bragging rights basically like oh I'm playing Halo and you're not or so that's that's it
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's the question I have to ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: How can Microsoft stop this?
[SPEAKER_03]: How can Microsoft stop that leak from happening?
[SPEAKER_04]: They can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have to be more secure about how they duplicate their game, just the whole handling process of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way other publishers do it, at least they try to prevent street date violators, is by delivering a product as late as possible to those retail chains.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking like getting it a day early instead of a week early, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, something like this, as far as we're aware, this hasn't even hit the retail chains yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, it's not good, but I don't think it's really going to hurt them in the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're still going to sell a buttload of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, the reality is you kind of have to ask yourself if you're going to download one of these games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Am I the type of person that sits there and goes, aw, every time I hear one of these stories about game developers closing or why did Big Bad EA close such and such developer or so forth, yet I'm not allowing said company to make money?
[SPEAKER_03]: You kind of can't have both, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: People have to get paid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't think that's fair, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what you're basically saying, though, those are a lot of these secondary companies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of it has nothing to do with how well the game sold.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to cut profits because it didn't sell as many copies as they thought it would.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily because piracy ate up hundreds of thousands of copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, that's assuming that every person that pirates something would have bought the game regularly.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: as much as I don't want to agree with you I think I actually kind of do I think a vast number of people who pirate games were never going to buy that game in the first place I'm going to tell you this much they only download it because they can
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I did it with Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto 4 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It leaked down the internet one week before it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still bought the game, but I wanted to play it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to play it as early as possible, and so I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it a week early, but who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I've more than paid for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought, what...
[SPEAKER_04]: 6 copies of the game when it came out and 6 copies of episodes from Liberty City when it came out and 6 copies of the first DLC before the episodes from Liberty City stuff came out I think they got my money so I don't feel so bad about playing the game a week early
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is why the industry is very eager to get on digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is why you see some companies maybe rushing digital distribution and really trying to push it more and more is because if you think about it, digital distribution is a great way to curb piracy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It won't stop it, but it would stop these leaks from happening because essentially you've cut out the entire process of printing the discs and the going gold and shipping and the problems there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're cutting that all.
[SPEAKER_04]: all out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what leaks out even earlier than games like this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: They leak out even earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Know why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because people have access to PartnerNet still.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people download them off PartnerNet and they put them out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just crack it and put it out and
[SPEAKER_04]: HALO 4
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's going to get pirated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, all the games get pirated, but I don't think that they're going to sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to be like, oh, crap, it didn't sell at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one's going to shut down 343 Studios because it didn't sell because of, oh, piracy, it just ruined the whole game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not that many people, compared to the millions of people who buy it, that pirate games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's such a small section, but they would want you to think it is because they've got to blame their loss of sales on something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think though that if this hadn't happened maybe they would have sold a quarter million more copies?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if this hadn't happened it's going to leak out again when it comes out and those same people will have pirated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ramma in our chatroom says Halo 4 could come out at $19.99 and yet it will be pirated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com follows that up with iPhone piracy is rampant and that's 99 cent apps.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's a perfect example where it's like people do it because they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you're giving someone the option to get something for free versus paying for it, why wouldn't you get it for free?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I understand that there's this whole morality of, oh, well, if I don't pay... I mean, they try to push this shit on you even at the movie theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: And legality.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are taking a risk.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand that, but it's just... Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's... It would be like...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: It just has a hole over everything that you can't catch everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: The best defense is to stop the people that upload them in the first place, and then there's nothing for them to pirate.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I could look you in the eye with a straight face and totally mean it and say, you would never catch me down there being one of those looters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think it's wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would never participate in a looting event like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I really believe that about my character.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not trying to say I'm better than anybody else or whatever, but I know they had a situation like that happen in Britain not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were these huge riots and all these things, and there were these looting, and a bunch of kids got caught and went to jail and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I remember looking at it going, what a bunch of fucking thugs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't be one of those thugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just ridiculous, that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mainly my analogy was that how do you go after everybody?
[SPEAKER_05]: As a literal metaphor, I don't really think that's the best comparison.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, once again, the video game industry or the movie industry would like you to think that that's exactly the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: the great debate that will never end but maybe this is why we see more free to play games happening because it's like fuck it we'll make our money other ways no seriously that's a great idea as long as you can secure DLC but that's a great idea because then it's like fuck pirate it as much as you want get as many copies out there because that's more people that can buy the DLC for it
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's why I think it is more popular approach because it gets the game into more people's hands and more people want to try it because it's free there if it sucks whatever I just delete it you know and that that's why I think it is a good way to go but then again at the same time some of these companies are getting greedy and they're taking the free-to-play model for their paid games and that's just pissing people off even more and they're like fuck you I'm just gonna I'm not only am I gonna pirate this game but I'm also gonna pirate all your DLC
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: This piracy debate will never be settled, so I'm going to go ahead in the interest of time and move on with the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what a great segue talking about a game that a lot of people probably just should have pirated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trolling.
[SPEAKER_03]: But pirated DLC and all that definitely goes with this, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Street Fighter X Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't pirate something that's already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the Trash Bags, hefty update later this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is supposed to rebalance the game, provide visual and mechanical tweaks, which I find interesting that they're going to actually tweak some of the visuals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every character in Street Fighter X Tekken is supposed to get some type of balancing tweaks and so forth, including Ken, Kazuya, Kami, Julia, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots, lots.
[SPEAKER_03]: also don't forget Street Fighter X Tekken is coming to the Vita I don't know if that means these same balancing things are already in that finished version or if there's a day one patch or whatever but that is due on October 23rd as a reminder that's just around the corner Street Fighter X Tekken on the Vita didn't that game flop?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think flop is a strong word but I think it didn't perform as well as they'd probably hoped word of mouth from friends who are usually like Capcom for life and just the reviews were like this is not very good
[SPEAKER_03]: what I'm really curious about is where's the other half of this because we were supposed to be seeing Tekken cross Street Fighter and I'm wondering if Namco just started working on it this year they were working on Tekken Tag 2 maybe they've been developing them side by side they have the engine their joint project for this was announced 2 or 3 years ago right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase CROWN Do you live in the Seattle area?
[SPEAKER_05]: If so... No!
[SPEAKER_05]: If you do, you might want to head over to Valve Software's website and take a little playtester survey and see if maybe you could become a hardware tester for their Valve appliance which clearly exists in some form though they haven't given it a name and we don't know what exactly it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope it's a fridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope it's a pineapple toaster oven.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, if you are in the Seattle and Bellevue area, is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're looking for hardware testers, and it's a questionnaire.
[SPEAKER_05]: How long have you been gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you a completionist?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you an achievement hunter?
[SPEAKER_05]: How often do you unlock 100% of everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: How often do you beat completely every game that you play from start to finish?
[SPEAKER_05]: You wouldn't be qualified for this, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can expect people that go into this to have to sign a non-disclosure agreement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, up through the teeth.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can expect that those will be broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: So from however many months ago that they were looking for hardware engineers, they have an alpha clearly that they want people under lock and key to go check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever their Steam box is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I look forward to what leaks out of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, remember that there was the announcement that Sony has bought Gaikai.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so now Gaikai's website, they've been updated to kind of resemble a little bit more of the PlayStation lineup.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see images of Loving Planet as well as Uncharted and it looks like Killzone in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have some stills from Metal Gear Rising Revengeance and...
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't really say any additional details or something, but obviously it seems like this is something that's going to be offered as part of the PlayStation platform soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can probably expect some game streaming either by the end of this year or maybe an announcement at E3, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, around the same time though, Gaikai, they've kind of found themselves as part of a patent lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Delaware company called T5 Labs, they filed a suit against them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess their patent for providing a system and methods of sharing a graphics processing unit between plurality of programs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the patent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm not sure if this is just a patent troll company or if this is actually a company that does this stuff, but I'd be willing to bet it's probably a patent troll company.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, they have no comment on it, but there is a lawsuit in place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this what really put OnLive out of business?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I would have thought if anybody was going to complain, it would have been one of the other companies that deals in this same technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be willing to bet that T5 Labs probably hasn't put anything out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You probably can't even find them on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to even check that out right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: T5 Labs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they even a part of the internet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: T5Labs.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, it looks like they've got some crappy flash animation on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's implied that it has to do with games because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Wars Scrolls
[SPEAKER_04]: T5 Labs enables people to play PC games on their existing set-top box.
[SPEAKER_04]: The service operates on a video-on-demand client-type system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says T5 Labs' patent-pending technology allows the system to work on ultra-low latency.
[SPEAKER_04]: We call it Instinct Gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that does sound like Dakai.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it does seem like then that they are actually making something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a patent-troll company, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I am corrected.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is refreshing to see that they're not just a patent troll.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect 3 Omega DLC Carrie-Anne Moss
[SPEAKER_05]: She was also the mom in that Shia LaBeouf movie, and I saw that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and I think she's in the new Silent Hill movie as well, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think she's one of the crazy... I think she plays the villainess, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where was the Borg queen last time?
[SPEAKER_03]: This time it's Carrie Ann Moss.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, I suggest you do not fuck with Arya in the Mass Effect 3 Omega DLC, which they are saying will be double the size of Leviathan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leviathan wasn't that big of a DLC campaign though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Lair of the Shadow Broker is still the one that they need to beat as far as quality and length.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Lair of the Shadow Broker in Mass Effect 2 was a badass campaign from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Lair of the Shadow Broker was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And especially if Omega is going to be kind of like a hub like the Shadow Broker Lair was that you got in 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Omega was probably one of the best design places in the entire trilogy because if you're a science fiction geek like I am a lot of the design was based off of I'm blanking Harrison Ford in the 80s Blade Runner a lot of Omega is based a lot of off the scenes in Blade Runner and the music was amazing and I'm really glad that we're revisiting this place in three
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the big news about this DLC, female Turians for the first time you're going to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, fans are wary.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always the comic books and so forth where they've shown up, but the first time in the game is certainly a big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the fans, of course, want to see, you know... When you say the fans, you mean who?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tumblr, Bioware forums?
[SPEAKER_05]: All of that, the fandom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because a lot of people want to see female Turians because the entire trilogy... It's like, how do Turians have sex?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because clearly they're all men everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are worried that they're just going to, like, put a Turian head on, like, Tits Armor and be like, there it is, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: They're fucking reptiles.
[SPEAKER_05]: They shouldn't have tits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks, BioWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm interested to see what they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when you're talking about all of it, you've researched the fandom through extensive online research, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I track Mass Effect tags on Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what sorts of things do you participate with in the fandom?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just reblog stuff and favorite stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, have you ever written a fanfic?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you ever read a fanfic?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've read some hot Emshanko stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was your favorite, M. Shinko?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Kaden was jogging through the Citadel in booty shorts, and everyone was like, you know, Cat calling him in Shepard was all flustered and offended.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kane's like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't believe you actually had an answer for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, just trolling you live on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, also apparently about this new DLC, one of Mass Effect 2's characters, Zaid Massani, is supposed to return in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember him being in 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he was in 1 Quest, wasn't he?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he's in the Quest with the little Volus from 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's in the refugee camp.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can talk to him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zaid sucked anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: $15 for the DLC, which is on the pricier end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that more than Shadowbroker was?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was Shadowbroker $10 or was Shadowbroker also $15?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it might be 8 or 9 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how much it was back in 2011.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never had a bad experience
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I was going to say, even though Cerberus took Omega, I'm sure there's a way to work it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Cerberus... I'm getting so nerdy into the ending of 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cerberus took the remnants of the Collector base at the end of 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if you blow it up, they still have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they could be controlling the Collectors now, or the Collectors show up and ambush both of you and Cerberus.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shayna Linko in chat says, they say that it's Cerberus, Rob, for Omega.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that means nothing but Cerberus is going to show up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but that could be the plot twist, that the Collectors are there, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, all through 3, Arya talks about how it's Cerberus.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Elusive Man kicked her out, and she's pissed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, maybe some of these other weapons that have been showing up and so forth, and even maybe the maps, because multiplayer maps get used in single-player sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, a lot of the multiplayer maps are unique to multiplayer though, now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not originally.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you definitely see some multiplayer map, or you see some single, like in the Leviathan DLC, I could have sworn one of those maps looked a lot like one of the multiplayer maps, but it was just kind of like different.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a different layout, but kind of like the same assets.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, enough Mass Effect talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki's getting bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I just totally tuned out that whole last segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, hater, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you'll be more interested in what Alan has to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember Darkstalkers?
[SPEAKER_05]: 2D fighting game, really creative characters, really underrated franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Capcom is bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Darkstalkers Resurrection was announced at New York Comic Con this past week, and it is a HD cleanup.
[SPEAKER_05]: Darkstalkers 2 and 3 and it's bundled together in one pack similar to Marvel vs. Capcom Origins and also if you remember the Final Fight Magic Sword combo where you can have it look like an arcade cabinet or you can have it be full screen it's going to be a package like one of those and it's going to be I think 1200 Microsoft points or $14.99
[SPEAKER_05]: so yay Darkstalkers were you a fan of Darkstalkers?
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a modded Saturn, Sega Saturn and I imported Darkstalkers 3 because it used the 4 meg ram cart for the people that played X-Men vs Street Fighter on the Saturn if you remember that it supported the 4 meg ram cart, it was arcade perfect, it was gorgeous do you think you'll be picking this up?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna say no just because how often do I turn on the 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if they ever shut down the Mass Effect 3 servers, maybe you'll have a reason to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect 4, Xbox exclusive.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trolling them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought... Didn't they announce a new Darkstalkers game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or was this all the announcement was?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they were teasing that something was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think this is that something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But obviously, I think it's trying to either get people...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people don't realize, well, the real people who've been with Capcom since the beginning will know this, but the combo system used in X-Men vs. Street Fighter and the combo system used in Marvel vs. Capcom, you know, the light, light, medium, medium, hard, hard, where you do the zigzag across all six buttons, that chain combo system, that was done in Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the engine that they did that combo system in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that also Killer Instinct?
[SPEAKER_03]: You could kind of do that, too?
[SPEAKER_03]: Zigzag combos?
[SPEAKER_05]: Those were weird Link combos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those were very specific things you had to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because when you say zigzag combos with the six button, that's honestly what I think of.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think of Killer Instinct before I think of that, but I get you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, let's travel around the world and look at some release dates of some games coming out near you a little sooner than Darkstalkers, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start with the US, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week, we have quite a few things coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting off with...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rocksmith Guitar and Bass technically it's like the first game with the bass expansion but they've got that coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360 and PC as well as bundled with an electric guitar Dance Central 3 coming out this week on Xbox 360 Mugen Souls on PlayStation 3 also let's see here
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got 007 Legends on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doom 3 BFG Edition on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zumba Fitness Core on the Wii and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeopardy on PS3 and 360, Wheel of Fortune also on PS3 and 360, Silent Hill Book of Memories for the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, that's been delayed forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was delayed quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I don't think it was very good from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they made it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I certainly hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, it's going to be kind of a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I'm not used to them being a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do know that one week from today, because they have to launch it on a Sunday because it's so special, Skylighter Giants coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, 3DS, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're going to have a portal owners pack in case you bought the first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that would be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's travel to Japan and look out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, wait, I want to read a comment from chat real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says, when are they going to do a Rocksmith for keyboards?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, keyboard smith.
[SPEAKER_03]: if they do that I am so there like I'm not that interested in learning how to play guitar honestly but I used to play I used to play the organ like the double decker pianos with top and bottom I used to play that when I was younger like way younger like five to ten and I can still kind of hunt and peck my way around a piano or whatever but if they were to do this so I could like refine my skills I am so there if I could like you know because I really enjoy it in Rock Band 3 I really do
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the keyboard mania that they had for the actual keyboard that was on PC?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't own it, but... Or what about Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you ever play Rock Band 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course I played Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved the keyboard mode in Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and then there was Keyboard Mania, of course, many years ago in Japan, and that was fun, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was always my favorite of the Moani games, even though it was horribly neglected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's go to Japan and check out some games coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Monster Hunter Frontier Online Forward 5 Premium Package on the Xbox 360 on the 17th.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is also, I guess there's a bundle with Xbox Live points you can get too, I guess for some of the transactions in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think Monster Hunter Online for them is actually a monthly fee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so that's probably a points recurring fee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance Central 3 gets a Japanese release on October 18th Darksiders 2 gets a Japanese release on October 18th as does FIFA 13 World Class Soccer again those are all Xbox 360 for the few 360 owners in Japan interesting about Dance Central 3 I'm imagining it's got to be the same song list I don't think they localize for you know the area or whatever so I don't like don't get excited if you're a J-pop fan I don't think there's anything to look for there but interesting that they got such a quick turnaround
[SPEAKER_04]: It is very disappointing that they don't have Wild Wild West like they do in Just Dance 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PlayStation 3, Darksiders 2 and FIFA 13 also coming there on the PlayStation 3 on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, going to some of the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Vita this week, FIFA 13 is there as well, and The Legend of Heroes Zero No Kisuke Evolution comes out on the PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying, if you haven't bought
[SPEAKER_04]: and the Vita version of FIFA 13, you may want to hold off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's exactly the same as FIFA 12.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I thought that was the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly on the Nintendo 3DS, Project X Zone on October 19th from Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, would you care to take us to the land of all things Britain?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And UK-ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 15th has The War Z, or The War Zed, coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 17th we've got Serious Sam 3 BFE on Xbox 360 and The Unfinished Swan.
[SPEAKER_05]: on PlayStation 3, 19th of October, 007 Legends on 360 and PS3, Dance Central 3 on the 360, Doom 3 BFG Edition on the 360, PS3, and PC, Madagascar 3, the video game, which I'm sure is going to be the best game released this year, because, you know, movie tie-in games are always phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_05]: on 360, PS3, DS, PC, 3DS, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those big cross-platform juggernauts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rocksmith on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skylanders Giants on Wii, iPhone, 360, PS3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter X Tekken on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a few more news stories for you guys, then we're going to get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura isn't here, so we're taking over.
[SPEAKER_03]: So see what we picked in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently SingStar is going to be a free-to-play game pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which kind of makes sense, because when you buy SingStar, you kind of get some songs, but it's basically just a platform to buy more songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you look at Rob's library, that shit ain't free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, don't be a jealous hater because I have SingStar ABBA, which is awesome, SingStar Queen, which is awesome, and SingStar 1 and 2 on the PlayStation 3, which are okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how many songs a la carte that you've bought?
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough to have a party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough to entertain my guests when there's a SingStar.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've been collecting them since I lived at that house with John.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't really have parties here in the tiny apartment.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when I lived in the house with John where OLR was in the garage studio, we used to have SingStar parties.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: and a lot of those I bought on sale, to be fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got SingStar Queen at the local flea market for like $8.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you going to say no to that?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was new.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was brand new, still wrapped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently you still need the microphone, obviously, to play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess there is a message now popping up on the SingStar games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're basically saying the complete SingStar experience will be available as a free download very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you don't like all of ABBA songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you only like a couple.
[SPEAKER_04]: You buy a couple ABBA songs and you buy some Britney Spears or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who the fuck is going to be satisfied with only a couple of ABBA songs?
[SPEAKER_03]: If only a couple ABBA songs is what it takes to satisfy you, get out of here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe those people want to spend their money on Queen or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look, if you're on a limited income, then I understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you need to set up your monthly ABBA plan to get you on your path.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good idea for Sony?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they haven't really done anything with SingStar in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a good idea because it's going to get more exposure for people and because the SingStar games don't really sell that well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they really don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet they do overseas a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: They probably do overseas, but honestly, karaoke games don't do very well, but everybody's got a USB microphone, especially those wonderful Logitech microphones that they put in everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They work on pretty much all systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you get one of those in a throwaway game, like Truth or Lies or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've got a SingStar mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, no, the SingStar mics are different.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, I mean, you could find a bundle for SingStar for like dirt cheap somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that like a GameStop or Walmart or something has them in their dump bin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go looking for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, let's move on to one more story about, you know, this always pisses people off when there's content on the disc that they call DLC, and you have to pay to unlock it, which, you know, we started using the term pay to unlock content instead of DLC for certain things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, when it was discovered that Resident Evil 6 has some things locked away on the disc, everybody was like, oh, here we go again, Capcom!
[SPEAKER_03]: Pay to unlock DLC!
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently Capcom announced that the things that were found on the disc, including No Hope, Difficulty Level, and Co-op for Ada Wong's campaign, these will be freebies, and they will be a free title update coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: So no word if they only made it free because they got caught, or...
[SPEAKER_03]: All trolling aside, I can see the value of doing free DLC because it extends the life of your game past the first week, especially in the very busy holiday season where there are so many games competing for your attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can actually see the value of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't believe I'm about to say this, but good on Capcom in this case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it is coming out that there will be paid DLC, but it will not already be on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming later.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to a time when there wasn't even a Resident Evil 1 yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think when this game originally came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe one was out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back when the Resident Evil series was good...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was no download content.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was all on this content.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was no download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: When Resident Evil 2 was going to be on the N64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, she ain't here again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we've snatched her pick away from her.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we've picked an awesome game in her place that we think you guys should be playing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we gave it to Alan this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Alan, what is your classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well,
[SPEAKER_05]: usually when I do this segment I do like old Sierra Online PC games or like LucasArts so I wanted to give consoles love this time and I wanted to do something handheld because I don't think handheld gets that much love in this segment so I chose Legend of Zelda Oracle of Seasons and Oracle of Ages for the Game Boy Color
[SPEAKER_05]: They are super awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of Zelda Seasons and Ages came out together, obviously, because you can play one, you get this huge, massive password code that you then plug into the next game, and then you continue the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: And once you beat both of the games, so you play one, you get your code, you play the other one, then you get to fight Ganon, who's the secret boss, and then you get to see Zelda proper, and you get the real ending.
[SPEAKER_05]: and one of the big deals about this game was the fact that Nintendo did not develop or design it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They let a subsidiary of Capcom called Flagship write and code and design the game and Nintendo simply published it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that may be one of the first times Nintendo has ever let a blue chip franchise
[SPEAKER_05]: Be in the Hands of Someone Else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's not that rare, because Sega's done stuff, and there was that Metroid game that was done by Team Ninja.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game came out in the US in May of 2001, which was the month of
[SPEAKER_05]: before the Game Boy Advance console proper came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is one of the last games for the Game Boy Color before that generation was phased down, the Advance took over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the best Game Boy Color graphics that you'll probably ever see, and even looking on the YouTube, that looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like eight colors, I think, on the Game Boy Color?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so if you play one game, some of the items that you get are upgradable in the second game.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are a lot of little side quests and little... Look at these little cartoony cutscenes, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: For Game Boy Color.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you play both games, depending on which order you play them in, you can upgrade certain items to a tier that you couldn't normally get if you bring all of your equipment and stuff over into the next game.
[SPEAKER_05]: In Oracle of Ages there is a time mechanic where you speed up time or slow down time to get past to solve certain puzzles in the dungeons or on the overworld to actually get into the dungeon.
[SPEAKER_05]: In Oracle of Seasons you have a rod that will if there's a river you'll make it winter and the water will freeze so you can cross the river.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was this the game that had the advanced dungeons or was that one of the other Game Boy games?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Link's Awakening DX wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm not sure about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you're thinking of the re-release of Link's Awakening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody in chat will correct me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the lovely part of doing a live show.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the awesome things about the Legend of Zelda handheld games is that, and Nintendo, Miyamoto's even come out and said this, in the handheld Zelda games, they will allow themselves to do things with the franchise and with the mechanics and the story that they simply can't do on the console versions, because the console ones...
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the three medallions, you're always going to have the Master Sword, you're always going to fight Ganon.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are these staple things that are always in those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the handheld ones, like Oracle of Seasons and Ages, Minish Cap, Spirit Tracks, Phantom Hourglass, that's when they really get super creative with the world of Hyrule and the stuff that you can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: They usually introduce a lot of new characters that you'll never really see again in the handheld games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Link's Awakening, with the big, you know, the fish or whatever that's sleeping, that whole plot was inspired by Twin Peaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you're a big Twin Peaks fan, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so that's just, yeah, that's just an example of how the...
[SPEAKER_03]: how Zelda really shines in a lot of unique ways on the handheld systems now I did some research and the advanced shop was Oracle of Ages and Oracle of Seasons it was a shop it was not a dungeon I think I called it the advanced dungeon at first that's probably what confused you when these games are played on a Game Boy Advance there is a shop they have two seed rings and a gasha seed depending on the game it's either the GBA time ring or the GBA nature ring while the other is a random ring
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, and oh, that's right, I remember it's right here in the article.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since this was so close to the Game Boy Advance release, if you played it on the Advance in addition to that shop, the graphics were also much improved.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they had, obviously not Game Boy Advance quality graphics, but the color palette and the clarity of the pixels, they actually was coded onto the Game Boy Color cartridge to be read by the Advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you look this up on YouTube, try to find the advanced run-throughs.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as how it played, again, it's Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've played Minish Cap, Link to the Past, the first Zelda game, overhead, big expansive map, you go into dungeons, you have to beat the dungeons in a certain order, because the items that you get in the dungeon, the treasure, is what you'll need to solve puzzles in the dungeons.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: The main antagonists, I believe, are Twinrova.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the double witches could be wrong there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been so long since I played this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, there are these...
[SPEAKER_05]: The oracles are these ladies that you meet when you're transported to these new worlds.
[SPEAKER_05]: These games don't take place in Hyrule like a lot of the handheld games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, they are in danger, and there's... Naru is one, and Din, I think, is the other one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you rescue them, and then as you progress through, you beat the one game and you play the other one, you do figure out finally how Zelda and Ganon and the Triforce factor into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: they're a lot of fun if you're a big Zelda fan and you haven't played these you're missing out
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your classic game of the week, The Legend of Zelda, Oracle of Ages, and Oracle of Seasons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two games for the price of one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much, Alan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Jamie would be happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's going to do it for part A of our show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got plenty more show to come when we get back, including some rapid-fire news, the Fugo question of the week, and some interesting rumors about Miyamoto's new direction.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: An event coming up appropriately named Fuck This Jam.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not our event.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's somebody else's.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about that a little more when we come back after a break with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Outro Music Outro Music
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't see it?
[SPEAKER_05]: When they did the galloping horse, it blew my fucking mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, it was really amazing some of the stuff they were doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you know, having done field shows in the past before, and I'm sure Bobby can attest to this too, I'm sure we're not the only band nerds that happen to be into video games and all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure there's plenty more band nerds out there listening to this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it is a lot of work, because you not only have to memorize songs, but you have to memorize where on the field you're going.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Jessica Harper from Under Station Live is in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com and says I was however the drum major my senior year I feel like she's told me that before and I forgot and that's awesome because I tried out to be drum major but I wasn't picked somebody else was picked I'm a drum major reject and now look at me I'm on a podcast about video games on the internet anyhow drum major reject laughs
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad Jessica could achieve where I clearly failed miserably
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I apologize again for my voice, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am kind of struggling through tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already had a hot cup of coffee and a throat coke cup of tea, and it'll fix it for about 30 seconds, and then I go back to, my voice is kind of scratchy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I will do my best.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is like the worst possible thing that can happen to a radio guy, but I will do my best to try to get through the next couple hours here, or not next couple hours, but next hour or so.
[SPEAKER_03]: of the show for you guys because we have plenty more gaming news to talk about.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to start off with some rapid-fire news, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: That is correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's talk a little bit about this really cool sale that they've got on Amazon right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bunch of Square Enix games, and I think it's a great deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $10, and you basically get Deus Ex Human Revolution Augmented Edition plus the Missing Link DLC, Hitman Blood Money, Just Cause 2, Just Cause,
[SPEAKER_04]: Quantum Conundrum, Supreme Commander 2, and The Last Remnant for $10.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the sale is running through October 20th.
[SPEAKER_04]: It expires at 11.59 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go get it because, I mean, that's seriously a great price.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, this is a sale we were referring to in Part A, and I got to say, kind of want, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's called the Absolutely Great Square Pack from Amazon.
[SPEAKER_05]: and these are all the PC yeah the last remnant which you know was their exclusive RPG for the 360 which was a huge pile of shit if you have a good PC it plays fine so the technical issues that it had on the 360 are on PC and you should actually play that game because it's good and no one would ever know because it was so awful on the 360 so Overlooked Square RPG
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft in our chatroom says Amazon won't let me buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if that's the Mexico thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's a deal that's only good in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of sucks for those that are in other countries.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It may not be available anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says currently unavailable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it sold out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe so many people jumped on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: The DRM on it was Steam, so you were getting some sort of codes or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: For a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see it right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says unavailable, but then there was this buy and download thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's try clicking that just out of curiosity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just come on.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch.
[SPEAKER_05]: uh no it will not let me during some of Steam's really insane you know 99 cent sales this happened with GTA 4 and um the you know Ballad of Gay Tony they had a note um we don't have codes so we ran out of all our codes so we have to contact Rockstar Games for like 20,000 more codes that could be the issue that's happening here well they may have had limited copies and then once they hit all the blocks and well that sucks
[SPEAKER_03]: Alpha Cananogram in chat is saying, don't know if Loki said, but feel free to use the code SQRLUVIO to take $2 off any digital video games purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: Code will expire when this product becomes available for purchase again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if that means Amazon didn't intend for this to happen or something weird's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't have that code either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't give me any code.
[SPEAKER_04]: These bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I bet you're mad for waiting now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, I do see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it says currently out of keys, back in stock soon, $2 promo.
[SPEAKER_03]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's right, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, well, just give it some time and keep checking back, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, oh, well, great deal either way.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, we have to talk a little bit about some DLC and Sleeping Dogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have quite a bit of DLC soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting next week, they're getting some street racing DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to add some new street races in the game, I guess, for $4.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it's going to run you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have three new races across Land and Sea.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, I guess, there's some new Street Racer DLC that they're... I guess they're adding a new motorcycle as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a new outfit that boosts, I guess, Defense Against Gunfire and Accidents.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then there's also going to be some DLC on the 30th that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nightmare in Northport
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: And really, if you played Borderlands 1 and played all the DLC in it, you know it's going to be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that the DLC will be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still waiting to hear on how it goes and maybe I'll have to plunk down the $30 for a season pass.
[SPEAKER_03]: XCOM Enemy Unknown
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a pretty nifty Easter egg in the game that allows you to bring in super soldiers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can put in certain names and they activate XCOM heroes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: For some reason, it makes me think of NBA Jam when you could put in certain combinations that would unlock Bill Clinton and Scorpion and shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the type of people you can unlock here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sid Meier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ken Levine I think that's awesome that they put Sid Meier in there Joe Kelly and Otto Zander are apparently all super soldiers so far apparently the one little trick to it is that once you summon the heroes the achievements are turned off so if you want to go for achievements don't use this little cheat but maybe once you've beat the game and got the achievements you want go back and play as Sid Meier for the lols
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: he's teamed up with an animator friend to make Street Fighter 3 for Inkazon it's a fan flick and it looks really really nice especially in these little posters it looks like even better than like I don't like Frankenweenie or one of those movies that's like in theaters it's a really neat art style kind of impressive that it's only these two guys even more impressive that Capcom hasn't shut it down yet but maybe the fact that they are in Brazil makes it complicated
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Much like animals in the real world, Pokemon are treated as unfeeling objects and used for things as human entertainment and as subjects in experiments.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way the Pokemon are stuffed into Pokeballs is similar to how circuses chain elephants inside railroad cars and let them out only to perform confusing and awful painful tricks that were taught using sharp steel-tipped bullhooks and electric shock prods.
[SPEAKER_03]: If PETA existed in UNOVA, our motto would be, Pokemon are not ours to use or abuse.
[SPEAKER_03]: They exist for their own reasons.
[SPEAKER_03]: We believe that this is the message that should be sent to children.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I just want to remind you guys, PETA is clearly trolling with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at that statement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Over half of the statement had nothing to do with the game they were putting out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They used half that statement to talk about the whole circus and the elephants and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: it is all about attention I mean clearly they play Pokemon they understand Pokemon because they know about like the Pokemon world they said if PETA existed in Unova they didn't say if PETA existed in the Pokemon universe or if PETA ruled Nintendo these people know what the fuck they're doing by getting attention congratulations you picked the right week to do it at least if nothing else Alan
[SPEAKER_05]: I played PETA's Cooking Mama game from Thanksgiving, and whoever they contract to do their Shockwave games, some of them are actually kind of good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That almost is the reason why these things are worth covering, because as much as they are troll-y and it's like you just roll your eyes at PETA, they're high-quality trolls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because the Cooking Mama one was how to make like a tofurkey in the like vegan Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, you click and drag the food ingredients.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, this is a pretty well done little shockwave game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember playing on the Genesis ToeJam & Earl?
[SPEAKER_05]: because I do, the sequel, ToeJam & Earl, and Panic on Funkatron are going to hit the PSN and XBLA online stores on November 6th and 7th, respectively.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never played this because I was, at the time, I was at the age where I was really kind of butthurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, it's a 2D side-scrolling platformer, and the original ToeJam & Earl was like an overhead sort of adventure game.
[SPEAKER_05]: and uh so yeah if you're a fan of Toa Jam and Earl and want some vintage uh Genesis nostalgia pick that up November 6th and 7th uh God of War Ascension which is the next God of War game because you know they're not going to let that franchise die off the demo is going to be in the Total Recall remake the one with Colin whatever his name is um uh that comes out on
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh boy, December 18th.
[SPEAKER_05]: So get the Total Recall Blu-ray Play God of War Ascension.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is going to be the only way to get that demo until four days before the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think like March 8th is when they're putting the demo on PSN and then the game comes out on March 12th of next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the graphics for it, just looking at these screenshots, look really like disgustingly awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very God of War-ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally, the game Injustice Gods Among Us, which I will admit I don't really know much about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's being put out by NetherRealm.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has a DC Comics character in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be Green Arrow, who some people might remember, like, you know, the show Supernatural, which finally ended after, like, 11 seasons that had Green Arrow in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Green Arrow I think that's best known.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, Supernatural's not done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still on the air, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I meant Smallville.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smallville, Superman.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now there's an Arrow series on CW.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either it just started last week or it's starting this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, is it a spinoff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it the same actor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think they're trying to make Smallville lightning strike twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, Green Arrow is going to be a character in Injustice Gods Among Us.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, it's the Justice League outfit, I believe, from the Cartoon Network show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shayna Linko in chat says, different actor, sadly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, that's just unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, Tigerclaw in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to go back to the PETA thing for a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, they're delayed, so sometimes it takes time for them to comment on things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tigerclaw in chat says, I wonder what PETA thinks of Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't they hate the fact that you play as animals eating other animals?
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, this is proof that they're trolling because, you know, obviously Tokyo Jungle is the game to take issue with, but they know that Tokyo Jungle is a niche thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one care about Tokyo Jungle, but what's a game that everybody talks about?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I'm giving this story far too much attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to address that comment because it was worth commenting on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they really have a problem with people or with animals eating other animals because that just happens in the wild, but as long as it's not people eating other animals, that's really the issue there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So by that logic, would they be okay with people eating other people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because they're only for the ethical treatment of animals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing about people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just wanted to make sure that was clear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, pet doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a people for the ethical treatment of people.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the foundation we really... I sound like such an asshole because it sounds like I'm saying fuck animals and that's not really what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think we should have a... What about how we treat each other?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that important as well?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, giving it far too much credit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what deserves more credit on our show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our Facebook and Google Plus fan communities.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Foogle question of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take Facebook and Google and put it together and you get Foogle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the question of the week this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of a little play on the fact that I've been on vacation for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody's done it at some point in their life or another.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is the worst thing you've missed in real life so you can stay at home and play a video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did work get in the way of a Final Fantasy launch?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you stay at home to raid on World of Warcraft instead of going to your friend's birthday party?
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me, hiccup, bad time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Worst nightmare for a radio person.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you stay home to raid on World of Warcraft instead of going to your friend's birthday party?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to some of the answers on Google, starting with Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't recall missing anything serious for a video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have come close, though, like almost missing class to get a Dreamcast on Black Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, I'm from Mexico and we don't have Thanksgiving here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sean F replied on Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, there are people on Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to say that every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And said, I wish I had a terrible secret to reveal, but I think the worst I ever did was I took the day off in 2005 when I got a PSP at midnight release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wipe out pure and luminous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Indeed, good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to Facebook and get some answers to the question there in our Facebook community.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting off with
[SPEAKER_03]: Critical Myth says, I've been far more likely to miss things like company Christmas parties to see Lord of the Rings premieres, but a friend of mine skipped his own performance review to stand in line for the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: He still got promoted.
[SPEAKER_03]: skipped his performance review at work to get a 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a pretty good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: He must have known he was going to get a good review and could get away with murder with his boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Degenerated Johnny, excuse me, says, I was leading my first raid in Molten Core during Vanilla WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, the raid was during the time I was supposed to pick my mother up from the airport.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was coming back from a trip to her homeland of Scotland.
[SPEAKER_03]: This resulted with her being stuck at the airport for two hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if it was through force, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Haseo Summer...
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me, sorry guys, the voice is going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haseo Sumiragawa says,
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Tetsuya says, I actually skipped school the day I got the original PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ironically, ran into my high school tutor at the time, who didn't seem to mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I did graduate.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, Chiggers on Facebook says, never happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: In real life is always more important than a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game will always be there, but real life experience only happens once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh you, what a party pooper answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's something we probably should remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody in here with a story to share?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the worst thing you skipped out on in real life to play a video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did some all-nighters when I was in high school where I just didn't go to bed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just played a game and then when it was time to go to school, I went to school because when you're 16, 17, you can do that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your body's like, fine, I'll be up for, you know, 36 hours until eventually you can crash.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as far as missing, I mean, when the PS2 came out, I went to bed at like 8 in the evening, got up at 1 or 2 in the morning,
[SPEAKER_05]: I walked, I think, two or three miles to Target, got in line at Target at like 4 a.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was already a line.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got PS2, I think, 38 out of 43, so my timing couldn't have been any more flawless from wanting to actually avoid camping the entire night out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I went into work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once I actually bought the thing, I think I was in the office by, I want to say, 10 or 11 in the morning, but I already cleared it with my boss the night before, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never done anything that scandalous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really think I've taken it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have I taken a day off work to play a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: If I did, I honestly do not remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: I took a day off work to play World of Warcraft but to be fair I ended up having a Disneyland trip and I would have taken the day off anyway but I guess my real answer would be that I cut a lot of class in college to play Final Fantasy 7 it was real good and I was really into it I was more into it than some of my classes I had at the time
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I skipped work while I took time off for, um, Grand Theft Auto, well, recently it was, well, actually it wasn't that recent, but Grand Theft Auto 4, uh, to try to get 100% on everything so I could get the keys to the city.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I technically did within the time frame that they had in the whole contest thing, but they only had a limited amount of keys and it wasn't registering the information correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a huge delay, so I unfortunately didn't get the keys to the city, but, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I got the achievement for 100% though I took time off work when Final Fantasy XI came out I remember that, I was so jazzed for that game I totally took the day off when that came out too That was years ago I didn't skip work, I just took the day off So I guess it's not as bad if you planned it in advance, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd probably take the day off work for Grand Theft Auto V
[SPEAKER_04]: in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: Planning for 2013.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we have some more news stories for you guys and then we'll get your Skype calls here in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so there's this new patent from Sony for a controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, at least in the diagram, it shows a PlayStation Move controller, but apparently it's a controller that allows the user to feel temperature change.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, for example, the controller could get hotter, like if your gun overheats or you get hit by a fireball or you're in an area where there's fire or something like that, or colder, you know, if you're in an icy area or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, um, it kind of like a temperature feedback as well as like, you know, how they have the force feedback and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's necessarily something that they're going to be, um, implementing into a move controller or something like that soon, but, um, you know, it's kind of cool to have this technology around for whenever you may use it in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, for some new controller or something, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it'd be a big deal, like, you know, a controller got cold and went into an icy area.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be kind of, haha, that's neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to leave it cold all the time, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes your hands get sweaty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you should detect whether your hands are sweaty and then cool off.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a third-party company idea right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: If PlayStation had indie games, somebody would release an indie game that's called Hand Warmer.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then the sequel, Hand Freezer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know who needs this technology?
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: When it detects it's getting hot, it gets colder so that the system doesn't crash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or it's just water cool everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it wouldn't be hard for the PlayStation controller to get hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They could just put in there whatever they put in iPhones because the iPhones get really hot if you're using it too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: When it's really straining for a signal, I notice it gets really hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how they could do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they could implement this into the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you piss off Siri by asking a bunch of stupid questions, it'll just melt down into your hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to burn your hand now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wrong answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Punishing games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: This would be something that you'd add to haptics later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's get the haptics thing out of the way first.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think more people would be interested in touching things rather than... Oh, it's cold now.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, actually, challenge number one, getting people to buy the move.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's challenge number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Challenge two, implementing temperature change in there and having people be interested.
[SPEAKER_04]: And seriously, how is temperature change going to come in handy in Just Dance 4 or like...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, archery and sports champions or... Maybe this is why the last Guardian got delayed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe he's guarding temperature.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's because it's going to be a launch title on another system or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, or maybe it's nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's just somebody had the idea and it was like, you know what, let's patent it just in case Nintendo's thinking of something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is an interesting little rumor that's going around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it with a grain of salt because it's spawned from a NeoGAF post, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes where there's smoke, there's fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes, rumor is, Shigeru Miyamoto is expected to leave Nintendo's EAD division by December.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many times has this rumor been around?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, there was another rumor that he, this was like a couple months ago, that it was the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: A major shift in Kyoto development sources involving three research and development buildings New groups and new producers being announced for EAD Kyoto and SPD Kyoto A Tokyo expansion of EAD and Mashihiro Sakurai possibly joining EAD Tokyo New division led by Miyamoto with younger staff focused on smaller scale games
[SPEAKER_03]: Miyamoto's departure inspiring new IPs for the EAD Kyoto division and Cliffy B going to EAD Tokyo I added the last one myself I added that one myself I was just waiting for Cliffy B come on I had to throw my own wank on there too why not everybody else is maybe that's a list list Nintendo wank best Nintendo wank come on let's make up a Nintendo rumor come on come on Alan make up a Nintendo rumor
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii U will use points like XBLA and have DRM.
Yeah, see?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh... Nintendo Wank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh... Ugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, this is tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's tough to come up with something stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: People pull this shit out of their ass all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, but I have to be selective when I pull out of my ass to make it sound a little bit more legitimate than the other people that pull stuff out of their ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I was giving it some thought there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Loki, the man who works for the distributor, what is Nintendo going to do next?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you posting?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to fake another shortage on the goddamn Wii U system to create an artificial demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, did you hear what... No, this actually didn't make our show, but did you hear what their fucking excuse was?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a fire in a production plant, and I guess that lowered their amount of units that they're going to put out by like a million or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that the same excuse they used for the gasoline prices going up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there was a fire in a production plant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goddamn, we used... We're there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do we store them next to the oil?
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Alpha Cananigram and Chat wants to remind me they did get rid of the points because the Nintendo 3DS eShop does use regular money for currency.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they got rid of those cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what they're going to do?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a Nintendo rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their online integration is going to be really mediocre.
[SPEAKER_04]: These aren't rumors!
[SPEAKER_04]: 3DS Micro.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's small enough to fit in your pocket now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to take inspiration from Apple, they're going to make their next 3DS super wide so they can have yet another attachment for the stupid... Have you seen the LL and XL?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you seen the... I was like, okay, we made it bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could have put a thumb pad here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, we're going to have an even larger thing that's going to attach to it and make it even wider than it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that really happening?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it's really happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it out yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's coming out in Japan if it's not out already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like this is an official thing because, you know, you want the larger thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, it's just  let me just add another, like, half of a laptop right here, and I'll put just a giant, like, analog.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, make a project.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have this analog stick that's just, like, the size of my hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll look like that Tetris game at Golf Land with the gigantic joystick that you use to move the pieces.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you seen that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sega Tetris?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised no one's actually sold one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a home thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, do you have some legitimate news for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Kickstarter, everyone's favorite controversial crowdsource.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said legitimate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going live in the UK on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a part of the same site.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is not going to be some Kickstarter-UK.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're within the UK, you can now put up your project online.
[SPEAKER_05]: obviously the currency available is going to be listed in pounds doesn't say anything about euros here yeah you can set your goal and your stretch goals and I imagine if you're in the US and you want you see something awesome over in the UK you can bid on it like you can any other Kickstarter but yeah they got the payment and the those sketchy you know legal financial stuff sorted out so yay UK you're getting Kickstarter sure they're all very excited that's all I got there you go
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they got their legal stuff worked out, but there was already, you know, the other... So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun getting addicted to Kickstarter or hating on it or whatever side of the fence you choose to be on.
[SPEAKER_03]: As diverse as we are on this show, have fun with that, UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Borderlands sold a lot of copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many copies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1.4 million copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a success.
[SPEAKER_04]: 60 bucks a pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, also that I believe it sold, I can't remember what percent, 234% more than the first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So at launch, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not so awesome, NBA Baller Beats, which sold 3000 copies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean there wasn't a market for basketball and music fusion games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Basketball, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basketball, you know, it's a Kinect game that requires you to have a floor that you're not in an apartment and that the floor is like hardwood or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the ironic twist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's a collector's item when it sells that few copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like saying that the Eye of Judgment is a collector's item.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of is in a way.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Borderlands, that is only hard copies of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this is saying digital distribution is not in that figure at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's even more awesome for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, the digital version of NBA Baller Beats doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can't use that to inflate the numbers there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com wants to remind us NBA Baller Beats had 50,000 Twitter followers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that whole thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: So how did they only sell 3,000 copies of the game with 50,000 Twitter followers?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you mean to tell me they had fake Twitter followers?
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't 50,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was 500,000 Twitter followers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's 500,000 because I think they have 100,000 for Call of Duty Black Ops 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, they bought their Twitter followers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean to tell me that they bought all those Twitter followers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was an article in the Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: 449,631 followers and they sold 3,000 copies of the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because all those guys are really legit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's great is even after all that they're like, we didn't buy those followers.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, people are really excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what game sold better than NBA Baller Beats?
[SPEAKER_03]: President Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Eye of Judgment The Eye of Judgment Sold better than NBA Baller Beats Oh, I feel like this is a game on like the $25,000 pyramid or something Or Family Feud or something Name a game that sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats Ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Go Barbie Horse Adventures 2
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not yet, but we will hit that mark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bungie Ferret Tossing will sell better than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tokyo Jungle will sell more than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sure it already has.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Secrets of the Mystical Unicorn, the game with the pink anus on Steam, has probably sold more than 3,000 copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think what was the worst game I can think of that's a paid game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worst game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Night Trap sold more than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say Bullet Witch sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Master Chu and the Drunk Nard Who on the NES probably sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, even like Steel Battalion, that last one that came out, sold more than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The $400 Xbox game?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was fucking broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Beatmania sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, burn!
[SPEAKER_03]: Poppin' Music on Xbox Live Arcade, or what was it called?
[SPEAKER_03]: Beat and Groovy sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guccigucci
[SPEAKER_03]: Gucci Gucci hold on I want to look this up hold on it was just it was just the single yeah please don't play it do you really hate your listeners that much um no it was don't ask it was just a single last year but she actually put out a full album with that song and no one gave a fuck but more people gave a fuck okay so more people gave a fuck about this song no no not oh that's not it sorry it's uh oh this one yeah okay more people bought this cd than bought baller beats
[SPEAKER_00]: Outro Music
This is really bad.
This is too long.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where's the chorus?
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't make it to the chorus.
[SPEAKER_00]: You probably picked the worst part of the song to... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you go, the worst part of the worst song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Worst part of the worst song.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, and DarkSakura says that song was probably in NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, Actdeft says more people bought E.T.
[SPEAKER_03]: on the 2600 than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jessica Harper said Britney's dance beat probably sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, burn.
[SPEAKER_03]: This, oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rock Revolution sold more copies than NBA Baller Beats.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a fact.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you win.
[SPEAKER_03]: You win in internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: This story's over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Marissa.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she just said, this bitch just rapped about Adderall.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, does this still work?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to point this out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Marissa to know this because this is how bad Marissa needs to come back to the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you know how Google has the predictive search feature, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I want to show you something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go to Google and type Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_03]: Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And oh, yeah, of course, the one time I do it here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm not doing global research.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I swear to God, I did this the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I typed in Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the predictive search, the number two thing that came up said Orange Lounge Radio, Marissa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not Orange Lounge Radio, Chatroom, Orange Lounge Radio, Loki It was Orange Lounge Radio, Marissa Swear to God I was looking at this yesterday and I was laughing my ass off In a good way because I love Marissa But it's just funny that how long ago was it she was on this show?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: An appropriate story to follow that last story is about a game design jam called Fuck This Jam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who is putting this on?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on a website.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called fuckthisjam.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's appropriate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's organized by Rami Ismail of Vlambeer and independent designer Fernando Romalo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck This Jam apparently was basically an inside joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out of a conversation that they had when they went to an arcade in Austin, Texas.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will take place from November 9th through the 17th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, why would you care about this besides the cute name?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: The participants in this little contest or whatever, they will be tasked with creating a game in a genre or style that you would ordinarily have disdain for.
[SPEAKER_03]: So in other words, let's say you're the type of person that's like, you know what, I hate sports games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I don't want to play sports.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never play sports games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then your job in the jam would be to design a sports game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or let's say, you know, I hate first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got to design a first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate retro games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate role-playing games.
[SPEAKER_03]: so I actually think this is a really neat idea to encourage people to get out of their comfort zones because this is where some of the best ideas come from and you know it's going to lend itself to crossover potential I bet something out of this ends up on Project Greenlight or something just you wait just you wait good luck to everybody that's participating in that fuck this jam
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we pick our favorites out of the mailbag and read them live on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura is not here to read them tonight, but Alan, being such a good sport, has volunteered to read the emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: It probably helped that there was only one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now there's one email, and I really empathize with the person who wrote it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind enough to write it in, because when I write stuff, I'm often very verbose and go on about something I care a lot about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Windows 8 rant email, and this person did say how long it is, and it is long enough that we're not going to read the whole thing on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not personal.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is from...
[SPEAKER_05]: 13x Forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he writes a Windows 8 email and he says, Hello, OLR crew and Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard you have an empty mailbox problem, so I finally took my time to write about that Windows 8 hate show two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, I love that our show is now a relay to Bobby, as well as just like blast us with an email and hope Bobby gets some splash damage from it all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an AoE attack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, all our crew and Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard you have an empty mailbox problem, so I finally took my time to write about that Windows 8 hate show two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, this mail will be long, so maybe you should skip it for the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I have to apologize in advance if I trail off topic or go on Rumble for too long.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, yeah, first of all, I highly recommend to read Paul Allen's take on Windows 8 with a link, interface changes, and Rafael Rivera's post on the Minecraft certification debacle, and optionally, his own rant, or the person who wrote this in, on Google+, on this topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it goes on, and unfortunately we can't read all of it, but he did include, thank you, Ryder, a TLDR summary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Smart idea when you send in a long email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Include the too-long-didn't-read portion.
[SPEAKER_05]: So TLDR summary, you should really try it for yourself before judging.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes to build something new, you have to break something old, and people will hate you for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All of the hate on the internet for Windows 8 stems from a few articles published by ignorant writers to get more clicks for their websites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Desktop experience is the same as for Windows 7, only much more polished, plus you have Metro, which is mostly optional.
[SPEAKER_05]: Notch is fighting some illusory threats of software freedom on commercial OS 2 in most unconventional ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Windows 8 will sell worse than Windows 7 and everyone will point and laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're probably biased Russian neighbor 13x forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm wondering maybe if I'm on the VOG article for when the podcast episode goes up, maybe we can include that email.
[SPEAKER_05]: on the forums, on the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because they've seen some screenshots and they don't like the fact that there's something different.
[SPEAKER_03]: That they're presenting this start menu and it's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, I'm paraphrasing here and this is the message I took from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was essentially, change is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Change is inevitable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Change has to start from somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you like the start menu, didn't the start menu start somewhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: So why is everybody hating on this when many of them haven't tried it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate this, I hate this cause it looks like an Xbox
[SPEAKER_05]: Not Gabe Newell basically said we've messed around with the Windows 8 kit and he was like personally he didn't want to design software for it because he thought it was a big steaming turd.
[SPEAKER_05]: So whenever someone from Valve says something, everyone like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Valve says Windows 8 is garbage and then it just echoes through the whole internet which is not really what they said right yeah that the whole game of telephone happens yeah so interesting now I will say there was also a portion of the email that really addressed the whole Windows certification thing and the fact that I think people are reading too much into it and it's not that Microsoft that was a huge part of what yeah the Valve complaint was too so
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to be clear, it's not that Microsoft wants a cut of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that Microsoft wants to certify it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm assuming it's similar to how they might certify.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know because I've done some of this development at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's harder to run macros and even access in Word if you don't certify your content because of the illegitimate stuff that's out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So imagine expanding that bubble to include software.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of where it's going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that kind of like the Nintendo's official CLO quality where they had to play every game even if it was bad to make sure it was good enough?
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't do that anymore because, of course, the Wii is the biggest shovelware console in like 10 years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and also people got around the Nintendo CLO quality.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like it worked for a while, but then when it was because Atari or Tengen, as it was, won that lawsuit where they tried to stop that from happening...
[SPEAKER_03]: They were able to keep Tetris off the shelves because that was a particular circumstance, but they were not able to keep those cartridges off shelves.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember if the lawsuit was Tengen specifically or if it was one of the other companies like Color Dreams or one of them back in the day, but Nintendo tried to stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They lost, so there was nothing they could do about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think at that point, they kind of gave up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, Nintendo put those locks into place because they were trying to prevent another video game crash.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other big, big, big thing they did on the NES, remember this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because a lot of the games on the 2600 weren't even designed on proper development kits.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were trash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, publishers could only put out three games a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you paid for these development kits or whatever, you could only put out three games a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's why, well, you had these publishers start to put out, just invent subsidiaries to get around it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where Ultra Games came from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultra Games was just Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just Konami and it existed solely to put out more Konami games on the NES like Metal Gear and Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles were Ultra Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway...
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a total tangent that that emailer was not expecting at all whatsoever, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So at the end of the day, let's go back, take a step back.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about the course part of the argument?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think what I took away from it was don't knock it until you've tried it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Allen, is it fair?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't tried it, so should you be knocking it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Windows, well, I made a joke once that Windows OSs are like the Star Trek movies, the original ones, that every other one is a piece of shit and the other, every other one is really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because XP Professional, I ran for years because it was rock solid.
[SPEAKER_05]: When Vista came out, they tried to drag gamers over to Vista by saying if you want DirectX 10, you have to use Vista.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, DirectX fine is 9 for me, I'll stay on XP.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now 7 is so fucking good, I can't imagine why I'd want to leave 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: 7's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the bummer is, it's not like you can just try 8 out and then go back or 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't think you can down rev windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's either all in or out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well thank you very much for the email, even if it was a little long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully we covered the points to your satisfaction.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we, you know, either way, we still appreciate the other perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: We get to disagree sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight with your FU?
[SPEAKER_04]: An FU to eMachineshop for their fur I'm not working nicely with Google SketchUp, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wonderful painstaking process of creating the part of the beatgear pad or whatever, it came out nice, so they can't import it at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I tried recreating it in their stupid pad editor, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you know, despite all the stress I went through in the past week, I had a pretty good weekend, so I can't complain too much, although I will say F you to my voice, and F you to the fact that I'm getting old.
[SPEAKER_03]: That part kind of sucks, and yeah, I didn't just do Rocky on Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually helped out with another performance piece that some of the gals on cast asked me to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just play a really quick walk-on roll-in, and I did it, so I had to do that last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is part of that performance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm supposed to die on stage, which means I have to take a stage fall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, totally bruised my knee doing that yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that part sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: So FU to getting old, where my bones are old and frail and I can't take falls like I used to be able to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, your FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things are going pretty well for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a second day off this week, which I wasn't expecting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the apartment's all clean.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate...
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two more stories and then Twitter topics and the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so there's going to be some price discounts pretty soon for the Xbox 360 coming in the form of their holiday bundles.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually going to have two bundles out that are actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one that's going to be the Kinect 4GB bundle, and they have a 250GB just regular bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: for $250 you can get a holiday bundle which is the 250GB Kinect and those are usually $350 and I guess the bundles have different games packed in they've got DLC codes for everything from Forza 4 Kinect Disneyland Adventures Fable 3 Halo Reach and also they're going to have I guess codes for a digital copy of Skyrim I actually saw that in one of them um
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get a 4GB console for $250 or just a regular system without a Kinect bundle in there for $250.
[SPEAKER_04]: That comes with Forza and Skyrim as a digital copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they have a 4GB Kinect bundle that's going to have Kinect Adventures and Kinect Disneyland Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would you buy the old one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know for whatever reason I guess I'm marking down the old bundles in case you know because it doesn't seem very smart to have the old bundle with less stuff in it for the same for you know more than what it is with more stuff in it but apparently they still have the same pricing you can get the holiday bundle without connect Disneyland adventures I guess if you really hate Disney and you just you know fuck it I'm not getting anything extra you do that
[SPEAKER_04]: so those are three bundles that are available I guess now so you can check that out and then some older holiday bundles too they've got one with Halo, Reach, and Fable 3 that was the old one but I guess that's not available anymore cool
[SPEAKER_03]: No surprise there, price drops in time for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for Wii U. Maybe that it's, yeah, true, competition there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And maybe to, you know, just encourage a few more copies to move after Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly though, I mean, if you don't give a shit about Kinect, which honestly nowadays you probably shouldn't give a shit about Kinect, at least this console generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one with Forza 4 and Skyrim is a pretty good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are pretty awesome games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good tip?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, one more story for you guys, and this is about what could have been.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blizzard had once planned a version of Diablo for the Game Boy Color.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you even imagine that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like StarCraft on the N64, you remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo Jr.
[SPEAKER_03]: each packing a different hero in the warrior rogue sorcerer vein as well as items that players would have to trade for in order to collect
[SPEAKER_03]: Development was only with a handful of staff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They started working on Diablo Junior after the release of Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could have been the Game Boy Color or the Game Boy Advance or both, I guess just due to the timing of all of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo Junior was ultimately put out to pasture because of the steep production costs associated with developing handheld games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess there is a book coming out or a project called Stay Awhile and Listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an unauthorized history of Blizzard based on the testimony of 80 ex-employees.
[SPEAKER_03]: This gonna be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, I didn't know somebody was working on something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like it's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, there was also another Diablo 2 expansion that never saw the light of day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was going to have guild halls for multiplayer clan meetings and two other character classes that also came out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: StarCraftGhost
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like this, the unauthorized look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or they're really awesome franchises from the 90s they haven't touched.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Lost Vikings, or Blackthorn, or Rock and Roll Racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't they also do the Shake, Rattle, and Roll?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that Blizzard?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They got more franchises.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Shake, Rattle, and Roll.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who did that?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is more out there than WoW and Diablo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or they could come up with something new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that's a hard to believe concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever Titan is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever Titan is supposed to be a completely unique IP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snake Rattle and Roll was just straight up rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did I think that was Blizzard?
[SPEAKER_03]: Am I really that dumb?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And while we're waiting for some calls to come in, we will do some tweets.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw sending a few tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: See in here I thought it was a slow news week and yet we've got more stories coming in thanks to Twitter so I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw on Twitter with a story EA apparently accidentally gave away thousands of free games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: How the hell did this happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a code that was, I think it was for reviewers or something like that, for Origin, where it gave people $20 off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it said it was a thanks for completing a survey, and it allowed them to download a free game from Origin, but the code could be used by anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an unlimited use code.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm reading it here on the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: The code was not secured.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone made EA lose money.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have to commit seppuku in a conference room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, it ended up on Reddit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect Mass Effect
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, anyway, before the new multiplayer stuff came out and the Omega DLC stuff got announced, Mike, I think it's Gamble, posted something about how the upcoming DLC is kind of like the shape of things to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm wondering if this DLC is kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, pointing at a more massive multiplayer Mass Effect game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go, Mass Effect MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, I'm justifying it, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: with the Volus class apparently it's pretty much just a support class you can still kill things and be really awesome but it's primarily for support so if you've got a support class your vanguards can take hits really well and everybody else can do shooty things why not something in the vein of a PSO style game where you have centralized hubs you can still do massive story missions but
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just all the multiplayer in Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Run this by me again.
[SPEAKER_03]: How is this going to impact the single-player side of it, though, with the expansion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I made a comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: And who knows if the Elcor and the Hanar don't show up sometime down the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see something happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Avolis, I have one if you want to, we can do a match together after the show if you want to see how they play, would be terrible support for a Vanguard because I couldn't stay close enough to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: They can't hop over cover, so they have to actually run around the map.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of adorable in a really weird way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, if a Vanguard biotic charges and fucks off, I'm going to have to run to your ass to refresh your shields and that's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all I do as my Vanguard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just fly around.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you with my Sentinel worked out all right, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_05]: We duoed, what, wave four, wave five?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, now my Sentinel was only level four, so that was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was collectors too, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which are super fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're bastards is what they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Commander Shepard just joined our chat room and said, Hi, I'm Commander Shepard, and this is my favorite Mass Effect podcast on the Citadel.
[SPEAKER_06]: If only.
[SPEAKER_06]: You jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll happen eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there anything non... Well, actually, let me ask you this question because whenever people bring up Mass Effect podcast in chat, Black Wolf likes to chime in and say there's not enough content out there to substantiate a weekly podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lie now, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's totally a lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a cop-out answer because...
[SPEAKER_06]: every like okay there is fan fiction there's fan works like art music there are books that have been out comics that have been out multiplayer updates that come out always speculation going on for the next games you it's there's enough content there for weekly episodes for sure well then you need to produce a pilot sir and prove everybody wrong
[SPEAKER_06]: But how am I supposed to do that and play Pokemon in Mass Effect and WoW?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And watch Once Upon a Time in Walking Dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just gave me an excellent opportunity to transition away from Mass Effect for a minute because you've been playing Pokemon Black 2, White 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know that you are an almost 30-year-old playing Pokemon games.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the original VOG articles was about your love of Pokemon and how you're a little old for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how are the new games and why do you still love this series?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll never not love this series they're just really fun RPGs and the Pokemon for the most part are adorable and who doesn't want to collect adorable things PETA that game was really fun I played it
[SPEAKER_05]: They're good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They contract good programmers.
[SPEAKER_06]: They really are good.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I'm going to see my friends up near Kansas City this weekend, and we're going to have a Pokemon tournament, I was just informed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, oh, heck yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're my age, too, and they're all excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I love this comment from Frisbee in the chat room talking about Shane's Mass Effect podcast, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee says, there's fan fiction, fan art, fan wank, fan dango, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are Skyrim podcasts that are still going just because of all the mods that you can talk about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: BlackWolf says, five weeks in a row.
[SPEAKER_03]: Five weeks in a row.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta have a show that's got five episodes and then...
[SPEAKER_06]: What if I make five episodes in one night and then spread them out over five weeks?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't say that's what you're doing in advance, dummy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would I cheat like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: As I write this down.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else was I going to ask you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yes, with Pokemon, I know you're playing a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's pet battles going for you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have stopped pet battling because I'm trying to level things and get gear.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's like a terrible addiction.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm trying to cut myself off cold turkey at the moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I still think about it every so often.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when somebody posts that they got a new pet, I'm like, I wonder how that would be in battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm just not doing anything with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before we let you go for the night, is there any message you want to give to horde tanks out there that might be listening?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I was going to say anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Glad you brought that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're a horde tank, preferably a paladin or a warrior, and you would like a fun, laid-back raid group that wants to do content while it's current,
[SPEAKER_06]: please please please server transfer to Proudmoore and get a hold of somebody in the guild Malevolence and we'll find you a home and we won't make fun of you much I promise
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else before I let you go?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, except I was very sad because, Alan, you talked about a Kaden and Shepard fanfic I hadn't read yet and I don't know where to find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I can dig it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't have any fix saved to a folder on my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just know what time my user wrote it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have any fix, but I definitely have fun, awesome pictures I found that aren't porn, so I have to make that distinction before it gets a lot out of hand.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as no genitalia is showing, it's not porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there isn't, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's none whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would be weird anyway to have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm ending this conversation before it gets awkward.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep it awkward.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Use your name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there was another Twitter topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have any last-minute stories, Loki, while I bring this one up?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had the EA one, but somebody took it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody took it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we got another call coming in, so hooray for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ow, my feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, you're calling in to talk about New York Comic Con, I bet.
[SPEAKER_01]: More or less, I was actually calling in to kind of agree with the whole pirating thing, because even in my fandom, we have to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We call the people that bootleg the anime and stuff, we call them spoiled entitlement bitches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, and just because they're spoiled and entitled?
[SPEAKER_01]: They feel that because it comes out in Japan, they can download the fan subs and watch all the episodes and decide not to buy it when it comes released here because they feel that, I already have it, why should I go out and buy it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can feel that because I was about to say when you started your thought, I was like, oh, because I was kind of like that for a while because like I and I've admitted to this in the show in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have downloaded games that were released in Japan only because I feel if the game companies aren't going to bother.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've also done it with games that were only put out in Europe before they were announced for the America.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm guilty of doing that too
[SPEAKER_03]: And when they release the American versions of DDR, I buy every single one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So did I. So, you know, to be fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's a little different than your scenario because you're saying they watch it and then when they release it in America, the Americanized version, or I mean, I guess not really the Americanized version, but the, you know, whatever they end up putting out here, they fuck off.
[SPEAKER_01]: but also on the same token they do it because they can and let's say the series just comes out in the US and the DVDs are like 40 bucks for an entire box set people will go and buy that 40 dollar box set, rip the episodes and put them online they'll even put the full disc online and people will find them and download them because they can well and that's the same thing with games right some pirates do it because they can
[SPEAKER_01]: and it's like I said if Halo 4 comes out at $19.99 it'll still be pirated because they want to save that $20 and that same person that doesn't want to drop $19.99 on a game will go buy a spindle of blanks to spread to make copies to give to their friends what's this comment you just made in chat Alan that's somewhat on topic with all this
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I was just saying, back in the late 90s, early 2000s, I used to order fan subs from anime all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's what he's talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Specifically Sailor Moon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, partially, and it's become where the companies will contact the fan servers and ask them not to continue with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of them will be like, sure, no problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of them are like, you know what, fuck you, we're going to continue to fan sub it because we do a better job than you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, a lot of times when a fan subber got a cease and desist, that was great news for the community because the only reason why the company was doing that is because we bought the rights to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out next year and then the community would be happy because, yay, they were finally getting it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, um, Alan, to also go with that, same thing happened when Fullmetal Alchemist came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Since Square Enix pretty much helped put it out in Japan, when Funimation picked it up, Square Enix told them, you gotta translate this pretty much word for word.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't mishap anything here or there.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're working on it, sending out the CNDs to all the fansubbers, telling them, oh, they can't do this.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're like, sure, why?
[SPEAKER_01]: or Leo will step back some of those fansubbers will go behind their backs and continue fansubbing the series under a different title and a CND goes to them and so on and so forth and so forth well Ranma I don't want to burn all the time talking about Piracy well no it's fine it's a good conversation but I want to hear about a New York Comic Con because I hear Travis was there too and Critical Myth I think was there too I didn't see Critical Myth but I did run into the one and only Travis Donovan
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that the first time you met him?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: He freaked the fuck out when I walked up to him with my big old afro.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what did you do and see in New York Comic Con?
[SPEAKER_03]: What was there to do?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mostly went for the cosplays.
[SPEAKER_01]: The exhibition hall was ginormous.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a few indie games there, but big games that were there was the Capcom booth showing off Darkstalkers Resurrection, and then there was the Halo 4 booth, and then further down there was Square Enix's new Tomb Raider game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow, I didn't realize they were going to be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And unfortunately, I wasn't able to check out any of these games because Comic-Con decided to give just me press and the rest of my staffers no press access at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and the lines were like three and four hours long.
[SPEAKER_01]: I couldn't even get up in there time to try out the Wii U. Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll just try to get over to Nintendo World later this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: well since I know you're all about the cosplay which I know the listeners can hear more about on Anime Jam Session Tuesday nights on VOG what was some of the good cosplay you saw?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, believe it or not, I've seen some pretty good My Little Pony cosplays.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Comic-Con is just comics, manga, pop culture, everything all together.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what it's come down to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I did see a couple of good Master Chief cosplays running around, but one of the most popular one was Scott Pilgrim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: BlackWolfInChat says Ranma's met two VOG people for the first time in the span of a month because you met Bobby last month, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, when I finally got to the hotel and rested up he shows up in his awesome car and we head on over to Waffle House and chilled As long as I'm still your favorite Oh, you know that
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and then Travis is going to make you take that back on his show later on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that always the case, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: PAX East is coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, one thing we didn't bring up on tonight's show, I just realized, but we should probably address.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could talk about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: PAX East badges went on sale, and then we can mention, oh, but they're already gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get me started on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am so pissed and aggravated about that whole situation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't you get a ticket?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, my brother got me a ticket.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when I got home, I got Jovi's ticket.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got her a Friday, Saturday, Sunday badge.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the only way.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the people behind PAX let people buy as many badges as they want.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they went directly to eBay.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why the three-day ticket sold out in 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to go, I'm telling you, you better get a Friday, Saturday, Sunday because I don't know about you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think you want to go on eBay and try to drop three bills on a three-day badge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really couldn't have happened on a worse week for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't buy a badge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am crossing my fingers and toes that our existence can justify at least one media pass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be more than happy to interview developers and have VOG articles and coverage on the shows and YouTubes and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just hopefully that'll work out because otherwise I ain't going.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this was just like after I spent a disgusting amount of money on Rocky Horror.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just ask Alan, although it might be a little bit of a stressful point.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I spent a lot of money on that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I didn't have money for badges.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob, I understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rocky Horror, that's your fandom.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's your baby.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's your pride and joy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't say anything about that because if it was something of a hobby of mine like that, I would have done the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've spent a lot of money on VOG too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these podcasts have a lot of
[SPEAKER_03]: That is so weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So weird, but all right, it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ain't my con.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good con.
[SPEAKER_03]: When the con gets here, everybody that gets to go will have a good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: BlizzCon ain't any better with the way they do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, the most important part is the fact that I secured two rooms for everybody so we have a place to stay.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was the most important thing, and we got hotel space from Thursday to Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you're the bomb.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm able to get a media badge, I'm going to be like, right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And in that case, when you come down, me and Jovi will head on over to the airport and pick you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you're the bestest.
[SPEAKER_01]: We try.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I should let you go so we can go wrap the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, take care, bro.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, Ranma's got my back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm his favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: We already established this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take that, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby's going to be at PAX, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know he's going, so who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Then that's kind of cool, because since PAX Prime is the same weekend as DragonCon, at least we get to have a little bit of PAX in our lives.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I shouldn't say that PAX East is less than PAX Prime.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the timing of PAX Prime with the exception of the fact that it's the same weekend as DragonCon I like the timing of PAX Prime a little more than PAX East but I know we'll have a good time at PAX East
[SPEAKER_03]: If I get to go Anyhow, I think that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight Because those were some long calls But thank you guys so much To those that called in If for whatever reason you weren't able to get through tonight Do send us an email Because we're always short on emails Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com One more Twitter topic here I want to read about And it has to do with Wing Commander So it's worth mentioning
[SPEAKER_03]: Weren't you a fan of Wing Commander back in the day, Alan?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know I was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is another tweet from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wing Commander and Privateer creator Chris Roberts announced a new game called Star Citizen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't we talk about this earlier?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot about it if we did.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think we talked about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was on Bobby's show at the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it wasn't on our show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, then I'm saying it twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Wing Commander.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Star Citizen from Chris Roberts is happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a crowdfunded game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it's already raised $455,000 with the crowdfunding.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's probably going to make at least a million.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can look for the return of Wing Commander, even though it's not called Wing Commander.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's from the same guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And obviously it has a spaceship-based name.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be the next evolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: of that series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully it will turn out better than the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I almost backed that Obsidian one and then I realized that the game's not coming out until 2014, so I was like, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a long way away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not gonna wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that wraps up.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have no other stories for us, Alan, I don't know if you have anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have any links or anything, but I have something quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who are in my age group who remember a show called Syphil and Ollie on MTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're back, and they're on the Machinima channel reviewing fake video games, and it's like they never left.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't, because I think this happened a couple weeks ago when the first one showed up, and I don't remember if we brought it up on the show or what, but yes, it is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because in the mid and late 90s, MTV did stop showing a lot of music videos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Siflinali
[SPEAKER_05]: and yeah, they're back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Liam, the guy who invented them and wrote them and does the voices was on the Nerdist podcast and he was talking, Chris Hardwick was like, I wish the Nerdist channel had snagged him up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, he's on, Sifl and Ollie are on Machinima.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're good for lulls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, episode one has 92,000 views.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys who tuned in and support Orange Lounge Radio tonight, whether it be through the podcast or on Stitcher or wherever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you're tuning in live, a big thank you for sticking through all the upsies and downsies of the stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like we've been okay for the past hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: People stopped complaining in part B, so I guess it was just for 30 minutes there or so where it was a little rough.
[SPEAKER_03]: But thank you guys for sticking with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really appreciate you guys, your troopers.
[SPEAKER_03]: if you like what you hear here at Orange Launch Radio remember we don't ask for your money to do this shit all we ask is help spread the word about Orange Launch Radio tell a friend or two or leave us a nice review on something like iTunes or a recommendation on Stitcher or TuneIn or any other site wherever you heard of this show there are plenty of other people looking for something like this so word of mouth is great
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan, as always, thank you for pinch-hitting his host tonight, especially on such short notice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Glad we could have you on, even if you do live here and you usually get picked on anyway, but you're always great to have on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have a final thought for listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm on a nap.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't nap at 9 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's called going to bed.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's called going to bed and then you're like a senior citizen.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to go to IHOP and get a senior citizen special?
[SPEAKER_03]: One piece of bacon and a pancake?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess an under sedation person after Rocky on Friday was asking Jessica where the big after party was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Denny's, you know, we're going to get coffee and chicken strips.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's like remember when we were all 23?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, actually, you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_03]: I got invited to go to Mel's by one of the cast members and I was like, I'm sorry, I gotta go home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because everyone else on cast is like 20.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our whole lives are ahead of us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's stay until four.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully play some Borderlands 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: my final thought is hopefully I'll play something besides WoW and Mass Effect this week not that those are bad games but also my other final thought is it is nice to finally be honored with the Golden Lotus damn you dailies damn you dailies alright
[SPEAKER_03]: thank you guys so much for listening to our show we really appreciate you guys let's all hope Jamie feels better and she'll be back next week that would be fantastic and we hope all you guys will come back next week as well be safe don't be a dick online treat each other with respect have a wonderful week good night
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_02]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week!