[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, October 7th, 2012, Sony sues a former spokesman, cheating allegations emerge in the playoffs of one PC game competition, and could pornography be on the way to the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet, and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Orange Lounge Radio with this episode number 476 for October the 7th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you happen to be listening to us live at the Voice of Geeks Network, head on over to our chatroom, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're listening to us on the podcast feed or via Stitcher or some other type of smartphone application...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's cool too, but please pencil us in some time for a live show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do tape Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are here to talk about video games and all that good stuff with myself, Rob Roberts, and my co-host tonight here, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, it was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did a lot of non-gaming stuff, like mowing the backyard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn that real life stuff!
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it all!
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been putting it off for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, once the weather gets cooler, then I'll do it, and then finally the weather got cooler, so I had to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, now before the chat room starts conspiracy theories, you'll notice I did not introduce DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do love DarkSakura, but she is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: She ditched our ass to go hang with gays at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, can you blame her, let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is the happiest place on earth after all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she is wrapping up her trip at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: She should be back for the next live show.
[SPEAKER_05]: No sub co-host tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan's usually our standby co-host.
[SPEAKER_05]: He had to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put a call out on Twitter, but I was a little late in doing that because I've been a little bit busy too with some other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's just Loki and I here in studio with you guys in the chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: The always present fourth guest on our show, or I guess tonight, third guest on our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf in our chat says, I can blame her, just like I blame Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: What am I being blamed for?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess Bobby does not want to go to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did perhaps you introduce Jamie to the love of Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, it was the other way around.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she was the dealer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, in this case, Jamie was the dealer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember the OLR lesbians, Chris and Meg Zee?
[SPEAKER_05]: Big giant pyramid scheme.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Who started Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that me or was that you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was kind of you on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think we were both on Xbox and then I decided to do the PC version and then unfortunately it was just downhill from there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: The officially recognized gayest place on earth would be San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, it's just today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would argue the gayest place on earth is a Scissor Sisters concert in West Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, that's one of those temporary designations.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas any other time it goes back to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: There actually is, if I remember right, in New York New York listeners, help me out here But right off of Christopher Street, which I recall is the gay district there There is a street called Gay Street
[SPEAKER_05]: If I remember right.
[SPEAKER_05]: New York listeners, correct me if I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there's several of you listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in our chat room at chat.live.vognetwork.com You have one home for so many years, it's hard to beat it out of your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brad from PodCultures in our chat saying, Rob Roberts, so Disney and games are social diseases now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now let's not call it a disease.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe just their distractions.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what Ranma confirming for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, there is a gay street over in the West Village.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if she was rich enough, she would totally be buying that replica Haunted Mansion that they have.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is that all about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a four-story actual replica?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a replica, except when they show the inside, I'm like, that doesn't look like the Haunted Mansion at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't resemble anything that I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember there being a nice kitchen set and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it's not the Nightmare Before Christmas version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Haunted Mansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Nightmare Before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the Ikea version.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's unfortunately a whole other nightmare there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before we get to our gaming weeks, we always like to start off with a kickoff topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got to tell you, I'm kind of in the same boat as Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've both been very busy lately just with other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know specifically what Loki's had going on, but I know here locally, I am working very hard with...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other people you might know actually, Jessica Harper from Understation Lives, Saturday nights here at VOG Network is a big part of this too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're trying to bring the Rocky Horror Picture Show back to Sacramento, which to take a trip down memory lane, I've been involved with Rocky Horror since like 98.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the first internet radio show I was on after my college radio shtick was Under Station Live, which was born of Rocky Horror.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can kind of thank Rocky Horror for getting me into internet radio in the first place in a roundabout way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's finally coming back to Sacramento and oh my gosh, it has been a lot, a lot of work and a lot of money and a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know, it's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really can't wait for the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it does kind of cut into the gaming time a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you've had the same experience with the stuff you've had going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I only did the lawn mowing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was like two hours of today and that was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest of the week it hasn't been any of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show is Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you happen to be in Northern California, I urge you to check it out in Sacramento at the Colonial Theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: 10 o'clock on Friday, October 12th is the big show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm hosting it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it will be a very crazy, different side of me than what you see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even worse than Horde House.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's all I'm going to say about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, if you're local, please come see the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: But after that, I will finally have some time to get caught up on a few things that I've been neglecting, like VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: and video games, playing games and things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just around the right season for Halloween and scary games and things of that sort going on, which I thought we could talk a little bit about scary video games and games, you know, seasonal Halloween games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Loki, do you ever play scary games that actually scare you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I know you maybe don't want to admit this, but do you ever play, like, scary video games that actually make you scared, legit scared?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, I honestly don't really play any scary games because I don't have a lot of time for that stuff, let alone time to turn off lights and play a scary game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really into Silent Hill, which is fine because all the Silent Hills nowadays are kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember, though, speaking of Silent Hill, I remember when you and I were living together a while ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: This has been, like, in the early days of OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was right when Silent Hill 4, The Room, was new.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was playing through that one night, and I legit got scared.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I, like, screamed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I let out, like, this total, like, girl scream.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because something really scary happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I walked into a room, and there was, like, one of those two-headed baby monsters was coming right at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, ah!
[SPEAKER_05]: and you're sitting over there playing Final Fantasy XI or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just kind of look over like, what the hell's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your response was classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were being highly insensitive and it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Locopoco in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says scariest game ever Spice World see everybody's going for the what's your favorite scary movie showgirls they're going for that answer Spice World is one of the most hilarious video games ever I could tell another story about that but I won't about friends playing that game and just laughing and laughing and laughing a lot
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the bus has the same technology as the TARDIS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot bigger on the inside than it actually is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a British thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the secrets that the British folks have figured out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares about physics?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it entertaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: WhatUpG in our chat says, when does that new Silent Hill movie hit and should I see it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's the last weekend of the month, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably near Halloween.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the new Silent Hill game, which is on the Vita, that's been delayed forever and it's finally coming out on the 16th.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably your next Silent Hill bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it looks good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got, what's his name from, I don't know what the hell his name is really, from Game of Thrones.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of, or I should say a lack of scary movies this year, isn't there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because usually we have a Paranormal Activity.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have a Paranormal Activity 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't seen any of those movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's a Paranormal Activity 4, there's Insidious, which apparently is really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's no Saw anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the Saw's done, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hated those movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had... I'm trying to think what else they had.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one... I think it already came out, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one that was... The Chernobyl Diaries.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was supposed to be alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, Paranormal Activity 4...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think what other ones there are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Tetsuya with the save there.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 26th, if I recall correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf with the gaming reference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paranormal Activity 4 apparently uses the Kinect to detect ghosts now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I read something about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotta keep it current.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just in a scene.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane Alinko is in our chatroom saying, the little Goomba-like enemies in Braid freak me out for no reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess sometimes there's certain mobs that are just really creepy looking in video games that might kind of freak you out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe just hits that nerve?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, live.vognetwork.com if you want to comment along with the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish DarkSakura was here so I could ask her about scary games because I know she's played her share of them, but oh well, we'll get her answer next week as we ramp up to Halloween.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about video games we have been playing, what little there may be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I at least have one new game to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what you got, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this week I played Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3, as I normally do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going for what I call Streak Week, which means I won every single game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed it by one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed it by one and by three points.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was just because we were down the plane with only three people, and it was a small map, and it was just one of those games where...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd end up spawning on the opposite side of the map as the other two guys, and they'd get killed, and then they'd spawn the other side by the time I got over there, and it was just back and forth like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So unfortunately, I just wasn't able to rack up enough kills.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't win the game prior to that by quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I usually was doubling or tripling their scores, but I got 16 out of the... What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even 16.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Go up to the chest and move it from the chest or your survival inventory into the chest.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you have to fill it all back up again.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't just open the chest, open the creative inventory or whatever and just drop everything in there that you want, which would be ideal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, stupid ass me actually destroyed my chest and everything in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thankfully to creative mode, I could put it all back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then some.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then...
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of, well, I had, prior to Rob getting on the server, I was hustling to get the giant snowman done, because, you know, the snowman went with the snow golems that were in his house, and the mooshrooms, which my friend put in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, thanks for that, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we wanted, well, originally I was going to have... That was a scary moment in video games, by the way, when I logged into that, and then all of a sudden, and it's like, moo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cows can be kind of scary, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they're changing all the sound effects for those cows soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the next update, they're going to have witches and bats.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a Halloween update, so witches, bats, and some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to have witches' huts, and they're going to redo all the sound effects for things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so Minecraft, I actually did start working on a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitsun's been making this kind of wild network of portals to the nether and stuff so you can walk around the map.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've been... I was dressing up one of those portals because it was near my castle, so I was going to incorporate that into the castle a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just like, maybe I should just expand my castle a little bit more since I was kind of having fun doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try to stay away from making giant spheres in the game because that's a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I did, you know, that snowman was huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I was originally going to have it where you'd step on something and it'd shoot snowballs at you, but it got too tall.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I put arrows in it now, but it still shoots, all it does is shoot the, like, billboard, which is kind of, you know, ridiculous, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: So you built something to actually shoot the ad for Orange Lounge Radio that somebody built in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it wasn't there when I was originally building that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they built it in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there was something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it something on my phone?
[SPEAKER_04]: Vita I downloaded the LittleBigPlanet demo so I haven't gotten a chance to check that out yet but I was going to because I charged my Vita again because I haven't been using it but I do want to pick up I may pick up LittleBigPlanet on that what else what else supposed to get Dishonored soon so I'll have that I don't know if I'm going to play it though it's one of those things I may just sell it I got Resident Evil 6 that's going
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I have not heard good things about Resident Evil 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some people that are talking about it in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few people, I've just been kind of keeping my eye on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people are saying it's really not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard something about a final boss that's kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks very over the top.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, this is something, like, I don't know who any of these characters are, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't follow the series at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just something I haven't gotten into and I don't really want to get into now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dishonored looks alright, so I'm kind of interested in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Modern Warfare, or not Modern Warfare, Black Ops 2 looks interesting, so I'll hopefully check that out once that gets around here.
[SPEAKER_04]: A whole lot of drama with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here come some of the comments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire in chat says, Red and Evil 6 is not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which says to me, it's kind of bad, but it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're a long time fan, maybe you'll put up with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, someone else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Codeman's asking a question about your Minecraft habits in another game that you've talked about before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Codeman says, Loki, have you gotten the Minecraft sniper rifle in Borderlands 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: It shoots Minecraft arrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really bothered to try to play it yet, but it's been a while since I've been playing Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one of the ones I was trying to go back and play this week, but I just didn't get a chance to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Minecraft because I haven't had access to the TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for it to get done with the season.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's on season 5 right now out of 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: When did she start?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that sounds like pretty fast progress to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: God, that show's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just you can totally tell when they switched up the writers because the first two seasons were all right, and then the third season, it got weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the fourth season, it got really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like you've been watching a lot of it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have been just because it's on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've actually watched some of it before, but the fifth season, it's kind of back to how it was before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that was when the writer's strike was or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just really strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, no Medium talk here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: Critical Myth in chat says, Medium is a terrible show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sympathize, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thankfully, I've already spoiled it for my wife.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, she spoils all the books for me anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll probably go back and play some more Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been having fun with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: My coworkers are having fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been trying to figure out plugins that I want to put in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, see, the server that I run can run... It's basically got... It's Multicraft is the front end, and it's got a bunch of different server types you can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do a default.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do, like, a vanilla server, an optimized Minecraft server, then bucket...
[SPEAKER_04]: A bucket server and a bucket beta server.
[SPEAKER_04]: And bucket's basically a server that has plugins in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you can add different bucket plugins to the game to do different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So one of the things I did, which doesn't require bucket, is I enabled Raise Mini Maps, which is actually pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because one of the things that, like, I'd explore the map and I'd get lost.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wouldn't be able to figure out where the hell my, you know, how to get back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than doing a teleport, which I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now I have waypoints and so I know, okay, my house is in that direction.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I know where I'm going and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, one thing I did do in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went back to the village because there's a village with actual villagers around there and their village was terrible because it spawned and
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like doorways that they can't get to so I made them a really terrible looking pink wool house that they can go into and I spawned a bunch of villagers in there and a bunch of these iron golems to defend them against the zombies because all they were doing is like getting eaten by zombies so I had to repopulate.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I'm looking for plugins.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to do the planes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to do the planes, but that requires like Minecraft Forge, and I'm not really sure how to install that on a server that's not really mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't have access to the files that, you know, I think I have to ask them to upgrade, you know, us when the new Minecraft version comes out or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you have to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they do it automatically.
[SPEAKER_04]: so I had to figure that out and I wanted to do the planes would be awesome and maybe the guns I do want to do like a mob arena where we can just set up there's I think a bucket plugin where you set up an area and you can just have it where you fight mobs and then when you die depending on how many mobs you kill you get a reward and you don't really die in the game you don't lose anything but you just die in the arena so it would be kind of cool might set that up that's it
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, I don't want to turn this into the Minecraft show, but I played a little bit of Minecraft as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I logged into the server and promptly got scared like hell as to all that crap that they put in my house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I went outside and I saw on this VOG server they've just built everything around my house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I use this analogy on Bobby's show as well, but it's like you're the one holdout in the neighborhood who won't sell their house.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like that old guy in Up where everything is built around the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: and they're trying to buy your house.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just gonna, I'm gonna bulldoze my house and go somewhere remote.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like I won't ever be able to get back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could build an elaborate rail car unit or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went to an unexplored part on my map that was just due south.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just headed south of all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Codeman in chat says, I got lost looking for Sky's new house.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went south.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's a brick house that's up on a hill that's half finished unless Bobby, I think somebody was threatening to finish it for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't finish... I technically didn't finish this field.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I did was just flatten it out, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's a joke now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't think of anything I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I'll just flatten up this mountain.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure he won't mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I started to build my little brick house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like the idea of being a little bit farther away from all the action outside the city.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my summer home.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was working on that a little bit, but I didn't have a whole lot of time for Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did play a little more World of Warcraft, because obviously the expansion is still pretty great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll leave all my thoughts on that to HordeHouse.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will talk about a new game, however.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new game I want to talk about this week is... Did the stream go down?
[SPEAKER_05]: People in chat are saying it went down.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I show that we're still submitting data, so I don't know what the hell's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The joys of doing live radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we have nothing, like, Alan's not even here tonight, so he's not playing Mass Effect or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's, her computer's not even here because she's not here, so we've got very little data.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well anyway, hopefully you all get back in time to hear me talk about the one game, new game, I did play this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because this is kind of important.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and it was a game from Japan that I think the actual name of it was like Tsukiban Suchaorena Wii or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Tsukiban Suchaorena Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I probably butchered that name a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apologies to Japanese listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that was the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we were looking at pictures of the game, we were like, oh my gosh, this looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like you play as this cat doing these crazy things like driving a car and doing all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're like, where are these games in America?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: where are these new ideas where are these things we haven't seen before that are for the lols and hilarious and we uh started i think we got our listeners to tweet the people that made the game and it caught some of the game bloggers attention like we ended up being on joystick and some of the other sites because of it like you know orange launch radio took it upon themselves to make president cat happen and then there was that whole follow-up article about how
[SPEAKER_05]: Suki Ban Sochao Renowi supposedly only sold 100 copies the week it came out, which I still claim is bullshit and somebody going for a sensationalist headline to this day.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those was mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, Loki bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: If there is ever a time to get President Cat, it is now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The presidential race is on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vote number three, President Cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was 2008 because I remember there was an ad that was poking fun at the Obama Hope campaign.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was 2008 when all that went down.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, the point is, and why I bring that up to Tokyo Jungle, is that here is a game that's kind of that same crazy Japanese idea, but it's actually coming out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the whole trick of it is that humans are gone, it's this world where the animals are basically fighting to survive, because humans are gone, but the cities are still there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the zombie apocalypse happened or something, but animals are still alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get to unfold part about what happened as you play more and more of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you basically select what animal you want to play the game as.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you start with two.
[SPEAKER_05]: You start with one carnivore and one herbivore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can play as a little Pomeranian dog, is the carnivore that you start as.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you can play as some type of deer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a silka deer, I think it's called, or something, is the herbivore that you can start with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: OffCanonogram says it was October 22, 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it wasn't that long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: and TigerClaw says the premise of Tokyo Jungle is similar to that show on the Discovery Channel called Life After People.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and you have to stay out of toxic dumps that could be in the city.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to stay away from all these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have all these meters that are constantly draining.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to stay on top of and make sure are full.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you're trying to complete all these micro goals.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe it's eating and then it's marking your territory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you get to mark your territory in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it's finding a female to mate with and then actually mating with the female.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, Loki, I died laughing the first time that scene happened because you play us as little Pomeranian and we found the little female Pomeranian and went to the little nest and it goes all the way up to the dog getting up on his hind legs mounting the female Pomeranian before it fades to black.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's no thrust, but there's definitely the assume the position.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that made me laugh a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you basically, you'll start the next generation.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in the next generation, you get stats passed down to you based on how you did in the first generation.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the key to maxing out your stats is to continue to mate and get all these stats from having played the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're dead, game over.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all over.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's like Dark Souls level of unforgiving.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is kind of awesome, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of ramps the pressure up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: but I will say this, there is a way you can get more than one life and it is if you breed and you happen to have like four children you'll run around as a little pack and if one of you dies then another can take over but because you're running around in a pack one of your pack might have to be a decoy and take the hit so you don't take the hit so there's all this crap going on that you kind of have to manage I have to say, it's pretty damn fun
[SPEAKER_05]: and you don't really see games like this that are out in America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, is it a perfect game?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes it can get a little frustrating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes it feels a little grindy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was really irritated with the way that you can only save after you breed because it might take you a good 15 minutes to get from one life cycle to another and sometimes I have to quit and save right now and if I don't save properly, my game's gone, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't do anything about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: for $12 it's pretty hard to not appreciate that value there's about like I think something like 30 different animals you can play as and then of course there's DLC if you want to play as more animals but there's crazy shit like panda bears and you know there's all this like funny stuff they even had in Japan they actually had it where one of the creatures you get was a salaryman
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think that happens later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt in our chat says, at live.vognetwork.com, a game where I can pee and have sex with everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sold!
[SPEAKER_05]: uh let's see uh Actdeft says it's Mass Effect with animals not quite because there's really no dialogue and that's kind of the big part about uh Mass Effect um Tigerclaw says when you play as the lions you have to protect the pride pride from rogue lions that are trying to take over yeah that's I mean even when you play as the Pomeranian a beagle might take your ass out in 30 seconds that's how I got killed the first time I'm running around doing my thing and then all of a sudden like a beagle jumps out of nowhere and attacks me and kills me game over
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll probably be on sale even more in a few months.
[SPEAKER_05]: The weird thing is, nobody's really talking about this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to look up reviews online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found like three reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: One great, one average, one negative.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this game is very polarizing, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_05]: but like none of the big sites reviewed it at all and I've hardly read anything about it anywhere so it really sucks that like Sony's like trying this experiment and it might fail due to lack of promotion so I'm just saying everybody I'll use what little podcast we have here if you think you might be interested in this type of game go check out Tokyo Jungle because it's a neat little little gem on the PlayStation Network
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Their audio is really good, so I was really happy to take on these microphones.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I really want to thank them.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are on Monday nights at the Voice of Geeks Network at 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern, and they have done a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brad from PodCulture has done a lot and is very supportive of the projects I've done.
[SPEAKER_05]: He hosts the website for Horde House.
[SPEAKER_05]: He did those decals, or I don't think he did them himself, but he arranged the deal for those decals for Orange Lounge Radio and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm really thankful for all Brad does for the show, so I really want to thank him.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of pod culture and all of the Monday night shows on the Voice of Geeks Network, it is Doctor Who Monday on the Voice of Geeks Network tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three shows all talking about Doctor Who, Critical Myth, British Invaders, and pod culture's special TARDIS Interruptus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doctor Who Doctor Who Doctor Who Doctor Who
[SPEAKER_05]: So I know Critical Myth and Pod Culture, TARDIS Interruptus, both want to kind of take that on a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: British Invaders, which is sandwiched right between the two shows, back-to-back shows on the Voice Geek Networks tomorrow, taking on classic Doctor Who before the Russell T. Davies era, going back to the 60s and 70s.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's a really nice mix of the new and the old tomorrow on VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's what I love.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that that's what this network's all about, is that everybody's got a common theme going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starts at 4 o'clock Pacific, 7 o'clock Eastern with Critical Myth, 5 Pacific, 8 Eastern with British Invaders, 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern with PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if you missed Doctor Who night because you're listening on the podcast feed or what have you, do check out these excellent shows another time on the network another Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they do rerun throughout the week as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also want to plug Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Umlaut season.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Umlaut is the rock band event for charity.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes place at the DNA Lounge in San Francisco every December and the fundraising season is in effect for this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: They still need a couple more bands.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very surprising they didn't sell out as fast as they did last year because...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Tim Schafer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: December 6th, 2012 is the official date at the DNA Lounge in San Francisco Thursday and I bet it's going to be streamed on the internet again just a bet because it was last year so I bet they're going to do it again
[SPEAKER_05]: uh one other thing it's a plug i got a lot tonight what can i say uh it is also awards season in the podcast universe podcast awards and stitcher awards two of them this year uh you can nominate for the podcast award one time at podcastawards.com and we really encourage you to nominate orange lounge radio as your best gaming show uh we would also really encourage you to consider other VOG programming and other independent programming in the other categories
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, TV Movie, there's Critical Myth is a great TV movie show, Sci-Fi, Pod Culture, Mature, Under Station Live, and lots of great, great shows on the network to consider for some of these categories.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I really encourage you to do that at podcastawards.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Stitcher Awards are also having their awards season, and you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: The links are available on our Facebook, and I will also place those links in chat a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you can nominate once a day for the Stitcher Awards so if you want to nominate multiple shows like you want to do oh you're like oh my god there's so many gaming shows I love on the VOG Network I want to nominate them all you can do Orange Sounds Radio one day then Bobby Blackwolf the next day then Girls Gone Wild the next day you know you can kind of cycle through and that'll work so that is available at Stitcher.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and as I was talking about at the end of Bobby Blackwell's show I really think because the iOS 6 podcasting app has not been super well received Stitcher and all this stuff is really the wave of the future along with TuneIn and other types of iOS excuse me not just iOS but Android and mobile phone apps is really the wave of the future so I really encourage you guys to help us kind of be on that cutting edge with the nomination remember we don't ask for your money for this show all we ask is to help us with the word of mouth
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, now we can get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, a lot of announcements tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk a little bit about Cliffy B. He is gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: He decided to leave Epic Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, basically, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's been doing it since he's been a teenager.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said, outside of my sabbatical last year, I've been going nonstop.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know grew up in this business as um you know he says as Mike Capps likes to say and now that I'm growing up it's much or it's time for a much-needed break so cool I'm not sure who else is going to be kind of taking over for some of that stuff now that he's gone but um it's cool to see him kind of get his break because he's definitely been busy with Gears of War
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I've heard a lot of rumors and this is total fanboy wank, but I want to indulge it a little bit at just how wanky this all is.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know which rumor this is, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like where he went or where he's going, who offered to buy him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you heard this?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would be the craziest fanboy company that people hope hired Cliffy B to show how serious they are?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are rumors online that Cliffy B went to Nintendo, which I... You know, obvious fanboy wank.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to indulge it too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can't help yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once the seed is planted in your head, you're like...
[SPEAKER_05]: God, Nintendo really should hire someone like him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it matters, because... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just... I don't know what he would be able to do for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully make another franchise, because seriously, they need some new franchises.
[SPEAKER_05]: Invent a hardcore franchise?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe with some of the Japanese characterization?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'm crazy, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: They've had hardcore franchises at one point, I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sin and Punishment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Sin and Punishment is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Eternal Darkness.
[SPEAKER_05]: But none of that on the Wii U. None of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says Cliffy B did get a letter printed in Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, apparently a lot of people leeching onto that, like, oh, he's always loved Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'd go work for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know if the reason he's quitting Epic Games was because he feels like he needs a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if he's going to jump right into something else right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless he's just making excuses, which is kind of a pussy way of doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, but there's also kind of the right corporate way of doing things, and maybe he's going to take a siesta for a few months until the next E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm leaving because Nintendo said they'll hire me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_05]: Technus in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Cliffy being a Nintendo is a real stretch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be surprised if he went to Microsoft, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little more like, okay, realistic category.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see that happening, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a crazy world.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seg asked a challenging question, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would he benefit from going to Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they offered him houses full of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Cliffy B is kind of a rock star.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've given you a Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: It prints money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, I don't want to buy into the fanboy wank too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not saying I personally believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can definitely see the angle of, shit, you've been doing one thing for 20 years, and maybe you just want to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to go design playgrounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just playgrounds with chainsaws attached to them, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the interesting thing is, the guys at BioWare, the doctors at BioWare, did a very similar thing recently.
[SPEAKER_05]: They left the industry after a very long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of don't think they're going to show up anywhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, you know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to make a game company that's like... Polytron?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you think all these game journalists that left are going to create the League of Super Game Designers and make this company that'll create like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, yeah, there's that Polygon, which did they ever like officially launch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who gives a fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is like the most hipster bullshit, you know, company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we're so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to print articles about, we're going to do a documentary about the creation of our company, our website that's not fucking finished yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one cares about your fucking website.
[SPEAKER_04]: That, I mean, how fucking, you know, snub-nosed, you know, pompous bullshit is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that you're just gonna...
[SPEAKER_05]: create a documentary because you know you all want to know how this happened no one fucking cares are you saying now I you know the views and opinions of Loki do not express those Orange Lounge Radio necessarily so what you're saying is you're really interested in that but but yeah I'm gonna say I'm not gonna touch that with a 10-foot pole are you saying that this site has lost itself up its own asshole before it's even launched yes
[SPEAKER_05]: Just checking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, SSJ100Mad is asking, do they print out game ads in Whole Foods and Trader Joe's?
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, I don't want this to be a shade-throwing competition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, we're going to walk away from this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's talk about the whole idea of the Super Justice League of game developers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you think maybe Cliffy B, BioWare, you know Zynga lost some people this week too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think it could be like the Super League of Mobile Phone Developers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if he went to Apple?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: He would be a pretty cool, like, presenter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because, you know, they need something kind of, you know, with a lot of... Are you saying Tim Cook doesn't have enough energy?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he doesn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, all right, so Cliffy B's leaving, and so we dedicate this to you, Cliffy B.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to something.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've gone from a very American company to something very Japanese, but a lot of you love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Kingdom Hearts 1.5 HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're rolling your eyes over there, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm rolling my eyes at the name.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, just come up with a better fucking name.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1.5 HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's it 1.5?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so glad you asked, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here is how Kingdom Hearts 1 is now Kingdom Hearts 1.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: The screen for each game will rearrange to accommodate for widescreen support including the HUD rearrangement.
[SPEAKER_05]: No reaction.
[SPEAKER_05]: The models for Sora and all his friends have been replaced with ones from Kingdom Hearts Dream Drop Distance, the newest game in the series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trophy support for Kingdom Hearts Final Mix and Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories.
[SPEAKER_05]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you were an achievement whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game mechanics have been updated to make the gameplay feel more like Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, in all reality, that could be a good thing if they fix the camera from the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping that's the hidden message in there without them wanting to admit that the first game had a board camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to admit, that's a little better, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a nice addition, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got something.
[SPEAKER_05]: 70% of the story from 358 slash 2 days will be represented with over 100 new scenes created with full voice acting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh!
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that an admission from Loki that there might be something worthwhile here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's all cutscenes from another game because they didn't want to actually port over 358 slash 2 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm so glad you said something about that because Tetsuya Nomura said he originally wanted to do a full remake of the 358 slash two days, but he didn't have enough time in production to start a project, thus the decision to utilize theater mode to tell the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ran out of time?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an excuse.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just easier to update everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, he was asked in this interview with Famitsu, would Kingdom Hearts 2 get the same treatment?
[SPEAKER_05]: And the response was a laugh and, quote, it'd be unusual if there wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we've already decided that we're doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I bet a lot of it is how well does this first one sell?
[SPEAKER_05]: If this one sells like crazy, then sure, that's a logical conclusion to get to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then they'll do the PSP games on top of it for the next one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Vita?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they'll do the PSP games up-res because just like they did with... Remember, Sony is already on the record saying that they've got a wonderful engine that can port PSP stuff into HD for the PS3, so why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: another quote along the same lines of this whole does this mean there's a 2.5 quote and from Tetsuya Nomura quote I figured there were people who had a hard time keeping up with the sequels we had to start from the beginning with Kingdom Hearts HD I also thought that familiar fans might make new discoveries seeing everything in chronological order with the sequels side by side I'm happy to be restarting this title I don't think it's a problem that people necessarily have problems keeping up with the sequels it's that people can't keep up with the fucking story like
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't Kingdom Hearts supposed to be aimed at kids?
[SPEAKER_05]: The story is crazy convoluted.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even understand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's worse than As the World Turns.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat asks, how can you remake something that isn't that old?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's getting there, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the time this is actually out, 2013 would be about the time frame this is out, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: The first Kingdom Hearts game was, what, 2003, maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: About 10 years?
[SPEAKER_05]: 9 years, maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: They remade God of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or rolled up Resident.
[SPEAKER_05]: Techness in chat says Square Enix is kind of like the honey badger of Japanese developers.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just don't give a fuck and just do whatever they feel like doing today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan Alchemy says you can't argue you have no fucking idea what's going on anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here comes a sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a good idea to have these re-releases because it's most likely ramping up to a Kingdom Hearts 3 or something like that so they're going to put these re-releases out there so people kind of have an idea what the fuck's going on let the hype train begin and get back into it and then go from there well we will see what happens I love this other comment from Alan Alchemy P.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: we made figuring out what the fuck was going on very very hard we know haters make us famous
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haters make us famous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a new service that's going to be coming out from Microsoft, Xbox Music.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to be coming this month and actually launching, I guess, alongside Windows 8, which I'm surprised that so soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's October 26th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares about Windows 8?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go see Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course...
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds very similar to Pandora.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, it's going to be ad-supported, and you'll be able to also use Windows 8, Xbox 360, Windows Phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to tie into Microsoft SkyDrive, and I guess allow you to sync your playlists and music libraries across all the devices and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm glad it's free because, you know, I don't want to have to pay for stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ad support is fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free is good, but I think, you know, because you're talking about Pandora and there's all these other services Xbox already offers that Xbox Music has to be better than that are also free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last.fm is available on the 360. iHeartRadio, which is kind of Clear Channel's little Pandora-esque theme.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can actually listen to over-the-air radio stations with it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think it's logical that they have to kind of put something out free.
[SPEAKER_05]: The subscription model for music isn't really working anymore, which is why I think Apple never ended up doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although maybe Apple can kind of get away with a lot of things that other companies can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll check out Xbox Music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I keep forgetting there is a dashboard update.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're due for one, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably either at the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to guess at the end of this month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it out there so that they can start banning people before Modern Warfare, or not Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep wanting to call it Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Black Ops 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want to get those extra security checks in there before all those big games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: When is Halo 4's release?
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 4 is the 6th and Black Ops 2 is the 13th of November.
[SPEAKER_05]: November.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are in October now, so it'll be like just before Halo 4 maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get to the release date soon enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, something else on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: One company is claiming that they are going to be soon heard on the Xbox 360 and seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the site YouPorn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never heard of this site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you believe that?
[SPEAKER_05]: A pornography site I haven't heard of.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's YouPorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the app on my boxy box.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can see some boxy box on your boxy box?
[SPEAKER_04]: Except they don't ever use it because it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's one of the... I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The boxy box had all these different repositories that you can get and a lot of them were porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I had to download all the porn ones that were free because I'm not paying for fucking porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we checked it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just links to their website.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks exactly the same as the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a streaming website for porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the name implies the YouTube of porn, sort of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they posted an entry to their blog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, I've got to read this from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpha Cananagram in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: at live.vognetwork.com says, Rob, I remember y'all talking about you porn on Guys on a Show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty sure that was the site y'all went to for, quote, Japanese fart girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember things about my life I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: And YouPorn was also the website that we visited on your Wii using the Wii web browser to find pterodactyl porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was PornTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all the fucking same.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyhow, here's the quote from YouPorn's blog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gamers and free porn lovers around the world rejoice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks at long last to the introduction of Internet Explorer for Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can now tap into and stream all your favorite free YouPorn videos right from your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whether you're pwning noobs in Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3, annihilating Bullymong in Borderlands 2, or taking the Saints deep in Madam NFL 13, you're never more than a few simple controller clicks away from being face deep in hot free porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because we all have the internet, so it's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: So all they're really saying is, we can't wait for Internet Explorer on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who says it's going to fucking work with your website anyways?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's Internet Explorer!
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's like, that's not guaranteed to work with anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I would hope that's HTML5, but I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know better than, you know, all these...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, different web browsers for stuff don't necessarily work with the porn sites.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, granted, the PlayStation 3 browser works well with porn sites.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wii browser works well with porn sites.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it is... They kind of have to at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with that news, though, VOG Network is also on your Xbox 360 because...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's HTML5, so it should work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Assuming that Internet Explorer 8 works with HTML5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to be able to code a website to show up like an Xbox channel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or not 8, 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we should make a VOG channel if that's possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it works that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll happen as soon as the new OLR PSP debuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, except the PSP's over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Bobby in chat says it does not stream on the Xbox 360 Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess he's in some developer thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has the XNA thing, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to make it work.
[SPEAKER_05]: The official response from Microsoft, who are quick to distance themselves from this.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be clear, we are adding Internet Explorer to Xbox Live, not specific adult content providers like YouPorn or any other specific website content.
[SPEAKER_05]: Additionally, we give members and parents the option to turn this feature on or off for their accounts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Access to Internet Explorer for all child accounts is blocked by default.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want to get far away from a scandal ASAP And who can blame them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because honestly, you know, if Fox News got a hold of this little spiel here Oh, they've done it with every single console that has a stupid web browser Exactly, and they'd have a It's a porn box, oh, Xbox, triple Xbox I think they've already done that before They'd have a pornography expert on with commentating, you know, whatever
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they've already done that too before with the Windows Media Center streaming or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you used to build these Windows Media Center to view what's on your computer and stream Internet Explorer or Firefox or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good lord, Jason in chat says, not to beat a dead horse, but Rob mentioned you porn in an unprotected six, too, I thought, referencing my old, old YouTube project.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear I have not heard of you porn, although I'm old and I forget things, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some folks in chat, I think, kind of wondering if maybe the Kinect would allow you to make your own porn and you could upload it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think Internet Explorer will allow you to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would look terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: That camera is not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: all right Frisbee in chat says I'm an internet expert and I just found out that boobies are online maybe I'm doing the show topless right now
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, porn, porn, porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: The internet is for porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The internet is for porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, apparently there are cheating allegations in the League of Legends...
[SPEAKER_04]: Playoffs.
[SPEAKER_04]: First you tell me there's boobs on the internet and now you're going to tell me there's cheating?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know!
[SPEAKER_05]: Get the fuck out!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the most ridiculous part of the whole thing is that
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, one of the referees said, we keep a constant watch on all the players on stage at all times.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have cameras as well as live people walking on stage to keep tabs on everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: All players are told that they need to remain sitting facing forward with headphones on at all times, including during pauses.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can confirm that no WE player looked at the minimap at any point during the match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although they have a screenshot showing otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like if you're going to set up a tournament like that, and I didn't watch it live, so I don't know how exactly they're set up, but wouldn't you think that you would put the players in a way that they wouldn't be able to see the mini-map showing the other team?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe so that they can't look at the other team's screen, or they can't look at something that's being broadcast on a giant screen in an arena, wherever the fuck this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, don't give them the opportunity, then you don't have to worry about them fucking, you know, cheating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Little mirrors on the side of my glasses allow me to see behind me and around me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: it's stupid but it's for two million dollars so of course some people are going to try to you know whatever they can do and and there was um you know they were talking a little bit about you know what kind of made them suspect stuff like uh ended up where one team was I guess pinging a spot in the map or whatever where um the other team was and basically there was no way for them to have known that those guys were there but they knew that the players were coming from that direction or something like that so it's like wait a second that's a little weird
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what if it's just that, you know, maybe you kind of read up on the competition and maybe you know their strategies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I know those might be kind of a stretch here, but what if, you know, they just kind of, you know, that's where they wanted to investigate and it was just a coincidence.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, maybe I'm giving it too much credit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be honest, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you have to look at both sides.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't want to just automatically assume everybody's a cheater.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because here's one of the comments.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said Azubu Frost did the same thing, only they paused the game, checked the map, and saw that the enemy team was going to ambush them, trying to counter the tactic that Azubu used in the past.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the pause, Azubu managed to mysteriously ping the exact brush TSM was in at the same time they were there, just after the pause.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coincidentally.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, it sounds like that they were
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, a little funny business is going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But once again, you know, okay, apparently what it was is the map was being projected behind the players, you know, so people can see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But put a fucking screen or something, you know, put that in a projection screen that's in front of the team.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, because you can maybe see the reflection in the monitor or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be very easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just, come on, you're running a $2 million tournament and you can't have decent, you're going to go that,
[SPEAKER_04]: you know that ghetto cheap on that stuff to where oh well you know people even in regular tournaments that run well people are going to accuse other people of cheating just don't give them the opportunity especially when this much money is on the line sometimes you don't think of everything I don't know on Horde House this week we talked about a guild Warcraft contest that went a little wrong because you know they didn't think about every possible thing that could happen
[SPEAKER_04]: not to mention that they also I think there was an issue where someone was DOSing the servers they were trying to use for oh great for something so they moved to like some different servers or something I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something completely different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something you can play with online to make your own chiptune music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like little creative sites like this, and this is pretty cool because this website kind of looks like a Game Boy, and you can sequence your own tones, play them back, and save things to a WAV file so you can make your own cool little chiptunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is called Pulse Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to check it out, it's pulseboy.com, and I think it's called that because it looks like a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was made by Roger Hicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you feel like kind of just messing around making your own chip, excuse me, your own chiptune songs, you can check out that website.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what else to say about it, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't had time to play with it myself yet, but I like those music-making types of programs, especially since there hasn't been a new Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a crime.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to have that with a tablet controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still no Mario Paint, but now they have Art Academy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Art Academy now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want Art Academy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_05]: Besides, there's GarageBand.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and games that are coming out soon near you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week is actually quite a bit because we're getting into the fall stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, today, Pokemon Black Version 2 and Pokemon White Version 2 out on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naughty Bear Double Trouble for the PlayStation 3 includes a Naughty Bear Gold Edition and Naughty Bear Trouble in Paradise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both, I'm sure, very underwhelming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I love Naughty Bear, said nobody ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spy Hunters coming back on the Vita and 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Dance 4 out this week on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Ball Z for Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you can be over 9,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Code of Princess for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Harry Potter for Kinect, Monster 4x4 for the 3DS, the cool game this week, Dishonored on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, let's see, XCOM, Enemy Unknown on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe that series is coming back, and it's probably going to look nothing like the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: the new one well this is the strategy one so they don't have the third person shooter one yet and then Fable the Journey on Xbox 360 for Kinect and god I wonder if that sucks or not haven't seen any reviews for that yet but that's it
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well traveling to Japan, some of the same stuff on the Xbox 360 over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dishonored comes out on the 360 October 11th, as well as Fable the Journey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something must be going on with Rocksmith because there's a new cable and a cable bundle that are coming out in Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Rocksmith must be landing in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either it already has or it's landing there soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty much all the same stuff I just named.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, just Dishonored and the Rocksmith thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other one isn't happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they also have Toki Toa comes out as well in a regular limited edition and Famitsu deluxe pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, I don't know what this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is some type of like... A wedding is supposed to be a joyous occasion for Princess Toki and her knight.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, the sneaky witch predicts that somebody is going to die at her wedding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's kind of a downer, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to... God, this is kind of fucked up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like it could be kind of a neat concept, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the PlayStation Vita, nothing this week, but you do have FIFA 13 to look forward to on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_05]: and going to the 3DS real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few things, quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Project X Zone, a Nintendo 3DS LL in blue and black, which I believe is the XL.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bravely Default Flying Fairy from Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_05]: No idea what that could be, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And game of the week for many people, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello Kitty, Toeiso, Block Crash Z. That means like Hello Kitty's like the Kool-Aid man crashing through some blocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's what that's all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's on the 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: still no mouth yes on the 3DS going to the European release dates since DarkSakura is not here I'll try to jump in there and check out the European release dates on October the 12th Dishonored on the 360, Playstation 3 and PC, Fable the Journey on the Xbox 360, Pokemon Black 2 and White 2 on October 12th Rocksmith on the 360 and Playstation 3 is that the initial release of the game there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they didn't have it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: WRC3 on the Vita, PlayStation 3, PC, and 360, and XCOM Enemy Unknown across the 360, PS3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: So a lot of the same stuff in Europe that we're getting here, so they don't have to wait for a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to add one more thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got some news this week that was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because my rep over at D3 knows I'm a huge Earth Defense Force fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Earth Defense Force 3 Portable came out in Japan on the 27th of September.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being localized, coming out over here February 12th as Earth Defense Force 2017 Portable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray, you're happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have to import it!
[SPEAKER_05]: We knew there was a cult enough fandom for it here, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not the only one that loves this series.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Earth Defense Force 4 hopefully is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_04]: That I may import depending on how long it takes to get over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to throw something out here too that was not in the news otherwise.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is that it's confirmed that there's more DLC coming for Mass Effect for multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it looks like one of the most robust ones they've done yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I guess there's going to be overall 16 new classes, which seems crazy to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're rolling it out slowly or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there's only four to start and then there'll be more.
[SPEAKER_05]: but new maps it's some of the older maps with weather effects now and the weather will impact some things but one of the biggest things that really surprised me a fourth enemy race which is really cool and what the game could really use some of so you have the Geth you have the Cerberus you have the Reapers and now you're going to have the Collectors which was a big part of Mass Effect 2 that's coming back so that's awesome
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think we have a date for that yet, do we?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, maybe we do.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be as soon as this Tuesday, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's coming out really soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: BioWare tends to announce these things and it's like, by the way, next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool, so this is very sad, apparently Sony is suing the fictional character Kevin Butler And by suing the fictional character, actually suing the actor that plays him, Jerry Lambert And apparently this is also, I think this has to do with their new commercial they're in for Bridgestone Because they're also suing them as well
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, basically, uh, he was playing, I guess, a competitor, he was playing Mario Kart on the Wii, um, for that commercial.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so, apparently, I guess, later on, they edited the commercial and removed him from it entirely, which is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, I guess, um, perhaps, maybe, there's some sort of clause or something that he couldn't be seen, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: They said the use of the Kevin Butler character to sell products other than those from PlayStation misappropriates Sony's intellectual property and creates confusion in the market and causes damage to Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I don't think he was...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it was actually, he wasn't playing Kevin Butler in the commercial.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just an actor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't sue because he's playing a different character that happens to be playing a video game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like he's like, I'm Kevin Butler with Sony, I'm playing Mario Kart, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, he didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I mean, people did notice it was him, and I'm sure there's a lot of people doing a double take, but it's like, actors have to work, and they have to take whatever jobs are offered to them, and if Sony cut him loose, then he should be free to look for other work elsewhere, playing other characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, he can't not play a manager for the rest of his life, because people might think it's the Sony guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't know, that seems a little messed up to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think people usually know enough to know, like, oh, it's the same guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: maybe it's because Sony was trying to push so hard that Kevin Butler was like a real thing when they brought him out of the press conference a few years ago and so forth at E3 like maybe that's more what they're worried about but that's kind of Sony that built that up right yeah it's weird though because I mean it at no point from what I remember um at no point in that commercial did they ever refer to him as Kevin or refer to him as like anything um
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, most people know how to differentiate actors from one project to another.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, just because somebody plays a villain in one movie doesn't mean they're, like, always a villain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, I guess some people get, you know, typecast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Daniel Radcliffe is not fucking Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, you're right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's not Harry... That's why he did that play with the nudie stuff, is he wanted to do...
[SPEAKER_04]: Women in Black is not Harry Potter and the Women in Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a totally different movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because this guy is in a commercial doesn't mean it's fucking Kevin Butler.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can they even sue over this?
[SPEAKER_04]: They can do whatever they want because they're Sony and they can bully whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, she's an actress, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: She had to take on a role of a person not a lot of people really care for, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let her be other parts in other movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, when I watched Battlestar Galactica, I didn't go, oh, Selina's dad is a spaceship captain now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that the teacher from Stand and Deliver?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chiggers asks, can that guy ever do another commercial without thinking of him being Kevin Butler?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess Loki gave a good example.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you ever think of Daniel Radcliffe as anything but Harry Potter?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just really quickly, I was trying to watch the commercial real quick to see if he's got a name tag or if they refer to him as... Actually, I'm going to do this real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just gonna see well let me read some other comments while you're working there Frisbee in chat says anyone who thinks Mario Kart is a Sony product those people are crazy yo Dungeon Buster says it was funny seeing him push the Wii in the commercial though Dungeon Buster says the only thing I could think of was it's nice to see Kevin Butler having fun with the Wii damn I need new tires
[SPEAKER_05]: Success.
[SPEAKER_05]: The commercial was a success.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got you to think about tires and that you might need to take a trip to the tire store.
[SPEAKER_05]: SJ100Matt says, All I have to say is no one cares about the dude you got a Dell guy anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they don't really even refer to him at all by any name at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just he's playing a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this whole lawsuit is fucking retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I feel bad after all the good shit I mean he was he was like a spokesperson for you know Sony that actually kind of got people excited about Sony stuff and here's the way they go and treat him yeah thanks Sony's had a lot of missteps in their advertising over the years and Kevin Butler was one of the things they did right and then they end it they end it and then they go they go they end it and then take a giant dump on it hey we're gonna fucking sue you because you're in a commercial for Bridgestone playing a Wii it's like dude
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the one that fucking let him go, you stupid idiot.
[SPEAKER_04]: He could have been still pitching, you know, Sony stuff, but you said, eh, fuck it, we're getting rid of him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Bobby Blackwolf in the chat room says, actors generally have non- He's the voice of realism here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actors generally have non-compete clauses about not directly or indirectly promoting a competing product when they do ad work for a certain time.
[SPEAKER_05]: He might have violated his non-compete clause, which was in the contract that his agent should have known, but not him.
[SPEAKER_05]: But technically, I mean, just play devil's advocate, technically it was for the tire shop.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ad was not for a Wii, it was for the tire shop.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's where things get a little fuzzy-wuzzy here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I mean, what if he's... What if this Kevin Butler... I keep calling him Kevin Butler.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not fucking Kevin Butler.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an actual person.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but what if, for example, you know, they... He walks past, you know... What if Jerry Lambert walks past, like, an Xbox 360 or something that happens to be on?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they go, oh, whoa, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were too close to another console.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to sue you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this...
[SPEAKER_05]: what if he gets a sitcom role or something like that and his kids are playing a fucking Xbox 360 or something what Bobby's saying in chat though does make sense I mean like okay for example Catherine Zeta-Jones was T-Mobile for how many years right like she was the reason a lot of people went to T-Mobile she was a great spokesperson for that company why they ever let her go I'll never know but like it's not like she started doing commercials for AT&T right after that you know
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, but at the same time, if she's talking on an iPhone in a movie, can T-Mobile sue her because they don't have the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be stretching it a little bit, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently, if there's anything out of it, they're going to try to settle out of court.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet Coden 1 and 2
[SPEAKER_05]: Great PlayStation role-playing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, there were five of them, but a lot of people remember very fondly the first two that were on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this Facebook group, the Suikoden Revival Movement, is a group that's trying to organize to get Konami's attention to get Suikoden 1 and 2 available on PlayStation Network worldwide.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to get to the bottom of this because I'm like, wait a minute, I have Suikoden on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought it several years ago, so I know that's already there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this is, I suppose, a campaign to get it done worldwide.
[SPEAKER_05]: My understanding is that Suikoden 1 is not available in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet Coden 2 is kind of a rare game, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, like, people pay a lot of money to get copies of that game if you can actually find it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it would be, although it would suck for the collectors to have it devalued a little bit, it's not like that kind of stuff hasn't happened before.
[SPEAKER_05]: So a lot of people asking, well, where's Sweet Coden 2, which some people say was the best that was in the series?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a little odd that that is missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there is a fan campaign going on on Facebook and it's basically kind of like Operation Rainfall-esque where it's like bug Konami on Twitter on Tuesday, bug Konami on Facebook on Friday and just keep banging down their door until they get you what you want to shut you up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Facebook.com slash SuikodenRevival is the place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: S-U-I-K-O-D-E-N-R-E-V-I-V-A-L if you feel like joining in on the campaign, which I bet Shane is going to sign up for right now, although he probably already has the games on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't there PSP remakes in Japan, too?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, is 1 and 2 really good enough?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or don't you want 3, 4, and 5 at some point?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that they're putting PlayStation 2 games out on the PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's move on to a time when gaming was a lot simpler and you didn't get to petition companies to tell them what you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: You took what you got and you liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week on the show, DarkSakura picks a classic game from the gaming vault that she thinks, hey, you guys should be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she's not here.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's too busy on the Matterhorn.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm jumping in and taking the classic game because Loki never told me if he wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to do the classic game tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I try to pick things I think DarkSakura may not have heard of and things I remember from my past.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the classic game of the week I picked this week is an edutainment title.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called The Island of Dr. Brain is my classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, really we should kind of consider Dr. Brain as a series because The Island of Dr. Brain was not really the first game in this series.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Castle of Dr. Brain was the first game in this series.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Dr. Brain was a series that had, I think, four games in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was...
[SPEAKER_05]: There was the island of Dr. Brain, the castle of Dr. Brain was before that, and then later on, like about three years later, we had the Lost Mind of Dr. Brain and the Time Warp of Dr. Brain, although I don't remember those games as fondly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think part of that is because Sierra, who actually created those first two games, created those in-house, but then they acquired Bright Star Technology, who was known for educational games, it got turned over to them, they made the Lost Mind of Dr. Brain and the Time Warp of Dr. Brain.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Dr. Brain is an absent-minded professor, and basically the idea in the games is to kind of follow Dr. Brain and kind of find him wherever he is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, The Island of Dr. Brain is kind of a play on The Island of Dr. Moreau, like the classic movie that then they remade into a terrible movie and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Brain's Island of Dr. Brain
[SPEAKER_05]: The Islet of Dr. Brain
[SPEAKER_05]: to get further and further in the island.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there were many types of different puzzles.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was like Tetris, Tetorino Animo, I forget what they call those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those types of puzzles, the classic Tower of Babel style puzzles where you're moving the little towers from one pole to another.
[SPEAKER_05]: Graphing calculator puzzles where you had to get the exact, thank you, Tetromino puzzles.
[SPEAKER_05]: where you had to get the graph to draw just right to separate the four types of little amoebas under the microscope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Latitude and longitude puzzles.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were all these different types of puzzles in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, in the plot of the game, the plans for the latest project were stolen and you have to get the battery from the island and bring it to Dr. Brain to basically fix the situation.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's security puzzles that Dr. Brain set up all over the island, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is what you're solving.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, it was a Sierra game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was for DOS back in 1992.
[SPEAKER_05]: And although it was kind of an educational title, I don't know, I kind of like puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of set the precedent for a lot of fun puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's really it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I have to say about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a lot else to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a variety of different types of puzzles in it, and it's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the prequel as well, The Castle of Dr. Brain, was also a solid entry in the series.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week's Classic Game of the Week, The Island of Dr. Brain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Therefore, just follow the trail of my security puzzles if you have any problems solving them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just give me a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's going to do it for this first half of Orange Lounge Radio, but don't go anywhere guys, we have plenty more of show to come, including Rapid Fire News, the Fugle Question of the Week, emails, if we got any, there weren't any in there last time I looked, the FUs of the Week, and of course, your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you have something to say about this whole Kevin Butler situation, or Cliffy B leaving Epic Games, or porn on the 360, or whatever you want to talk about, we'll be taking your calls when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live with episode number 476 of our show for this October the 7th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just myself and Loki holding down the fort tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're just joining us, DarkSakura, she is at the happiest place on earth, which is even happier today with the Gay Days Anaheim going on right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people that are there right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you might be wondering why aren't you there um my pass expired for Disney I had an annual pass for Disneyland it actually expired at the end of September so I wouldn't have been able to make it and um it's like $450 or something to renew right now which you know if I was in a better financial situation I'd spend it because that's you know it's Disneyland's a great place but uh
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to use the excuse to kind of take some time off from Disney for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just there two weeks ago anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the point, was to be like the last hurrah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Jamie, she's enjoying it for now while I'm on a little bit of hiatus.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she'll be back next week to pick a new classic game of the week and do all the things she does on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: But meanwhile, Loki and I holding down the fort.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki, you gotta tell the listeners what you were telling me during the break about your shopping excursions here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not shopping on anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm making, well, designing something right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, plotting.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're plotting something over there, clearly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not necessarily shopping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, so no, I was, um, you know, I'm always looking for, like, DDR machines and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So one of the things I wanted to do was rebuild my, you know, DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I kind of saw, you know, all the designs that are out there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually had bought stuff to make a certain, uh, design.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just kind of don't want to do that one anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I happened to catch there was, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: On Bomani Sao's site, some guy was selling one of his beat gear pads.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if you don't remember, beat gear pads, at one time there was a guy that was going to be creating the most arcade authentic pads out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we played some awesome music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I guess it was appropriate since Loki's talking about old games to play the classic Game of the Week music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyways, so this guy's selling the beatgear pad and they've got some shots of it and stuff and that kind of linked to another website that had some more shots of the pad and likes it taken apart and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So based on those pictures, I'm designing the schematics for it to make my own or to mass produce them if I want to since no one has done it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so that's why I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you wouldn't scam people out of their money.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're an honest guy, and I know where you live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, everyone knows where I live.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I was kind of curious to see how much it's going to cost to do it and how I would actually have to do it, because I think it looked like it was injected molded plastic and stuff, and they use different sensors than arcade sensors.
[SPEAKER_04]: They use...
[SPEAKER_04]: They're tape switches, or what they're called, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually buy those really cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: They come in a big, long string of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I found them for $10 for eight feet of that stuff, and you'd only need a few inches per pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: um maybe a few feet per pad um but I mean 10 bucks for you know a ton of switches versus 10 bucks a switch kind of a kind of a big deal there but um yeah so arcade parts they actually use the arcade arrows they use um the way I'm designing is going to use arcade um neons as well um and I don't know about the arcade switches because those are really fucking expensive I'd rather go the tape tape switch route um
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll always be the DDR fan, now and forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Half the stuff I do is for DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did it for the dinner.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, so that's what I've been working on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that's what I've been working on this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last few days I've been playing Minecraft or anything, or Borderlands 2, because I've been playing in SketchUp trying to draw what I see and getting the measurements right based on...
[SPEAKER_04]: Other things that are injection molded and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have the support braces and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just getting the right size.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I have nailed it pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just knowing measurements of different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing about injection molding stuff is...
[SPEAKER_04]: it may be somewhat cheap for the parts but the initial cost is pretty expensive so it may not even be by the time I'm done worth it doing because make the parts would be a few thousand dollars which you know it's good if you're mass producing them because then you know you cost average all that stuff out and it gets pretty cheap but if you're making like one pad or two pads that might not work out too well you know it'd be well over the cost of a DDR machine what's the point at that point
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, before we get into rapid fire news to take things a slightly different direction for a minute, I like some of this reminiscing people are doing in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're talking about this service Imagination.
[SPEAKER_05]: I personally never heard of that one, but they're talking about some of the other old school dial-up services and things that used to exist back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Qlink.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that actually called Quantum Link?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I think they shortened it to Qlink.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that and I always wanted to get on that with my 300 baud modem.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my parents, you know, I was only like probably eight at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't want me on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Vandy brought up Genie and Prodigy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was on Prodigy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was on Prodigy too and I still remember my number to this day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I know I've talked about it on a previous show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got in a lot of trouble thanks to Prodigy chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got in trouble just I think because one of the Prodigy numbers it dialed was a long distance number and we were on it for like a long time so it like you know it racked up a pretty big phone bill but yeah the earliest modem I had was just a 2400 baud modem but yeah BBSs that was some good times oh I spent so much time on BBSs back in the day
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And BBSs wouldn't suddenly disconnect the stream like apparently just happened here.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is up?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a Comcast issue, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should be back online now, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It shows the streaming data.
[SPEAKER_05]: But where were we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, BBSs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to call so many BBSs when I was like 12 to 15.
[SPEAKER_04]: What we used to have was the California Computer News magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You and I probably hung out on the same BBSs and didn't even know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: What were some of the big... My favorite BBS back in the day in the Sacramento area was one called The Open Mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still remember it to this day.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was huge on the forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had a very active forum community.
[SPEAKER_05]: I met a lot of great people on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there was one you could dial into to play Doom 2 online.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that was the one where you had to buy credits after you used so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember some of the big ones that were here locally, but I used to play all that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of the Red Dragon, Trade Wars 2002, The Pit with its graphical client.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one BBS I used to dial into that actually would let you have internet access for like 15 minutes a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then also all the AOL discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you would just be swimming in those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd go to cancel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, would you like in there a free month?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free month.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember asking and begging my mom to let me call the long distance number to the Sierra BBS for like 20 minutes so I could download a game demo that I really want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember what it was now but there was something on there that I really wanted because Sierra had an official BBS back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dial back verification, all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried running a BBS, but my parents would never let me have the second line.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was one of those, you know, my really good friend Neil could call in when we set up a certain time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then my mom would pick up the phone to call one of her friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, what the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enough reminiscing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I'm very excited about this game coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a long, long time coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Retro City Rampage, which originally started off as a Grand Theft Auto game for the NES and then just spun out from there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has so many homages to, like, just all this 8-bit stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they've got...
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything you can possibly think of.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have levels that are based off of Metal Gear, levels based off of Breakthrough, levels based off of Bionic Commando, Mega Man, Blaster Master, all sorts of crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be coming out on the PlayStation 3 and the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing the cross-buy thing too with that, so that's where I'm purchasing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I do also want it on my Xbox 360 and maybe on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I may actually purchase it on every single platform that comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's $14.99, so that'll be coming out this week on the 9th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll probably be the game I'm playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's very much like a Grand Theft Auto 1 or 2 type game, top down.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just all sorts of crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like Super Meat Boy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a Super Meat Boy game that's done like the Virtual Boy in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's going to be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also this week, one of the announcements, I guess, Namco Bandai is removing Nobi Nobi Boy from the iOS App Store, also on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently they haven't really said why it's being removed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is being removed by Namco Bandai, not Apple.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently there's some functionality that hasn't been working for a few months.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe they've just decided that we're going to get rid of it or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to play the game, I guess download it now so you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is $1.99. $1.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's a new Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually saw this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Kickstarter for Old School RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's being created by Brenda Brathwaite and Tom Hall.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may not remember them, but of course they worked on some of the older game series like Wizardry and Dungeons & Dragons.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, Brenda Brathwaite actually sounds very familiar.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was like an old school RPG person, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and then Tom Hall was the founder of id Software.
[SPEAKER_04]: He made Commander Keen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy shit, Commander Keen.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one of those demos I downloaded for 30 minutes on my 2014 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, one of the things I liked doing was we had a local video store that had a shareware table.
[SPEAKER_04]: A table where you just buy floppy disks of all sorts of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: in less than a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think of where we're going to be 20 years from now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not even.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like five years from now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently if you pledge $15 you'll get a digital copy of the game and of course they've got all sorts of different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: They even have a $10,000 pledge point where they will show up to your door with a red velvet or deliver the game in a box on a red velvet pillow on a red carpet.
[SPEAKER_04]: so that's pretty funny and you know they also had one of their stretch goals is that they'll make two full games so neat also DLC Quest the game we kind of talked about a while I actually played it on the indie games but it's one of the games that's on the whole green light thing and one of their promises if they get green lit is that they're going to add some new content which is good because that game's only like one or two hours long
[SPEAKER_04]: and the new DLC is going to be called live freemium or die and they have I guess a new campaign world or new campaign new world new enemies and buckets of new DLC to purchase and that they're saying that that's at the launch um the fourth quarter of this year uh which is pretty funny and um
[SPEAKER_05]: and yeah, and then that's it alrighty I got a few stories for you guys as well first off, something about Star Wars Final Assault hopefully this will be one of the Star Wars games that isn't terrible because they're hit and miss sometimes they're really good sometimes they're really not good but Star Wars Final Assault will be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade there is an image out there floating around of the actual artwork that will be used on the arcade that's kind of how they spilled it there
[SPEAKER_05]: So the game was first announced way back in August when there were trademark and domain registrations.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this game, it's funny to note, still has not been officially announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we don't even really know exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they haven't announced it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out of a leak.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a leak of all the different...
[SPEAKER_04]: All the fourth quarter titles that were coming out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually some other ones I saw that were interesting, but I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, could one of them be this game I'm going to mention next?
[SPEAKER_05]: Karateka?
[SPEAKER_05]: I could never say this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically karate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Karateka.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's the way you would say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember this old, old game.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was back in the Commodore 64 days and all that, and it was in the arcades too.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a remake now coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously it's now 3D, a little more inspired by the Street Fighter IVs of the world and so forth, but still kind of cool that it's on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's small enough to be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox.com actually had this posted.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't supposed to be an official announcement, but people that were scouring Xbox.com actually found it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one is supposed to be out, I believe, relatively soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: November-ish is when that remake is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: November 16th?
[SPEAKER_05]: 14th?
[SPEAKER_05]: 14th, that link is to be believed that was found on Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: This fad isn't going to die anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Gangnam Style Dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's now available to your character in Free Realms.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might remember Free Realms as the free-to-play MMO that's available on the PlayStation 3 and
[SPEAKER_00]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, you can do this dance in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I love about the trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: They can't use the actual music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care about the E.T.
[SPEAKER_05]: re-release.
[SPEAKER_05]: Show me the freaking movie I really want to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they don't have walkie-talkies anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's important.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even on the Blu-ray version?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought they went back to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they got rid of it, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Spielberg said he regretted that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we need to have a conversation about E.T.? ?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the actual trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have to use fake music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it's the actual dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the problem with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not only is Free Realms kind of crap, but let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: The moment that sold that video for most people was when he was dancing over the guy in the elevator.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the best part of the entire video, and I don't see that represented here in Free Realms.
[SPEAKER_05]: and everybody's saying, why aren't the panda bears doing this in Mists of Pandaria?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because they programmed that dance in like nine months ago, way before Gangnam Style was a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, a Wii U demo interface has been shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is because the Wii U demo kiosk is now available in the official store in New York City.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't know if some of our New York City fans are nearby.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to check that out, but you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Wii U demo station.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it has some of the cover art for some of the various games there you can select whatever demo cover art you want to play and you get a video or you get to actually play the demo depending on what it is apparently only Rayman Legends is actually usable but who knows I mean this is still really early on the console is still a good month and a half away so I imagine they'll add more to this but that's available at the official Nintendo store so those of you that are in New York might want to check that out
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma, the ever great reporter for VOG, says he'll go by there tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get on it, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fugo question of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very simple this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought I'd tie it into what we talked about at the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the scariest video game you've ever played and why?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: James S replied there's another games on PC that I haven't played but would love to like Amnesia or Slenderman my computer is ancient so I have to go with a console game I know it sounds cliche but Silent Hill 2 and 3 collection was phenomenal I can't remember how many times I had to turn it off when playing alone at night because I was literally dreading turning around that next darkened corner freaky music in the background and none of the stupid team co-op stuff to ruin it
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead Space 1 and 2 Need I Say More?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shattered Hawk says as a kid I used to own Shadow Man for the N64 the music mixed with monsters gave me nightmares the pig guys with the hooks that screamed when they spotted you still gives me the chills I never played that game but that sounds scary Tim N says Silent Hill 2 it is peerless as far as horror goes the rest are pretenders some strong words there
[SPEAKER_05]: Gamer Girl says, I know you only asked for one, but I have two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eternal Darkness was really scary for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but when you get to the part where your heart starts racing in game, it was over for me in real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm a huge music lover.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel whatever I'm listening to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same goes for Fear, F-E-A-R.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are two of the most scariest games for me, but somehow I still love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan Shadow says the original fear was really creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first few missions had great jump scares and you didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: He spoils part two.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll have to read that on Facebook to see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mike B says Jaws Unleashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was scary bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew somebody would go with the showgirls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Jaws wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it was Unleashed though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that like the remake one where you can play as the shark?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the shark one looked fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Falcon said, return to Castle Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a small part in the game that just startled the crap out of me during gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was walking through a snowy field and everything was quiet and calm and the Nazis jumped out of nowhere and made me jump out of my skin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shot the crap out of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nazis always scare me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another vote for Silent Hill 2 from Clover N. Chiggers says, Bioshock had a moment that scared the shit out of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those zombie dudes jumped out from behind a coffin and made me drop the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock was really scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Dollar Bill says Haunted House on the 2600 when you could not see the walls at all no weapons and could not even see behind the doors drop my damn controller every time I opened one and a damn spider or bat or ghost killed me quite honestly I'd like to see a follow up of scariest moments Haunted House on the 2600 was kind of old school survival horror I think they remade that for the 360 yeah and it's shit yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: and DJ Ranma S replied and said, Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a very similar story to what Chiggers had mentioned before with somebody popping out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said, well played 2K Games, well played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to Google Plus and look at some of the answers there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marcus E. says, Haunting Ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though the Capcom game focuses on a busty gal running around like some horror flick, it managed to be much deeper.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any game where your only option is to run seems scary by default, but the atmosphere in Haunting Ground was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pair that with supremely creepy stalkers, foreboding locations, and a terrifying soundtrack, and the game was one of the best horror titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I must give you one example of how the game managed to be so scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haunted Ground focuses on hiding since you can rarely fight back.
[SPEAKER_05]: At one point, I was running from an antagonist, rushed down a hallway into a room, and
[SPEAKER_05]: went down in the room and went to hide in the closet guess what she was in the closet waiting for me moments like that just made the game near perfect Actdeft says aside from Silent Hill, Eversion that game is really fucked up and so much too lastly Red Entertainment says Silent Hill 3 I had to stop playing that game near the end so the fear that was building up in my body could leave me I occasionally still hear the sounds of those damn demon dogs
[SPEAKER_05]: so there it is the answers from Facebook and Google Plus Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio or you can look us up on Google Plus if you want to answer in a future week some things I was surprised not to hear did you notice some of the games that were left out?
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard one person mention Amnesia but didn't pick that as their most scary no Resident Evils I didn't hear Clock Tower which I always thought was kind of a fucked I guess that was maybe more I don't know I kind of thought it was scary Fatal Frame yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of a lot of stuff that wasn't there, but still some good picks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not saying you guys didn't pick good stuff, but lots of love for Silent Hill, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, there it is, your Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get back into some more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not too far away from the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just yet, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some more news stories first.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Sony likes doing a lot of different bundles, especially around the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the things that they said, yeah, we're not...
[SPEAKER_04]: Not going to do it, but it might be a cool idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently they're thinking that, hey, maybe someday we'll do a bundle that includes a Vita and a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that could be possible if they have some more of those games that are going to be kind of working like...
[SPEAKER_04]: and the Wii U or the Xbox Smart Glass stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe if that becomes popular, they might do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd have to get a hell of a lot cheaper, though, because it's going to be a hard sell to have a portable system and a regular system in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that bundle's going to have to be a heck of a deal, but it's going to look like twice as much as the Wii U. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, they don't have a whole lot of interconnectivity between the two systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some games kind of use it, but not a whole ton.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they could.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could bundle it with a TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure they've done that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not outside the realm of possibility, but is it going to be something that people are going to be looking for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Options!
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, people like options.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some options people would like to see on the Wii U is more variety in games and some more things that address the hardcore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, follow-ups to some of those big Operation Rainfall games, The Last Story and Xenoblade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Reggie Fils-Aim made a comment, I believe this was to, I think it was to Kotaku, actually, about Xenoblade and The Last Story and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: The comment was about What is Monolith Soft doing now?
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the Wii U game that they're making?
[SPEAKER_05]: And the quote is this We know that they're working on a game I personally haven't seen it But I know there's a lot of excitement in Japan and Kyoto About what they're working on So I look forward to seeing it
[SPEAKER_05]: In the end, if it's a game that we decide to publish from what would be a second-party standpoint, certainly we'd love to bring it here to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way we look at the opportunity is, given a level of marketing support, how much are we going to sell, and is it going to be a profitable venture?
[SPEAKER_05]: So a whole lot of nothing kind of about, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we'll release it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we won't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found some of the comments on this particular website a little more interesting than the article itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: MyNintendoNews.com is where some of these comments come from.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some people are kind of talking about, like they're fighting about, did Xenoblade do well or not?
[SPEAKER_05]: One commenter says, I bet the Wii U game will do well since Xenoblade did well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody replies to that, it did well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It barely sold 300,000 copies in North America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just saw this this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last story, it's out of print.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not making it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was something that was being put out by XSEED, so it's kind of their M.O.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atlas does the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of make a small initial lot and then they sell through it and put it out of print.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, I don't think they sold that well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, somebody replies, though, and this is a good point, okay, $300,000 doesn't seem that bad when you consider it was only available at two places, Nintendo's website or GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: No Amazon, no Walmart, no Best Buy, none of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it doesn't matter, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the people that wanted that game, they could get it there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's be honest, GameStop is the largest game retailer out there, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, BlackWolf wants to correct something you said.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says Walmart is the largest game retailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameStop may be the largest specialty retailer, but Walmart is the largest retailer of a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they're the largest retailer of, you know, retailer out there, but as far as game specialty as, you know, category, GameStop is far beyond Walmart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Walmart may sell through a lot of stuff, but the biggest chunk is going to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I see a lot of
[SPEAKER_05]: special stuff being done for GameStop like a lot of exclusives you don't see Walmart exclusives for that stuff on movies though you do you do see some Walmart exclusive things rarely but you do and I would argue that you probably do see more actual games at the end of the day sold at Walmart than you do at GameStop same thing with the CDs you wouldn't think Walmart's the largest CD retailer in the world but they are maybe with iTunes in the picture it's a little different now but the largest physical CD retailer in the world they're the largest retailer of a lot of stuff like it or not
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that's all I wanted to say about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: to the Washington, D.C.
[SPEAKER_04]: Public Library, I guess the Martin Luther King branch.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to allow different gamers with all sorts of different disabilities to be able to enjoy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're going to see games with maybe some audio-only games, that kind of stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't really said what specific types of games are going to be in there, but I can kind of imagine the stuff that they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess this is opening very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or actually, by the looks of it, it's already open.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's nice to hear that not only is something opening up, even though it's a library and all that stuff, so it isn't like an arcade in the traditional sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's neat that not only is something opening up, but it's opening up with a broader idea in mind and something new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, you know, now we look at it and go, oh, this is something we should have had all along, but this is a great idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's hope it does well for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it'll start a trend.
[SPEAKER_05]: But sadly, I think with how arcades have been doing recently, I think the trend has already been had.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, there were a few Nintendo Direct conferences this week that talk about the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we get to find out what's in store for the 3DS this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess there's a sequel being made to Pushmo, Ninja Gaiden and Castlevania the Adventure, and some other games developed by Level 5 and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some good stuff that's actually original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Night Sky is coming out October 25th that is an action puzzle game that will be an ambient gameplay experience with cerebral challenges that will be uniquely designed picturesque worlds by the way these are all eShop titles I probably should have put that out there too Crashmo is the sequel to Pushmo on November 22nd
[SPEAKER_05]: Fluidity Spin Cycle is on December 27th.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to make use of the tilt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of games have been using the gyroscope in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this will have tilt and turn and all that stuff to maneuver a puddle of water named Eddie through a maze-like world.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can do liquid to ice or steam, solid liquid gas type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that sounds just like that one game that Konami put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I remember that, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dewey's Adventure?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo eShops will get level 5 stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Suda51's Liberation Maiden.
[SPEAKER_05]: 100 years in the future when the President of Japan boards her liberator, Kamui, and fights to free her country one region at a time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arrow Porter and Crimson Shroud are also on the table to be released by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Pedestrian Tossing Pandemonium in Tokyo Crash Mobs, an action puzzle game in early 2013.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, some 3DS titles that are full games that are now available for download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Mario 3D Land, Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, Star Fox 64 3D, Mario Kart 7, all coming on October 18th for $39.99 each.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of those you can start to find in the bargain bins for far cheaper, so be careful, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's nice to Nintendo to offer such bargains on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Virtual Console, Mario Golf on October 11th, Castlevania The Adventure on October 25th, Ninja Gaiden on November 8th, Zelda II The Adventure of Link on November 22nd, Wario Land 2 on December 20th, and Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Lost Levels on December 27th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also in Nintendo news, Animal Crossing 3DS updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some characters might set up a tent and camp outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can help your in-game friends with purchasing decisions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Use your office as the mayor to make decisions on putting things in town.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pick a location for construction to begin on the items you plan on adding.
[SPEAKER_05]: A megaphone lets you gather people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got something to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's now a shoe store, a museum store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Shrunk will be back at the club.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are now many more emotions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can view the homes of people you street pass and trade items with people you street pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can take a picture with a photo booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's now a massage parlor that will relax you and put you into a dream stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe this is leading into Animal Crossing Happy Endings.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be the next game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can explore the town of someone else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thought you could do that in the last one on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you can do that with How to Invitation or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: K.K.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slider will also be the DJ at the club as well as playing the guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: More K.K.
[SPEAKER_05]: songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can explore a town with other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can take the boat to the island, grab items from the bottom of the sea.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's mini games and various stores when you visit the island by boat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tortimer is the host of minigames and wears a tropical shirt, so it sounds like the former mayor is retired to the island.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one minigame has you navigating a maze to collect a certain item.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a profound and new concept.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maze navigation.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never heard of that in a video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat asks, can you still hit animals over the head with the bug catching net?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so or this whole fucking game is invalidated, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you drag animals into an abandoned house and set up a saw style trap system for them?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not buying this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: yet so right yet so right I think that's worthy enough of being a dream game to be honest Animal Crossing after dark but I'm pretty sure we've talked about something like that before Animal Crossing the line
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki, what do you got next?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so next thing I've got, this is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what would you say, and I completely forgot about this until I saw the article.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember, no doubt, in Activision, there was a little lawsuit there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, I remember this.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were suing because, you know, people were singing other songs that they shouldn't have been singing, you know, didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, shock, settle that in court.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, you don't say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another lawsuit in the gaming industry settled out of court.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get out now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've settled.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word on the settlement.
[SPEAKER_05]: As usual, no word on who got what.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com We dive into the mailbag and pick out a few emails that we think we should read on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the emails?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there's no emails in the mailbag this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So even if DarkSakura was here, there'd be nothing to read.
[SPEAKER_05]: Womp womp.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, why don't you start?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess an FU to not being able to play Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play that this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FU of the week goes to the listeners for not sending us any email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you voted for us in one of the podcast award things, then you're forgiven if you did that, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: But FU to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a not so serious FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, I would say an FU to just all the money I've spent on this rocky project.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty disgusting, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a community I really love, and I'm excited to see it back in town.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just F you to nerves and the realization that, like, oh my god, this is happening in, like, five days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I'm just, like, freaking out a little bit, but it'll be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get to a couple more news stories, then we'll take your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so now we talked about it last week, how there was the oh, so wonderful promotion that Microsoft is doing tied with your gamer score where you got a 1% or 2% kickback.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: 1% kickback.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Sony...
[SPEAKER_04]: Side to up the deal a little bit because, you know, they think 1% is not necessarily good enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They announced that apparently if you buy $100 or more in October, you're going to get a $20 voucher for the PlayStation Network in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's enough to buy Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of games online, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's 20%.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's 10 times better than 2%.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does the money I spend on PlayStation Plus count towards that?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they said just on PlayStation Network, so maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that would count?
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, you can buy... I mean, I think it's kind of to push you a little bit to... And this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're thinking on the fence about the digital stuff, remember you can buy those digital games.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have PlayStation Plus, you get 10% off of the digital games, plus you get $20 back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that could really cut down the cost of these new release games if you're interested in picking up about $100 worth of product.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says, I got 20 Microsoft points for my birthday from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: A whole 20 points?
[SPEAKER_05]: That is a whole quarter.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what your birthday is.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the quarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what the special birthday thing was.
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what that will buy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a goddamn thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that will do is that will bug you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be like someone went into your house in the middle of the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: and plucked out one of those pixels in your TV and made it not work.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's just going to fucking bother you because you're going to have 20 points left over.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're like, fuck, I can't buy anything with these 20 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to purchase more points to buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just going to drive you crazy until you put more money in and then still end up with 120 points left over or some other freaking multiple of something you'll never be able to spend.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can buy, according to Dark Tetsuya, you could buy one quarter of Bungie Ferret Tossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is a $1 game and a great deal on the Xbox Live Indie Marketplace right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Microsoft, you're so generous.
[SPEAKER_05]: So $20 does sound a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't even give you a buck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fake money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, $100 on the PlayStation Marketplace, that seems like a lot of money to spend, but... If you're buying new release games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: All it takes is two new release games, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or even one new release game and maybe three PlayStation Network games to get you there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if PlayStation Plus dollars count towards that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: um if you have PlayStation Plus or if you buy PlayStation Plus if you buy PlayStation Plus uh maybe like maybe maybe this is my month to renew uh I don't know maybe I'd be interested to know that to register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase quarter
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, one more story for you guys tonight, and then we're going to open up the Skype line for calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: This doesn't have to do with gaming per se, but I think this is a good story because obviously gaming owes a lot of thanks to this, and that is the anniversary that we celebrate this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The compact disc turns 30, or the CD is now 30 years old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Loki, you and I are older than the CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: The CD was a joint effort of Philips and Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were working independently on different versions of the technology in the 70s.
[SPEAKER_05]: and they started to come out right in June of 1985 was when the CD-ROM was really born and that, of course, led to where we're at now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, without the CD, we would never have had the PlayStation era or really arguably DVDs and Blu-ray and all the stuff we have now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, DVDs and Blu-rays still are shaped like a CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: and of course it was a great sound remember the whole big thing about it was like you can skip right to tracks like no more rewinding and fast forwarding I think you could skip to tracks on 8 tracks but you still had to rewind them at some point
[SPEAKER_05]: I just remembered the giant buttons that were 1, 2, 3, and 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this leads to a great question in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love where Tigerclaw is going for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go ahead and open up the Skype line and we'll tackle this question.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: While we wait for some calls, Tigerclaw in chat says, Do you guys remember the first CD you ever bought and still have?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tigerclaw says, My very first CD was the Too Unlimited album called No Limit.
[SPEAKER_05]: VIRGIN MEGA STORE
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember what my first CD was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sorta remember my first CD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a tape adapter for my car.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I don't even remember what my first CD was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay, I don't really have a first CD because I bought two CDs when I first went.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of them was the soundtrack to The Addams Family, which came out that year.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I bought that even though it was mostly orchestral.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember having that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You ready for this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was another soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's one of my big gay moments.
[SPEAKER_05]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my first CDs was the soundtrack to Sister Act.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, the Whoopi Goldberg classic was one of the first CDs I ever owned.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't still have them though, which is kind of tragic because I got rid of all my CDs during one of my moves.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, let's see, I'm going to, uh, the chat to check out some of these answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, DJ Dark Knight says, my first ever CD was Dr. Dre, The Chronic.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, there's nothing to be embarrassed about there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like a classic album.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I remember what my first CDs were, because they weren't actually my CDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: My parents, they bought a new stereo system that had a CD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we had, uh, one of the first CDs we had was, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Michael Jackson, Black and White.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was like a landmark song when that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, our Skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: That album wasn't Black and White.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it called?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dangerous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dangerous, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to some embarrassing answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma in chat says, My first CD was the Aqua Barbie Girl single.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ziba says, I think mine was either Ace of Base or No Doubt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some answers that you can't really be embarrassed about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says, my first CD was an Aerosmith album.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Right says, Coolio's Gangsta's Paradise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan Alchemy remembers buying CDs for other people were the first CDs he bought.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wayne's World soundtrack, Primus was Sailing the Seas of Cheese, Weezer's debut, and Madonna's Erotica.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zether says my first CD was Weird Al's The Food Album.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I need to load up the Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot to get out my iPad, so I guess I'll have to do this the regular way.
[SPEAKER_05]: See if there's any tweets tonight at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know TigerClaw usually sends us a couple.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll see if there's anything else in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, do you have any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes!
[SPEAKER_04]: At least nothing I've seen so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, I got some tweets while you find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: From Codeman asks, Did you guys find a host?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could do the Skype host thing, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, a lot of this show, you have to remember the history of this show, we've always been in one room together.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, whereas taking calls on Skype is one thing, to have the host on Skype is weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: To me, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand Tiara's filled in when I'm not here, and that's different, because Jamie emcees those shows, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: that works out a lot better but uh yeah i don't know the not being able to see the co-host thing is is weird for me but then again horde house works okay i can't explain it i can't it's just olr's got a formula you gotta stick to it uh moving on to some tweets from tiger claw uh tiger claw oh reminds me of something that happened in world of warcraft today i did not experience this but i heard about it apparently and they're blaming this on a hacker
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I just was reading that.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the subsequent graveyards.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: No official comment from Blizzard, but I will say the servers were down and then the authentication servers were down as well for quite a bit this morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to play around 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I couldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think they were trying to fix this as it was happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure Blizzard's seen this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They certainly follow the fan sites and I can't believe everybody and their mother wasn't filing a complaint about the characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they will find the IPs and they will obliterate them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: You got shy listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or does the number not work?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what's happening there.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me make sure the number's working tonight because that was the problem last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is wrong with this thing, man?
[SPEAKER_04]: Angry Birds Star Wars Jenga?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like a three-way crossover there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just throw everything and see if one of them sticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Star Wars needed more Angry Birds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if we mentioned this, Atlas is publishing all the Calypso stuff now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or distributing, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: This other link here from Tigerclaw is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, we got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_05]: This should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does your Skype work yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: I called it from my phone and just verified the 800 number was working.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's working.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is your opening act.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, our co-headliner.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you, Bobby Blackwolf?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been in your position where I'm sitting there asking for calls, so I figured I'd help you guys out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've always been very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've literally had us on every episode of your show.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at Siege this weekend, which is the Southern Interactive Entertainment and Game Expo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think of it more like GDC rather than E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was basically, you know, a lot of students were there about getting into the industry and things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was really interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got to meet a lot of great indie artists.
[SPEAKER_02]: and developers primarily here in the southeast and hopefully lined up some stuff for us to cover in the future here at VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm really excited about that and a lot of people are really excited about VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of the first times I've really pushed VOG as a network really hard on people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of our first times in print.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the tweet with the little logo in the flyer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually the program that everybody got and probably didn't read.
[SPEAKER_05]: That happens, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually they all did read it because that had the schedule of all the panels.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I heard the VOG logo was above the Microsoft logo.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're coming for you, Gates.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had a pretty neat interview tonight on your show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight I was talking to Dustin Klingman.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is the chairman of the International Game Developers Association.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were talking about that I've done some interesting episodes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've started trying to theme what I'm doing instead of just talking about the news.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's a theme I can do, and if it's more like a discussion topic, I'll talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple weeks ago, I did a whole theme on people getting laid off.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm tired of talking about people getting laid off.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did his keynote speech at Siege about a time for optimism.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it was talking about how you should be optimistic about the game industry in spite of and he actually put out 120 studios have closed in the last 5 or 6 years that's the official number 120 have closed in the last 5 or 6 years and all this stuff people are leaving Zynga's stock price dropped and he did this entire keynote about why you should still be optimistic
[SPEAKER_02]: I interviewed him and basically tried to distill his one-hour keynote into a little 25-minute interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I basically asked him, why should we be optimistic?
[SPEAKER_02]: and just let him talk.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of the questions you asked him was about the video game Crash as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you kind of asked, do you think we'll see something like we saw in the early 80s happen again?
[SPEAKER_05]: And he said no.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he had his reasons.
[SPEAKER_05]: As a consumer, I'm not sure I necessarily agreed with everything he said.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I get the...
[SPEAKER_05]: I get the optimism and the fact that, you know, kind of like for every door that closes another opens and that there's this whole mobile thing is now the fad, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe we're seeing kind of like less AAA things and more mobile things.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of wonder, like, part of the reason the Atari 2600 and all that collapsed was that you had this oversaturation of these little...
[SPEAKER_05]: Games, although granted they were charging full price for them at the time and mobile games are more in the $0.99, $2 size.
[SPEAKER_02]: And his thing was that the reason also the crash happened is because stores just stopped wanting to carry them because they couldn't return them.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Evil G doesn't sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: NautiBear2
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me jump in with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, the man who works for the distribution company, you say that's not totally true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all one-way sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do not allow returns.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that maybe just your arrangement?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think it's mass retailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reason why they do that, that's why they do a pre-order program because otherwise they can buy a bunch of stuff and then return it all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's all one way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what it is now is they get a lot more perks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They get a lot more back-end rebates and a lot of price protections and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: but uh no it's definitely there are no returns on that stuff because the publishers do not want to be sitting on that stuff interesting and is that why amazon isn't that part of the like the rumors why amazon stopped carrying a lot of the nintendo stuff right the hardware uh well defectives are a little different but yeah once again you have to usually what they'll do with the effectives is they'll want the cut the consumer to go through the proper routes through the publishers but
[SPEAKER_04]: or the hardware manufacturers like, you know, they want a person that buys an Xbox 360 to go to Microsoft and have that repaired it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, a consumer doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, well, why did GameStop sell me a defective system?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go back to GameStop and return it instead of actually, you know, even if there's instructions in the box, do not return this back to the retailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, all that stuff has to be approved, you know, and obviously, you know, they're going to approve GameStop over, you know, some mom-off shop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish I knew that when I was doing the interview yesterday so I could have, like, called them out on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, now we'll just have to have another interview at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or we'll invite him on OLR, let Loki grill him.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but it was a good interview, and the fact that he was pretty open.
[SPEAKER_05]: You did have some tough questions, and that's always great when an interviewee can handle those questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so I have to ask you about something you didn't talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you did talk about it on Twitter, so that's why I know it's fair game, because you did post about it on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got to tell me about what's happening with a certain voice actor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: So I, well, and actually I phrased it on my Facebook, my private Facebook profile a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, my friends on Facebook know why this is amazing a little bit more than what people on Twitter would do.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will tell you this, I am not the type of person to go near a dance floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so I don't you know but I like you know going to concerts and stuff so I'm you know because I'm a musician so I'm actually watching the musician and so I've actually never been really you know on a dance floor you know
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually I can get out of being pulled onto a dance floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Professor Shy Guy was playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: All those years of DDR did nothing?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta realize, I did an aero stomp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Bimani was fingers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were a Beatmania guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and, you know, so she got pulled up to the dance floor by somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, so I'm kind of sitting there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have some pictures of her dancing up there, which is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he's like, okay, everybody here go out and get somebody and Ellen McClain comes right to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: and she's like come on and I'm like you know I do the whole no thing and she gives me this look like the motherly you're gonna do this I said so look you and when the voice of GLaDOS comes up to you and like just kind of like stares at you
[SPEAKER_02]: saying you're going to do this and starts pulling, you don't resist.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't say no to GLaDOS.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the way I phrase it is I don't know what's more impressive, the fact that I got on a dance floor and danced for two songs or that it was by the voice of GLaDOS.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a great story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thankfully, there's no video of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there never will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no clue what I'm doing up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she was trying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, she actually like she was wearing kind of like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what the clothing thing is called, but it's something that she wears over her shoulders.
[SPEAKER_02]: She was actually using that and wrapping it around me and doing something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: John Patrick Lauer, you're on notice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is like getting to be Dancing with the Stars level scandal right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Ellen made Black Wolf his slave for science.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you meant her slave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Her slave.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's definitely a woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: For science.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he said, okay, everybody go out and get more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she took me by the hand and we found two other people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then she handed me off to the other woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she took the, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: GameCon Dance GameCon Dance
[SPEAKER_05]: I plan to walk up to her and go, and I'll just say, hey, I'm a friend of Bobby Blackwolf's.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: She does know that name now.
[SPEAKER_02]: She does remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've met three times, so she now knows me.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now all the listeners are going to try that at a convention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you dare.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could tell her that you heard her on VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because she did, and I know I told you this, and we haven't started putting these on the stream.
[SPEAKER_02]: She did multiple bumpers for VOG on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Multiple.
[SPEAKER_02]: She did three of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't vote for my show, vote for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was at the top of Bobby's list, I'm sure, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You dummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't ever do a bumper for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a bumper for VOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I find I promote the whole network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, exactly, as we've been saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if you're not going to vote for us, vote VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I like the ring for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vote VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't we think of that when it started on October 1st?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We still have a few days left.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have until the 15th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat says, Ellen bumped for VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: alright well Bobby thank you for sharing your stories from SiegeCon and of course you got more interviews coming up throughout the week on your own show which I can't believe anybody who's listened to OLR at this point hasn't heard your show at one point or another but if for some crazy ass reason they have still not heard your show how can they find you Bobby?
[SPEAKER_02]: VOGnetwork.com is actually where I point everybody to go to my episodes now yeah we do that for Horde House and OLR too
[SPEAKER_02]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the upcoming coming up shows next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a live interview with the game recruiter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually is the CEO of GameRecruiter.com, Mark Mencher.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is going to be taking live chat questions as well about getting into the industry, but I'm also going to ask him how you can stay at your job and what needs to happen to stop all these layoffs.
[SPEAKER_02]: He doesn't know I'm going to ask him that yet, but I'm going to run it by him.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then I've got a couple pre-recorded interviews I'm going to be playing throughout the next couple weeks Tom Buscaglia who is the game attorney so we have the game recruiter and then the next week the game attorney from GameAttorney.com he mostly works he's mostly general counsel to a lot of independent game developers and indie game developers and he works with
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's all the fun stuff coming up on the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then hopefully I'll be doing more themed stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: What big interviews do we have coming up, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do we have to compete with Bobby here on Orange Laundry?
[SPEAKER_05]: What big interviews have we landed for the rest of the year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, next week we've got Cliffy B and Miyamoto's the week after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I do want to, can I throw one more thing in?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I take one more minute?
[SPEAKER_02]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so when I got there Friday, I saw the Microsoft booth, and it was the Windows 8 developer booth, and, you know, the guy behind it, and I was like, so, what do you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like, oh, I'm the developer evangelist for Windows mobile programming and Windows 8 programming and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, oh, so can I ask you something about Xbox Live Indie games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, so, blah, blah, blah, prepaid codes, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I basically go through the whole thing about the prepaid codes that I know you guys covered as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I hadn't heard of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that like a developer here that's having problems?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, no, it's every developer.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's the entirety of the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's like, I have not heard of that, but if you give me more information about it, I will start an email chain inside Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I found his Twitter, and I tweeted him the link to our article, and I'm like, it's been three weeks and counting.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually got a comment on our site from one of the other independent developers that actually posted a statement about how he's stopping support for all Microsoft platforms until they fix the prepaid code issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you saying VOG Network may save Xbox Live Indie games?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: because nobody else writing about this except me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we got Reddit love from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Bobby, we should let you go to see if anybody else is going to take a chance on calling in tonight, but I'm really glad you did have an opportunity, whatever the reason, to come on the show and plug all the good stuff you're doing right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to test your Skype, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I like the pop filters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, do you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the new stuff, our new toys, we all have the same mic now, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that was out there before, but we used to have three different microphones, two different types of connections.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all different, but now everything is the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are growing up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a condenser mic in the studio now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did that for the voiceover in the intro.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why it sounds a little different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks again to Brad from PodCulture because I know he's listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, the mics?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, they're great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And plus I color-coded them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you notice?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're the same colors that they are in the show role.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a green one, you have a blue one, and she's going to have a pink one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which she'll hate, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we need to get the fancy, like you know how they have the blocks on there that have the network logo and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we could do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cheesy and stuff, but sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing, I got to find the stand for this condenser mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: He sent everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to find my old condenser mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a condenser mic somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know where the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: That condenser mic and this condenser mic both have the same problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have crazy ass gain on them.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the good news is, because he sent us all those mics, these mics aren't bad that we have, so it'll be a great mobile kit so we can set up a better way to do OLR on the go.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we'll give it one more chance for calls, and then I'm going to shut it down and close out the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did have another tweet topic that Tiger Claw sent.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a great story, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of one of those, this is really unfortunate, but I will...
[SPEAKER_05]: I will go ahead and share it with you guys here.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is somewhat local, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: This happened in Hercules, California, which is one of those towns you pass going to the Bay Area before you hit the Bay Bridge in Oakland and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, unfortunately, the mother of Neversoft concept artist Simon Coe was murdered.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really tragic.
[SPEAKER_05]: ABC News 7 was reporting that Susie Ko was found in her home Friday evening while the family's sky-blue 2011 Subaru Outback is also missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The police have no motive or suspects in the death.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are asking anyone in the area with information to call the police 510-724-1111.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very tragic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really sorry to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a call coming in, so let's take the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, it's Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was also trying to call you earlier to test your Skype, but it seems it works.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep, it works.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, what have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, actually, I do have a topic in mind.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially with a game that came today.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually has gotten...
[SPEAKER_00]: Reviews below 8, but it hasn't been below 7.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's around the 7th or 8th mark.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's something that has bugged me since I started reading and probably writing reviews.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's that any game below 8 is automatically bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's stable like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's something that the whole internet is like, oh my god, it got a 7, it's bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't understand that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's what leads to this whole artificial inflation of gamer scores, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about the Xbox kind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about review scores.
[SPEAKER_05]: An average game, an okay game, should be a 5, shouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's really not the way it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Average games in this day and age tend to get a 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you give a game a 5, it's a stinker.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why at VOG Network we prefer to use the grading scale that you have from high schools and stuff because the A to F scale is a little more realistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's why I think 7s also feel really harsh.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much are they charging for Pokemon Black 2 White 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't these like $40 games?
[SPEAKER_05]: $35, I think.
$35.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, still, that's a big chunk of change.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's a high end on a DS game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And most games that are reviewed for the console systems, you're talking $50, $60 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're going to drop that much money on a game, are you going to drop $60 on something average?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it depends because if the game is fun, if the game will accomplish what it's set for, to be entertaining, it should be worth it.
[SPEAKER_00]: At least in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: But he was telling me that there's some online title that was released That in some ways, I guess it was only three bucks in the 3DS eShop And in some ways it's better than the actual Pokemon game that came out today Just with some of the ways it's different and so forth Let me see, hopefully he won't mind if I read a little bit of the message here The relevant parts here, what is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: You get.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sounds like in some ways the $3 title might be providing as much value as the $35 title and that's an issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: But of course that's one person's opinion.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, like I said, it can be entertaining.
[SPEAKER_00]: The price in this case is that you're paying for a full... It's supposed to be a full game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: At least that you're going to be playing at least for, I don't know, 20 hours that you can probably play a Pokemon game in that time and beat it to an extent.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I do get the value of...
[SPEAKER_00]: and how much of a replay you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_00]: But like I said, if the game is entertaining, if you can enjoy it, then it shouldn't be labeled as bad, especially with a 7.
[SPEAKER_00]: It should be an average.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I do get why the game might get that score, but telling people that it's a bad game...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like if I were saying that a certain game, I won't name any game in particular, but, oh, it has good graphics, it has good music, and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, but it has some very bad flaws, and it has some bugs.
[SPEAKER_00]: But overall, it's good.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, oh, I'm going to give it a 3, for example, instead of a 7 or a 6, probably, that it should get.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: is it may be bad in a relative sense where you know this game is getting review scores that are lower than the other Pokemon games so either a people are feeling burnout or b it's not a bad game per se but it's a bad Pokemon game because all the other Pokemon games are so good and this one's you know not really the best in the series
[SPEAKER_00]: Probably a former, since most people have been talking about that, that the gameplay has gotten pretty repetitive.
[SPEAKER_00]: It hasn't changed, but then again, if it isn't broke, why fix it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Actdeft, anything else you want to say tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, nothing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just expect a few, well, a little plug here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just expect a few little new articles from I Love That Song, especially since Halloween is coming, so it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, I'm behind on posting articles, but I know you've got some great stuff in the queue, and when all this other mess in my life is over, I'll be able to focus on that again, so it'll be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't worry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll get done eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it will.
[SPEAKER_05]: I won't let it fall off the radar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: You too, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, 1877 GameOLR, our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if anybody else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you out of stuff to talk about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember if you had anything else left.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just looking at some of the stuff, just going through different websites and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently in the manual for Pokemon Black 2 and White 2, they have an advertisement for the Pokedex 3D Pro.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming November 8th and for $15 on the eShop.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why the old one's no longer available.
[SPEAKER_05]: It all makes sense now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: See over 640 Pokemon in full 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's worth 15 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was another thing I saw.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was another hack on the Vita, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I do follow Dash Hacks and they post that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been...
[SPEAKER_04]: Not patched, but they removed the game that had the exploit for it, but it allowed people to run a custom firmware for the PSP on their Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they can run a custom firmware for 6.6, and it'll actually allow you to run ISOs for the PSP and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, they've removed that game off of the PlayStation Store, so you can't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately, that was the whole issue where there was some...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is 9 o'clock, and it looks like no more calls are coming in, so I guess we're going to close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks to those that did call in tonight, and if you think of something a little later on, you can always email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, or of course there is always Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR, or our Facebook community at facebook.com slash orangeloungeradio.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and who knows what will happen in gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're starting to ramp up into that really busy holiday time of year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So out of all those games coming out, it'll be interesting to see which ones we play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by this time next week, this play stuff I'm doing will be over with.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll be able to kind of focus on this stuff again, which will be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is I don't know why I keep getting updates for Stitcher on... Freaking app.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye app.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's somehow Stitcher added itself to my Facebook, and I keep getting updates for Stitcher stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, maybe because you voted in the award thing or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_05]: Although we like Stitcher, you could always unlike it after voting if you need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought tonight is seeing Loki's McDonald's bag makes me think that I just impromptu had McDonald's for breakfast yesterday and a sausage biscuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Totally not healthy, but good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got a free, was it free McFlurry?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, we playing Monopoly?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so pathetic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've gotten McDonald's the last few days because I ran out of stuff to make lunches with, and it's literally almost the same game pieces every time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, they're not even trying anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've gotten Boardwalk Park Plays like three times already.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, fuck this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they want to get you really excited about maybe having a million.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm totally going to win one million dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like,
[SPEAKER_05]: which is payable in 20 yearly installments or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's still a million dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll take that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks everybody for tuning in to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back next week to do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, continue to support independent podcasting and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!