[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight, October 21st, 2012, Xbox will soon unfriend two of their social applications.
[SPEAKER_08]: More Sega games are being re-released as download titles, and a PC game ships without the necessary activation keys.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, you've been out for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You went from really good stuff to really not so good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disneyland, let's focus on Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad you had a happy time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we didn't actually go into the park on Saturday because our good friend and listener got into a little bit of an accident.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he's okay, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you first told me that, I was like, oh my god, but he's fine, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: The car came out a little...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, a car is a poppy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things we learn in our lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cars are just cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are people.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan and I had a fantastic time regardless.
[SPEAKER_15]: And when I came home, now I'm going to get into the horrible part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: and she even curled over with an ear poking out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've got pictures on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll repost them in the chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: She finally started doing better and started eating again.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I put her back in her room and made sure her towel was in there with her and I let her come into the computer room whenever she wanted.
[SPEAKER_15]: and um Tuesday like around midnight or so she um well actually yeah it would be Tuesday she was uh half in the laundry room and half out in the hall and she batted my foot and so I stopped and petted her and you know we had a good cuddle and she purred she was a little wheezy when she purred
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, oh, it's old lady kitty, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Around 2 o'clock, I was actually about to go to bed, and I went to look for the cat to pet her goodnight, because I always pet Shermie goodnight.
[SPEAKER_15]: And she was in the living room, dead, just laying on her side.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I couldn't tell if she was breathing, because she was so fat.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I went in, and she was still warm, and so I couldn't really tell.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the moment, there's like a muscle tone that you can feel the difference, and yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, um, Shermie, I'd have to say she probably died around 1.30 in the morning based on her temperature and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the fact that, you know, she had rigor mortis doesn't set in for like a few hours anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, um, yeah, Shermie died.
[SPEAKER_15]: She was...
[SPEAKER_15]: 15, actually we redid the math and she was probably 16 because I got her when she was a year and a half old so which would have put her birthday in October so she was 16.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: In case the newer listeners don't know, because we've been taping where we're at now for about a year almost now, probably a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we used to tape the show at your house.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've actually taped the show at like five different places in the 10-year history.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we did tape the show at your house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you, obviously, you had Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Shermie was pretty notorious on the show for sleeping at my feet and so forth.
[SPEAKER_15]: Her bed was under the table.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you would sometimes put the mic down near her and say, what do you think about that, Shermie?
[SPEAKER_05]: And she would actually go, meow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here he goes Exactly So, yes, this does affect the show in many ways And of course, there was a very infamous moment that happened at one point on the show That I want to bring up a clip of here And I really want to thank Dark Tetsuya for finding this clip for me But this is a clip from, I think he said it was episode number 357?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah This is old, this is old, here it is Well, what's that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: I was talking about Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shermie just crapped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, did she?
[SPEAKER_15]: That was her review of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was us talking about the tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Shermie notoriously took a poo on the floor and gave her review of the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Her secondary poop spot was... I've told people this before.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shermie had arthritis in her hips.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so when she could manage to pee in her box, she just couldn't poop properly in her box because she couldn't actually physically get in her box.
[SPEAKER_15]: So sometimes she would just wait until people were around and take a poop in the hall.
[SPEAKER_15]: Look, I have shat!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Dan let me sleep in the next day and he went to have her cremated.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because actually in Citrus Heights, if a pet is under 15 pounds, then you can just throw them in the dump and he's like...
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, a lot of love for you in our chat room as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Live.VogNetwork.com Critical Myth, R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie, Orange Ride, R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie, Actdeft, You Shall Be Missed, DDR Dollar Bill, Still Want to Say Sorry About Shermie, City Vampire, I'm Sorry, Dark Sakura, Dark Tetsuya, R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie, Black Wolf, Shermie had amazing parents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of love from the listeners as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I know it's hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Most cats aren't so lucky.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd say what was funny too is that I was actually, because you know, basically the reason I wasn't here Sunday is because I had cramps so debilitating I could not walk.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it was literally, I felt like someone had put my girl bits in a vice and, you know, was trying to get orange juice from them.
[SPEAKER_05]: La la la la la.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: but I had ended up just sitting down on the floor you know because I couldn't move and it was the most comfortable spot and Shermie padded right over and she liked to sit in between my legs for some weird reason and put her head on my thigh which I've got pictures of her doing it and sticking out her tongue and being cute and she just sat in my lap like that for like an hour and we just hung out and
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, not to be morbid, but maybe she knew.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, they know.
[SPEAKER_15]: When a cat knows that he or she is going to go, they stop eating.
[SPEAKER_15]: They go to the same spot over again.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I was getting that feeling with Shermie.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why the first time I picked her up and brought her in the computer room with me, and she was like, oh, okay, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, it's funny, she wouldn't eat her regular cat food, but she'd still eat the treats from my fingers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a video of that too on Facebook of her eating treats and making the kitty wants nom face.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, my baby.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're not going to get another cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: It's also, you know, and I hate to put it in terms like this, but are you going to, you know, immediately replace your cousin if they die?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to go to the store and buy a new cousin.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or if one of your friends, you know, she's a member of my family.
[SPEAKER_15]: And maybe it's, you know, some people are just like, oh, it's just a cat.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can get another cat.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, but they have their own personalities.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I had her for 14 years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a teenager.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, she's a whole lady, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, 14 years ago was PlayStation 1, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was about that era.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dreamcast, that's when Dreamcast were coming into your house.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Shermie used to sniff at the VMUs, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, you know, she's a good cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yes, it is a video game show, you guys, but sometimes, you know... She's named after a video game, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: She is named after a video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is Shermie, for those that may not know?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, um... Shermie was one of the characters in the King of Fighters series, the one with the dancer type with the hair in front of her eyes.
[SPEAKER_15]: But when we got Shermie, the adoption paper said Sherman.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, I'm not naming my cat Sherman.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nina Little didn't know she would become the size of a Sherman tank.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_15]: So, and I wasn't necessarily going to name her after Sherman from, you know, Mr. Peabody.
[SPEAKER_15]: So she'd go back in the Wayback Machine.
[SPEAKER_15]: But she, we were like, well, we need a good name for her.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so Shermie popped up and it seemed to fit her.
[SPEAKER_15]: She was graceful at one time.
[SPEAKER_15]: At one time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to go AFK a minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: At some point, go say hi to the chatters.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a lot of very kind things to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I've been reading it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think we'll help.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thank you for sharing the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, if you do a show for 478 episodes, we're on at 478, you know, the listeners start to get to know you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We start to get to know them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we want to share these big moments that happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: We always liked you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we like Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love Shermie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_15]: She was... I remember when she actually... Because she would sit on my feet sometimes.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I remember when she actually got out of her box and sat on your foot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of her bed.
[SPEAKER_15]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Duke Nukem in our chat room puts it very well video game podcast or not life isn't all about video games sometimes stuff like that happens and intervenes for the games and we all understand no I know you guys understand I'm saying that mostly for the benefit of the new people who might be hearing OLR for the first time because you know every week somebody's gonna hear it for the first time like what is this show I just downloaded all they talk about is dead animals ah but it's it's much more than that guys hopefully that story kind of tells you the family that we've built up here over the years so sure sure is my baby
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Especially, and just to share a little personal thing, I mean, Dan and I have been trying for a couple years to conceive.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, mostly I've been doing the work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because... All right, we'll leave it at that, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: We all know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate when people go, we're pregnant, when really the wife is pregnant.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're not carrying that baby, dude.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, but he has to put up with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, um, but I mean, Shermie was pretty much, you know, if without that cat, I think I would have been a big wreck.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, and now I'm like, I don't want any kids.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want more cats.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm clearly not going to get another cat, at least until after we move from the house, which will be after December.
[SPEAKER_15]: and I'm gonna be a rescue just to give a little plug here the animal outreach out here in California they're actually in Placer County they are a no-kill shelter that's where I took Donut or Batcat or Bruce whatever people want to call him there's a little kitten I rescued from the dumpster outside my synagogue
[SPEAKER_15]: They are a no-kill shelter.
[SPEAKER_15]: They get animals fixed shots and take them to PetSmart to have them adopted out.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I would say anyone in the Northern California area, give them your support.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you're going to get a cat or a dog, go through animal outreach.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're really good people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf in our chat room says, For those of us without kids, our pets are our kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put up just as many pictures on Facebook of my babies as my friends do of their babies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's a really good point.
[SPEAKER_15]: When I come back, I'll spam chat with pictures of Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds great.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need an OLR pet community of some sort.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe I'll make a... Why don't we have a Tumblr?
[SPEAKER_05]: A pet Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_05]: A pet Tumblr?
[SPEAKER_05]: OLR pet Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_05]: You work out all them specifics and we'll work that.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll name this episode Cat Shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ragenator says we should dedicate this episode to the memory of Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cat Poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cat Poop?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll name it Cat Poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's probably take it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft in our chatroom says Petsagram.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there's a good point to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Without deviating too much, I finally did the sheep thing and I got an iPhone 5 over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's husband sold it to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: My 4, the button was broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: The camera was broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I haven't had a camera on my phone for like a year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what's the first thing I did with my iPhone 5?
[SPEAKER_13]: Take cat pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Redownloaded Instagram.
[SPEAKER_05]: Took a picture of Maruko in the kitty bed and put, I'm back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you decided to purchase another phone from a company whose phone broke in a couple years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, admittedly, I didn't use a case or anything protective with it, and that's a long story.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it's kind of my own fault.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get an OtterBox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny enough, Alan bought one for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good, because OtterBox is seriously... I'm on my second OtterBox.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not because the last one broke.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was because actually the rubber surrounding it broke and not the thing itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's skip into video games a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before we get to our gaming weeks, we usually have a kickoff topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, we've already been talking a little bit, but let's have a game-related kickoff topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, I'm going to put you on the spot because you put up this very cryptic tweet over the last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And obviously, I perked up because it had the word Disney in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki, I don't know if now is the time you can tell me to F off, but what is this tweet all about?
[SPEAKER_05]: You said Disney Universe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney Infinity is a new property from Disney that's coming out next year in the spring or summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to start tying in with all their movies that they come out with animated and stuff, including re-releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wreck-It Ralph?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, like I said, next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because they're going to release, isn't Little Mermaid on deck to be re-released in 3D and all that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's the next one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's Cars, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think that's the next Pixar movie to be done in 3D or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, basically, because I don't know too much about it yet, and there's a lot of speculation to what it is, and I mean, I know a little bit, but it's basically their version of Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's a game of some sort, I assume some sort of adventure game, although I don't really know what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: They're starting off with some weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would think it's like Mickey Mouse and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe those are in the starter kits or something like that, but it's basically the Cars characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also Pirates of the Caribbean characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else was there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Later on in the fall, they're going to be doing stuff for Frozen, which is their new animated movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's their big movie for next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wreck-It-Ralph
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Tangle was two years ago at this point, because technically it came out Christmas of the year before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, last year was Winnie the Pooh, and this year is Wreck-It Ralph, and next year is this Frozen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so Frozen, and they've had some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the characters I did see that they mentioned, Jack Skellington, Mickey from the whole Sorcerer's Apprentice stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantasia?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they said Sorcerer Mickey or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, as much as I might want to sit here and roll my eyes, it does make a heck of a lot of sense for Disney to cash in on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, obviously, you put the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spyro and Skylanders, say what you will about the game and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Makes them a buttload of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes them an assload of money when you don't even know these characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody has any attachment to these characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: These characters were made up for this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spyro being the one lone distant exception.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even...
[SPEAKER_05]: And put Spyro side by side with Mickey Mouse or Jack Skellington or any of the characters you mentioned.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the power of the people.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think people are...
[SPEAKER_04]: are consumer whores over Skylanders characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do not even understand how many consumer whores there are for anything Disney.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disney did have that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that was the one that was called Disney Universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did have that game last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't going to win any Best Game of the Year awards or anything, but for a family game, pick up, go, it served its purpose.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, so I could totally see that type of engine in that game taken on this, you know, because that game was set, it had a very LittleBigPlanet-esque element to it where you could kind of dress the characters up and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it wasn't as detailed as LittleBigPlanet, but like, you know, TigerClaw in chat saying, no Tron characters, well, Disney Universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is only, they only have, you know, the first and second wave stuff announced so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney Universe did have the Tron character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, LittleBigPlanet actually had Tron characters too.
[SPEAKER_04]: They still could do that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they think about it, they probably have a Tron movie in the works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know they have another Tron movie probably in a couple years.
[SPEAKER_04]: If not an animated movie or something to cash in on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That animated series is pretty awesome, which I guess it restarted recently and I have to go catch up on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they renew it for another season?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's a new season or if it's the second half, like the fall season or something like that, but yeah, it's still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you said when you were at Disneyland you saw a lot of the Skylanders stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw like a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was interesting because, you know, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it might have been downtown Disney.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do see a little more bleed over in downtown Disney.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the same time, though, I really hate dealing with Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just more of a... It's gonna be all these pieces.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an internal thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that the toy industry does not line up well with the way things are done in the game industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_04]: hundreds of SKUs hundreds well it's not that everything's assorted so unfortunately our system the way it's set up there's no way to set up hey you're going to get random stuff in this box so you have to sell it by the case quantities that come in thankfully the case is 6 or 12 for the characters but
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a receiving nightmare because the way they do it is that case has a UPC on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That UPC you have to use for each individual character that you order.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if I order 12 of this UPC, we get in one box with that UPC.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it looks like we're getting one twelfth of what we order.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Suddenly Kingdom Hearts is being recognized by Disney again.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very exciting.
[SPEAKER_15]: They thought that it was like a Jedi one, but when you pull up on the receipt, it says Kingdom Hearts Mickey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_15]: There's two other pins that I saw online, but they weren't in the park.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome if they did like a LucasArts, Kingdom Hearts type crossover, like have one of the worlds be Star Wars world or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go crazy now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Muppets world would happen before Star Wars, because Muppets is Disney now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe Pixar's next movie is the Monsters, Inc.
[SPEAKER_05]: prequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_15]: I played some Espegaluda, which I'm actually now in my head thinking of it as ESP Eagle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Espegaluda?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because Garuda would be Eagle.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm thinking it's Psychic Eagle.
[SPEAKER_15]: So Espegaluda.
[SPEAKER_15]: And...
[SPEAKER_15]: I played, of course, WoW.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fucking Pandas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that what the expansion's called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking Pandas.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I finally did Heroics, by the way, which were pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did this new Sholomance, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: it's actually really well done I liked it played Mass Effect 3 I would play more Mass Effect 3 if it wasn't that the stupid EA servers won't connect I'm going to try Alan's suggestion and try to connect to my Mass Effect 2 but I never had this problem until the patch
[SPEAKER_15]: So, it's clearly something having to do with the patch.
[SPEAKER_15]: In my estimate.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've bought DLC that I can't use because I can't get into single player.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it won't let me play for my saved game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Low origin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Low, low origin.
[SPEAKER_15]: More like fuck origin, you know?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um... And, uh... I...
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, not much of anything else.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like, I'll sit and play something, but I really have tried not to be at my house too much this past week, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Understandable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any playthroughs of stuff that you've watched, Dan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you and Dan like to watch these playthroughs.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's obsessed with Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I cannot get... He's beaten it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's like, oh, it wasn't much harder this time, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of playthroughs, I should give this a shout out.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an important shout out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But shout out to everybody who participated with Extra Life this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, I mean, there were tons of playthroughs all over the internet for a great cause this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think most of those marathon fests and so forth are probably winding down around now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But props to all you guys who participated with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a great cause.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really want us to do something like that at some point.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even our buddy Breslow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: You raised $3,300?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not a bad chunk of change.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I'd played more, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played, let's see, lots of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I worked on a giant roller coaster the entire week, and I pretty much finished it, although HitStone was working on some stuff, so I don't know if they go check to see if it's still working again.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then also a giant marquee with Chasing Lights.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had those on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also play Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I managed to pull off Streak Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That means I did not lose one single lunch game that I played against my coworkers in Call of Duty to their dismay, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I'm rubbing it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to go for Streak Month, however, I can't play on Monday because I have to go look for costume stuff for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you doing for Halloween?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we'll see if we're going to be too lazy about it or not, but we're going to do costumes for the Yip Yips from Sesame Street.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But then, so it's that and then some like styrofoam balls for the eyes and pipe cleaners.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, so it's really easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just kind of doing the impression, I guess, would be... Just saying, if you ever get hard up for ideas, the chatters would love to see the tingle thing happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's not going to happen just because, once again, I mean, this is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, here's what we've got, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the three costume backup plan ideas that we have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily something that... Obviously, it's not going to be something that we do this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Italian Spider-Man, because that's going to be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is Italian Spider-Man different from Spider-Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you not seen Italian Spider-Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: Giant Cardboard Robot You're not one to say no to a challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really want to buy painter's stilts, so probably not going to do that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be funny to do the yippee-yips if we can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we may do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm not entirely broke right now, but I could be doing other things right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the chat room is trying.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf in our chat room says, Let's say, just as a hypothetical, if I paid for Loki's airfare, accommodations, and Dragon Con badge, would he cosplay as Tingle at Dragon Con?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I would if you paid for all of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, I would.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fail to understand, though, that I can't travel, remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's... There's no one of the difference about having the baby and having the kitty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody can come watch the kitty and you can leave them on their own for so long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can do that with the kid later on, but not right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Delorean
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also I did play a little bit of the PlayStation All-Stars Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just played one ranked match and did the tutorial.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it is similar to the Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the problem with that game, I mean, playing with four people that I don't know, it's very chaotic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really know any of the characters' moves or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: The tutorial doesn't really... It just basically tells you, okay, this button's a hit, this button's to throw people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you kind of have to figure it all out.
[SPEAKER_05]: How long is that thing going for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have yet to jump on board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten more days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so I've still got some time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so you've got time on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe during break I'll go set the PS3 up to download that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not on... Well, yeah, PlayStation Plus, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I have PS Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, it's cross-play, so you can play against people that have the PS3 version and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else did I do?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I worked a little bit more on the whole DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep thinking about it, and I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll try to be quick because I know we're running long tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's some new things I want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, let me get the old out of the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing more World of Warcraft, Mr. Pandaria.
[SPEAKER_05]: And while I overall do...
[SPEAKER_05]: And while overall I do love fucking pandas
[SPEAKER_05]: Good lord.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I played Mists of Pandaria or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: As much as I love the expansion, dailies are going to drive me fucking insane.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm done with dailies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you want to get the best gear in the game, you've got to do the dailies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm so over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I want to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Despite DarkSakura's issues, I'm actually able to play even though it will take me like five minutes to connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally, it will connect on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to play more on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe the days are here where it's easier to do it on Xbox Live than it is the PC, but believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been really enjoying this expansion content and even though the collectors are such assholes, like every time they show up as the enemy, you're like,
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_05]: Praetorians are such dicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, he's possessed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But otherwise, Mass Effect 3 is great So let's talk about new stuff One game that I know y'all probably saw the review on Vognetwork.com of And if you haven't seen it yet, you should go Like, go check out Vognetwork Because not only am I reviewing games But we've got reviews up of TV shows and comic books And audio dramas Everything geek you can think of It's there at Vognetwork.com And there's plenty more coming throughout next week And so forth So make it a habit to check every day, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, when you boot the game, it's do you want to go to the main menu or do you want to just start the party?
[SPEAKER_05]: And when I'm talking party mode, I'm talking pretty good mix of multiplayer things.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the two people dancing at the same time that you're used to.
[SPEAKER_05]: This whole dance battle tournament style thing where, you know, the crew battle where you can set it up with like eight people, I think, can all do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Jump in, jump out, high five, play.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really smart the way they did it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think it's going to get even better.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's unfortunate I couldn't see the game's full, full potential right now because Smart Glass, it's supposed to be one of the first games that's going to support the Smart Glass where while people are dancing on the couch, maybe you're not the type that wants to get up and dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can sit there on the couch and control what songs are coming up next through Smart Glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think that's a pretty neat use of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: using the technology wisely without whoring it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that's a smart way to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, there's a lot of good stuff in Dance Central 3, especially when it comes to multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the mimic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do a dance move and then your partner has to mimic it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Solo stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: When it comes to the solo stuff, it's kind of what you know already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's only so much one person can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, there is a comprehensive new story mode in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was a little silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people will enjoy its over-the-topness mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was a little bit like, alright, why am I playing this mode again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'd rather would just like choose the songs I want to do and dance to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to give the game credit, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can just go into the dance mode to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I did kind of sit there going, oh, it's kind of a
[SPEAKER_05]: This mode is actually put together really nicely.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a shame it's so silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I liked the concept that you were traveling through the decades because it really gave it a comprehensive song list.
[SPEAKER_05]: But to give you an idea how silly it was, you find yourself in Dance Central Intelligence...
[SPEAKER_05]: DCI, and they send you back in time to find the dance moves of the evil guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was a good excuse to put things like YMCA and some of the 70s classics are there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually thought the 70s... Did we get The Hustle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, The Hustle is in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, I have to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know what song is in the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: You will lose your shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Car Wash?
[SPEAKER_05]: To represent the 80s.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let the music play...
[SPEAKER_15]: Ice Ice Baby
[SPEAKER_15]: You know he's 45 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh God.
[SPEAKER_15]: Vanilla Ice is 45.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hangin' Tough or one of the new Kids on the Block songs is in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is silly, silly shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so as much as you can look at that and laugh and whatever, when you get into the modern stuff, I was not a big, big fan of the modern stuff they picked.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, but they, here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central 1 and Dance Central 2 had such good song lists when it came to contemporary stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was really slim pickings for three.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, some of the newer, like they have moves like Jagger and the J-Lo song and, you know, some of them are represented.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it didn't feel as modern club as Dance Central 1 and Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the good news, of course, if you own the prior games, you import the song list for 400 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to pay it again for number one if you already imported one into two, which is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Overall, I ended up giving the game a B-plus on VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: The strengths, of course, were the party mode, the instant stuff, the fact that I felt like there were more things to do in Part 3 from Part 2 than there were from Part 1 to Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was there a gay dancing mode?
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny you should bring that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, if you play Dance Central 2, a lot of the dances are very, shall we say, feminine?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central 3, I wasn't feeling that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe a big part of that has to do with the song list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although there was one song.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know that song?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to do these little moves called seduce and things where you're basically smacking your ass and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was still a little bit gay dancing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I liked it a little bit.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And plus, nothing is more hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care who you are.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have some real talk right now about Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing is more hilarious than when you get to that freestyle section of the song where it takes 16 pictures of you or whatever really fast to run up to the camera and start booty popping and then turn around just in time to see your butt back on the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know you've all tried it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then you need to try it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I still think, though, that nothing is as wonderful as watching you play the ABBA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, that's the sad thing, is that the 70s, unfortunately, did not have ABBA to represent them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I always thought Sony had the lock on ABBA because of SingStar, but then Ubisoft had that You Can Dance game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't know, I guess I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to hold my breath for Dance Central to get the rights to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire in chat says, yes, but can I bend and snap?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do whatever you want in freestyle mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says, I've never tried that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've also never fucked pandas like Rob has.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, what else new can I talk about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I went into GameStop this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was there and I had this impulse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to have LittleBigPlanet on the PlayStation Vita right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't going to wait for Amazon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to go get it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why didn't you just buy it digitally?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I don't like... That worked out for me getting Mass Effect 3 because I was impatient and actually got him to go down to the Amazon price.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ended up buying it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But not only did I go into GameStop to buy that game, but they had a Wii U demo unit up and running.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think these things are starting to show up at your Best Buys and GameStops and where have you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to get your hands on the Wii U, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll say this much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to get into the whole Wii U debate thing again because we're already running long but I will say this much I was surprised those tablets were a lot bigger than I was giving it credit for because in my mind I'm thinking oh that thing is kind of like the bottom part of a 3DS or whatever so I was thinking it was going to be like I didn't think it would be that small but I didn't think it would be that big either so I was pleasantly surprised with the size of the Wii U pad otherwise there wasn't a lot on the demo unit to really get a feel for the system the only thing you could play was the Rayman's
[SPEAKER_05]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: So was the controller comfortable?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really hold it for very long because Alan did the playing of the demo, but I thought it was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like bigger than a PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you do have to kind of get used to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like holding this small little laptop in your hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's almost bigger than this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's slightly bigger than this, and I'm pointing at this laptop.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Dell Mini 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's using what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: I apparently just got an answer from EA about my...
[SPEAKER_15]: Stupid Mass Effect thing, so I'm going to check it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to try playing Mass Effect right now during the show?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I can't play on the netbook.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll make that thing implode if you try to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It won't make it implode.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll just melt into a puddle of for fuck's sake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nate4322 in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Rob, would you buy it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking about getting one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm probably going to get one because I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't pre-order one, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how?
[SPEAKER_05]: So unless I can get the hookup, wink, wink, nudge, nudge, through friends, I may be shit out of luck.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can do what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait in line outside Target.
[SPEAKER_15]: All night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, Target didn't do pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_15]: We bribed our way into the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say that, well, if Rayman Legends is your type of game, you're not getting it at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out in March now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, that's Launch Window because, you know, Launch Window is like this, you know, if Nintendo has windows that large, I mean, shit, I'm surprised they haven't gotten broken into.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not debating the Wii U tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will talk about, though, LittleBigPlanet Vita briefly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't been able to spend a whole lot of time with it, but I will say I'm pleasantly surprised with it so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really does feel like I'm playing LittleBigPlanet 2 on the go.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game looks really nice, and the new touch mechanic, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: but the one other thing I'll say about it that I actually liked compared to LittleBigPlanet 2 is that it did not default to let's go online and play with strangers yay like no it defaults to play by yourself and if you want to do that you can but you don't like it's not being shoved down your throat to do that so I'm I was very happy about that that already has me liking it almost a little more than LittleBigPlanet 2 although I do love LittleBigPlanet 2
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get into gaming news already, but first, some quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twitter.com slash OLR and, of course, Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio if you want to be our friend on various social networks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's really it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The award nomination stuff is all over now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're just waiting to hear if enough of you nominated, and we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Stitcher's stuff goes up tomorrow, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll let you know on the next show.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: and, um, also, I guess they, uh, had already laid off 10,000 people earlier this year and, uh, I guess just trying to, you know, make up some of the lost money that they've had because, uh, they're trying to, I guess, save $378 million annually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny enough, somebody asked me earlier, we were playing that clip about the tester and all that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody asked me, do you know if there's going to be a tester for The Answer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I actually can answer that for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: The answer is no, there's not going to be a tester for.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the reason why, it actually has nothing to do with the quality of the show or whatever, or whatever easy joke you want to make.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when all those layoffs happened at Santa Monica Studio that majorly hit the PR department in that area?
[SPEAKER_05]: The people who did the tester were let go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatcha gonna do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're saying that they are going to be letting go 840 employees as part of their lens factory in Minocomo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, they do make Blu-ray players and CD players and DVD players and cameras.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of lenses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, do you think this has to... Is this the usual ebb and flow of what we see happening at game companies where projects end and people get let go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or do you want to go so far as to make the argument that the PlayStation 3's performance or lack thereof is to blame for this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's neither of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think all it is is just that they're maybe suffering losses in other areas.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they just don't have work for these people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or they decided, hey, we don't need a reality show that kind of is alright, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's costing us a lot of money to put this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really, we're not seeing much of a return on people signing up for PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I don't think that was exclusive to PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we don't have people coming to our network because of the tester.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's just cut some costs there and let's give people free games instead for PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger Claw in our chatroom says, do you think the people who won on the tester also got laid off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can Sony lay off game testers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yes, they can.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, go back and listen to the show that had Asuka was on the show when that was new.
[SPEAKER_05]: It ended up being the week before she was kicked off.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she said that they would get everybody hyped up about the prize and then the cameras would cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just so you guys know, it's a six-month contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: So technically, Sony was never under any obligation to hire those people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we talk about it like a couple weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was the guy that, I think it was the first guy that won, and he came out like smashing, like totally dissonant on a bunch of stuff, like talking about how they've made mistakes, you know, left and right with their properties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think we talked about that here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I remember reading that.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, you know... He got into PR, so he might have... I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't speak for the guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another thing to consider, too, is all these layoffs are in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we did have the PR layoffs that happened just not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what would have happened with the third guy that won because he was a very recent winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: But most of these guys... And he was an associate producer, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he was probably under contract somewhere or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: and as ShadowNextGen in chat says, any company can lay off anyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Been there, done that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck to those that were impacted by this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is never any fun to report on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, I'll use this as an opportunity to plug Bobby's show from tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: He had a great interview tonight with a game recruiter.
[SPEAKER_05]: and who was very motivational about how to you know kind of be resilient about what happens when you get laid off and kind of what not to do and I found that very interesting because he was very honest so I'm not going to give it all away though you have to go check that out Bobby Blackwolf show which will be posted to vognetwork.com at some point this week or look him up on Stitcher as well Bobby Blackwolf let's talk about Zynga real quick
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Zynga is having a very interesting year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their stock, their games, and now people seem to be abandoning ship left and right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of these people that's left is getting sued.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's the former Cityville general manager.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even realize there was a game called Cityville, but I guess that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guy's name is Alan Patmore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in this lawsuit, Zynga believes...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Alan Patmore uploaded company assets to a Dropbox account from his company computer both on the day before and day of his departure from the company.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's a no-no.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be information on Zynga's game mechanics, Cityville's performance assessments, monetization plans, emails, design documents, including an unreleased game design document.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Mr. Patmore went to a social game company called Kick's Eye, and Zynga is alleging, again, we can't say he did it, we don't know, but Zynga's alleging in these documents that he is going to use this information to directly compete with Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: A quote from the lawsuit, "...could be used to improve a competitor's internal understanding and know-how of core game mechanics and monetization techniques, its execution, and ultimately its market standing to compete more effectively with Zynga."
[SPEAKER_05]: Pat Moore apparently refused to sign a termination certification.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying this reaffirmed all of this information.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to block Pat Moore and his company from accessing the data and they want it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kixi, in an interview with All Things Digital, said they have nothing to do with the suit, but apparently they slipped this thing in at Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, unfortunately, this appears to be Zynga's new employee retention strategy, suing former employees to scare current employees into staying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one thing to take company typefaces that were designed for the company.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another thing to take game mechanics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's kind of different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's still not appropriate.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't help it if they had pretty font, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, I mean, let's say that if you did design work at the company, what's appropriate for you to take with you in master files?
[SPEAKER_05]: Technically, you did it on the company clock, so they belong to the company.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there is, you can keep your own work for the sake of your portfolio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just about to say, now, surely you can have like a PDF for your portfolio or whatever, but you don't get to keep... If it's stuff this guy designed, then he's entitled to retain a copy for himself.
[SPEAKER_15]: He just can't use it elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but if we're talking about information on Zynga's game mechanics, assessments of the performance, that's not one person.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what you're saying is he had a copy of Tiny Towers on his computer that he uploaded to the Dropbox, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I'm... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zynga... We're going to get into this a little later when we get to the Google Question of the Week, but I'm very interested to see where Zynga ends up in a few years because it really seems like that company is... It's abandoned ship fast over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: I kind of point and laugh at them every time I'm in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: While I'm at it, fuck Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know I couldn't use the Facebook?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how like Facebook has a separate camera application?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would not let me use it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says location services are required to use this application.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said fuck you and deleted it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll just use Instagram where it's optional.
[SPEAKER_05]: and like every time I turn location stuff off on Facebook and I've talked about this before if I want to advertise where I am I'll use Foursquare otherwise I don't see the need to always post every place I'm at including my home address so turn it off but it just keeps magically coming back on on Facebook I'm about ready to go back to Google Plus I'm about ready to just delete Facebook but I've threatened that about four times on this show and I haven't done it yet so I need to put my money where my mouth is I guess
[SPEAKER_15]: On top of that, Facebook has turned into Attention Horse Central.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pay attention to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook does exist on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's pay attention to your story, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is awesome because it's Sega.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sega!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure you've all heard of the Model 2 arcade board, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: There's some great games on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Virtua Fighter, well I won't say Virtua Fighter was great because I hate Virtua Fighter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you said great games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, well there's a lot of people who are fans of Virtua Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I only played that game to try to knock Kage's mask off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sonic Fighters, Sonic the Fighters was great.
[SPEAKER_15]: And one of my favorite ever games, Virtual Lawn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, there's going to be an Xbox Live Arcade and a PlayStation Network, which is a release game that's a Model 2 collection, Virtua Fighter 2, Fighting Vipers, Cyber Trooper Virtual Lawn, Virtua Striker, and Sonic the Fighters.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll tell you what my experience with Sonic the Fighters is, is Fighters Megamix.
[SPEAKER_15]: You could also play as the car from Daytona and beat people up with a car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I believe is another Model 2 game, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it was Home Only.
[SPEAKER_04]: That already came out anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Daytona was... No, Daytona was Model 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was thinking Fighter's Megamix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already released that already a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still another excuse to play this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, it's going to be... For Japan pricing anyway, it's 800 Microsoft points or 10 bucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure we're going to get it, so... Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need a Fighter's Megamix 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fighters Megamix was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just the fun thing about playing as a car.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a car.
[SPEAKER_15]: Punch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sonic versus car.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just thinking, I saw a Robot Chicken clip this week of Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they were... It was basically Ryu, I guess, telling people what to do as far as... He was scheduling all their fights and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the fights was...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ken, he's all, I thought I was supposed to be fighting E-Honda.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That says you're fighting A-Honda.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this is stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would I want to fight a car?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just punch the car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: He starts punching the car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this is actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it was like the bonus round?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was the bonus round.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so, let's talk a little bit about some cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, we always talk about...
[SPEAKER_05]: Holiday or not holiday holodeck gaming as like kind of the you know oh my god everything we've ever done in gaming has been taking us one step closer to the holodeck because we were always like oh my like remember when we were kids and we all saw mode 7 for the first time like pilot wings and stuff and it's like oh my god this blows my fucking mind Dracula X on Super Nintendo like
[SPEAKER_05]: The fire's moving!
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of saying the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine the spectrum of what's possible in the computing world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, look at how fast everything is progressing, how the engines are getting bigger and bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: The real exciting thing is about the people, the relationships, and the business involved and how they're working together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, there's going to be...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, better simulations, better... And, I mean, if you think about it, look at how far things have gone in just the last, like, 20 years, 30 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just been, like, holy crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, I mean, Super Nintendo was 1990 when that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, like, 92 would have been right at the height of, like, Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean... We're 20 years since then.
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine what 20 years from now is going to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, fuck, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or what did the Ultra H...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well now there's you'll get to make out with Garrus for real.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Ultra HD now is that new thing right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was reading on the internet this week that's the now approved 4K is now Ultra HD or whatever so that's what we have to look forward to and you know 3D is already a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure it's just a matter of time before you have an environment where you can have TVs on three walls so you can like look all around you and see things in 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean that's where we're going to be at in 20 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would basically be the Microsoft thing that they have with their projectors and stuff what we were talking about before.
[SPEAKER_05]: they actually are doing holographic television I was watching a special on it just like a month ago and you want to know what kind of creeps me out like now that I have an iPhone 5 you know what kind of creeps me out a little bit Siri like for real like Siri kind of creeps me out a little bit because like I can tell it open the pod bay doors yeah she's a little slow that's a rather insensitive thing to say to an intelligent agent
[SPEAKER_05]: See, but like she does shit like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the other day, or no, no, this is earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like just earlier today, I hit the little button.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, Siri, wake me up in 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she goes, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I set the alarm for, you know, 440 or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I just out of habit, I went, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she goes, I live to serve.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, I just talked to my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: You live to serve.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you programmed?
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you ever told Siri goodnight?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I never had.
[SPEAKER_15]: Goodnight to you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, we're getting a little closer to this Cylon thing that has me a little bit worried.
[SPEAKER_05]: Artificial intelligence has really taken off in 20 years too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you imagine that type of interaction in a Mass Effect type of game?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_14]: How much wood could a woodchuck chuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: No one cares.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hush.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because it could doesn't mean that it would.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't it just say, stop fucking wasting my time with stupid and mean questions?
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't she get offended if you go like, fuck you or whatever?
[SPEAKER_15]: You are entitled to your opinion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or, this is about you, not about me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can also, though, ask her how to make meth and it'll pull up the chemical formula.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if you go up to her and you go, hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like friends.
How you doing?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm testing it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Siri's thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Beep, beep.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that was boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me try one here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where could I score some marijuana?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have that schedule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Schedule?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't take the train to Marijuana Town.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Where can I hide a body?
[SPEAKER_10]: What kind of place are you looking for?
[SPEAKER_10]: Funeral services, mortuaries, swamps, metal foundries, cremation services, reservoirs, mines, or dumps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metal foundries?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this, Terminator?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, turn that bitch off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where were we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Holodeck.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can I stop Skynet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so holodeck gaming, of course it's always going to be the goal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that it seems to be the whole 3D is coming back, the whole VR stuff is almost coming back a little bit with that Oculus Rift stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course more of the haptic technologies are kind of taking off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure in 10 years time we'll have...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, some pretty interesting interactions with the computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to become more seamless.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's just like, you know, if you think about it now, you know, like 30 years ago, someone told you, yeah, you're going to be carrying around computers with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like everybody's like had that whole futuristic fantasy of like a wristwatch computer thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got like an HD screen in the palm of your hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically better than what you...
[SPEAKER_05]: 20 years ago, you had a 40 megabyte drive in your computer and that was like Uber storage for everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now you can store what, like almost a thousand times that in a little tiny chip in your hand?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm glad that our game developers are already thinking about the holodeck.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad it doesn't matter because the world's going to end this.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one believes that, except for crazy people.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, one thing that the holodeck may not have in it is Facebook and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because Microsoft is doing away with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: In their fall 2012 update, Twitter and Facebook are going to be gone from the dashboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: These apps are officially being retired.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's be real, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's talking about this on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's mentioning this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet if they had just deleted them, a lot of you would have never known.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because seriously, when was the last time you used Twitter on your Xbox?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you when you used Twitter on your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: You loaded it up the first day it came out and wrote a tweet that said, Hi from my Xbox 360 LOL butts goodbye.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was probably the last time you did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So instead of making Twitter and Facebook so terribly difficult to use in the Xbox 360, why couldn't they have implemented it into the dashboard?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, because that would have taken too much work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because before it was like, okay, you had to exit out of your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had to exit out of all this other stuff to see information on Twitter or Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Windows Messenger, you can get messages on that and you can see them pop up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But why can't you just have the same thing on the dashboard for the Xbox 360 where you can pop it up immediately, just hit the guide button or something like that and see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, because that would be too much work.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want you to use our shitty fucking internet browser, Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_05]: If a console really wanted to be cutting edge, you should be able to press one button and get a menu and hit Facebook and your feed comes right up.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of this loading time, none of this going out of the app, it needs to be embedded or it's useless.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's also kind of stupid that, well, I mean, I'm sure they're proud of Internet Explorer, but no one's like, fuck yeah, I get to use Internet Explorer on my Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call it the Xbox web browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because Internet Explorer doesn't mean fucking kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means fucking garbage is what it means.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because Microsoft is not going to give up on their branding, end of story.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically the thing I use to go fucking download Firefox or Google Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I use it the one time when I load in my operating system to download that fucking program if I don't already have it on Jump Drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, now here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say this about the Facebook application.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's one thing that I did think was very useful about that Facebook application.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could go in and you could instantly see what your friends, your people on Facebook, what their gamer tags were.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you were like their friend on Facebook and they connected to the Xbox, you could see their gamer tag so you could easily add people to your Xbox friends list.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was useful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope they will retain that in some capacity.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really all I can think of.
[SPEAKER_05]: of course they still have not upped the limit I was just about to say so I can't add anybody else anyway but you know if somebody decides to you know face if somebody decides to Xbox break up with me as this happened in the past then I'll have a couple slots where I can add more people and I would like them to be people I know on Facebook and what have you so let's see Black Wolf in our chat says hey guys remember we could watch videos on our 360 without loading a Zoom video app those were good times
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to make this stuff easier, not more difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their apps thing is kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's what bugs me about Mass Effect 3 on Origin and why I keep giving Origin a bad time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Origin, if you want to get it right, I should be able to load Mass Effect 3 and instantly go into a multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Instantly!
[SPEAKER_05]: Not five minutes later.
[SPEAKER_14]: And not have to verify my DLC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the stuff that's starting to bug me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what's going to keep the holodeck from happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bullshit is going to stop the holodeck from happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we're headed towards the holodeck, but we are having to go through so much bullshit to get there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, we can't authenticate your person because you've gotten a haircut.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come back in two months once your hair has grown out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how they were talking about, and I don't even know anybody that would ever do this, where you would leave your Xbox 360 on and Kinect would recognize your face and log you in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or I can hit the guide button and just log myself in probably infinitely faster than that stupid thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't have to have Kinect hooked up.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100, Matt in our chatroom says, at live.vognetwork.com says, where is my MySpace or GeoCities app?
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't GeoCities finally officially close?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's totally gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: MySpace, however, it's coming back, baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: to be fair I use the Twitter app or I use the Twitter app in Xbox about as often as I use well maybe a couple more times on the Vita but I haven't really used it on the Vita or the Facebook app because I have a phone I mean that's the thing kind of nowadays it's cool they have this integration and weren't they going to have it where you can send like screenshots of your gameplay and stuff like that on Facebook some games have that like NBA 2K13 or whatever why don't we just add that to all games instead of just you know
[SPEAKER_05]: here's the other thing like i'm now gonna access twitter on my phone okay ready tap tap wait there's my feed it's up and it's already refreshed that's how long it took me to get twitter up on my phone that's why i prefer to use my phone because you know how long that would have taken me to do on my vita you know it would have been and then like oh downloading new update but
[SPEAKER_05]: and then like, oh, going to connecting to Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Downloading tweets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like it doesn't work that fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray for you getting Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now make it work better.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, real quick, I was going to say it's even more ironic the fact that they're getting rid of Facebook and Twitter is how integrated that stuff is in Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of seems a little backwards that we're getting this Windows 8 dashboard thing on the Xbox, and yet they're not having that same type of integrations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe they're able to do it instantly on the desktop where they are having that problem on the Xbox for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_15]: Tangled yarn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you knitting during the show?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm crocheting, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excuse me, crocheting.
[SPEAKER_15]: But my ball of cheap-ass yarn has got a tangle in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never buy yarn from the dollar store.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, how many people liked Elder Scrolls 3 and liked Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_15]: Me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who liked Kingdoms of Amalur?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think we should give it too much shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: The lead designer for those two Elder Scrolls games, Ken Rolston, jumped ship.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's off with Turbine now, which is the developer for Lord of the Rings Online and Dungeons and Dragons Online, which I'm kind of playing low tour.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's got cherry blossoms, so I like it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically,
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm trying to see if I can... Yeah, he basically said they're, like, really excited to have him, and I guess that Oblivion... Well, that the Elder Scrolls franchise will just have to keep going with whoever the new people are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he didn't have Skyrim on his resume.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game turned out all right, so... But still, I mean, I'm not... This guy, obviously, it's a name I've heard before, and I know he's contributed a lot to these franchises, so I think any company's lucky to have him.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he's wearing a beret.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: which instantly makes somebody awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates of games you can look forward to real soon and it is getting to be that time of year, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already been that time of year for a few weeks now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean like next month is a huge month, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, there's a lot of games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week, of course, we had Skylanders Giants come out today along with all those wonderful packs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was on PS3, Xbox 360, the Wii, and the 3DS and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Vita this week, we get Street Fighter X Tekken.
[SPEAKER_04]: On PC, PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, Medal of Honor Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: On PlayStation 3, Xbox 360 and the Wii, Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they have a bundle with this
[SPEAKER_04]: FearMasterGun, it senses your fear your fear of playing a mediocre game but it senses it
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be a gun for Silent Hill or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A fear gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It senses your heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically the Nintendo sensor thing that never came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's the Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it's the Vitality Sensor for Cabela's.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they also have Cabela's Hunting Expeditions on the same systems as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that was something that was originally being developed for the Vitality Sensor, but when that kind of went away,
No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Dance Disney Party on Xbox 360 and Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero Escape Virtue's Last Reward on 3DS and the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what else we got here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also this week, Myst on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's been delayed a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully it's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naughty Bear Double Trouble on PS3 and it's both mediocre Naughty Bear games.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh just see here Forza Horizon on Xbox 360 as well as the collector's edition of that um what else we got here uh Super Monkey Ball Banez Splits on the Vita
[SPEAKER_05]: They are still trying, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: They are trying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smart as on the... Not smart ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smart as.
[SPEAKER_04]: With one S. On the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's supposed to be a brain training game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got some controller kind of game combos.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're re-releasing the God of War Saga Collection with a red DualShock controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also have the Infamous Collection with a metallic blue controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was the last one?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was another one of their collections that they released with a silver controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those games are already out anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: And last but not least, Professor Layton and the Miracle Mask on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zona of the Enders HD Edition Muvlove
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Muv Love and Muv Love Alternative.
[SPEAKER_05]: out on the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that Muv Love or Muff Love?
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost said Muff Love, but it is Muv Love.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say it's an anime, but then again, yet again, here we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is too great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to post a screenshot chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so sorry to the podcast listeners who can't see this, but look this game up.
[SPEAKER_05]: MUV-LUV, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because look at this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got these Japanese girls in school outfits, da-da-da-da-da, and this one is sucking on a hot dog in the corner, and then what the fuck
[SPEAKER_05]: What the fuck is this bitch down here?
[SPEAKER_05]: She's in a barrel or a bundle of sticks or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got to post that for the chatties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is absolutely amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now wait, what's Muv Love Alternative?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that going to be the one with the dudes on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't even the same game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's like chick with the sword.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same, but that doesn't even look the same at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: So maybe it's like the dark version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like one's all about love and one's about killing.
[SPEAKER_15]: One's like the cutesy, happy universe.
[SPEAKER_15]: The other's like the cyber baby universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I need help.
[SPEAKER_05]: Live chatters.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys tend to know this stuff when I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is muv love?
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody tell me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got to know now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't say a lot about these games on the... It's an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, does that mean... An adventure through panties?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait, here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there's a YouTube here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Every anime game ever!
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, that told me nothing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, Total Eclipse...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that totally summed it up for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like, oh, it's even bigger, even more love, something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Play it again.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, don't play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason says it's a visual novel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Read Japanese porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and to be fair, that is definitely a bundle of straw and not necessarily a barrel.
[SPEAKER_15]: For the record, I have bought a Japanese digital novel that they had in the US.
[SPEAKER_15]: They put it on Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, right, right.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was by the guy who created Cobra.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 3 this week in Japan also gets Heartful Simulator Pachislot to Heart 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pachislot means, you know what, pachinko game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two Hearts Anime Series Dark Souls with Atorias of the Abyss Edition I'm assuming that's the Dark Souls DLC bundled with a regular game Borderlands 2, Bioshock in a 2K collection price reduction I'm assuming gearing up for the sequel next year and Killzone Trilogy also released on the PlayStation 3 again these are all Japanese releases this week on the PlayStation Vita this week Street Fighter X Tekken in Japan as well as Next Rev
[SPEAKER_05]: Kaigo Fukushishi Shiken comes out as well on the Nintendo 3DS this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: AKB48 plus me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, good lord.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a little girl group.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, is it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, AKB48 is like this, I guess it's kind of this pop group that keeps cycling in, you know, kind of like Minuto was, you know?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Morning Musume?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_15]: But Morning Musume was also like a variety show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, right, right.
[SPEAKER_15]: But AKB48, they're like top 40 list everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there it is, your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to the UK, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: As soon as I get to the list.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have, well, on today, which means it's already yesterday there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wanted to say it was Cairo, but it's Calro.
[SPEAKER_15]: K-A-L-R-O.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then on the 23rd, there's Hotline Miami, Killzone HD, and Medal of Honor Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_15]: On the 24th, Killzone Trilogy, PlayStation, All-Stars Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_15]: The 25th, Incredipede.
[SPEAKER_15]: and the 26 Forza Horizon Roller Coaster Tycoon and Super Monkey Ball Banana Splits.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not to be confused with the TV show of the same name from the 60s.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, thanks to the chatters, did a little research.
[SPEAKER_05]: Muv Love, it was an adult game on the PC in February of 2003.
[SPEAKER_05]: They redid these with the adult content removed on the PC, Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_05]: Muv-Luv Extra, Muv-Luv Unlimited, and then Muv-Luv Alternative came out a little later in 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm assuming this is some type of repackaged stuff, or it's like the game's re-revised, up-rezzed, or whatever, reimagining.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, because...
[SPEAKER_05]: They show later release dates there.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 25th on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess this game's been around a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just have never played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now I kind of want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to know what the girl in the straw is all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple more stories and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have, by the way, been graced with Maruko.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Maruko.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he finally decide to stop being shy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me scratch his butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stick his tail in the air.
[SPEAKER_14]: Look at my butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the closest I've ever seen him get to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: He must be getting used to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We interrupt this kitty appearance for more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so let's talk a little bit about Steam Greenlight.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got some new games that have been given the go-ahead, and those are 21 new games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of these are actually backed on Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but see, Afterfall, Insanity, Extended Edition, Air Buccaneers, Blockscape, Contrast, Flyin', Folktale, Forge, The Gianna Sisters, Twisted Dreams, which is Project Gianna, that was the one I backed and it's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, uh, Genorm, Genoria, I guess?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nomoria?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Nomoria, that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interstellar Marines, Lost Story, The Last Days of Earth, Mia Samada, Minor Wars 2081, Neo Tokyo, Octodad, Dadlius Ketch, Perpetuum, Postal 2 Complete, The Secrets of Grindia,
[SPEAKER_04]: The Intruder, The Stanley Parable HD Remix which is also supposed to be a pretty awesome source game and Yogg Ventures those are going to be the 21 new games that they're going to be adding to the Steam store at some point soon
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also, of course, the non-gaming area, which they added recently, is also added to Steam Greenlight as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you can begin voting on submissions for other stuff that's not necessarily software.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't know what exactly is on there yet, but I'm probably going to go poke around that at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: and last but not least they're also adding a new thing to Steam Greenlight which is called Concepts basically allows you to post your game without the $100 fee to gauge kind of interest in what people would want to you know if people would be even interested in your game and so if you get a lot of interest then you may pony up the $100 to you know have it actually greenlit and put on the Steam store so that's kind of neat sounds like that project's doing very well for them yeah sounds pretty cool
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, one more story for you guys, then we'll get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is another legal story.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is kind of, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Rushton, who was the founder and president of Sensory Sweep Studios, they were in Utah, he got sentenced to 12 months in the slammer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Find $1.2 million in unpaid wages to more than 100 employees.
[SPEAKER_05]: This goes all the way back to a lawsuit from 2009 by the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: Department of Labor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, employees claimed they were not paid in over 100 days for their work.
[SPEAKER_05]: The employees also alleged their 401k money had been stolen by the company.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Rushton has already served jail time for other charges relating to the company he pled guilty to one third degree felony charge of failing to file taxes and one second degree felony charge of engaging in a pattern of unlawful activity this is all according to the Salt Lake Tribune
[SPEAKER_05]: How not to run your business
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta pay your... That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta, you know, if you're gonna, you know, hire people, you do have to send them a paycheck at some point or they might get angry because they're kind of waiting on you to pay them to say they can like pay their mortgage.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's kind of things they want to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you probably want to pay your taxes as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially when you are the head of a company like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you can just write it off for your horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you're a singer, like Lauryn Hill, or who else got busted for tax evasion?
[SPEAKER_05]: They get caught.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guy who won Survivor?
[SPEAKER_05]: They all end up getting caught.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wesley Snipes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a big one too.
[SPEAKER_15]: But remember, that's how they got Capone.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's how they got Capone.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's travel to a classic time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe not as classic as DarkSakura is referring to, but let's go back a few years into gaming's history and a classic video game that DarkSakura thinks, hey, brats, play this game or else I'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can find it, good luck.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I can say tonight's game, I had never fucking heard of this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had never heard of this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: You've got the Namco collection, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Valkyrie no Bokken, Toki no Kagi Densetsu
[SPEAKER_15]: The game title translates to The Adventure of Valkyrie, The Legend of the Time Key.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it came out on... This is the Famicom version.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is sort of overhead-y, Zelda-ish, scroll-y.
[SPEAKER_15]: It actually, with the way the enemies appear, makes me think of Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I love the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I just say the other English name people would know this by?
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of the Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nope, that's actually the sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my bad, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is why I said two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So basically for the original one, you're in Marvel Land.
[SPEAKER_15]: and basically you have to get the Key of Time back from whoever stole it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It actually really has a lot in common with Dragon Warrior and the real-time combat system of The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, this was, it has absolutely no text in the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: There is a patch that changes the title screen if you've got the, like if you're playing it on an emulator.
[SPEAKER_15]: And look for the one that was done by DVD Translations, that one is the best.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, there is a sequel, and this is the one that people have probably heard of, is Valkyrie No Densetsu, which is The Legend of the Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this came out in 1989 as an arcade game, and then it came out on the PC Engine in Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it is the sequel to the 1986 Famicom game.
[SPEAKER_15]: This one also came out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: as part of Namco Museum Vol.
[SPEAKER_15]: 5, the O. And the PC Engine version came out on the Virtual Console in Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this one is basically a two-player game.
[SPEAKER_15]: The player one has Valkyrie, and the second one has Krino Sandra.
[SPEAKER_15]: which was romanized actually as Zandra with an X-A-N-D-R-A and was named um Whirlo in the English version of uh the prequel which was uh Zandra no Daibouken Valkyrie no Valkyrie Tono Dei I think is how it's pronounced um who's a green lizard and basically it's you know a lot of
[SPEAKER_15]: Over the World, scrolling, shooting, punching enemies in the face with your sword, going into little huts and buying stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's such an adorable game.
[SPEAKER_15]: If people don't have the O from the Namco collection, which as I understand the O is a little hard to find, get this game.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a really, really fun little game and it is fully translated and available in the US if you can find the Namco O. It actually though has a different ending from the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_15]: With the home version you do have a level save.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually have, Rob, I've got the Famicom version of the first game.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I have the HuCard of this too.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I was very happy to pick those up.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I mean, it's just really, it's a straightforward little, you know, adventure game.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's very Zelda slash Dragon Quest-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why, maybe it's the cartoony style or something, but I'm suddenly reminded of Willow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking about like, I want to play Willow again.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like all the little monsters and the little Valkyrie are all chibi and adorable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, I mean, but you can get super powered up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, you see how on this video here we're watching how she's jumping from platform to platform?
[SPEAKER_15]: That used to always screw me up because I would think that it was over the regular ground and I'd walk off of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I know better, but the first time I tried to play it, it was actually pretty difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to check this video out over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping some dude isn't talking over this, but this is the main version, so I'm assuming this is just a direct arcade version.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to hope it's without any dudes talking over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me see what happens here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this looks okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty much the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it definitely has that arcade-style interface, though, but okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, I mean, the PC Engine version is damn good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've checked this out at some point.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, I'll tell you where I first heard about this game is I had a gachapon capsule that was a little Namco figurine set.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan and I tried to collect all of them and one of them was a Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I was like, oh, this is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then it turned out that, hey, there's this whole game and you should play it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, oh, yeah, we actually have that because we have it on the Namco O. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zandra no Daibouken, Valkyrie to no Daibouken
[SPEAKER_15]: Valkyrie Tonodai I think I'm pronouncing that right and pulling this one up that translates to Zandra's Great Adventure a counter with the Valkyrie and that's the little green lizard man meeting up with the Valkyrie chick and that one though is a side scrolling game it's a lot different I usually I'd say that for any of them my favorite of the three is the Valkyrie No Densets so totally awesome game
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's the classic game and I'm sticking to it alright there it is your classic game of the week a couple of games there but we'll say Valkyrie no Densetsu as that seems to be the one that if you're going to go find this game that's probably going to be the one you're going to find if you want to play it in English it's on the Namco Classics which was the Playstation version and it's the letter O
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is a nice, obscure pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we're going to take a quick break, but don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio to come for tonight, including your emails, or is it lack thereof once again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, we're going to have some news on some things going on with Kickstarter, more lawsuit news, and you are not going to believe what happened with this PC release.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Google Question of the Week and more when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live on this October the 21st of 2012 with the 478th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: During the music break there, we can't play these on the podcast because, you know, copyright reasons and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I will say we played a song there from Second Detsetsu 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was giving the chatters a hard time trying to figure out what game that was from.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anybody ever play that when it had the translated cartridge?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I played that, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played through about half of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still say though to this day, Secret of Evermore was sadly hazed and underrated by the folks here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Secret of Evermore wasn't a bad game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I do understand it was a different, you know, it was the one square USA title that, you know, for whatever reason, people didn't seem to like it as much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, before we get into rapid fire news, you were playing during the break there this interesting music shooter game you were mentioning before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I had mentioned it on the show before because it was something I kickstarted.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was called Rhythm Destruction.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since they got funded and they're kickstarting it, basically, I think it was like five bucks and you get the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game, it's interesting because the way it plays, it's a shooter, like a top-down shooter, space shooter, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: All the shooting is done as a rhythm game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the enemies come up on the screen and you see a circle come around them and you have to hit them with the beat of the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it uses an Xbox 360 controller so they're mapped to the face buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then all the dodging of bullets and stuff is done with the analog sticks and your triggers are kind of like a boost type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're dodging stuff and having to do the rhythm game part, which is kind of really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's got music from Kyle Wardner.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing one that was a Kaa song.
[SPEAKER_04]: He shows up in the strangest places music game wise, doesn't he?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for him.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotta pay the bills.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not really sure where... I think you can buy it off their website.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to remember where it is because, you know, obviously... I don't think they... I think they're trying to get...
[SPEAKER_04]: onto the Steam store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they've done it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: RhythmDestruction.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's by a company called Curious Pandas.
[SPEAKER_04]: The group did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think you can... Pandas, you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Pandas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you can buy the game on maybe...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's a buy it now on the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to see $4.99 is all they're asking for when you pay for it with PayPal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, good luck.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like music games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like shooters.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase BRAIN.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some rapid fire news before we get to the Fugo question of the week, which tonight is all about Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Far Cry 3 Locations and Character Skins
[SPEAKER_04]: Far Cry 3 Far Cry 3
[SPEAKER_05]: Dirt Rob, Dirt and Water Sundermen
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: Slenderman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enderman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Ops 2 on the Wii U is not going to have Call of Duty Elite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because all the other systems are going to be getting Call of Duty Elite at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're kind of doing it as a free thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And instead of having to pay $60 for all the perks of Elite, you can get everything for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you just pay $60 for a map pack instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the...
[SPEAKER_04]: and subscription for the map packs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really why they got Elite in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, the Wii U is not getting the support.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, we're currently evaluating options for Call of Duty Elite to support Nintendo's Wii U game system.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Call of Duty Elite for Call of Duty Black Ops 2 will not support this platform when the game launches November 13th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which makes me wonder, what is borked about their fucking online?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty Late is kind of like this app thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're not going to allow these third-party apps for the Wii U dashboard or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what didn't make the show roll tonight that's worth talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear about the updates with Nintendo Voice Chat?
[SPEAKER_05]: and how they're not selling a headset they're going to be third party headsets and if you use the Nintendo Pro Controller there is no space for a headset so you have to have your Wii Pad with the headset and the Wii Pad and then your Pro Controller not looking good for Nintendo convincing me they understand online finally not looking good
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised we didn't put that story in here because I could have gone on a whole tangent about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, not thrilled by that news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be not so bad if that system supports Bluetooth and they have Bluetooth headsets and stereo stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or that they're not doing a first-party headset because they're going to support any headset.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently on the gamepad they do have a spot for headphones but not necessarily a headset type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can enable it, but at default it's disabled to use the microphone that's actually on the gamepad for...
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact we haven't heard much about it other than, hey, check out this, like, I don't even know what the fuck they're calling it, the Mii Plaza or whatever the fuck their community thing is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, check this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can leave messages for friends and games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what about accounts?
[SPEAKER_04]: What about, like, achievements and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, check out this, like, Mii Plaza thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you can leave messages for friends and games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's all it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that and a shop and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, here's something else that's not coming to the Wii U version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, the Wii U version is going to be kind of similar to the rest of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think, I don't know, I think something's borked with their online.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how it is, because this should be something that should be easily implemented, but it's not for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then last but not least, Obsidian.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've concluded their Project Eternity Kickstarter at $3.9 million raised.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess that's even more than Double Fine Adventures got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because remember, Double Fine Adventures had $3.3 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They beat that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Planetary Annihilation was another one similar to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Multi-million dollar raise.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got 2.2 million and the OUYA had 8.5 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost backed this but I saw that the game wasn't coming out until 2014 so I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just not something I want to back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need your games to be designed faster.
[SPEAKER_04]: well it's just that's kind of a long ways and and I'm assuming that you know they're not necessarily going to hit their you know date for that stuff because like for example the Kickstarter I did for my very first Kickstarter which was for VGHS video game high school they still haven't delivered the DVDs on that stuff yet
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, how about free games?
[SPEAKER_05]: We like free, and this is a very interesting sort of free game.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is being developed by NeoGAF members, you know, the big popular gaming forum, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they formed a studio called Grimoire Assembly Forge, and they're creating this parody on modern shooters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Dude Bro 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The actual title is, Dude Bro, my shit is fucked up, so I gotta shoot slice you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's straight up dog time.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's based off of a meme that someone was, like, complaining about something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, well, why don't you just go play Dude Bro 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: So someone started, like, making character art and started doing, like, box art.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like bungee ferret tossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody took the joke way too far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotcha, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, though, you want to talk about the joke going way too far.
[SPEAKER_05]: John St.
[SPEAKER_05]: John.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know John St.
[SPEAKER_05]: John?
[SPEAKER_05]: He is Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the voice of Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_05]: He will be John Dude Bro.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to play the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this the little trailer song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me play a little clip of it here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's straight up dog time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a rap even.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks very old school.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least in these cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like Commander Keen or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's actually kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where Duke Nukem got its start, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I like free.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation All-Stars apparently have been hacked into Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how this happened, but yeah, this is some modders.
[SPEAKER_05]: They developed the Smash Brothers, but they actually have some of the PlayStation All-Stars, but they put some other people into this as well, like Nico Bellic from Grand Theft Auto 4, John Marston from Red Dead Redemption, Laura Croft from Tomb Raider, Old Snake from Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's a hack.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they don't have to worry about licensing or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just put whoever the fuck they want in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kazuya from Tekken, Tomba, Isaac Clark from Dead Space, get this, Commander Shepard from Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's Man Shep.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a free mod, but again, you will have to mod and do all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think those mods, I'm not sure with the whole character skins and models and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of them you can do with just an SD card.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even need to mod your system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just going through a hacked save type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that might be one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really researched it too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, and one other story about Nintendo Land.
[SPEAKER_05]: The final little mini games inside Nintendo Land have been announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Captain Falcon's Twister Race, where you hold the narrow end of the Wii U gamepad upright to guide a high-speed wind-up vehicle towards the finish line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Octopus Dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't say it without laughing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a single-player rhythm-based game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You use the gamepad.
[SPEAKER_05]: You memorize the movement of the character on the screen and reenact the poses using the control sticks or the gyro sensor.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly, Yoshi's Fruit Cart.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, are you a fan of Yoshi's Fruit Cart, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just made me snort.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guide Yoshi's Cart towards the goal while collecting fruit on the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, that's not just a clever name.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see fruit on the TV but not the gamepad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like innovation to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, now you being a big fan of F-Zero, do you think that homage is worthy of, like, you know, they're going to get the fans excited about F-Zero with this wonderful game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they can stop being fucking cocktease.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what they can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope to hell that... That's a page out of Capcom's book right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That better be the secret project that Retro or whatever is working on is the new F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: F-Zero wind-up shit that you don't care about.
[SPEAKER_05]: At this point, I give no fucks about anything else.
[SPEAKER_05]: It better not be Pilotwings or some shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It better be fucking F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: We already remade Pilotwings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Pilotwings, the remake of Pilotwings is fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three goddamn things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't go that far.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3 fucking events way to go Nintendo way to not like even put any effort in that's Nintendo doing the least bit of work so we can sell some shit that people will buy anyways because we're fucking Nintendo there just needs to be a Captain Falcon game where all he does is punch people now that would have been a classic minigame that would have been great Falcon punch show me your move
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Pikmin 3 is going to be on the Wii U and no one is excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, that came from Iwata making that little announcement.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next up, do you want to learn about video games at school, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, school sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like school.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's a class that is at Rice University in Houston, Texas called Scandinavian Fantasy Worlds, Old Norse Sagas, and Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_15]: And basically it's, and I'm reading the quote here, introduces students to fantasy as both psychological concept and the driving force in gamer culture by having students read selections from Old Norse and Old Icelandic sagas in translation and as they play different quests in Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's pretty awesome because there's a part of the midterm where you get to give your best last but not least Just Dance 4
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: So yeah, I have actually just introduced a friend of mine to the video last night, so it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what you did, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You went there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have the album.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I have to say, look, I... The album's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of already over this, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really weird to turn on the radio on a top 40 station nonetheless and hear this song played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not as an act of parody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not as a, lol, listen to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not as, hey, this is what the kids on the internet are.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: You hear, up next, Psy with Gangnam Style.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought it was PSY.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think most people were saying Psy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because in one of the songs, it does this little thing where they say the name of the person and it's PSY.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: but actually it's a good album and I really like I think the song's called Passionate Goodbye it's a really good song so I like the album
[SPEAKER_05]: JustMyStyle
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, just wait until he releases his US album.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: He did get signed to a US label.
[SPEAKER_05]: Buying it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Justin Bieber's label, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That guy, though, not Justin Bieber, but Psy, you have to admit, he's super adorable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen him in interviews and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: You just want to pinch his cheeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I mean that in a totally...
[SPEAKER_15]: Bro Way like he's just he's really just I don't know there's something about him he's got a great personality the album seriously I think it's like seven bucks on iTunes and it was totally a worthwhile purchase for me not just trying to sell it but it was pretty pretty good I love driving to it I'll put it that way I drive very fast no I like the Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune soundtrack if I want to drive fast
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish they'd do another one of those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are we at?
[SPEAKER_05]: What time is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's Fugle Question of the Week time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: Facebook, smash it with Google+, and together you get Foogle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's where our segment comes from.
[SPEAKER_05]: We ask a question in our fan communities every week, and we read some of our favorite answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: The question was short and sweet tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, we've been talking a little bit about Zynga and some of the things that have been going on over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The question this week is, in 10 years, how do you think people will remember Zynga?
[SPEAKER_05]: What will their mark on history look like?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to know, and I'm looking for some serious answers here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know some of you want to take the cheap, easy way out and say, LOL, poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I'm really curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are they going to be remembered by?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to Google+.
[SPEAKER_05]: Redertainment says, I believe the answer to this question will depend on how many of the people who currently actively play Zynga games will in 10 years time succumb to dementia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, it's like 10 years.
[SPEAKER_05]: 10, not 45.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend668 on Google Plus says, Zing who?
[SPEAKER_05]: Already fading from my mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monster B says, what was Zynga?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Sean F says, no, people may not remember Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually a good point, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much longer is the Facebook fad going to last?
[SPEAKER_05]: Their stock sure doesn't seem to indicate it'll last much longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But people can't stop using it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, if you want to see more answers from Google+, head to our community, Orange Lounge Radio on Google+.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are some of the answers tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: and some of the answers we got on Facebook at facebook.com slash orange lounge radio for our frugal question of the week about Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I'm waiting for it to load.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, there we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes, I remember this story from Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'll forever remember them as the only company I ever said no to when their recruiter contacted me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably for the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: Codeman says, a company that made a very addictive crack kind of addicting games and secretly taking our money like a reverse tooth fairy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, you've given them money?
[SPEAKER_13]: Secretly?
[SPEAKER_05]: You just admitted something on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lauren T says,
[SPEAKER_05]: and almost completely alienating its loyal players.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very good answer from Lauren, a company that alienated its loyal players.
[SPEAKER_05]: How not to do... Why are you showing me animated GIFs while I'm trying to do this segment?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because this is in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is... It's a football player doing the... Oh, is he... I didn't even catch that at first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, can I read the answers from Facebook?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: RedTheHay says, it'll be remembered as that company that made those games like those other games but wasn't Gameloft.
[SPEAKER_05]: AZHP says, I'm guessing if people still talk about them in 10 years, they'll talk about Zynga the same way the people who talk about Neopets do now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when Neopets was a thing, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_15]: Lord, I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we were talking about how technology is advancing so fast and stuff that in 10 years, who knows if that type of gaming will be even popular because they'll have stuff that's comparable to what we're playing on consoles right now on the mobile devices.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire says, is that a legendary Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw says in 10 years they will be known as the one company to single-handedly destroy the concept of social gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty powerful stuff there, but perhaps.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burr responded saying, we'll remember Zynga the same way we remember MySpace compared to 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although honestly, to be in a retentive here for a minute, was MySpace really a thing 10 years ago or was that when Friendster was the big deal?
[SPEAKER_05]: 10 years is a long time in tech terms.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I never used Friendster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I never used it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never used it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Never.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt J said, they will forever be remembered by me as that company with those horrible apps I had to block which was responsible for the downturn of Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other answers here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Steven M says, Farmville, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitstun says, Zynga taught us an all-important lesson.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want your game to make the big bucks, it doesn't have to be original or good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just has to be annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Endwithville.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to read this long answer here from Matt J because it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Truthfully, in my opinion, they'll certainly be remembered.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel that they'll be remembered for a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, really just for Farmville and the legacy it created.
[SPEAKER_05]: It helped to create a market for Facebook games, really for social network games in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I do believe there were some before Farmville, but they never really got the light of day they have now until Farmville.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zynga will be remembered in the end for creating the Farmville phenomenon and helping to create a new gaming platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Farmville is the game that got so many into Facebook gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surely there will be some footnotes in the history books for Zynga seemingly stealing ideas from others and the lawsuits involved.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, some will remember the foaming hatred some in the gaming community had and have for Zynga.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, most will simply remember one little word, Farmville.
[SPEAKER_05]: That will be the biggest thing Zynga will be remembered for, Farmville and helping launch the Facebook social network gaming phenomenon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty good answer there that, you know, hate them all you want now, but when you look back on history, it's really going to be about Farmville and the social stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good answers from everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry I didn't have time to read them all, but a whole lot of you responded tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio if you want to read all of the answers, which were very good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll remember the day that someone drew a tank through their business and spelled out Sega in bullets.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry, that hasn't happened yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't say that kind of stuff on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want the po-po coming over.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wouldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you can remember them by the fact that they probably popularized freemium gaming and made it a little bit more popular as far as a business model that everybody's going to start using.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll remember the day that I blocked FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll remember every other day that Facebook has unblocked FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a little ashamed to say that I did play FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will tell you this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it to impress a guy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I never played FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never touched it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And when I blocked it, I never got another thing for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, my mother would keep saying, Why are my cows dying?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd be like, You don't have cows, Mom.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've never... Oh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Cow's Dying Now, Digimon, Dying... Hey, I love Digimon.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like Digimon better than Pokemon, I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tamagotchis.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you're trying to think of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's do some more long news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neopets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta correct something BlackWolf said in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf said, Alan likes FarmVille.
[SPEAKER_05]: Confirm.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, this was pre-Alan.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was another guy several years ago when FarmVille first came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he was really into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, alright, I'll try this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it's like, oh, I have to keep checking on these blueberries and shit every three hours or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: which is why I refuse to do the farming in WoW I can talk about this now because he's a thing of the past but he really liked the Farmville song which is so stupid because it's like the same five notes over and over again in different keys I remember joking about having a 70 minute soundtrack to Farmville and it was just those same five notes over and over Lord
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you staring at me like that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've never heard of that song.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've never heard the Farmville song?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Neither have I. I would like to not hear that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't go all this time and then be all like, oh, I have never heard the song and then not expect somebody to not play the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally expecting an awesome song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this is like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, that's like all different now.
[SPEAKER_05]: When did they modernize it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It used to be just these little tones that would play over and over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was fantastically non-generic at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody must know the old Farmville songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm not the only one that played Farmville back in the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that's why I refuse to do the farming in WoW.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't give a damn about your scallions.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Ubisoft, I guess they were ones to swear off DRM in their games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or they patched it out for the games that had it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they apparently didn't do that all the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Rocksmith just got released this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the PC version missed having the codes to activate the game inside the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't play the game, no activation code.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you know, people are like going, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, so they went to the Rocksmith forums and, you know, you have to go to a customer support site, fill out a form, attach a clear digital image of your receipt showing the store details and the product.
[SPEAKER_04]: And your credit card number.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just, it's kind of stupid though that they have this problem in the first place, that the serial wasn't part of the game manual or something like that, it wasn't printed somewhere in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hey, you know, no one QA'd the fact that these games went out without codes in them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how many people would be pirating that game anyways, because you're talking about such a niche thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're talking about a game that requires an electric guitar, that requires a special connector, so even if you did pirate the game, you'd still have to go to the store to get that USB connector to plug your guitar into your computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's just it's the PC title it's not even the console title it's that is like niche niche niche you know I mean yeah people are gonna some people probably will pirate it because they can but dude I mean come on I don't think that this is a type of game that necessarily needs that kind of DRM in there
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, especially when you make money in so many other ways with a game like this that has peripherals and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, I think I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of useless to pirate this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: To play it with a keyboard is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't ever tell a hacker they can't do something because you can remap the keyboard or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, it's pointless.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's absolutely pointless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you have to have a guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, so it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of ridiculous that they would even have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: But they did, and of course, they said, we apologize for the inconvenience caused and will provide any affected customers with the Guitarcade Time Saver, which gives players instant access to all the Rocksmith minigames.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Ubisoft, I guess it's one of the forum mods.
[SPEAKER_04]: So cool, you get free DLC to unlock shit in your PC game to make up for the fact that they fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hey, Assassin's Creed 3 is right around the corner, well, actually about a month away on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: More fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you know, if you're one of those people, you know, word of mouth is really going to hurt them in this case, and that's really unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least this is the title that they fucked up on in Assassin's Creed 3 or Far Cry 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still, you know, I think it's worse in this case.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's worse when it's a niche title like this that really has relied on word of mouth, I think, to gain popularity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, and you should be thanking these people left and right for buying your game on PC anyways, because once again, that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: This is such a niche game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see a lot of people on PC buying this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it just doesn't seem like something that they would purchase.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess there's going to be people that make music on their PC and stuff, but they wouldn't necessarily be wanting to learn guitar or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Ubisoft, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would think that you would figure out this whole DRM thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you've fucked this up before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Driver... What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Driver San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you not learned?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, the answer is yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have not learned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, speaking of the continued adventures of Ubisoft, Ubisoft actually filed a $1 million lawsuit yesterday against BEP Music, LLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what BEP stands for?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Black Eyed Peas, the band.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Boom Boom Pow, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually wrote a song that uses the days of the week as lyrics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is a top 40 song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if Friday can do it, we're going to make our song seven times better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, the Black Eyed Peas experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you know, but this was one of the dancing games that Ubisoft put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was on the various consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably PC as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just Wii and 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't even do it for PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or PC?
[SPEAKER_05]: None of that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No one gave a shit about PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all Kinect?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, it was supposed to happen on iOS.
[SPEAKER_05]: iOS.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently, BEP breached the company's contract The contract stated that the band agreed to approve or disprove the iOS version within 10 business days of request However, the music company failed to acknowledge requests for approval despite repeated attempts Ubisoft claims they spent $233,000 developing the iOS game That's how much it costs to develop a game like this, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just curious
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe the band felt burned by the other games and didn't want to do it, or maybe they just felt they were too good for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, this year we have the hip-hop dance experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is what it is, type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, that.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about some more Wii U stuff?
[SPEAKER_15]: There's going to be a Square Enix game that's done by the developer that's porting Mass Effect 3 to the Wii U. It says it's a AAA Square Enix port, but who knows what it is?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was actually listed on a LinkedIn page, which has since been changed.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_15]: But it will be a Squeenix game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eh, probably.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a... I don't care, because I'm not getting a Wii U. You think so, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Hitman's going to be coming out, because they'd be kind of late for it if they just started development on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Tomb Raider makes sense, because it's coming out about a year from now.
[SPEAKER_15]: They also mentioned a possibility of a Deus Ex.
[SPEAKER_04]: once again that would be really delayed I mean Deus Ex came out last year if Arkham Asylum that's a cash in on the beginning but no one's going to want to play a game that came out three years ago that just has some different controls in it well Crystal Dynamics actually already denied Tomb Raider saying that it would have to be completely redesigned so it would be a much later released game it could still be Deadline and Riptide because I think they're publishing for that South Peak game
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, ready for my tinfoil hat?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about, I know this is going to be crazy talk, what about Final Fantasy XIV?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the new one could be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: We still don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, monkeys could fly out of my butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything's possible, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But once again though, we're talking about a system that can't fucking handle Call of Duty Elite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Kingdom Hearts 1.5 redo.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I start farting primates, then I'll believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, though, you were talking about a game that's probably going to be coming out next holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be very well a title they haven't announced yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's... Let's see, I'm trying to think of... I mean, they have Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's other Square Enix titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just use your imagination.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chocobo Racing 2!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might get a Wii U if there's Chocobo Racing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talk a lot about Kickstarter and there's always a conspiracy theory or not even conspiracy theory but the reality that some of these projects may not turn out well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that kind of happened to be the case of one of the kickstarted projects that actually did get funded is a turn-based haunted house game called Haunts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was being done by a company called Mob Rules Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and um you know they raised um i forget what it was it was like maybe twenty thousand dollars and uh the problem is though that you know that it's been a few months or whatever um all of his programmers quit
[SPEAKER_04]: and apparently all the money has been spent because $20,000 is not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at least it seems like kind of an olive branch from the developer.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says he's still going to continue working on the game and that if there's anybody that's seeking a refund, he will refund them out of his own pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of cool at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: And things happen, I guess, but at least he's still moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: The majority of people actually have a product that they want to put out and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, you just got to do your research.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, that guy that wanted one million for an MMORPG and had no idea of what... Just like it was such a generic, I want to make an MMO that's going to be bigger than WoW and it's got things and races and items.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you pledge this much, you're going to get a special item.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I own a baseball or I used to play baseball so I know I can do this oh wait sorry no no no wrong case sorry but no you just have to do the research and they obviously kickstart stuff that you know there's a lot of developers that have pedigrees in developing games and stuff like that they're putting stuff on kickstarter you just have to you know be aware of what you're kickstarting I mean some of these companies like the one I you know like I said the rhythm destruction game
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like some people that, you know, some guys that are making a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you don't know if that's going to be done, but they weren't asking for much money.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sure enough, they got the game out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, you can't just go, oh, they're all going to fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just keeping that in mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, even if you do pledge money to Kickstarter, you always have up until that close date to change your mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've done that before with stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, eh, I don't want to kickstart this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can take your money out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just pledge nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is now taking a position at KO University.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is a project professor.
[SPEAKER_05]: He will remain at Q as a spokesperson, but it sounds like this is kind of his new path here now.
[SPEAKER_05]: KO did make an announcement about this and noted that his position in the Graduate School of Media Design will allow him to continue to produce games and further expand his expertise in the field of media design and innovative content production.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the stuff he's done for music games
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft does make a good point.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mizuguchi Sensei is what we have to call him from now on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point, good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, good luck to him in the new career.
[SPEAKER_05]: And at least, you know, as much as we might be sad that, you know, he'll have less time for games, although they're staying, he'll still do games.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least he'll be... He'll be grading papers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he'll be influencing more people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'll be...
[SPEAKER_05]: Noob, noob, noob, win.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's anything like it is here, the TA's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: All papers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You and I both know that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Popcorn's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should eat popcorn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm eating yours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com We actually got some emails this week, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com DarkSakura's gonna dive into the mailbag head first and pull out some emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: She thinks, hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna read this email.
[SPEAKER_15]: This one's long, so I'm gonna read it first.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dear OLR, I just wanted to chime in with my thoughts on a recent game I completed, that game being Final Fantasy XIII-2.
[SPEAKER_15]: Originally, I played the demo when it was released on the PS3, and I wasn't drawn into the game at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: They didn't really explain anything that was going on story-wise, and it seemed to make the game out to be a Final Fantasy filler.
[SPEAKER_15]: I also read some reviews that spun the game in a negative light.
[SPEAKER_15]: So just saying that the music in the game was terrible and that one reviewer in particular had to turn off the sound for a final boss fight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Boy was I surprised when I picked up the game at Best Buy Summer Sale and finally put it in my system.
[SPEAKER_15]: The story turned out to be really interesting with time travel being an interesting mechanic as a method to traveling to different areas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, if you have it, you need to play this game to the end.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played to the end, but I've played a really good chunk of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it is a good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do need to beat it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That brings me to a question for the hosts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you ever played a game demo that you ended up not liking at all, only to play the full game later on and absolutely love it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Final Fantasy VIII, except I started hating it again, but I beat it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought Parappa was kind of stupid at first, and then I ended up loving it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendogs
[SPEAKER_05]: First time I played it, I wasn't that into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it at a party.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that was really a demo, but that's the best answer I got.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, I've found that after hearing from multiple friends of how much they dislike Final Fantasy XIII, yes, the first game, then their impressions rub off on me, making me skeptical if I would even like the sequel.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I would have liked the sequel, sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thinking back on it, however, I really love XIII.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, the battle system wasn't exactly my favorite, but it was far from enough to make the game not enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now for a final question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Has a popular opinion about a game that you played had an impact on how you felt about it, or do you not let what people say affect your gaming experience?
[SPEAKER_15]: I honestly try not to let what people say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I try not to, but if I really dislike a game and I go read that the popular opinion's very good, I do kind of go, did I miss something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I not understand something?
[SPEAKER_05]: But that doesn't happen very often.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I have to say for now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for reading, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to cry again.
[SPEAKER_15]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's really sad to hear about Jamie's dear cat, Shermie.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure she led an awesome life with her owners and will be missed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rest in peace, hearts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, she led an awesomely lazy life.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what a lot of listeners are thinking right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I miss my baby.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is from Tybon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tybon here emailed you a few years ago, and I thought I'd report back now what we're doing here in the heart of Africa.
[SPEAKER_15]: My Xbox was red-ringed a while ago, so it's been all PlayStation here at the household.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's very hard finding new consoles here.
[SPEAKER_15]: All Borderlands and Skyrim marathons recently for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hope you're all doing well.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tybon, this message is brought to you by Dirt Garden, home of the never-ending empty plates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did we do research the first time to see if this was like a legit thing or if it was a troll?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we found out, yeah, this guy's like legit there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he send a picture or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, thank you for checking in, sir.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for still listening even after.
[SPEAKER_15]: Skeptical.
[SPEAKER_05]: And every time I read your email, I think of that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember the rains in Africa.
[SPEAKER_15]: Toto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Toto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, what's that song?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've heard a really good cover of it at a concert.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_15]: By a group, a men's acapella group called Straight No Chaser.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it something local?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're kind of the big thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: They do tours and a lot of them were, I think, Broadway performers and various singers and other things.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, look up the Straight No Chaser version because it's really, really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I want to just make sure our listeners... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to shame myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ads are going to be the death of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's terrible radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would think one of these days I'm going to learn to load this stuff in advance.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yes, I know all the lyrics to this song.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You were right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's...
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I know this one by his harmony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that song in Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but it should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_15]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's an interesting dilemma I'm in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, noes.
[SPEAKER_05]: A dilemma.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm interested in a new PC game that's just come out on Steam, XCOM.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like the demo, but I don't think it's worth 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I can either get it by other means or wait for the Christmas sale or not get it at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: My question is, if I wait for all PC games to go on sale on Steam, will publishers stop making PC games because of the lack of release sales?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or will they notice if people like me will wait for those games to go on sale?
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to send the publishers a message that their games are too expensive, but I still want to support the game makers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't want the lack of release sales to deter them from making the games to begin with.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think, your loyal turtle in Philly, Serious Turtle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a reality check.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game won't be $9.99 when the Christmas sale comes around.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game will be like, what is it, $60 now?
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be like $30.
[SPEAKER_05]: $30 or $35.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like best case scenario because I don't even think Skyrim went that low that fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, don't assume that the game... Now, I certainly am not going to encourage you to go to more nefarious means because then you certainly are sending the wrong message to the publisher.
[SPEAKER_05]: And plus, if you do that, I don't think you'd get to do the online play and all that stuff, which I think is supposed to be... I used to love the old XCOM games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really need to look into this new one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just, you know, I've been playing all this other crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: I think they're still gonna make their money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's certainly better that you wait for the holiday sale than pirate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's certainly the better of the two options.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you sending the wrong message by waiting?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to actually say not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you're not the gamer that was pre-ordering this, eager about this the first day, had to have your hands on it right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were other people that filled that niche for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are on the fence.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the company would rather have you at least tilt over and get the game eventually a little cheaper than not pay anything for it at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan Shadow in chat at live.vognetwork.com says by the way XCOM is addicting and TigerClaw says the new XCOM is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not helping you being able to resist buying it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm really curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of want to see if one of my friends has it and like go over to their house and watch them play and then see if I want to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is 200Matt in our chat at live.vognetwork.com though warns it's hard from what I've been seeing.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any more emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: Then let's get to the FUs of the week, because damn, y'all angry.
[SPEAKER_15]: FU to Origin slash EA and or Bioware if Bioware is involved in this for the patch that just came out for Mass Effect 3 that's not letting me and other people connect to the game to actually play it and also not verifying my DLC so I can't play the game that I paid money for.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sue.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh no, I've already put the three magic words on EA's help forum.
[SPEAKER_15]: Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've gotten two responses already from other people in the community, so maybe it'll greenlight it, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Heavy to my cold.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all stuffed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you get when you have a toddler in preschool?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't have a toddler in preschool or whatever, but I do have a boyfriend and he's sick, so F you to the fact that he's sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get me sick, anybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: He can't help it, but I'm just saying, you know, I feel like Dead Man Walking right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm going to get sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I'll have to try and enjoy the time off work while I'm sitting here on the couch with a fever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, lucky for you, you can take time off of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I take time off of work, I'd probably have to watch Josh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not really time off of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here's the other perk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I have a cold, I'm obviously snoring because I have to breathe through my mouth and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have to sleep on the couch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been sleeping on the couch for the last two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that means I'll have to tend to the baby all night long when he loses his bank and cries.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm up about once every hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't worry, in a few more years, he'll be able to take care of himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he can take care of himself now.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just too tired to find his bink that's right next to his head.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's like, I want my bink.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's under my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, why don't you get it yourself?
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in our chatroom is reporting that the Mass Effect 3 data pad hasn't been working for weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mine's worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm at 100% right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just you, TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uninstall, reinstall.
[SPEAKER_15]: that's actually what I did is I uninstalled and reinstalled Mass Effect 3 and tried to play it and what happened is that it gave me the same error before so I went on offline mode and it let me go into the single player game and then I later on was able to get into multiplayer but it since hasn't allowed me to do any of it again TigerClaw in chat says I've been playing XCOM on my Twitch TV recently
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one of those things I'm surprised I'm not into right now is streaming video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'd have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't you guys like to see me play Mass Effect 3 online?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't that be fun?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Tiger Claw, saying the galaxy at war won't load.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's actually, it was saying that it wasn't for me, so let me play everything, but now it's actually saying cannot log into servers or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you can hear it, I'm actually in the thing right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple more news stories for you guys and then Skype line and Twitter topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so let's talk about Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Minecraft's got a pretty awesome update coming out next week.
1.4!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty scary update.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course it's sort of Halloween themed.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did one a couple years ago that was also Halloween themed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're adding a lot of cool shit into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So first, let's talk a little bit about what they're adding.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the things I'm very excited about is command blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what the command blocks allow you to do is actually issue some of the commands from the admin panel in-game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can have a block set up, for example, to have a certain area set to peaceful.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no mobs spawn in a certain radius or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: They're updating all the different sounds in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're adding sounds for placing different blocks, for walking on those blocks, sounds for the enemies, all sorts of cool stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Portals are changing a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The nether portals in creative mode, you're going to be able to instantly go through them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Adventure mode, they're allowing you to break blocks now and you can also place blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're changing how they're doing the breeding stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're adding different characters into the game, including bats, witches, and what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wither and Wither Skeletons Creepers
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can toggle how long it takes for them to explode and their explosion radius, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then new blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got, besides those command blocks, beacons, which will kind of create that Luxor pyramid beam into the sky thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can give you different buffs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anvils to repair armor and tools.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mob spawners, as I mentioned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flower pots, so you can put, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Saplings, Mushrooms, Pots, Cobblestone Walls, Wooden Logs, Stairs, Item Frames, Heads, Trap Doors, Wooden Buttons,
[SPEAKER_04]: and Potatoes, Carrots, Carrots on a Stick for riding pigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can ride pigs and control where they go now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to have, I'm going to set up a pig cart racing track.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Different potions including night vision and visibility potions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maps now you can spawn them or you can craft them so they zoom out and create larger maps.
[SPEAKER_04]: And leather armor can be dyed so you can wear pink armor if you want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: and of course the new villain or boss character in the game, the Wither, can be spawned too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I'm kind of scared to spawn that because you can actually create it with Soul Sand and Wither Skeleton Skulls but he will attack mobs and players and he's got explosive heads that will actually blow up everything including Obsidian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'll have to make a rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: No spawning the wither.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just sort of blanked out and had no idea what he was talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like when you talk about Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I at least hear you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, bats are going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, those will...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and uh yeah very cool all right well one more story for you guys tonight and this is uh a bit of a sad thing uh we did lose somebody in the gaming industry this week and it was um a UK based individual Mike Singleton unfortunately passed away this week at the age of 61 he died of natural causes and this was after a year-long battle with jaw cancer
[SPEAKER_05]: You may not know the name, but you might know some of his contributions, including Space Ace on the Commodore VIC-20.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's to be confused with the arcade title.
[SPEAKER_05]: War in Middle Earth for the ZX Spectrum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Midwinter and Midwinter 2 for the Atari ST, Amiga, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the most recent things he was involved with, Grid, for the PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Mike Singleton, again, passed away at 61.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please, a tip of the glass here, a toast to Absinthe Friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Skype line is now open, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to give us a call, again, the Skype line is open, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to go grab the iPad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, do you have any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just some small stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were talking about having a change to the Xbox Live, I guess, service.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to do Xbox Live migration to anyone, I guess, and it's going to be automated soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what migration means is that if, for example, I'm in North America and I move to Europe, you can change your account so that it will, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Show the European Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which would be completely useless if you brought your system.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for whatever reason, if you want to change regions or something like that, then you can do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're going to allow you to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me quickly go to the phones because we do have a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Shane.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's up, Shane?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are two things I would like to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silent Hill Book of Memories is a piece of garbage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You probably would have used another word, but I know you don't swear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's also a piece of crap or a piece of... Well, I've already used two words, so it's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it so terrible?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're like the biggest Silent Hill fan I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not lately, because they've all been crap games.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, this weekend I watched Downpour, because I haven't played it yet, and that was pretty crap too.
[SPEAKER_03]: My boyfriend picked up the main game, and I forced him to return it, because I've heard bad things.
[SPEAKER_03]: So then I downloaded the demo, which, you know, not always indicative of the quality of the game, but from what I understand, the demo's really close.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's just, it ruins everything that I like about Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a dungeon crawler with breakable weapons, mixed up characters and it's got a store for goodness sakes that you visit to buy things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get your Diablo out of my Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and I expected better from this company because they did like the ports of Contra.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not ports, but like they did Contra 4 and A Boy and His Blob, the remake.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know, very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, BlackWolf in our chatroom says, quote, I hate Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane, back of the box.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that is not true.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like other things that are not Mass Effect, just not as much.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, what's the number two thing you want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Crap, what was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am greatly disheartened at the fact that they have confirmed no Shepard for the next game, and they also are saying that it's not going to be like another Shepard-type character, which leads me to think that it may not even be the same style of gameplay, which I'm very, very, very worried about.
[SPEAKER_14]: It should be the saga of Garrus.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a dancing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that means you're going to get this drastically different gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, whatever the niche is about these new consoles, Mass Effect's probably worked it in somehow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just worried that it'll be like an RTS or something that I hate or a sports game or a strategy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just gonna be I think it's gonna be very similar but you know it might handle a little differently might play a little differently like just don't expect the same like interface and all that stuff you see in the first one I think it'll be alright give it a chance I'll give it a chance BioWare made Mass Effect 1 after all and 2 and 3 Shane yell at them for me yell at who?
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyone who's involved with my Mass Effect not connecting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know who to yell at for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's been trying to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny enough, I know somebody she could yell at.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob is your answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know this person, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you off air.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need my Garrus fix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's not able to play multiplayer with us instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played some multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can't even play single player.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have more achievement points than Alan.
[SPEAKER_05]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or not achievement points, but challenge points, whatever that new thing is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not know.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf is trolling in our chat room saying, a Mass Effect with the writing team of Borderlands and Portal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Want.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, not as good as previous Mass Effect games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Borderlands is a good game.
[SPEAKER_15]: That just means that they'll throw in a lot of dirty humor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the seriousness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Technus Reality Check says, unfortunately, Bioware has to finish Dragon Age 3 first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Dragon Age.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like 2, but I'm actually thinking about giving it another shot on some system that I own it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know which one I'm going to play it on, but I got excited for the information that leaked out, or not leaked out, but that came out about Dragon Age 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's no Garrus.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Garrus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not all about Garrus like you, so there's no Kayden for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's no Kayden.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_15]: There are the little weepy emo elf boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played one of those in the first game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anything else you want to share with the listeners tonight, Shane?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently you broke our stream anyway, so thanks for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm proud of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I'm hanging up on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who am I talking to right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody, because the stream's not connected, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it did just reconnect, so hopefully some people will hear this and know that the Skype line is open again.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I say that right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we ever figure out if that was the host thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because obviously our internet here is not having issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's not our internet here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is either... Well, I don't even think it's our connection getting to the server because wouldn't that mean our IRC should go down?
[SPEAKER_05]: Our internet would stop working.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd get booted from Mass Effect or whatever you're doing in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All that should happen too, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I blame New Jersey the entire state let's try to go I think maybe other things don't get disrupted by little internet hiccups but the feed will just shut down if that happens
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, anyhow Let's move on Loki, did you have any last minute stories for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I've got some tweets I can do here No, I don't have any Let me go to a tweet from Actdeft that says Oh, the Wii U's first commercial from Europe
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know the Wii U. That's actually the commercial.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_01]: At last, a brand new console with a brand new controller that redefines how you interact with games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what is Wii U?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shoot at the TV like never before.
[SPEAKER_01]: Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin!
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice shooting.
[SPEAKER_01]: And say someone wants to watch TV when you're halfway through a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to watch the TV now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do both, and everyone's happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: See a different perspective with the gamepad and get closer to your target for a more precise shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this a real commercial?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a real commercial.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in here, but I wanted to point out something that I read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do notice when they say play games that you've never seen before or something like that, and they show Batman Arkham City.
[SPEAKER_05]: The skyline is ringing off the hook, so I need to get one of these calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, can you guys hear me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, you're very, very quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turn it up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: This guy's being a pain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we can barely hear you and the listeners probably can't hear you either.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, you're still quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll give it one more go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crank it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: May I have to shout it in this case?
[SPEAKER_05]: We can hear you a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, this is DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, DDR Dollar Bill, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, not much.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys mentioned earlier about you gave a shout out to those who participated in the Extra Life Marathon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I took part in that too for the first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_09]: How'd you do?
[SPEAKER_09]: I lasted for quite a while, but I dozed off at around six something.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but it taught me something very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, me and my coworker at work actually managed to raise a decent amount of money in two days because we just got the okay from our job to take part in this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And second off, it is so hard to do 24 hours of gaming alone.
[SPEAKER_09]: on some games because some games just bored the hell out of me after an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you try to do one game for the whole 24 hours or were you like, okay, every hour we're going to switch or how did you do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I switched it up about every one hour or two hours depending on the game and how I was feeling when I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what kind of stuff did you play?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't re-bought a new game in a while because I'm waiting on a new computer to ship in.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it was mostly stuff that I had to catch up with in my queue, which is quite a lot, but quite old.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, things like...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was catching up in Arkham Asylum for example then there was Red Dead Redemption things like Mod Nation Racers and even Infamous and then I went to the 360 where I caught up with some Rock Band 3 and things like Virtua Fighter 5 so a lot of modern stuff but that's good and were you live streaming this all?
[SPEAKER_05]: did you stream or were you not or Twitch or whatever one of those sites or were you just kind of doing this at home and trying to get people to sponsor you doing that at home
[SPEAKER_09]: Most of it's on Facebook, and I just stayed at home.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't really do the streaming or tweeting because, like I said, it's my first time, so I wasn't exactly sure what to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: And even raising $1 is a great effort for the cause, so congrats to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask you, though, how did you go about raising the money?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you just spam a lot on Facebook, or what was your strategy to get people to care?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had two days to get the money, so I just said, all right, I'm just going to post on Facebook, and whoever gives, whoever gives.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wasn't going to be picky.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just like, hey, just whatever you can spare.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care if it's a dollar or $2 or $12.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's whatever you can spare.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of my coworkers gave money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, assuming you're doing it all again next year, what are some things you're going to do differently?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get the okay about a month in advance.
[SPEAKER_09]: and then start doing a fundraising there and asking everybody I can think of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also would like to see you guys participate as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's kind of hard when one of us has a baby to do the 24-hour straight, but we definitely want to get involved in the charity effort.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, last year, DarkSakura and I both did a lot with Umlaut, and we're going to do whatever we can to help this year as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's something that we're really passionate about.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do want to try to do our own thing outside of the holidays, just because the holiday is a very crowded time for charity, but charity needs TLC 24 or 7, 365.
[SPEAKER_05]: so we do want to do something at some point we think especially with the VOG Network behind us you know get Bobby and Critical Myth and some of the other shows in on it try to do some type of and maybe not necessarily just games we have to really think about this but some type of nerding out for charity and I got we got to really put the put the borders on that but I think there's an idea in there somewhere
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good idea, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think anybody would say no to geeking out for charity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just have to figure out exactly how to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have one more quick question.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just a quick one.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it about World of Warcraft that keeps you guys playing?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to know that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pandas.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other people that play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just, you know, having the community.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not necessarily just talking strangers, but like friends or people that have become my friends through the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just, you know, being able to log in and say, hey, it's a chat room with fireballs and swords.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thanks for doing Extra Life.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anytime.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we do need to get in on more stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, there's a lot of charity events.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can't do them all, but we'll plug wherever we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1877 Game OLR, username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm falling way behind on some of these Twitter stories, so let me get to some other ones of these here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tigerclaw sends a few over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: One saying, UK man faces jail time for selling counterfeit Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'd read about this previously.
[SPEAKER_05]: A 41-year-old Justin Success Brooks, well, not living up to his middle name right now,
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, he did fraudulent sale of counterfeit Nintendo games, this is all allegedly, according to the Criot and Guardian.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was caught in an investigation conducted by Nintendo and then the UK Interactive Entertainment Association.
[SPEAKER_05]: He trafficked illegal Nintendo goods from 2009 and 2011.
[SPEAKER_05]: He made almost a million dollars in US dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was about 600,000 pounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: selling counterfeit Wii DS and DSi games he was charged with seven counts of fraud two counts of fraudulent trading two counts of supplying an article to use in a fraud two counts of unauthorized possession of goods bearing a trademark and one count of unauthorized use of the trademark is what that all boils down to he did plead guilty to all counts he's awaiting sentencing boy oh boy all right let's do one more call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, this is Braginator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, what's up, Braginator?
[SPEAKER_05]: Haven't heard from you in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know, it's kind of a long story.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of posted on what's been going on on the blog forum, so I won't rehash that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I, God forbid, I actually got my first PC game last weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of an older title, but definitely good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you guys would approve Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is a classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in fact, you should just keep playing that one and pretend it's 3 because then you'll be more satisfied.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm trolling, I'm trolling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Making the Diablo 3 fans mad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Truth be told, seeing that I don't have access to a PlayStation 3 for the time being, I need something to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was sure that Diablo 2 would run on my machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Saw that at the store.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of figured, what the heck, pick it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're playing the classics right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What made you choose Diablo 2 out of all the games you could have picked out there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I wanted to get a game legally as opposed to some kind of torrent.
[SPEAKER_11]: So torrents were out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of the edutainment titles they would give for kids definitely don't appeal to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm pretty sure that even though my new computer is a little bit more high-tech than my old computer that was stolen, games like Grand Theft Auto and whatnot probably won't run on my computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I kind of figured, all right, Diablo II is what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It might even be older than that, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very old.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to put a new battery in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't set fire to your house when it's crying out for a low battery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just be careful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, how do you sleep with that going?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I learned to tune it out, actually, so... Yeah, well...
[SPEAKER_11]: And I don't engage in any kind of dangerous activities in my place, but I never know what my neighbors... That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your neighbors might be smoking marijuana, and you don't even know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, the thing I really wanted to tell you about was you should check out this website.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're interested in getting games legally, especially old stuff that will play on your computer and, you know, safe, I would look into a website called GOG.com, and that's G-O-G.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Good Old Games, and they sell...
[SPEAKER_05]: tons of old stuff and a lot of it goes for like five bucks, seven bucks and there's some really good stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, they're trying to kind of cash in on the indie bundle craze right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that it's really an indie bundle per se but they have like an interplay bundle going on right now where for like 35 bucks you can get like 50 games and there's some classics in there like Descent and Castles which was a game I used to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great website and I have to recommend it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and Dungeon Buster says... Another game that I probably should get back into is World of Warcraft, if only because
[SPEAKER_11]: I did download the clients and go compare and try to play although the framing was extremely choppy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can say goodbye to your life if you get back into World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but well, the graphics have come a long way.
[SPEAKER_11]: More powerful.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game will be better.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Ragenazer, I need to let you go so we can wrap things up, but take care and have fun with Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: take care, bye bye
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's all hope that Ragenator gets the battery replaced and a smoke detector soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to do the rest of these Twitter topics because there's still a bunch of these here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I did the one about Tigerclaw and the counterfeit time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me read one other tweet from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: He sent a couple others.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually I do a two-tweet max, but these are both pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: This is about the Zynga lawsuit that was settled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zynga sued the makers of Pyramidville because they used the word ville.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kobojo was the name of the company.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually settled and Pyramidville is now Pyramid Valley.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They caved.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poor guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here's the other one from Tiger Claw that I think is definitely worth reporting on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's a Steam vulnerability that can lead to a remote insertion of malicious code.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now don't panic, for God's sake, but you know when Steam gets a hole poked in it, a lot of people are going to be talking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently there's a vulnerability in the Steam browser.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does Steam come out when you poke a hole in it?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's the Steam browser protocol.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you use, instead of like HTTP to go to a website, you use Steam colon slash slash to go to a website.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can get a user to click on a link for a specially formed Steam URL,
[SPEAKER_05]: An attacker can remotely exploit buffer overflow bugs and other vulnerabilities in Steam games and Steam itself to get malicious code on a target's machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So please be careful what you click on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But knowing Valve, this shit is probably already patched.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to be on it very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So very cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is available for download.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only place you're going to find it is on the forums at vognetwork.com slash forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check the Orange Lounge Radio Forum for the President Cat Pong download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_05]: tweets about Forza Horizon's rally expansion and Street Pass, oh, Season Pass, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forza Horizon, of course, is launching on October 23rd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, what's happening with this, for 1,600 Microsoft points, you can get the Forza Horizon rally expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is included with the Season Pass, however, and I guess you get...
[SPEAKER_05]: An off-road racing experience with deeper ruts, higher jumps, and new surface types to explore.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an add-on pack for Forza.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else do you need to know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at them shiny cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at them shiny, pretty cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am terrible at Forza, just for the record.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt sent that same link about Skyrim at Rice University.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bummer, we already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have anything else you wanted to throw out there?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: A new system software update for PlayStation 3, 4.3.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll make changes to how trophies are displayed on your PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's now in the PlayStation Network on the cross media bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, by the beginning of November 2012, we will retire the services available through the Life with PlayStation application.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will stop offering the Life with PlayStation application to new users with the 4.3 update.
[SPEAKER_05]: this includes the conclusion of our participation with Stanford University's Folding at Home over 15 million users participated in the program they've donated more than 100 million computation hours to the Folding at Home project considering the contribution PS3 has made to the project we decided to retire it as a result of discussions with Stanford University so at least it wasn't like they just yanked the plug but I guess it was a mutual decision that's kind of interesting
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they find the cure of what they were looking for?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at least it was a mutual decision, but I hope it wasn't one of those mutual decision meaning Sony went to Stanford saying, this is what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us how you're going to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems like it was a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beg for us to change your mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that's all I've got.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you don't have any more last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have any more last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that means we're at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Windows 8's out this week, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Excited?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, of course, kind words on iTunes reviews, Stitcher promotions, things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other iOS devices.
[SPEAKER_05]: What other apps are there?
[SPEAKER_05]: TuneIn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even think of them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's so many.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Android, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan has one I've never even heard of that he uses to listen to podcasts, and it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: So wherever you heard about Orange Launch Radio, please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, support all the shows on VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: VOGnetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a ton of great shows on the network all week long talking about various geek things, not just gaming shows, but TV shows and movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no dedicated movie shows yet, but some of them talk about movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things about British TV culture, anime shows, Warcraft shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all there, VOGnetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, we'll start with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Lisa, if you're going to use Windows 8, there's Start 8 by Stardock that'll actually put the Start menu back so it's not so broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm still pissed that I can't play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_14]: Still so pissed.
[SPEAKER_05]: As you should be.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I miss my kitty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, my final thought is I'm hungry and I can't wait for dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's really too bad that I haven't eaten dinner yet because you know what even sounds better than dinner is Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe later this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pinkberry for dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pinkberry for dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, and I have one more final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: RuPaul's All-Stars Drag Race starts tomorrow, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Judging you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the disappointing thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can watch the first episode online right up to the elimination.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't as good as it should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate the twist.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reality TV twists are stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I haven't scared you off already, thanks for tuning into the show and downloading and listening to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back to do it all again next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good night!
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_08]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_08]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next week!