[SPEAKER_08]: Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, October 28th, 2012.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has the PlayStation 3 been hacked again?
[SPEAKER_01]: Zynga makes some big layoffs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And could not all Wii U features make the system launch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Orange Lounge Radio for this October the 28th of 2012 episode number 479 of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games and all that good stuff with my co-host.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're like sick and stuff, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a sinus infection.
[SPEAKER_05]: You better not be contagious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sinus infections aren't contagious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last time you had a sinus infection, I got the swine flu.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm never going to let you live that down.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what that's from?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not eating enough pork.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hi, Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: You mentioned pork.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: What were you going to say, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, I thought I had a sinus infection, and then I ended up getting like really sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ended up like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not having a very bad version of it, and you ended up being like, what, bedridden or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't help it if my immune system is wonderful, Rob, and that everything is just weak sauce when it hits me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am stronger than the swine flu.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to join us and talk about sickness, or games would be preferred, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Live.VogNetwork.com is where you can chat along with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can also check in if you are listening live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, those are on now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, if it's not up by like the first second the intro music hits, I start getting private messages.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check-ins are down.
[SPEAKER_05]: But check-ins are now on for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit late.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are, of course, live after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do tape live at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after Bobby Blackwolf at The Voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: VOG Network.com Lots of great shows that play on VOG throughout the week, including my other show that's all about the World of Warcraft, The Best Lil' Horde House in Azeroth, or Horde House for short.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the reason why I bring that up, crossover week this week with Girls Gone Wow, our friends over there in the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we were on their show today, and they're going to come on Horde House later this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's crossover week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Sweeps Month is coming up!
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweeps Month!
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's where we gotta pull out all the stunts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crossover shows, super special episodes, and at the end of the month, somebody will die.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just haven't figured out who yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, um... Also, I feel kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: For crocheting when I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I feel like whoever is gonna get the scarf is gonna get diseases like I'm a European settler.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should feel bad for crocheting when we have so many things in the gaming world to talk about this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can talk and crochet at the same time, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it was kind of a slower news week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight we have Listless making a comeback tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has been forever since we played an OLR game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just realizing that earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we are bringing back Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of my answers are pie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you don't even know the topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we'll get into the topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of my answers are pie because of Alan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was going to say you got to try Alan's award-winning...
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to escort him to the parking lot to make sure he wouldn't get jumped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you afraid of severe judgment?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But everything was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, live.vognetwork.com if you want to join us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DarkTetsuya pointing out, there goes Loki talking out of turn again, as he tends to do at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Technically not out of turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: She talked.
[SPEAKER_03]: I talked.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just talked sooner than you were expecting me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not out of turn, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surprise, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Surprise!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I don't have a lot of stuff to talk about before we get into our gaming weeks and the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we actually give Loki a full introduction?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you mentioned it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this guy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this person that's talking?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to flip the table in a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have missed the 478 prior episodes of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this guy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm taking back my tootsie rolls.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't figure it out based on the intro and the two people that have been introduced.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wish I could deduce who this was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me go back for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me listen to Midi Head again here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm on drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show is called Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm on drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There he is!
[SPEAKER_02]: You hush.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will poke you in the eye with this needle.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, for real though, I have a serious kickoff topic tonight, for real.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, okay, probably the most number, like the highest concentration of listeners for Orange Lounge Radio is here in Northern California, because that's where we are, that's where a lot of the video games industry is.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the highest concentration of listeners of Orange Lounge Radio is in Northern California.
[SPEAKER_05]: The second highest concentration of OLR listeners, I'm pretty sure, is New York City.
[SPEAKER_05]: So obviously New York's going through a little bit right now with this whole... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some woman named Sandy is coming to blow everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because she's... You're the one that she wants.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sound like a porno.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, hoo, hoo.
[SPEAKER_05]: In all seriousness, if you are in the path of that hurricane, I hope you've taken all those precautions to be safe.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they've told you to evacuate, please turn off OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be there on the podcast feed later.
[SPEAKER_05]: And evacuate if that's what they've told you to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you have holed yourself up in the house with the...
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma's picture earlier was any indication?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see the picture that Ranma posted earlier of all his booze?
[SPEAKER_05]: He had all this booze.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, I'm ready for the hurricane.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about New York City and think about trying to evacuate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they closed the subway.
[SPEAKER_05]: They closed the schools.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the time a hurricane hits up there, you know what it's going to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: A sneeze.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because you know last night... They lose...
[SPEAKER_05]: Momentum Inland I'm more worried about Florida Is that big of a hurricane?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, even a small hurricane is fairly big, Rob
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no matter what, look, we live in California.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't something we really have to deal with here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the earthquake thing instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're in the path of this thing, I hope you're safe.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I really wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fill your bathtub full of water, buy bleach, get all the bread in the grocery store, and cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ignorant California question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you fill your bathtub with water?
[SPEAKER_02]: In case the water pipes break or you get sewage backed up into the water, you have a tub, which is like what I think
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say seven gallons of fresh water.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you put like two drops of bleach in it to purify it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that way, even if the water lines are down, you have drinking water.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you just need to have plenty of drinking water.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and you know why you tape the windows, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That has to do with the pressure, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Apart from that too, if they actually break, the tape will hold it and keep it from shattering.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah, that's what I figured.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew it was something along those lines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also stops the fog from coming in that turns people inside out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a Simpsons reference.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to bring up this story because I had no idea that somebody was already waiting in line at Nintendo World for a Wii U. Isaiah Triforce Johnson, I guess he changed his name to have Triforce in it, he is a diehard Nintendo fan to say the least.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe this is him last time with Reggie getting his Wii, so this guy is no stranger to camping out overnight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why does Reggie always look like a mannequin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he's pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at his eyes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because his body was ready for cybernetic enhancement.
[SPEAKER_05]: He looks like he's a wax man.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's perfectly groomed.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a well-groomed man.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's got to be a public figure for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: He can't look crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like if Doc Brown came up and like, Hi, OU!
[SPEAKER_02]: His skin looks waxy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does he wax his face?
[SPEAKER_05]: That might sell me OU.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyway, look, the real story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mr. Triforce Johnson had to give up his spot in line because they basically said the security at Rockefeller Center said you need to vacate by 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he had to actually leave.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it has been promised that he may return to his place after Nintendo World reopens when the hurricane has passed.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: The hurricane has already caused at least one major disruption.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, then we should just call this Hurricane Common Sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because who the fuck lines up for a Wii U a month before it comes out?
[SPEAKER_05]: If this thing is disastrous, you are going to feel bad about making jokes about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not going to feel bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel no remorse.
[SPEAKER_02]: No pity, and he will not stop until you are dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, that was Terminator, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can understand lining up a couple days ahead of time or the night of, but a month ahead of time?
[SPEAKER_03]: He wanted to be the first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Might as well just stay in line for the next Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Taiki asks Who's prettier, Reggie or Cliffy B?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Cliffy does have the youth going for him.
[SPEAKER_03]: He does.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is a lot younger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Reggie's kind of trollish, so it's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Reggie is probably much nicer in person, whereas Cliffy kind of comes off as a douche.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing about Cliffy, and I know this is exactly what you wanted to hear on a video game podcast this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing about Cliffy is he kind of has that male porn star hair going for him that's not doing him any favors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because like...
[SPEAKER_05]: straight men in porn not always that exciting to look at you know like and he's kind of got that hair going for it and it's kind of I don't know it's it's like some minus points but you're right he does have that youth factor he doesn't look waxy like Reggie male porn stars always make me think of diseases walking herpes uh what up G in chat says Nintendo should just send him a Wii U do you think Mr. Triforce Johnson has earned the damn Wii U at this point
[SPEAKER_05]: for staying in line for a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo wants money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw on chat says, Nintendo did say he will still be the first in line, which is good PR for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have laughed if someone snuck in front of him before.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was waiting here before you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You left.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma, run out there quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though we're having fun with the subject and the story and everything, first off, props to that guy for being so damn dedicated.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Props to you, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: And second off, for real, we hope everybody is safe in this hurricane.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please be safe.
[SPEAKER_03]: don't be stupid no props to him for standing out there a month in advance he's actually he's on the payroll for Nintendo a little bit as well he's done some of like events and stuff for Nintendo and actually covered stuff as you know
[SPEAKER_03]: A liaison for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No props for this dude staying a month in advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, cool, you're a dedicated Nintendo fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you couldn't be up Reggie's ass a little bit more than you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, cool that you're really excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Reggie's ass is as waxy as the rest of him, then it should be as smooth... I just... This is starting to go to a place I'm not okay with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not... Just throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just... It's just like those people that stand... You know, I understand it's like, oh, hey, it's fandom and stuff like that, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's gotta be a line to draw here, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be like me, well, I'm gonna stand out in front of this building for a year because I'm waiting for the next Xbox 360 or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are gonna be like, no, you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should go stand in line for Breaking Dawn Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know someone is somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no one is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they don't have to do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Fandango and places you can buy tickets online.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that, you know, all those people are like, oh, hey, I waited here for, you know, a couple days to get my tickets to Batman.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're like, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just spent two seconds and went online and got tickets for Batman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, who's the idiot now?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there are some movies where they do the midnight openings where they don't put them up on Fandango.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's... I, however, saw Frankenweenie opening night at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: And trust me... Well, can I touch you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might catch gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of movies, speaking of movies, and I know we already have movies as a kickoff topic a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can we just see the gift?
[SPEAKER_05]: but I quickly want to say Silent Hill 3D Revelation.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not see it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of us did.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I hear it is so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like it's showgirls bad without the tits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like it is really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that makes me want to see it more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, let's do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to see it at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have your people call my people and find a time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_05]: That actually probably will work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to make sure the other half won't be mad that I see it without them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll be going, sniff, snort, because I'll be sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, this coming week, Wreck-It Ralph, which I know we've all been excited about.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other thing I heard about that movie is that the flashlights, the shine from the flashlights are in 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Our buddy Mel, you know, Mel B, the classic DDR freestyler, he, I don't know, he got some type of hookup or passes, won him, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: He got to already see Wreck-It Ralph, and he gave it his stamp of approval.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty important, so we know that movie isn't going to completely suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire, pointing out in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com, Silent Hill has a less than 10% rating on rottentomatoes.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's when you know it's like really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like 30% bad, it's less than 10% bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually liked the first one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw it four times in a theater.
[SPEAKER_02]: I own two copies of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have to see this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ragenator in chat says Showgirls should be remade in 3D Nothing beats 3D boobs, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That may be true, but honestly when it comes to Showgirls, nothing beats going to the Castro Theater and watching a bunch of drag queens reenact the scene where she comes out of the volcano
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so mad I missed it this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like your reason to live right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you want a close second to a possible Showgirls in 3D, you can just watch, like, was it Piranha 3DD?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually super upset that I missed Showgirls this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's always next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next year we need a huge group.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's talk about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back to video games and what we have been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect, the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because my Mass Effect 3 still doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I can kind of get it to run and I've gotten into multiplayer now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like, it's just awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've escalated me again.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will come up in the FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've hardly played any WoW, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had like hella customer service EA stuff this week, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was on with two different customer service reps in their live chat for seven hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, dude, no offense to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to speak to somebody in U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: customer service who actually will listen to what I'm saying and not just make assumptions about what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you go back and read the log, you'll understand this has nothing to do with my DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to do with Dan Patch.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing about outsourced customer service in general, and it doesn't matter what country it's from, even within the US outsourcing sometimes, is that they usually are stuck to a script.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if your inquiry or your question deviates from that script and the things that they are very literally trained to handle, that's when you start to run into issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: And unfortunately, what upper management fails to see a lot of the time is that most inquiries go off script.
[SPEAKER_02]: I worked in customer service for how long?
[SPEAKER_02]: The reason why I was good is because I stopped following my script.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I knew what I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just gone on way too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I finally, they said, oh, we'll do the email service.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had me do a trace, which that I thought was a good idea to see if there was a connection problem on my end.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I can tell you right when the problem started, it started with the last patch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The patch did something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because before that, I had no problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, just, ugh, I'm so tired of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, just with, uh, I started getting, I started with the sinus infection yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was while I was out running errands.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I haven't really felt like playing much in the way of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when I got home, I was like, I'll want to play as Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: It does not work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It feels very wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, these are all fake people, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Liara is blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the point, though, of believability in what one... Because, I mean, yeah, some people are really into dating children, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I... Maybe it's just I'm spoiled by Garrus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire in our chatroom asks, have other people had the same problem with the patch?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not the only one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's been going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, people are now referencing my thing on the EA answer thing on BioWare's forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: Several people have reposted it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A bunch of us have actually gone on to the Mass Effect Facebook page and linked it, which they've deleted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki, let's move on to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I was working on some stuff for that, just on the roller coaster that I had there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We added some more pixel art stuff in there, have a portion where it jumps into the mouth of a piranha plant, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, was it, Hidstun was making, he made a knight's, I don't remember what the main character knight is, I guess knight's.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be knights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, made knights flying in the air, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got the new patch this week, so I've updated the server and been playing around command blocks, made some teleportation stations so we can hop to different parts of the map pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wish more people were on there, because it's usually just me, and then occasionally I'll see people pop in.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's been pretty slow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know there's a lot of games out right now, so it's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was actually going to play some of those games, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't know which one I wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got into that weird gamer ADD stuff where I was like, I can play Dishonored and start that game, but I don't want to start another game because I'm already in the middle of Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan's already beaten that game three times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure he has.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and then I guess I played Call of Duty a little bit, Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't wait to play Black Ops 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be nice to switch up to something different.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week, I don't have a lot of new stuff to talk about, but I did decide I finally had it with Mass Effect 3 and Origin in general, so I am done with the PC version of Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want nothing to do with it anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went back to the Xbox 360 version, which, although it kind of stinks that it's harder to do with the controllers than the keyboard and mouse, I got used to it pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it is really sad that I really don't have connection problems on the 360 whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have none of those loading problems or delays or any of that shit that you get with Origin, and it's so refreshing.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I had some characters unlocked on the 360 prior that I just really missed like my Quarian Engineer so Mass Effect, Mass Effect, Mass Effect, Mass Effect lots of that other games though besides Mass Effect believe it or not LittleBigPlanet Vita I played some more of that I mentioned I touched this game a little bit last week but I didn't really play a lot of it I got to play some more of it this week and I'm overall pretty satisfied with it a lot of what I said last week still holds true it's a lot of the good stuff from LittleBigPlanet too and
[SPEAKER_05]: However, I finally figured out why the game wasn't bugging me about the online connectivity when I was playing it last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the game has an online pass and I hadn't put in the code yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, so when I finally, cause you know, you have to beat the entire first world before you unlock the moon and the community levels and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So once I unlocked that, it's like, oh, hey, you need an online pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, you need to enter in the code from the manual.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, there's no manual with little, and I started like, oh my God, did I get, get ripped off?
[SPEAKER_05]: But I opened up the box and there was a code there for, it said, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: The costumes from the Bioshock characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said, congratulations on your pre-order bonus for Big Daddy costume and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, wait a minute, that's not an online code.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, I'm going to put it in anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure enough, it was the online passcode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I put it in and it said, you've unlocked the online pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if I didn't think to try that, I would have thought...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: That was LittleBigPlanetVita.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do like some of the enhancements they made to the online community stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download levels now, so you don't have to go connect and find them every time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the levels online are really stupid, though, but that's to be expected with any creation game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're only going to find a few gems in the haystack.
[SPEAKER_05]: but uh yeah it's as far as you know execution it is what you would expect on a little Vita screen and for that it's it's pretty awesome I gotta say something else I played on the Vita it's only a demo and I don't like to review games based off the demo but after Shane's strong words last week about how he felt about Silent Hill Book of Memories you know I had to go download the demo and so I played the entire demo which was a good I don't know it was like the whole first level up through the boss I didn't hate it
[SPEAKER_05]: but it's really not Silent Hill like it is a dungeon explorer crawler game with Silent Hill graphics stamped on it and so like if I were obsessed with the lore and really into the storytelling as Shane was talking about on the call at the end of last week's show I could see where that's offensive like having Valtiel be the quest giver at the beginning of the floor some of that stuff's really hokey but I didn't hate it
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't pay 40 bucks for it but I would totally rent the game for a weekend just to beat it because I was kind of interested in where the story was going because it was very like you are the main character and you're doing all these things and I liked kind of the haunting memories that were playing on the TVs and all this stuff so
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of into the story, so I didn't hate it as much as Shane did, but I get why people aren't into it, because it's not really Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't play it after that description.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could bring it out here and show it to you, but you'd probably be like, eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to blow infected snot all over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I had to do was look at the back cover, and I was like, nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's that bad, but it's not Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really the best way I can describe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: One other thing I'll quickly say, Smart Glass came out for Android devices.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm sure many of you have checked out Microsoft Smart Glass because it's on all the Android devices.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's where me having an iPhone and Alan having an Android device comes in handy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we got out his Galaxy 3 and downloaded Smart Glass to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was playing around with the Xbox on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really doesn't do anything right now that the app didn't do before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to remember the existing app would allow you to control your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: How did you use it with, what was it, Dance Central?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, it was just, okay, big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can swipe on the menu and use, but I'm almost positive the existing Xbox app that was out there would allow you to remote control your Xbox in the same way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't think that's new.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, and then we're waiting for the TV and movie stuff, but none of that's in there yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like, okay, they've got the framework for smart glass down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now let's see you use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming in 2013.
[SPEAKER_03]: Usefulness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's just like, was it the Xbox Vision Camera?
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got the framework in place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now let's see the one, two games that are going to use this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can make a user icon out of your face.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about the most that Vision Camera is good for.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I really use that for.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't do that with Kinect either, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, can you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well then, so much for the Vision Cam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's... Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for Gaming Week for me and for our other hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about housekeeping and then we'll get into the news this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Follow us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Follow us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have an interview next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't had an interview in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one is for the old school listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: As you know, Orange Lounge Radio started as a show about music-based video games and for a long time we were pretty much exclusively about like the DDR and Beatmania and music game community.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's pretty surprising to me that in our ten and a half year history we've never had this guy on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We may have had him on like for five minutes on one of the E3 specials but we are going to properly have on the show next week
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie from BomaniStyle.com is going to be on the show talking about what you know especially because we have a news story tonight about like DDR's reboot and all this stuff and I'm not going to spoil too much about that but we really want to get his thoughts on kind of where the music game community is going because I'll tell you this
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie obviously has a lot of love for the Bomani community and a lot of the stuff that he did was a lot of the stuff that many of us dreamed about he had the Uber website he started this record label thing or this record distribution thing where he was shipping out a lot of the music he got some of these artists to come to ASEN he's really been intimately involved with a lot of music gaming like today so getting to pick his brain on a lot of like music gaming and his thoughts is going to be a lot of fun
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is going to be a fun episode next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie from BomaniStyle.com will be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds super.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's live.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you guys will be able to ask him questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: So make sure you're here in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is next week, November 4th, 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's all I have for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get into the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, G4 has finally canceled the last two bits of the old G4, which would be X-Play and Attack of the Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even Attack of the Show is not...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Loki,
[SPEAKER_03]: and apparently the rumor is that the channel is supposed to shift towards like a guy network.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying it's like Esquire or GQ channel, which sounds very boring, but cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder where Cheaters reruns and Cops reruns fit into that, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, to the news that these shows are leaving, this is all I have to say on the matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's all, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the scream.
[SPEAKER_02]: The scream really does it for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a really good particular Bugs Bunny ending, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sad, but it's not like we all didn't see this coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't... You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the merger that was the beginning of the end.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, without sounding like a heartless bitch, it's really not sad either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, but I mean, the biggest...
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: I miss Tech TV so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, that was the most awesome network ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it's like, hey, G4 sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they mixed them together and it's like, whoa, this is like the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it went so downhill from there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like, I don't even understand how that's possible, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com, Acidic Vampire in our chat says, Oh, I thought you were going to play a RuPaul's Sashay Away clip.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish I'd thought of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next time, next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Sag in our chatroom says, Man, I wonder what the people who have G4 tattooed on them think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were doing that on E3, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty sure they were at one point.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, they better pay for the removal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, look, and here's the thing, especially judging off the Twitter reaction and all the stuff this week, like people were like, I'm so sad that these shows are leaving and man, G4, there's no video game thing on anymore and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm like, you guys are... They still have their same presence at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are remembering these shows from three years ago back when you were actually watching them.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you all were actually watching them, this news would not be coming because it's all about ratings.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they hadn't changed them, people would have been watching them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, the new guy on Xplay was fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't... See, I don't even... I watched the clip.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a clip of something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what it was about, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: The guy was a total asshat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ragenator in chat says, Personally, I love the shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those shows were the reason I subscribed to cable in 2008.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people kind of reminiscing on the older G4 stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, you know, it's unfortunate, but the network was already over several years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when they started showing reruns of Cops?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first downfall was the merger.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I want to really know where the financial status was that made the merger necessary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, according to Blackwolf in our chat room, and he was pretty intimately involved in the early days of G4, and he talks about that on his own show, but Bobby's in chat and says, Paul Allen got tired of tech TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: that's why he sold it to Comcast even though they were about to have positive ratings for the first time so somebody just threw their hands up and said I'm kind of over it
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people talking about the E3 coverage.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, for some people, that's all G4 is now is E3 coverage because they have done the live stuff from the show floor and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So does that mean the tiara goes to Spike TV by default?
[SPEAKER_03]: They've already been doing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spike TV was live streaming all the coverage through game trailers, their partnership with game trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weren't they like across the street?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were actually in the... Yeah, they were doing all of the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Spike had a thing going already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Spike's alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they're going to be shifting to this guy channel thing, that's kind of what Spike's already doing right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not really doing the GQ stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're kind of taking more of the lowbrow route to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shows with big-titted women and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: A Thousand Ways to Die or
[SPEAKER_03]: GameTrailersTV GameTrailersTV
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of surprised me because, you know, I thought video games were supposed to be like the modern version of movies or music, you know, some new art form.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we have tons of shows about movies and TV shows and music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Entertainment Tonight, Access Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who watches Entertainment Tonight and Access Hollywood?
[SPEAKER_03]: Old people.
[SPEAKER_03]: People that are old.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grandma.
[SPEAKER_03]: That don't know how to use the internet or just don't care to watch the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: and then they can get kind of like a quick feed of you know what's coming out and you know what the news is and stuff but unfortunately the gaming demographic a lot of those people are just like internet crazy and so the news travels a lot faster on the internet than obviously these shows can pick up on but
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't mean that they can fail.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, a lot of these shows, if they have... And this is kind of the whole thing with GameTrailersTV is they make a lot of news because they get a lot of exclusive interviews and exclusive trailers and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to see it first on that show before you see it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where the key is to running a successful kind of entertainment business, at least as far as gaming stuff...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, look at Game Informer, same thing there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how they were able to kind of, other than, you know, coming free with, you know, subscribing to GameStop's card, but a lot of their stuff is, you know, they leverage these interviews and exclusives and stuff, and so they're kind of the source of news.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlackWolf wants to point out that Electric Playground and Judgment Day are still around.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know Judgment Day as reviews on the run.
[SPEAKER_05]: Electric Playground is in syndication.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of ABC affiliates on the weekends right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess for me to say that Game Trailers TV is the only video game show left on all of television is a falsity.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sorry for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess you could say on all like cable because syndication doesn't really hit cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would syndicate Electric Playground have anything to offer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I don't really give a shit about a review of Halo 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say it's the equivalent of Ebert and Roper, although I don't even think that exists anymore, but At The Movies or whatever they call that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, what's the point of that show?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's reviews on movies, so why not have a show that's review on games?
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's any different than the Roper or Ebert stuff from five years ago, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the niche it's filling, I assume.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw on chat says, Old people watch those shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Young people, they watch things like TMZ.com for all the entertainment news and gossip.
[SPEAKER_05]: TMZ's kind of trash, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I look at your Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's happening to... Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf thinks... Oh, I didn't get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf thinks that you missed the point that these are new episodes.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are not syndicated old stuff from G4.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are new episodes, but it's like Baywatch was a syndicated show when it was new and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So these are new things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't catch that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you meant to say Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if it's new stuff, then that's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's new stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember watching Electric Playground.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Tommy Tallarico still doing that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's still him and that other guy, Victor's guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I do respect Tommy Tallarico.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, one of them was really annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just can't remember who.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it was Tommy Tallarico.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, but then it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people think Ebert was annoying or Roper.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just the one that you agree with.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure a lot of people think I'm annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let's see, what, uh, what else is gonna bring up with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the TMZ.com bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: TMZ is kind of a trash, trash thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: All TMZ runs is trash, and it's the type of stuff that, you know, gets posted on Facebook, like, oh my god, Lindsay Lohan with the intervention, da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck is up with her playing Liz Taylor?
Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just about to ask, so where is our trashy gossip site about video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is the Perez Hilton of video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: But then Jamie has to go and open her mouth and say that, so I'm thinking maybe it's us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just saw Victoria post about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can be your trashy gossip site.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just not enough gossip in the game industry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, you know, we can make up speculative rumors about things, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think there's really anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one cares about gossip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just daylight rumors.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you talking about nobody in video games cares about gossip?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you high?
[SPEAKER_05]: That is all people ever talk about is gossip.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they talk about rumors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where did Cliffy B go?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gossip.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cliffy B went to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a friend who's uncle... Cliffy B went to go bang his wife, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where he went.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii U is causing all this turmoil within Nintendo and blah blah blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gossip.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So why did we just talk about how Reggie Fils-Aim looks like a wax figure?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is two celebrity within video games, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's start stalking him and find out, Reggie Fils-Aim double parked today, woohoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there's a difference between the A-list of standard celebrity, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's a difference between the A-list of geek celebrity.
[SPEAKER_02]: where we might care more about like say what Will Wheaton put on his blog because honestly he's a really good blogger.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many of us can really give a shit about Lindsay Lohan?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not raising my hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was in Mean Girls and that is one of the best movies ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my point, you know, who cares how many more kids, you know, Brangelina adopted?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can afford it good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let them raise all those damn children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do care, you know, if, oh, well, so-and-so developer left whatever, you know, company, and that means no more of this, or he's going to be doing this.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's shit we care about, you know, and that, and we do care about D-list celebrities like Kathy Griffin.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, because, you know, Felicia Day is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like, even, you know, the geeks on her friends list were all going, eee!
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know there's people on her friends list that aren't in the whole geeks culture that look at that and go, who?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I've met some famous people before, and I was just like, oh, hi, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I completely geeked out when Wil Wheaton answered a question of mine on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I completely geeked out when I met wrestlers back when I was into wrestling.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had my moment earlier this year because I told everybody I knew that I got to shake Latrice Royale's hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like, you know, I met Latrice Royale and she was gorgeous and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everybody's like, who?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, it's a drag queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hang my head in shame.
[SPEAKER_02]: or my autograph from Kondo Koji or the other Koji, Igarashi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the picture that you took of me with him at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like... And first of all, he was pretty floored that my horrible Japanese came across, you know, understandably, but still.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was...
[SPEAKER_02]: and you know running into Kojima three years in a row literally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stan in our chat room says everybody's or excuse me everyone's idea of a celebrity is different.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very good point because I really got to address this topic carefully because I really don't want to sound like I have ego.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was very humbled and thankful that when I went to PAX East a couple years ago I did have people that like came up to me and like I had like a group of people that just came up to me and was like are you Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're Rob from Original Radio aren't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was some random guy at John's Incredibly Crappy Pizza who wanted to talk to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was as much of an OMG moment for me as it was for you, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where it's like, oh, people actually do listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a humbling moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stan in chat says, I made Latrice Royale in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got a lot of weird looks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should just tell him to eat it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you when it was the most freaky for me was when I went to Alabama a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were doing a tourney in Biloxi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was in Biloxi?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think it was in Biloxi, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I showed up for some DDR tournament on a 5th Mix machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it was their new 5th Mix and they were all happy and we'd had it for a while, but it was all cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like, you're here!
[SPEAKER_02]: You said you'd be here, and you're here!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, hi everybody, nice to meet you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I went to some 2DX party on a widescreen TV and had to play Karaoke Revolution and
[SPEAKER_02]: it was pretty fun but I mean it's at the same time though it's I prefer it more when it leads to you know making friends with people no one cares about Loki I'm sorry Loki but you're a shut-in too you don't go out as much as Jamie and I do true you know what our listeners are my kind of people most everybody else in the universe I'm like don't touch don't don't touch me don't talk to me
[SPEAKER_02]: Our listeners, I'm like, okay, you're allowed to touch me on the arm.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Dave Falcon in our chat room says, I met the nature boy, Ric Flair, in a bathroom in a bar in Tampa and I asked him for his autograph.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope he didn't do that when he was peeing because that's a little awkward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's time to talk to people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sign it with your urine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have his DNA.
[SPEAKER_05]: That reminds me of this scene from Priscilla Queen of the Desert about Abba.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with the news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ahem.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ESRB, the Entertainment Rating Board, Entertainment Software Rating Board, they are trying to streamline the release of downloadable games doing a new rating service that is targeted for Xbox Live Arcade, PlayStation Network, eShop, WiiWare, and Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: This service is no cost.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's a big incentive for people to use this because there's a lot of indie developers...
[SPEAKER_05]: and people that don't have very big budgets making games for these platforms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is a no cost service.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the deal is, you do an online questionnaire and through this questionnaire you basically self identify the adult content.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's interesting about this, the questionnaire will also rate a game in terms of what is shared.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's some new content descriptors in the game that will indicate that the game shares information, shares location, or interacts with users.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty awesome, I've got to say, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love this idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even as, like, me, I love the fact that I will know exactly which games are going to want to share my location.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we see those ratings on Facebook with what they're sharing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see why it wouldn't work if Facebook games were willing to put it on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Facebook, the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, we should rate Facebook the website, but that's another ratings board that'll have to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: apparently this is very similar to what PlayStation mobile games already have going forward on the rating system some are saying that could have been inspired by that so very cool I love that it's no cost let's just hope everybody's honest in those questionnaires I'm almost positive there will be a story in the near future about a game that is missing one of these labels that should have had it but we'll see it's an interesting step forward for now so I can't see how this is a bad idea looking forward to it
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's new!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what that means.
[SPEAKER_02]: More Bimani.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, Konami has announced that the newest DDR game is just called Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they haven't put a whole bunch of details about it, but they're doing their first location test at Tokyo Leisureland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that next Friday, I think it is?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's already happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: They already have the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, there's a location test page and everything up now, but isn't it supposed to do all of its updates over the internet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, some of the tweets were indicating that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, that I guess they're calling it Dance Dance Revolution because they're not envisioning that there will ever be a second mix or a third mix, that it's just going to be one mix that can be constantly updated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it actually, there's a quote on here from SoInLove about future DVR series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked with Usan, and they named this version as just DVR because they will update it, but no new versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's an English-y post, but still.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: And we saw how well that worked out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It tanked, and they said, oh, but we're going to provide lots of DLC for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They provide some DLC, and then it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get the game dirt cheap now, and there's no DLC support for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, I see that totally happening with this, where they're going to have some DLC for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's what I want to know, is if they're going to constantly update this game, then how are they going to sell new games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they just want to make profit off it anymore, or are they going to sell DLC to arcades?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're going to have some arcades that have these extra songs, and some arcades that don't have these extra songs, or...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's how it would have to work is selling DLC to the arcades.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of think it's a great idea, but remember, this is Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not something that's being tested here.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a very Japanese-centric thing, and for a Japanese arcade where you have karaoke booths that have their own songs and what have you, I could actually see this really working, and yes, I think it would give arcades some identity.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've tried it with Tekken, I want to say, was one of the games that they're going to have DLC for that arcades are going to have to pay for or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is, though, is like, so that basically kind of excludes all of the other territories other than Japan because a lot of these can't connect to EMUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're going to be stuck with basically the default song list, which may not be a bad thing, but it's just kind of, what's the incentive?
[SPEAKER_02]: You put out things that aren't specifically Japan licensed for that first release, but all the DLC will have Japan only licenses.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's what I see happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, what do you think about a reboot of DDR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, really, I'm kind of like, eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I always play the new stuff when it comes out, but I kind of hit a point where I stopped caring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm good for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's be honest, they've rebooted DDR like four or five times already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly think Konami doesn't understand what makes DDR good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, you know, with Extreme, remember, we're starting all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they had Supernova, and that was kind of another reboot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they had the X series, which is kind of a reboot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did three games into that, and now they're rebooting it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's like, do you guys not know what fucking makes these games good?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just kind of like, well, we're just gonna draw straws here until we figure out why this is selling, you know, or why people are playing it or not playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a strong formula for a while and people were excited and then they changed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: which I think that that might have been you know because I mean keep in mind how long have the guitar freaks and drum mania still been going on how popular is pop and music still pop and music is way popular and just because they've kept their formula they haven't kept trying to redesign it they haven't tried to reinvent it and that's I think the problem they're doing with DDR is that they've gotten away from they're trying to make it edgy trying to keep it new but really it's that quirky classic that people like
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of with Jamie on this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said this for years when we were mostly music-based.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said DDR really does need to reinvent itself, and I don't think Supernova or X really were a reinvention whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of it really did anything to push the franchise forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm a little bit hopeful that if they have to go back and put in this infrastructure to support DLC for arcades and all that, maybe they're going to approach other ideas for the game as well, like something to make it a little more competitive or some of this new stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I think a creative reboot would be a great idea, but I don't know if that's really what we're getting with this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But kind of like Jamie's...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they're not charging for that DLC, then what's the real incentive for them to do it anyways?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're not helping themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to sell any more games.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they are charging for DLC, then it all comes down to how much is this stuff costing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because obviously in an arcade machine, we're not talking like $5 a song DLC.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're talking probably like, you know, a couple hundred dollars or, you know, whatever for these songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if arcade owners back there, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This is sort of what I was talking about a lot earlier with Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because people, when Tekken 3 came out, I worked at a Namco arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we had people always coming in saying, how many more matches until we unlock somebody?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, even though I think they were all on a date cycle.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, who's the next person?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in Japan they got this person.
[SPEAKER_02]: We must be different here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which they ended up being different.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, that worked for DDR where you would unlock things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I really wish that they would go back to something like that I mean if they're gonna do DLC updates it should still be unlockable stuff you know to keep that excitement to keep people feeling like there's a sense of achievement that it's a community-wide effort
[SPEAKER_05]: that was always the best part about Max 2 was that community part so I'm all for that I will withhold judgment until I actually get to play it which may not be anytime soon if recent DDR releases are any sign but I hope for the best what else can I say
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on with news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk a little bit about the Wii U. And honestly, this news doesn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the rumor is that the Wii U is not going to launch with all the features on the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of sound a little familiar with Nintendo's kind of MO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they're seeing right now that the features including Miiverse and the near field communication that they won't be on the actual system.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to have to download Miiverse in order to actually have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which kind of seems a little odd to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that supposed to be what you see when you turn on your Wii U?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess, you know, obviously later on they're going to add some other support and stuff for multiple gamepads and that kind of thing, which makes no sense right now because no games use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But and even the near field of communication stuff doesn't really make any sense to have that right now because nothing uses it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Miiverse is a little weird that that wouldn't be on the actual console because, I don't know, they're saying that it's possible that it won't be available at launch because considering third parties can't access it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... Hold on, let me get this straight here.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are they going to have any games incorporated?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me get this straight here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they have this thing that's supposed to tie into these games, but no games can tie into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, it's kind of funny that that's true because third-party games can access it.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the big games that they showed this whole Miiverse thing was with Zombie U. So that was all bullshit that they were kind of pushing our way?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of retarded that you have a Nintendo system launch without all the features in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where was the web browser?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it didn't come out until months after.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're selling me this broken piece of shit that you're going to patch in the stuff later on?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't you delay the release a little bit and have it done?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why bother pushing this out when stuff isn't done yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: or, I don't know, this is a main feature of the console and you haven't fucking finished it yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not that complicated of a piece of software.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is all rumor.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all rumor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, me versus me could be also one of those things that, like, they're gonna, like, quote-unquote, patch in day one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, it could be one of those things that, like, they're really working right up to the last minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm totally theorizing, just throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me vs. One Thing Near Field Communication
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say as much as this opinion may not be popular there's been other Nintendo stuff in the past where they slowly unraveled things like I seem to remember the original DS and the whole like downloading demos and all this that wasn't there when the system first launched that was something that came up later and the whole internet connectivity and it was like that feature was just waiting in your DS the whole time to be enabled so if there's stuff like that that we don't yet know about that's kind of hiding and waiting in the Wii U that's
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and, oh, maybe later on we'll have a way that you can store things, you know, on your SD memory card instead of just backing up your saves on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, oh, I don't know, how about we just, you know, have a feature now where you can download digital copies of the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're so far behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, all these other companies have been doing this for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just like they push it out to their customers like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, look at what Nintendo's doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're offering demos of games and everyone's like, fuck yeah, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is awfully new technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, no, it's been fucking done for years now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were doing demos on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yet, for some reason, Nintendo is unable to give you a demo of anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Nintendo's big thing is that they've been trying to avoid anything that's going to damage, not necessarily their reputation or their brand, but avoid ways for pirating, avoid ways for region outsourcing, not outsourcing is not the word I'm thinking of, but
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, going outside the region, avoiding incidents for online chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're really, really trying, I think, way too hard to preserve their brand.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're sacrificing a lot of the options that people have come to expect from a modern day gaming system for the sake of that little neurosis, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let me get into this next story, because it's almost right up the same alley of what we've been talking about here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this really caught wildfire all over the internet, because Origin, the ever-popular EA service, updated their privacy policy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this has a lot of people wondering, how exactly does Origin play into the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because in the new policy, it says, "...by signing up to play EA's titles, you agree that limited user account information can be transferred to EA."
[SPEAKER_05]: Information transferred to EA includes your Mii information, email address, Nintendo Network ID, friends list, country, language, and date of birth.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this seems to confirm that Origin will be a part of how you're going to play EA games on Wii U. But my thought is, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because before we start saying, oh my god, it's going to be Origin on the Wii U, which would be dreadful news indeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I were to see that Origin logo pop up on the Wii U, I'd be like, it's over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo did not convince me they understand online.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is done.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hold on a minute because EA and your Origin account, they also interact with your Xbox 360 account and your PlayStation 3 account.
[SPEAKER_05]: And your Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and your original Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all of that kind of interfaces in that EA console when you go on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, hopefully this isn't much different.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's any different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially like, okay, maybe it just wants the me information, so put your little picture on the origin account or whatever, but I don't think that's a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other people are learning out of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure you haven't done penis face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, to also draw out of this, the Nintendo Network ID is seemingly telling, that's a huge part of it, that where's the friend code?
[SPEAKER_05]: so maybe they finally are doing some type of universal ID is that an ID name that I get to pick or is that a Nintendo Network ID number I don't know we shall soon see so of course all the big blogs reaching out to Nintendo for comment but they're not saying anything right now I wouldn't panic I don't think this means it's Origin on Wii U at least I hope not because Origin is terrible and it will be a terrible thing for the Wii U if that happens they would never do that
[SPEAKER_05]: I would not buy Mass Effect 3 on the Wii U if it has the origin tie-in.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's literally no point.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's definitely going to have Origin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect 3 on the Wii U will have Origin.
[SPEAKER_05]: But in what capacity?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, on the Xbox 360, you don't see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's fine then because what it's doing, it's talking to Origin's servers to get your Galaxy information and get some of that stuff and update your stuff on the EA social Bioware site or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine because the connectivity isn't happening through Origin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: but I ran it through Steam I never had a problem it wouldn't connect to the servers right when I loaded it up but I could log in I'm not even getting the option anymore with my Mass Effect 3 which if it was the patch I'm just saying but I think Origin has something to do with it too even though I'm connecting just fine through Origin so they just need to get their shit together
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, unfortunately these are things we just aren't going to know until the Wii U actually comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, meanwhile, more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hopefully something better than freaking Origin.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Super Mario 64?
[SPEAKER_02]: 16 years since this game has come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband and I used to play a crap ton of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now there is a PC mod for Super Mario 64 that lets you play co-op online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was modded by Skellux.
[SPEAKER_02]: S-K-E-L-U-X
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Mario Star Road
[SPEAKER_02]: But this one keeps the level design and everything, but makes it co-op.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not playing as Luigi, though, however.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're playing as sort of a recolored Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean... Luigi.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not like the taller... It's like a gray Mario, gray and red Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, kind of like a palette swap.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually want to check this out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, Tigerclaw in our chatroom is telling me, Rob, it's been done.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course it's been done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and some video games that are coming to a store near you, hopefully with less dubstep.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a few games coming out this week since we're in the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's start off.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing some re-releases of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the Namco Museum DS and Pac-Man World 3 bundled together on one DS cart.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also Tekken 6 and Soul Calibur 4 are being bundled together on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh we've got Assassin's Creed 3 on PlayStation 3 Xbox 360 and on PC Thundercats on the Nintendo DS Transformers wow hey it's probably based off the new Thundercats series which is probably not that good uh Thundercat or Thundercats
[SPEAKER_03]: Transformers Prime, the game on the Wii, the DS, and the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Nike Plus Connect Training on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Need for Speed Most Wanted on PS3, Xbox 360, and the Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a Vita game I can actually play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Myst on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moshi Monsters, Moshling's Theme Park on DS and 3DS Toy Story Mania on PS3 and Xbox 360 Those are kind of HD redos of the Wii game that came out The Trash Pack on DS and 3DS Zone of the Enders HD Collection on PS3 and Xbox 360 Let's see, moving on here
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got the Rockstar Games Collection Edition 1 on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It includes Red Dead Redemption, Midnight Club Los Angeles, the Grand Theft Auto episodes from Liberty City, and L.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: Noire for $60.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bratz Fashion Boutique on DS and 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: And WWE 13 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lalalupsi, Carnival of Friends on DS and 3DS Winx Club Magical Fairy Party on Nintendo DS Wreck-It Ralph on Wii 3DS and DS and let's see here Marvel Avengers Battle for Earth on Xbox 360 for Kinect and then oddly enough only the portable versions of LEGO Lord of the Rings this week on the DS, the 3DS and the Vita
[SPEAKER_03]: and Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that might be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and PC version of Lego Lord of the Rings this week as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Assassin's Creed 3 Liberation on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't forget that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Smartass on the Vita and Ragnarok Odyssey on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's it for this week, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's travel to Japan and check out some of the releases over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: On November 1st, Medal of Honor Warfighter on the Xbox 360 and NBA 2K13 gets its Japanese release also on the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to the PlayStation 3, Dead Island, Zombie of the Year Edition, Medal of Honor Warfighter and NBA 2K13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okami Zekkaiban, this is the HD remaster of Okami, is finally out on the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Tales of... Are you supposed to say Zillia or Shillia?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's an X. Exilia?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's Tales of Shillia.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would be Zillia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zillia?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tales of Zillia 2 is out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's even a version that comes with a new DualShock controller and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xylophone, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: All these different little limited editions coming with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: That must be a major holiday release in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing on the Vita this week, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just checking the 3DS real quick to see if we have anything there.
[SPEAKER_05]: A black Nintendo 3DS XL and then one that has Monster Hunter 3G as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, World Soccer Winning 11 2013.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soccer games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, I just shot my yarn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, nose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: As I had the list up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming out on the 30th, we have Assassin's Creed 3 Liberation for Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sorry if I sound weird, I just took a cough drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: 31st, Assassin's Creed 3 for 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sports Champions 2 for PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I have to move on to November's dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: November...
[SPEAKER_02]: On the first, we have WWE 13 for a number of systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the second, Football Manager 2013, Just Dance 4, Need for Speed Most Wanted, Nike Plus Connect Training, Silent Hill Book of Memories.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a few more news stories for you guys in the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did DarkSakura pick this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Find out after two more stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's unfortunate that we have to report on more closures and layoffs, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Zynga has laid off 5% of their workforce, kind of a restructuring that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They let go roughly 3,200 employees, and with that, they've closed Zynga's Boston studio, and also the studios in Japan and UK are being kind of slated for...
[SPEAKER_03]: Shutdown soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the Austin office.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've laid off quite a few people there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they've also shut down, I guess, 13 of their older games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what they quote, significantly reducing their investment in The Ville.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably a good thing being since they're being sued by EA for The Ville, so it sounds like the outlook on that is not too favorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of disappointing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what Dan told me?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said that their stock right now is lower than RadioShack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ouch!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I got one story for you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, that was shady that they did that during the whole Apple conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't, like a lot of people assume that was intentional.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it really wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to give Zynga what little shred of doubt I can, maybe that actually wasn't intentional that they did it during the Apple conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because seriously, how are you going to hide something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: You think the internet wouldn't notice?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to judge my Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people went and got it the day it came out, and they're actually really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, they're really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give it a couple months before that whole super sale is done at the end of January to see if it's something I really need.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet you're dying to know, what about the games?
[SPEAKER_05]: What are the games that come with Windows 8?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's tell you about the new games with Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft Solitaire Collection is one of the games in Windows 8, which of course, it's Windows, it's gotta have Solitaire, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, these all have achievements and stuff too.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's like Klondike Solitaire and Pyramid and all the stuff you'd be used to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Minesweeper is back in Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the crazy part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Minesweeper now has an adventure mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: No one care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at the screenshot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like little explorer dude going through the cave.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: As much as you say no one care, I gotta say it looks better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mr. Driller did it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other games within the Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft Mahjong, which I think they've kind of been including ever since Shanghai, the old PC game was popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wordament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Adera
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of got like a little story that goes with it, a stone and sorcery magic type game, but it's more like a puzzler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get like a, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it's like a very simple type of adventure game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's another free Windows 8 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've come a long way since the days of just good old solitaire with the bouncing card when you finish, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: The moment that you said that, my brain instantly went to, like, a Virginia Slims ad.
[SPEAKER_04]: How so?
[SPEAKER_02]: With, like, gamers, you know, sitting around making shit faces at, you know, Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has, you've come a long way, baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: You, listen, classic game, play, now.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Classic Game of the Week is Panzer Dragoon, which I thought that I had done it before, but I had done Saga, or RPG as we got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, as it came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Panzer Dragoon is a rail shooter by Team Andromeda.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out on the Saturn in 1995.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then later on there were other versions for PC, PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it came as a bonus in Panzer Dragoon Order on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you basically play as Kale Fluge, who is unnamed in the US version.
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically you just go through and you shoot stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the game's freaking gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, people gave the Saturn shit for its 3D, and yeah, it didn't do 3D as good as the PlayStation did.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was built originally as a 2D machine, but this game really illustrated what you could do with the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, you have machines and monsters as your enemies.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's sort of like a post-apocalyptic fantasy world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to go through, you've got the different boss battles that actually pause the game before the boss battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you have X and Y axes that you can move across on for those boss battles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but basically you can look all the way around, I mean, your enemies are coming from everywhere, but you're still on rails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so you've got two weapons, you have a handgun, and then you have a homing laser that your dragon fires.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has six levels, each one about five minutes, and then there's a boss battle, and the sixth, though, is a special boss battle, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say that, just going back into this one, now, I played a little bit of it, but you know how I get with certain games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get motion sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one that made me motion sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, since this was a Sega game, of course it was out on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: It started off, though, as a different project.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said they were trying to develop a shoot-em-up game, and it eventually evolved into Panzer Dragoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: so yeah pretty awesome game but they were under a big time frame for actually developing it and they were the original name of the game was actually Kikoryu which is Armored Dragon but they wanted to pick something that sounded a little bit more exciting so they picked a German name Panzer Dragoon and there you go
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a pretty game, though, especially for its time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a gorgeous game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was actually named the best Saturn game of 1995 by EGM.
[SPEAKER_02]: R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_02]: and this game also sold well enough that they could do Panzer Dragoons Vi which of course is keeping with that German naming.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was also give it one up, give it a retro review of 8 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is, Panzer Dragoon, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good pick, DarkSakura, good pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good pick, Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, what should I pick?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can bring Dan back to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a fourth mic now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks to the kind, benevolent people at PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have Dan all the time, then it's not special.
[SPEAKER_02]: Must be like my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to do it for Part A, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a very busy Part B when we come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do some rapid-fire news, the Fugle Question of the Week, and listless all when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live on this Sunday evening, October the 28th of 2012, with the 479th episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting into Part B, and we'll be doing some rapid-fire news and the Fugle Question of the Week and a special list list tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But first, we have some breaking news to start off Part B. Breaking news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Breaking news.
The 8th Annual Podcast Award nominees are in at podcastawards.com and we got nominated!
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Launch Radio is a nominee for Best Gaming and there's 10 shows in the gaming category including a couple that also got some bigger nominations for People's Choice and Best Produced so it's going to be some big competition this year and
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, we would really like it very much if it's us.
[SPEAKER_05]: A specific indie to win, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we very much want this specific indie to win.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if we can't, we really hope one of the indies takes it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, good luck to the indies in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as the corp cast goes, you're going down.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, podcastwords.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Power to the people, yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Power to the people.
[SPEAKER_05]: The daily voting, and I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know all of those shows, so I apologize if you are an indie show and I did not name you specifically.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will do more research before voting opens on November 1st is when the voting opens.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be trying to whore for your votes like crazy come November 1st because we are going to need them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can vote every day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you can vote every day, so we will be reminding you every day, so please help.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, we don't ask for money, we don't ask for subscriptions, we don't have a plus feed or something that you pay extra money to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: All we want, we want your votes to help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying that, you know, obviously we want legit votes, but they do allow one vote per email address.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in chat says, Rob, aren't you torn that Horde House did not get nominated?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it's much easier this way because then I only have to champion for one show to get votes because that would be weird if the other show had gotten nominated.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did notice it was interesting that The Instance wasn't nominated because I know they've been nominated almost every year so maybe they didn't go for it this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Four Player Podcast, they've had the lock on this thing for like three, four years because they have a huge...
[SPEAKER_05]: Huge fan community and they're very rabid.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were not eligible this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they're not nominated because they won the biggest of the big awards last year and there's some weird rules.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they'll be back next year guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if there's any year we actually stand a chance in hell to win, it's going to be this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So please throw us your votes come November 1st.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And unfortunately, I also have to say this, no other VOG show nominated I looked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was a little depressed because I know I nominated some, but I guess it was just a lot of competition or what have you, and we were whoring the nominations quite a bit, so hopefully we were able to catch some eyes there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're going to do our best to represent VOG and try to win it for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the whores we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys very much for helping that happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, really, really, really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lots of celebratory stuff in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire says, will you pay me to vote for you?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll pay you in hugs and kisses.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are not like the presidential nominees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, we don't pay people for votes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Taiki says, fuck the podcast awards after irreligiosophy got snubbed twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I've kind of had some give and take feelings about the podcast awards because let's be real, it is a huge popularity contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it's great promotion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great promotion.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've got to do the best we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some rapid fire news, some quick gaming news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you like collectible figures, there's going to be some new vinyl figures coming out from Funko Pop.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got some Halo 4 figures and very chibi looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got Cortana and it looks like Master Chief and a couple other of the Spartans.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got a red Spartan and a blue Spartan.
[SPEAKER_03]: so those should be coming soon I'd get a red one but make him purple so it could be donut or pink yes that'd be pretty cool and I'm sure you could paint your own Spartan if you want to but I believe those are going to be available soon if they're not already available I mean they've got to be probably available now since Halo comes out in a week
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, it's already a week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, that's right, because it's election day that it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, election day is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then all this bullshit will be over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where is my mailing bell?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't gotten that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Alan got his.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got mine like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: um okay so Team Fortress 2 they're doing some fun stuff for Halloween of course um Scream Fortress is coming back and what would come with you know your staple Halloween thing why of course zombies zombies would come
[SPEAKER_03]: and, you know, they've got different events going on including Haunted, King of the Hill matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, they've got, I guess, a game, what was it, BombinupCon?
[SPEAKER_03]: and some wizards and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all, of course, Halloween themed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're going to have a brand new man versus machine mission called Wave 666, which will have undead robot enemies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure there's some unique hats to be had there because why wouldn't they have unique hats?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then...
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh oh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what you said, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: You said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came on my radio, I said, last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Pee Wee's Playhouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whenever somebody says the secret word, you just have to start, you just have to get down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that gif that's out there, by the way, of the football player that's getting down doing the Gangnam Style dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: um they're saying other artists that are going to be coming soon Justin Bieber, One Direction, LMFAO and um yeah that's all they've mentioned so far did you hear about the hacking of Justin Bieber's twitter that was fucked up oh my god that was so fucked up I am sorry that was amazing it's one of those things like you're laughing at and then you're like oh my god I'm going to hell for laughing at this because this is terrible alright repeat it for those that may not have heard
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think it was 4chan people that did it, hacked Justin Bieber's Twitter and posted that he had cancer and was going bald from his treatments.
[SPEAKER_02]: So all these girls started shaving their head and posting little signs that said bald for Bieber.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is messed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just goes to show the whole sheep thing, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they're probably disappointed when he's not really dying from cancer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to news about the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you heard me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Crate Box is a game that's been out there and it's turned two this past week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they did a free iOS version to celebrate.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, what's awesome, they're doing a game called Super Bread Box that's going to be an adaptation of the game on the Commodore 64 by the guys who did C64 Cannibalt.
[SPEAKER_05]: C64Ball So there's already a YouTube out there This is going to be available, they say, in early December Check out that awesome soundtrack going into this God, the C64 was so great Flamethrower Every game needs a flamethrower A brand new website launched this week that has a lot of people excited Polygon.com finally officially launched this week
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's notable because there's a lot of like game journalists like people that were big on Joystick before and Kotaku before and some other websites that kind of all came together to form this website and I saw a lot of people on Twitter that were kind of spazzing about the website launching and you know it's a nice looking website I don't know Jamie have you seen this website at all yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you feel about their design choices?
[SPEAKER_02]: The other problem with that being too is that you're going to deal with different resolutions and this is clearly optimized for max resolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not going to work for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The mobile site's really good looking though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So congrats to them for finally starting this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I am going to say one little thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am going to dog on this here because we do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get the whole documentary and making of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little too much ego for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little smug.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a little smug.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very smug.
[SPEAKER_05]: All these little documentaries about the launching of the website and the making of the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one gives a fuck, except for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That shit should be organic.
[SPEAKER_05]: This feels forced, and it makes me not want to like your website.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just being perfectly honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I do like the writing, and I like a lot of the people that are there, and ultimately that wins out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I gotta say, all that self-serving bullshit is kinda...
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be like hosting an awards ceremony where you're going to award yourself for being so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm sure that's right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Polygon's awards for Polygon.
[SPEAKER_05]: And realize that we just told people to please go vote for us in an online awards ceremony, but I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I don't have a fucking documentary about... Let me start a new website.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to create a documentary about starting said website.
[SPEAKER_02]: But really to go back to this though is that their design, I like consistency.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to have consistency with a good website.
[SPEAKER_02]: And with it switching back and forth, you're really not giving it enough consistency.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus you're sacrificing memory for people who may not be optimized to use your site.
[SPEAKER_02]: I prefer it to keep a constant format.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the large splash image up at the top and then the sight going into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the three columnular point of view.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think that you need to pick a style and stick with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the end of the day, of course, the writing is the most important.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they do have some really interesting in-depth articles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Writing doesn't do anything if you can't find shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Snap.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to one other quick thing I want to get out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, one of our co-hosts, we sometimes have a guest host here on the show, and our lovely webmaster of OrangeOnStreet.com wanted me to plug this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to this I say, but of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many of you are fans of the website GitHub.com?
[SPEAKER_05]: GitHub's a pretty awesome site for developers, programmers, and basically nerds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a super nerd site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, GitHub is going to be doing a game jam of their very own.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have the entire month of November to create a web-based game, and it's got to be loosely built around one of these themes.
[SPEAKER_05]: forking that's forking like a spoon or a fork or forks branching or branches cloning or clones pushing or pulling what do we mean loosely based they mean loosely based like you could do a first-person shooter where you throw forks and so on and so on some of the prizes shiny new iPads with retina displays ooh ah github swag and so forth and you know featuring on the github blog
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Moth Game Moth
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking of this little moth with big rainbow wings flying around to ABBA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well that's all I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what's up next for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have more stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a voice that's failing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Souls Prepare to Die Edition is coming out for PC for $19.90.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has warp zones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, warp zones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: then um there is a uh uh nine minutes of footage up for the Mass Effect 3 uh prequel uh which is uh Paragon Lost which I think I'm like the only Mass Effect fan that's really excited about this so I don't know I'm gonna check it out it's Vega it's about Vega but oh hi Mariko um so uh you've got Freddie Prinze Jr.
[SPEAKER_02]: you know playing Vega with his you know not very good you know
[SPEAKER_02]: Spanish.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's loco.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it should be, the actual DVD and Blu-ray will be out on December 28th in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although there is not a date for the UK yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you can find the footage out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there is a Halloween bundle from Indie Royale.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has Sam and Max, The Devil's Playhouse, the full season.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has Home.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has Pathologic, MacGuffin's Curse, and Evil Quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you...
[SPEAKER_02]: Pay over $8, you also receive a FLAC or MP3 copy of C. Jeff's chiptune album, Preshtale.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I was hoping that McGuffin's Curse, I kind of read that as McGruff's Curse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take a bite out of crime!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a noir, a film noir game starring McGruff, a crime dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever happened to McGruff, the crime dog?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he got replaced with something more hip and young.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you forgot to lock your door.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's too bad because all crime needs is a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't give it the chance.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's my job to teach you to protect yourselves.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make it your job to learn.
[SPEAKER_00]: Write to Box 6600 Rockville, Maryland.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, and one more thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lock your door and take a bite out of crime.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand, like, that was a commercial on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lock your damn door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, when I was a little kid, we actually didn't lock our doors that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Growing up, you know, and it was different times, and especially if you lived somewhere a little more rural, there's still a lot of places like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't live somewhere rural.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lived in the suburbs.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a lot of places still like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That they don't lock their doors at night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, McGruff would like you to take a bite out of crime.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a McGruff the Crime Dog monster truck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma in chat says, I remember when McGruff the Crime Dog came to my elementary school.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he take a bite out of the principal?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stan says he was fired when they found a dead prostitute in McGruff's car.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, that answers everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always the dead prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: They find themselves everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, they ruin everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn those dead prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's take a bite out of the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us a story about a time when game over came too soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: In other words, have you ever had an experience where you were really into playing a video game and then suddenly the power went out?
[SPEAKER_05]: The internet went out.
[SPEAKER_05]: A parent came in and turned off the system while you were playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you react?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, I'll get to the host in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, something just popped into my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start with Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you get for talking all that smack.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Panaxium answers the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, for me, it was Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to beat that obnoxious final boss for over an hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I was finally about to beat the damn thing, my dad gracefully trips over the GameCube cables, yanking the power out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember doing a Vader style, no!
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: He looked at the blank screen a few seconds, then turned to me with a big dorky grin and said, Sorry, I'm prone to power trips.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was some punishment for the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much for that, Dad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm prone to power trips.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to Facebook to get some of the questions here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brandon H answered the question and said, Just unlocked everything in Guitar Hero 3, then in the middle of saving the power went out, and then it came back on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red ring of death and corrupted saves.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a really bad day, to have your machine red ring of death on top of the power failure and corrupt your saves.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Joe G answers on Facebook and says, Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used the wrong name.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have to put it at the beginning or I might miss it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haseo Sumerogawa says, I was playing Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was on Mad Moxie's Underdome Riot and I was playing the last arena there and was about three quarters of the way through and I had finished all other quests from the games and Zombie Island is rolling.
[SPEAKER_05]: I died, got booted out, and I played the whole thing offline, mind you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when I died, I was shit out of luck
[SPEAKER_05]: and what the fuck did the autosave and power flipped off corrupting the save data and I think people in Texas heard me yelling obscenities.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burr replies, Growing up, I always remember getting kicked off the computer mid-game because my mom wanted me to take a break and go outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: I always end up spending my time away from the game thinking about what was going to happen next, and it would continue on to the next day during school.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can physically separate a gamer from their drug, but you can't keep it out of their mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: James S replied and said, when I was about six years old, I was playing Yoshi's Cookie on the original Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game was awesome, just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that game on the SNES.
[SPEAKER_05]: Earmark that for a classic game some weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Yoshi's Cookie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of frustration on a high level, I proceeded to rage and I slammed the Game Boy against my head, causing the screen to shatter instantly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep in mind, I was six.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never been so mortified yet satisfied in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever, like, has your rage ever broken something that was like several hundred dollars like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan, back in the day, would break controllers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one time he took a controller back.
[SPEAKER_02]: He bought a new controller and then returned the controller, except he returned the broken controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was like a Saturn controller wow Ronnie B answered and said when I first moved to where I am now the breakers would trip every day often erasing hours of my Civ progress on the 360 I also hate when broken games often downloadable games glitch so badly the only option is to restart due to locked menus stuck cameras or whatever
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt with an arcade answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back when I used to play a lot of Initial D in the arcade during my college years, I once lost my entire record and stats for my main car in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in the process of transferring my data from Initial D2 to Initial D3 and the machine errored out and my card got jammed inside the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since my Initial D2 card was already voided because of the transfer, I lost everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: several months worth of work on my main car was gone forever needless to say I was frustrated but after it happened I quit playing Initial D all the work that went into building that one car and then losing it got rid of my inspiration and drive pun intended to play the game anymore then
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, I'm going to do one more answer here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitstun says,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some good answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I didn't read everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_05]: But go check out the rest of the answers at Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio or our Google Plus community.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around the room and see if anybody has things to share.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, I know you said you had something.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I was in high school, my little brother Matthew got hit by a car.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was six.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that night, basically, I got dropped off at the mall with my best friend Jennifer.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we went to the movies, went to the arcade because basically there's like here's some money and I ended up getting in on a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game in the arcade and we, this is the first time I'd ever played a full four player game they had me on Leonardo so I was like okay he's kind of cool and we got all the way to the end of the game had just got the last hit and they shut off the machines
[SPEAKER_02]: We were all like, no!
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, can you think of a story?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have one while you're thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a lot of good ones, but do you know how old NES is?
[SPEAKER_05]: You had to blow on the cartridge to get it to work, and then sometimes the game would just spontaneously reset, like right in the middle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that happened to us the night my friend and I decided to play Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3 from start to finish with no warping, around like World 6 or 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: If something hit the ground too hard, which I think is what happened, I think we dropped something on the ground, and it just threw everything off balance enough so it was like, reset!
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything was ruined.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we gave up and moved on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really have anything that I remember as far as power outages and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing I can remember is that I was making a pretty awesome...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we take a moment to remind our listeners of the mutual love we have for the game ZZT?
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish there was something like that again.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's still Megazooks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they still make stuff for ZZT?
[SPEAKER_05]: Megazooks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new one.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, he said the magic word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I one time spent four hours working on a sim house and forgot to save, and then the power went out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should have a VOGZZT contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've thought about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seriously have.
[SPEAKER_05]: You and I would be the only ones that would enter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Prove me wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: If there's interest in a ZZT VOG contest, email the show and tell us you're interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we will put something together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, just a few more stories for you guys, then we're going to get to listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the PS3's been hacked again, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically what happened was a hacker group called the Three Musketeers finally released the level zero keys.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not necessarily the way to get those keys themselves, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think that's why it has to run on the 355 firmware, because anything newer doesn't use those keys anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, for compatibility's sake, they need to have everything, you know, use those keys at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, it's been so long since I've looked into the hacking stuff, it's... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, apparently, this is supposed to be unpatchable as far as they can keep using this exploit to forever have custom firmwares on PS3 and run new games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll have to see if that's actually going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as of right now, they haven't really released any new...
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, I have to double check that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say I saw something about a custom firmware for 4.3 come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Debug firmware for 4.25 has been leaked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Homebrew for custom firmware 4.21.
[SPEAKER_03]: Updated DMCA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what does this really mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this going to be like rampant piracy on the PS3 now?
[SPEAKER_03]: No more than it already is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just means that they're going to be able to keep doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: alrighty I would say you have to have I think a firmware that's like 355 or lower which I don't remember what mine is right now because I haven't updated in a long time so I don't think I'm 355 I think I'm newer than that but you know if you have an older firmware then that means that you'll be able to translate the old ones so that they can run like a custom firmware on those or based off those
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know the old saying we have on the show, hackers gonna hack, but at least no personal information stolen, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that kind of hack?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that kind of hack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, because a lot of people were... I think there's some misinformation out there because people were saying, did it get hacked again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh my gosh, PlayStation got hacked again?
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's not that kind of hack, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm going to get into another story here on a completely different note.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is something that has me very excited, and I want to see if this is something maybe a few of you out there can recognize by the music, which I love the soundtrack to this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyone recognize this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, if you played this game as much as I did, you probably heard this song a lot more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shadowgate, Shadowgate, Shadowgate, Shadowgate, Shadowgate
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Marsh and Carl Roloffs, I apologize if I'm mispronouncing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave Marsh and Carl Roloffs, they worked on the original Shadowgate with ICOM simulations 25 years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've started this new company.
[SPEAKER_05]: They bought the rights to the old Shadowgate game, and Uninvited, and Deja Vu, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: and also got the rights to the 8-bit soundtrack which apparently was done by somebody completely different it was done by a Japanese guy who I guess maybe in the port of the games over to the NES maybe it was done there so like if you listen to the trailer for Shadowgate it has like a newer version of that music which is awesome let me see if I can play a little bit of this for you but yeah um
[SPEAKER_05]: They're doing a Kickstarter for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be redesigned puzzles and an expanded storyline.
[SPEAKER_05]: But most of the plot devices from the original game will still be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like in the trailer, you can definitely see the room with the lake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you used to put the orb in the lake to freeze it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can see the room with the dragon breathing fire at the other end.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's all of that in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So very, very cool that they're doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are seeking $120,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: to do versions for PC, Mac, iOS, and Android.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do $10 right now to get a DRM-free, and they're really emphasizing that, a DRM-free download when the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are projecting 2013 November for that, so it is gonna be a bit of a wait, but I will say this, this is only the second Kickstarter ever that I've given money to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did donate to this Kickstarter because...
[SPEAKER_05]: I really like Shadowgate.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked those old ICOM games, so I'm really excited about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only have so much money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't do the $130 or more, but that did sound really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: An original Shadowgate card game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would have been kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a little bit out of my price range, personally.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm sure there's people already... It's already up to $41,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sound again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me fast forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to do this part of the trailer here.
[SPEAKER_05]: so you can tell they're like totally like which is pretty awesome there's the wraith i remember that from one scene so you definitely see the artwork is gorgeous oh yeah i would pay for this just for the artwork yeah it's it's it's gorgeous so um yeah zojoy is the name of the company that is putting this together that uh these guys started so good luck to them and obviously as a fan of these games since i was a kid i hope they do it i really want it so very cool
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: One more story and then we're going to get to Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I do have another story, don't I?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about the game Waking Mars?
[SPEAKER_02]: This one was an iOS ecological puzzle adventure game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually going to be coming out to PC, Mac, Linux, and Android on November 6th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a revamped version done by Tiger Style Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is going to have high def with voice acting throughout the game and be just a great big step up from the iOS version.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, this was really interesting to me is that they specifically listed Linux among the platforms, which I think is great Linux getting more attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, a lot of people kind of giving Mars attention with the whole curiosity and all that, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I... This is a game that I kind of had my eye on to play for a little while and I just never went back for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It...
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a game that was supposed to have really shown off just how great iOS can be programmed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I'm definitely going to play this on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to tell me how it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm waiting for your review before I check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to that time, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is time to bring this segment back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been forever since we've done it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is time to play Listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've never heard Listless before, what we're going to do tonight is we are going to create the definitive list, the definitive answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a highly scientific process, the definitive list around a topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's how it'll work, and I'll tell you the topic in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be four of us playing tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have a special guest join us here, so everybody help me welcome to the show or welcome back to the show, Alan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing, Alan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so Alan is going to be playing listless with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The four of us will give our top three answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to leave us a list of 12.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we're going to go around the room and each eliminate one answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a really tough thing we got to do, but it's part of the process.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to leave us with a list of eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then those of you in the chat room will vote on those final eight answers and help us come up with our definitive list of the top three answers to this topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Earlier in the show, we talked about that G4 is losing its last bit of video game programming and that it will no longer be a video game network.
[SPEAKER_05]: And most of us have thrown up our hands and said, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice knowing you, G4.
[SPEAKER_05]: So tonight's listless topic...
[SPEAKER_05]: The TV show that would make me watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be an existing show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be a new show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be anything you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show that would make me watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to give your suggestions in our chat room, live.vognetwork.com in case an answer should get duplicated or, you know, sometimes we just like the chat answers better than our own.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make your suggestions in the chat room and we will read some of our favorite answers from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: So again, TV show that would make me watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's go around and start building the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we will start with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what is your number three answer for a show that would make you watch Chief Oregon?
[SPEAKER_03]: The brand new Iron Chef series that they're doing, the Japanese Iron Chef, but translated in English.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, to be fair, the Food Network probably has a lock on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, it hasn't started yet, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's a pretty serious answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want new Japanese Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, new Japanese Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your number three answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Show that we get you to watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, first of all, I never actually watched it, but I would go for Real Housewives Disney Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like on SNL.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like an actual version of that sketch from SNL The Real Housewives of Disney Yeah, that's a good suggestion, I like that Alright, my number three answer tonight And I see people saying this in chat right now So chat and I are on the same page My number three answer is Starrcade 2, Electric Boogaloo Yes Where the contestants who don't do well at the games Will actually get electrified Starrcade 2, Electric Boogaloo
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say Nick Arcade, but that wouldn't make sense because it's Nick Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so so far we have New Japanese Iron Chef, Real Housewives of Disney, and Starrcade 2, Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan, what would be the number three answer for show that would get you to watch G4 again?
[SPEAKER_06]: A documentary special.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're responsible for Olivia Munn, and we're very, very sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: A five-hour apology special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to shorten that a little bit to Olivia Munn apology special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, that would only be one movie, unfortunately, or a miniseries.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be like a miniseries.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what things about Olivia Munn should be apologized for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen her face?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's cold.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are cold.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, so far, we have New Japanese Iron Chef, Real Housewives of Disney, Starrcade 2 Electric Boogaloo, and Olivia Munn Apology Special.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deanna Allers, look at her and go, girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to check yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what is your number two pick for the list?
[SPEAKER_03]: The screensavers.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, your number two answer My number two answer is Gorgeous Ladies of Wrestling
[SPEAKER_02]: because GLOW was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want gorgeous ladies of wrestling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was addicted to GLOW when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a good show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this was an old show?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't...
[SPEAKER_02]: Back in the day, I had Godiva, the woman who wore the skin-colored bodysuit with flowers all over it, and Mount Fuji.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hated it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: GLOW is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: My mom used to let me stay up until 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: and watch UHF and see the GLOW show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I might have to vote for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you mean USA?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't UHF like the Weird Al movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: A weird movie based off of the alternative band of TV radio that had channels on it, yeah Alright, alright My number two answer tonight for a show that would make me watch G4 again The Days of Our Citadel, the Mass Effect soap opera There you go, Days of Our Citadel, the Mass Effect soap opera You mean The Shitadel
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe, DarkSakura, I do not have your support on a Mass Effect soap opera.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: You would watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extra garris.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: If Nickelodeon could have 15 as a soap opera, we can have Days of Our Citadel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan, your number two answer for the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: How not to market something special 35 year old nerds They're loaded, they're loyal, they're distracted
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, you need to explain this one a little bit while I figure out how to shorten the answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would this show be?
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole basis of the G4 channel model is let's appeal to adult geeks because they have money, they play video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to put shows on TV that they'll want to watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: They still buy lots of video games each year and they're not watching this yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're confused.
[SPEAKER_05]: I shortened that to 35-year-old nerd special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that work?
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, you and I turn 35 next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to point that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know something sad?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: My brother Phillip yesterday turned 30.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 26th, sorry, the other day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so so far we have on the list New Japanese Iron Chef, Real Housewives of Disney, Starcade 2 Electric Boogaloo, Olivia Munn Apology Special, The Screensavers, Gorgeous Ladies of Wrestling, Days of Our Citadel, Mass Effect Soap Opera, and 35-Year-Old Nerd Special.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The number one answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: The number one thing that would most make you watch G4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, if they're going to compete with Spike, then really there's only one choice, and that is big-breasted bikini car wash.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how exactly would big-breasted bikini car wash be a show?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just women washing cars and sudsing up each other with large breasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And would Loki get to be a special correspondent that motorboats the boobies?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be the host.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be doing the play-by-play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nelly will get to motorboat the boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love... Or you can just have me, like, you know, in the beginning of each episode, I'll drive up the car, honk the horn, cast a smile at the camera, and... I would love you and your wife to host this show, because your wife would just walk up to the ladies and be like, how did you let your boobies get so big?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have really big areolas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, that's just shameful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're not going to be topless.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that could be the whole web series, but you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The unrated Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm fine with topless car wash too, but you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Big Breast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it doesn't say, well, they could start off with bikinis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, but then we're getting the Playboy content there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't want to infringe on any of their rights.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised you didn't do World Series of Strip Poker.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where I thought you'd be going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura I would actually watch the Angry Video Game Nerd TV show if they did one.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I love watching the Angry Video Game Nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love watching his movie specials.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think it's time for the Angry Video Game Nerd crossover?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's time.
[SPEAKER_05]: From YouTubes to cable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost said ScrewAttack, but I think the Angry Video Game Nerd would be more marketable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, my number one answer, and this is big, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every single one of you know that if this show was on G4, you'd be click, I am there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My number one answer is Loki's cosplay challenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand what that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who am I challenging?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would basically go around to different anime conventions and interview people that are cosplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the viewers would pick their favorite cosplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the challenge would be that you have to imitate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I'd watch that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's cosplay challenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lastly, but not leastly, certainly not leastly, Alan, your number one answer for show that would get you to watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to preface this response by saying that I used to watch Tech TV back in the very beginning when Adam Sessler, the host, extended play out in front of the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's very cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: My number one answer is Adam Sessler and Kevin Pereira present Black Boxer Brief Boner Boxing, a Gaynor Telethon to please, please come out of the closet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just shortened it to Adam and Kevin Black Boner Boxing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It works, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, even though there was something about boxer briefs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Adam and Kevin Black Boner Boxing works for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is, the list as it stands right now, the 12 on the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: New Japanese Iron Chef, Real Housewives of Disney, Starcade 2 Electric Boogaloo, Olivia Munn Apology Special, The Screensavers, Gorgeous Ladies of Wrestling, Days of Our Citadel, The Mass Effect Soap, 35-Year-Old Nerd Special, Big Breasted Bikini Car Wash, Angry Video Game Nerd TV Show, Loki's Cosplay Challenge, and Adam and Kevin Black Boner Boxing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, unfortunately, it is time to go around and take items off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's part of the process.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's painful, but science is painful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do it for science.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a lot of them, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Alan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do the... Let's get rid of the Olivia Munn apology special.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a one-time special.
[SPEAKER_06]: She is on the Daily Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: She is fucking awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are responsible for her and they need to pay reparations.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's part of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's why Jon Stewart is the best person on television.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, the Olivia Munn apology special is gone, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing left to apologize for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DarkSakura, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: Big Breasted Bikini Car Wash.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, because...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so cliche.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, why don't you have big-breasted monster truck driving or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_03]: We can have a network based on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big-breasted entertainment.
[SPEAKER_03]: The BBB.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, my turn to eliminate something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am going to eliminate... Oh, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hate to do this, but DarkSakura, the gorgeous ladies of wrestling, has got to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never watched it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not a wrestling person.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's plenty.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't just that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have UPN for your wrestling needs or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: CW or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's no more glow.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will you forgive me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Will you forgive me if Pinkberry is involved?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_06]: Last time I did a list list, I would say that I would be the chat room's voice, because I'm infamous for getting rid of the things that they most want to win, like President Cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm trying to look at what they don't want to get rid of.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say New Japanese Iron Chef, because I don't see that mentioned at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, new Japanese Iron Chef, it is stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so there it is, you are left with... How did 35 year old Nerd Special survive?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even understand that one still.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you explain that one more time?
[SPEAKER_05]: We live it, don't resent it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, don't dream it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the comments from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the answers from our chat room that did not make the cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane kind of was on to something because Shane suggested hot guys playing games in underwear.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you sort of did do that one, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw says, when G4 gets syndicated episodes of RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stan says The Late Show with GLaDOS Taiki says Clippy B's Drag Race Virtual Phil says RuPaul's PVP Bloodbath A lot of folks, Duke Nukem saying Arena, Portal, Icons, and the shows that actually were on G4 some time ago
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is one more time in chatters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is time for you to vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send Rob Roberts a private message with your number one and number two pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Real Housewives of Disney, Starrcade 2, Electric Boogaloo, The Screensavers, Days of Our Citadel, The Mass Effect Soap Opera, 35-Year-Old Nerd Special, Angry Video Game Nerd TV Show, Loki's Cosplay Challenge, and Adam and Kevin Black Boner Boxing.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shouldn't it be Black Boxer Boner Boxing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Black Boner Boxing, but Black Boner Boxing sounds better.
[SPEAKER_05]: It goes back to our reoccurring theme of Big Black Cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: But remember, it's really guys in black boxer briefs wrestling with boners.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Adam Sessler and Kevin Ferrer's Black Boxer Brief Boner Bonanza.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alliteration special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, send in your votes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please vote now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send a private message to Rob Roberts with your number one and your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and while we do that, it is time to go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to read these tonight, DarkSakura, or do I need to?
[SPEAKER_05]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_04]: My voice is actually going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we pick some of our favorites to read here on air, except I haven't pulled up the mailbag yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have it up, so I'll just go ahead and do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, I'm there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you want to do... Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are we going to start tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you going to read all four?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I didn't know if you'd screen them or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Professional radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start with AZHP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_05]: I decided to check out a new anime called...
[SPEAKER_05]: Aoi?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how to say that word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aoi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aoi.
[SPEAKER_05]: It means blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aoi Sekai no Chusen Dei.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's touted as being a parody of the old console wars between Nintendo and Sega with gratuitous fan service.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as far as I'm concerned, it delivers.
[SPEAKER_05]: It tells the story of the small country of Seigua fighting against Ninteldo for control of their continent.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only on its first episode as of this writing, but so far they've introduced a number of somewhat easily recognizable, at least by DarkSakura, not sure how massively knowledgeable on classic Sega games Rob and Loki are, parody characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: A blue-haired protagonist named Gear, who is super speedy and is trying to avenge the death of his beloved friend Teal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I know Sonic and Tails, come on, cut me some slack here, cut me some slack here.
[SPEAKER_05]: A purple-haired sister, Nell, who is his emotional support, like Nii from Phantasy Star 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The General Hermes, he has colored gems on her necklace, maybe a parody of columns.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rival lieutenant with little angel wings in her hair, Opal, based on Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_05]: Opa Opa!
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a genius tactician, Tetraloff, who loves sticking a long stick into things to fill holes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you three guesses on what that's from.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pornography?
[SPEAKER_05]: A picture for the host's benefit.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little picture there of all the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I need to see this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the little monkey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's super dumb and has girls clothes coming off for pretty much no reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all you need, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's classic TV right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the main villain has a giant mustache, a sword with a mushroom shaped grip, and he rides a flying dragon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, look at how dumb he looks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it says no hot linking.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to copy paste this link because it doesn't like me linking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, this is great radio when I copy-paste.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not gonna let you, because it's... So is it Alisekaino what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's access it from the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue World of what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alisekaino Chushinde.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I know the first part's Blue World of something.
[SPEAKER_05]: In conclusion, I highly recommend this anime because it's super dumb and pandering to people who like classic games and big boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I figure it would be perfect for OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Correct!
[SPEAKER_05]: It is!
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen manga for this, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: The design looks way familiar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too bad we didn't hear about that before we were talking about the G4 shows we'd like to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to our next email, which is from Nutman.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just wanted to give my condolences to Jamie after losing her cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: My dog I had for 13 years just passed away recently and it was awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think she had a stroke at some point and she may have had many seizures before we could get her to the vet to be put to sleep.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was terrible and I wish that they would not have been the last memories I have of her.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like Shermie, I butchered the name I'm sure, and they did spell it wrong, but that's okay, they tried, went peacefully during the night though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could never talk about it on air like you, so massive kudos to having the courage to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I would tear up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie did a very good job last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, I did have a pretty significant sniffle Losing a pet, and that was not the sinus infection either Losing a pet is something that only other pet owners can understand I hope you will feel better about this terrible situation soon, happy face
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's been about a week and a half now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's funny, like last night I was walking back to the bedroom to go to bed and I saw a shadow at my feet and my brain instantly went to it's Shermie and stepped over the shadow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, wait, that's not the cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, it's getting slowly better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I still have problems doing laundry, actually, because that was Shermie's room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, good excuse to make Dan do the laundry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Redertainment starts this email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trainer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Podcrafters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does he have a thing for, like, Trainer in the Mass Effect games or is this another reference?
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to know this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Redertainment wants to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Podcrafters.
[SPEAKER_05]: After seeing Loki's Halloween costume on Twitter, which, by the way, Loki, amazing Halloween costume.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you worn it yet or is that for work?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's for work.
[SPEAKER_05]: This question comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the weirdest costume you ever wore for Halloween?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine is the Kigurumi I wore last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might wear it again this year due to its supreme awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay Care, Red Entertainment, Trainer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sent from my iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the record, that's basically the animal pajamas.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what those are.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the weirdest costume you ever wore for Halloween?
[SPEAKER_02]: My weirdest costumes have always been from my actual cosplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really think I've done anything weird for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did go as a pirate wench, which was fun, because I walked around with a whip and just started smacking on my coworkers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and Halloween's about being slutty.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it wasn't slutty at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just, you know, the bodice, that was about as slutty as it got, but it was a long skirt and big boots and a whip and my hat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried one time to wear, I was going to wear my bike in costume one year, but that would have just been cold.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to the next email from... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to answer the question, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The weirdest costume you ever wore for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I was in eighth grade, I dressed as a bag lady, and I got sent to the principal's office because I hit a kid with my purse.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he had it coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was an asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was one of those eighth grade bullies, and he dared to make a comment about my costume, and so I thwacked him with my purse, like a bag lady would do, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: He deserved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you... Oh, you're sending one from... Oh, an email?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except I'm like full up on messages right now, so look at that, because I've got to count the votes still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, talking behind the scenes and no one could hear any of that anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Geez.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, one more email from Flaco Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: He always emails Horde House, so I'm very happy to hear him crossing over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Flaco Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't heard anyone else on the show bring it up and it's getting close to Halloween, so I thought I'd write in and give my review for Welcome to Silent Hill, The Haunted House, or Maze, as they call it, at Universal Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am glad to hear about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone mentioned that to me, by the way, having seen it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Extover?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he saw it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it was X4, I think it was somebody else, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a great time and they did a fantastic job.
[SPEAKER_05]: It better be there next year because we can't wait to go back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Halloween, Flaco Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, bad news for Flaco Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movie came in sixth place at the box office this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not looking good for any long-term memory.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, if they invested all that money in it, who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they will bring it back again next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does it for emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com if you want to send us your emails for a future...
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, it's time to get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to my son, this infection.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really hate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate my voice going.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then my really...
[SPEAKER_02]: I like having short hair, but it wasn't stacked quite right, so it's a little uneven in the back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and Origin, EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: After you did my weekly headache.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you have a headache again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, I get them every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's... I don't know what it's from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I stay up too late.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you're allergic to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's before I get to the show, so... It's not anything to do with the show, it's just... I get a headache.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, an F you to not having enough hours in the day, because, like, I'm really... Like, we have not had time to go to the grocery store today.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been doing so much, but... Eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I shouldn't complain about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you were running around when I got here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: I took a 15-minute nap.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I was like, where are Loki's stories?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it all worked out.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, Loki has another story for us before we get to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll let you know when here in a moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: But meanwhile, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, apparently the Urban Outfitters is selling unlicensed Nintendo product.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my goodness!
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: How dare they not license stuff to sell?
[SPEAKER_03]: And all this, like, really random stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, considering Urban Outfitters is basically, like, apparel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's kind of not really something that I would see them selling.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, like, they're trying to sell Nintendo 64 controllers, USB Nintendo, or Super Nintendo controllers, and, like, Supaboy portable game console and one of those knockoff Super Nintendo things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not really sure why this is news, but we're talking about... Well, because it's knockoff shit, and it's at a major store, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, everybody sells those stupid knockoff Super Nintendo Genesis things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, all the indie game stores sell them.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Urban Outfitters.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: That just seems like Sears selling something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who gives a shit that they're selling that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm going to go run to Urban Outfitters right now after the show and check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, I got a story for you guys here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about a favorite game of mine getting an MMO, but there's a twist to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't there always?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Civilization MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, Civilization Online MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be available soon in Asia.
[SPEAKER_05]: FireAxis is working with XL Games a Korean studio that did the game Lineage you might have heard of that game it's like the biggest MMO in the world yes bigger than Warcraft they're going to create Civilization Online it is an online only game it's going to be in Asian markets soon
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're doing Civilization Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't say a whole lot else about it, just otherwise the partnership there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of news about what is going to be in the game or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a little weird to me because Civ 5 you can already play online.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how does an MMO work?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it like never stop?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it like an endless world that you can always explore?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's more things about this I'd like to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other one is...
[SPEAKER_05]: Why won't we get a version in the US?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll announce some type of partnership to publish it here locally?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'd like to be able to try this, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's going to do it for the news tonight, which means it is time to open up the Skype line!
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about whatever you want to talk about in the news tonight or maybe something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, we'll get to Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR or Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if there's anything you want to add here for last minute stories while we wait for some calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Bobby Hey, Bobby, good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's up, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys were talking a lot about G4 earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we were.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, we dedicated a whole segment of our show to it tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't dedicate anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a little conflicted just because of my past and stuff with G4, and I'm trying to figure out how I want to say what I want to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, for those that don't know, tell us a little bit about what the past is for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so for those that...
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't, you know, well, I mean, obviously we came from All Games and Scott Rubin, but I had met Scott Rubin a long time before then.
[SPEAKER_07]: I met him in 97.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he was one of the people that started G4 after the first incarnation of All Games went away in the dot-com bust.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was pretty much right there at the formation and creation of G4 as an outsider, as a volunteer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back when we just knew it was something that a Disney guy was going to be starting with Comcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's all we knew about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was there when they launched the site in April of 2002 and the network didn't go on the air until for a couple months later, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so I was there and I actually was the first forum moderator over the G4 forums.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ran the chat room for about two years.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was on the majority of the shows that were on G4 at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually have a VHS tape that's like 30 minutes long of every single time I was either mentioned or shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never realized that you were actually on the network at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never realized that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was the...
[SPEAKER_07]: for some of the shows I was like the backup caller because they had a talk show G4TV.com which was hosted by Scott Rubin and Laura Foy and Tina Wood and they taped they would do a live stream of their taping but since it was a TV show it was like a five hour taping and so we were all kind of in the audience and they would take calls and sometimes I would be the one who would call in and I'd work out with the producer what I talk about or I would be the backup if the guy that they wanted to call in flaked out
[SPEAKER_07]: and so I would have to make up stuff about games I've never played and act as a caller like there was one about Splinter Cell and you know me, I would never play Splinter Cell but I actually called into the show once it was still me, I wasn't playing a character or anything talking about Splinter Cell
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to make a minor correction to something you said because you said we came from all games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was our previous home prior to this, but we had started elsewhere before.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we were around on our own live 365 thing when G4 started.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we were those viewers out there that was kind of little critical and cynical of what was going on on G4 television.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was also critical and cynical because I left.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was basically, I mean, everybody... And it's kind of funny because my version of G4 is different from other people's version of G4 because I stopped my involvement with G4 about the same time Scott did, which was right after the Tech TV merger because I didn't like the way they handled it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to a lot of people, when they say, oh, G4, they think the screensavers.
[SPEAKER_07]: They think Call for Help.
[SPEAKER_07]: They think X-Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: That wasn't G4.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was Tech TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: The G4 that I remember was mostly G4TV.com and Icons and Cinematek and Pulse and Portal and Arena and all those.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had some great ideas.
[SPEAKER_07]: The execution was lacking just because of budget, but they didn't give them a chance to actually get the budget for any of those shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember Pringles Presents.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was cheat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pringles presented cheat.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what was interesting is because I actually did get to meet most of the hosts from the 2002 to 2004, including the illustrious Will Wheaton.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they all kind of knew who I was.
[SPEAKER_07]: just through the forum posts and stuff because they interacted some and I would be the liaison sometimes and a lot of them a lot of the hosts actually did know what they were talking about with video games which was the main complaint everybody had about the original G4 hosts is that they didn't know what they were talking about they were just reading a teleprompter two or three of them were reading teleprompter and didn't know but I could actually have intelligent conversations with the majority of the hosts of all the G4 shows about video games and that's one thing a lot of people didn't realize back before the merger
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you think people didn't get that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you think that got lost in translation?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that overproduction?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I see Tigercloss in our chat says, the G4TV.com show was heavily scripted.
[SPEAKER_05]: The callers couldn't call in and call about whatever they wanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that because maybe they took some of the organicness out of it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, because basically it was a video game channel being made by cable television executives.
[SPEAKER_07]: so they followed the cable television model they didn't know that much about video games they just they thought they knew the way to do it and that's one of the reasons Scott Rubin left was because he couldn't get into their head that they were doing it all wrong and they didn't listen to him because all he had done is web stuff he didn't know how cable industry worked
[SPEAKER_05]: Josh Crane and Jim Downs
[SPEAKER_07]: also worked with Sudo and the All Games Network, and Josh Crane became an executive at G4.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's no longer with them, and Jim Downs was a producer who was also no longer with the network.
[SPEAKER_07]: So none of them are with the network anymore, but there were some people that are still there, and I don't know if they're still going to be with the network after the change or what, because they kind of did more generic stuff with the TV network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, is there anybody still at G4 that was there at the very beginning?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, there's one guy, his name's Derek, I'm not going to give his last name, but people who probably from the All Games era know who I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: He is still there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's the only one I really know of that is still there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he was also kind of from that pseudo-online, he might have been, I don't know if he was flown from New York, but I know he was one of Scott's friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let me ask this, I mean, you know, obviously this news has you a little conflicted because it is kind of rough to see the last remnants of G4 disappearing, but these shows were tech TV shows that are the last.
[SPEAKER_05]: So didn't this all kind of already end five years ago?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it all, well, G4 to me ended in 2004.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I liked tech TV, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched both networks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched the screensavers every day on tech TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the reason G4 bought, well, the reason, I'll kind of explain because you read some of my comments.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, Paul Allen, who was one of the VPs of Microsoft, he bought a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's the guy that started tech TV because he wanted a cable television network about technology.
[SPEAKER_07]: He got bored with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and said, you know, I know you guys are about to pull a profit and pull high ratings.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Tech TV was on the rise.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like, but I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Comcast is offering money, so I want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Comcast wanted Tech TV because G4 could not get on DirecTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: They couldn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: DirecTV rejected them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Said that we don't want your content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tech TV was already on...
[SPEAKER_07]: DirectTV, so that was their Trojan horse.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so they became G4 Tech TV, and this is why they actually did that, because they could not change the type of network until they renegotiated the contract with DirectTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: So in order to be broadcast on TechTV's signal, they had to retain TechTV's type of content.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's why they kept the screensavers and kept some of the other TechTV-type stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: and became G4 Tech TV and then once they renegotiated the contract they went back to G4 interesting
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's funny, I told you I was going to tell this story in chat about one of my most famous acts one of the acts that has shaped cable television that I did or at least I claim to do and when I say this story, realize that at the time I believed this was true and to his credit, the other person played along and told me it was true
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: to help him get leverage over the director.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now it's two voices instead of just one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because G4TV.com really devolved into what can we make Laura Foy and Tina Wood do to appease the teenager male demographic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's why they did the challenges that had the gross ending to it or whatever, the humiliation at the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: And
[SPEAKER_07]: In comes chat one day is somebody that I kind of remember from the old pseudo days from Shooters, which is one of the old All Games Network shows, Captain Emmy.
[SPEAKER_07]: and he was sitting there talking about how he didn't like where he was.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was working at some public access station or some real old TV station and I knew Scott was looking for a production assistant but Scott actually told me he didn't want me to come out for it because I wouldn't get paid enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I told Captain Emmy that, hey, Scott's looking for this guy for a production assistant.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like, oh, no, I couldn't ask him for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, no, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's looking for somebody to fill the job.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Scott comes into chat and I'm like, hey Scott, Captain Emmy's looking for a job.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was, oh really?
[SPEAKER_07]: And to kind of tie the story together, Captain Emmy was the screen name for Kevin Pereira.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I believe for the longest time, and to Kevin's credit, he agreed with me that I got him his job at G4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the real version is more like Kevin knew the job was open, he was coming into chat just to see when Scott was around to talk to him about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he...
[SPEAKER_07]: He'll play along and say that I kind of pointed him in the direction when I think that was the direction he was going in anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just happened to be in the right place at the right time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, in some ways you can blame me for Kevin even being hired at G4 in the first place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe thank you in the case of Alan and what he said during the listless segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: The shows I liked on G4 the most were actually not produced by G4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Electric Playground and Judgment Day were from Greedy Productions.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're still in business.
[SPEAKER_07]: Electric Playground is actually the longest running television show about video games in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been running since 1995.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually recently went daily.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're mainly Canadian.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're produced up in Vancouver and Judgment Day is actually just a reskinning of their show Reviews on the Run.
[SPEAKER_07]: G4 wanted something specific and so they took the Reviews on the Run footage that had Victor Lucas and Tommy Tallarico and put G4 graphics around it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's all they did.
[SPEAKER_07]: So in Canada it was Reviews on the Run.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it was Judgment Day.
[SPEAKER_07]: They still do Reviews on the Run and what's funny is Tommy Tallarico no longer does any of that stuff because he's so busy with Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: but one of the people that does reviews on Reviews on the Run was kind of like me in the same sense that we were in the G4 forums together and kind of attached to specific shows and personalities I attach to Scott Rubin, I do podcasts this guy, Jose Sanchez he went by Fubar attached himself to Victor Lucas and he now is one of the hosts on Reviews on the Run he was a production assistant there for Greedy for the longest time and worked his way up wow, that's awesome huh
[SPEAKER_05]: well it's been story time with Bobby Blackwolf but this is this is good it's kind of neat to hear the history and I hope you do end up doing your piece for VOG Network about kind of reflecting on it gosh I'm trying to think what else to ask you with this thing but do you think there is a future for video game television do you think somebody else we don't know of yet could come in and start a video game network or is it just you know what no video game stuff is always going to be on the internet this is something always internet based
[SPEAKER_07]: There's only one way, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, I'm looking to Korea.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only way that we can get a video game channel is if esports takes off in America the way it's taken off in Korea.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the only way I think it'll happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think we're going to see a generic video game network like G4.
[SPEAKER_07]: G4 tried a whole bunch of different things.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't have all new shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had one show that was a scripted show.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it was about and took place in MMOs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was an early machinima show using a whole bunch of different MMOs to tell this overarching story.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Portal and they tried stuff like that and it didn't really take off.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I don't think anybody has the patience to make that take off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think with esports, I think if esports does take off, if League of Legends takes off or StarCraft or something we don't know about yet, we may be able to get a dedicated esports channel, but that's probably as close as we're going to be able to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would see it probably ending up more being an esports show on the Ocho, you know, or something along those lines.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to be able to see something, and hopefully it will be less corporate controlled.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I know that's just looking at it through such, you know, dream pie-in-the-sky ideals, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it sounds like a lot of the crap that happened on both G4 and Tech TV were just bad executive decisions.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, and I'm going to point this out, Leo Laporte tweeted this week, Attack of the Show and X-Play on G4 lasted eight years.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was longer than any show on Tech TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Tech TV started in, I think, 99, and they were off the air in 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Bobby, before we let you go to take more calls, do you have anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been doing a lot of interviews lately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you have.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they've been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got a big interview show next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not live, but I've got some big interviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hotline Miami, which is a new indie game that everybody's loving right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then MechWarrior Online and Fallen Enchantress.
[SPEAKER_07]: All those interviews next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I interviewed a local studio about their first-person Magic game this week, earlier tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're Xavier, and actually a lot of their developers were in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I've already gotten an email from them thanking me for it and telling me that it sounds like one of the quotes I said may be on the back of the box in two years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, I wasn't the one that initially said the quote Dungeon Buster did, so I don't know how this works.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they specific because it's a first-person magic game and...
[SPEAKER_07]: Dungeon Buster in chat was like, so it's kind of like Skyrim's magic system done right, and I repeated that, and that's what they quoted in the interview that they really appreciated hearing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, if you're not already tuning in an hour early at vognetwork.com before OLR, you're missing out on a great, Bobby's having a great year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, not that like the other seven sucked, but you're having a great year.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I still got snubbed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you look at the list of who got nominated?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of corp stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the corporate stuff gets nominated because people want to make a complete ballot and they don't know who else to nominate.
[SPEAKER_05]: but uh yep there you go uh Bobby you you definitely earned a place in our hearts oh thank you all right all right well Bobby I'm gonna let you go to get some more calls okay okay all right have a good one buddy you too bye that was fun reminiscing with Bobby we have another call coming right in though so let's get to the phones hi you're on Orange Launch Radio who's this
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh, I thought I heard wind in the background there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is the storm rolling in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you getting blown by Sandy right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to rain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right now, I'm going to tell you the same thing I told Travis and Jessica.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last August, when Irene, Rita, I was going to stand up in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's windy as hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little bit of rain.
[SPEAKER_08]: The shoreline of Jersey has been more or less flooded out, but this Jersey, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the important things in life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm sure you didn't call in to talk about the hurricane though.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you really want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there was something else that we had did as part of my podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: On Friday, we went to an event in Lower Manhattan called Girl Gamers Meetup New York City.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you're not a girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but some of my staffers are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's meeting up with a lot of the girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just went to go get some phone numbers.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we'll save that for another time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But pretty much the point of the meetup was to get more girls involved into playing video games to prove that it's not just boys and men that are playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Girls and women play video games, and they can kick as much ass as their counterparts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, DarkSakura?
Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: She said right, but you can't hear her anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, everything's just exploding because the Giants apparently won.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, is that their fourth game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so glad I didn't go to San Francisco this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am so glad because, oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, given that I am a born and bred New Yorker, trust me, we feel the pain of not being there, and whereas there are the Mets fans that are like, well, this is really going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what we did was we got a chance to interview Jen Vargas, the founder and creator of Girl Game Revolt.
[SPEAKER_08]: The point of our creating this is to prove that girls are just as good as gamers as guys, and to break the stereotype and prove that there is a difference between
[SPEAKER_08]: Girl Gamers, and Gamer Girls.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the type of girls who sit there and they kind of look sexy with a controller and, you know, they don't like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you still there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you hear me good, sir?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that last part you said?
[SPEAKER_08]: I said the last part was about how to try to break the stereotypes and prove there is a difference between girl gamers and gamer girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Olivia Munn is not necessarily a representation of gamer girls everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get what you mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they had some gamer girls there in costume talking about their YouTube channels and how they give tutorials on how to play various games, how to get through certain action games, and they had a theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were playing, we had Gears of War 3 with zombie mods, Left 4 Dead 2, Gauntlet, and Friday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Friday the 13th, like the 8-bit NES game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So where can we hear these interviews?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we are holding on to them because NRA Jam Session is so ever grateful to Orange Knowledge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: This interview that we did is exclusive to OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play that next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So not only will we have Eddie from A Money Style with us, but we're going to play that interview as well on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thank you so much for doing that for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: When this popped up, the first person I thought of was my darling group, John.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, barf.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I brought you vanilla tootsie rolls.
[SPEAKER_02]: You did.
[SPEAKER_05]: You did.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're delicious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Talk about barf.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since you are the man behind the anime show, and I know you have a whole staff behind you, but since you are the guy on the show here representing Anime Jam Session, I've got to ask you, I don't know, did you hear that email about the anime that's Nintendo and Sega and all that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear that email?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I did not.
[SPEAKER_08]: We may have to investigate and talk about that on our show coming up on this Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll send you more information.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's available on Crunchyroll, apparently, for free, and it's inspired by old Sega characters, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember the name of it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Aoi no... Aoi Sekai no Chushinde.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good memory.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm actually looking at the page right now on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantastic memory.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because...
[SPEAKER_02]: I linked myself so I would find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just linked it on my Facebook, Ranjan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will definitely check that when I go back inside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, Ranma, be safe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't float away.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have enough battery backup.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have enough alcohol.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are good to go for the next 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fill the bathtub with water.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have a stopper for the water.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are so blown up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get every glass in the cupboard and fill it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Condoms.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm ending this conversation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: You safe driver is good, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank you to everybody that called in tonight, both our callers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since both those calls were a little long, we're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we still got to do some more last-minute stories on our Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're not even close to being done yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to go for four hours tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki, do you have other last-minute stories before I get to the tweets?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the John Sisters Twisted Dreams is now available.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get that on Steam as part of the Greenlight thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have a token for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just have to download it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Zynga's bringing FarmVille, or I should say, you know, their online stuff, into online gambling.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they're planning on doing a slot-based simu- or slot simulator based on FarmVille, and, um, may expand into other online casino or bidding type things, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they have like Farmville Casino, like actual slot machines, like real slot machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say they do have those, so I'm not surprised there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, they lost $52.7 million in quarter three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably why they had to fire a lot of people or lay off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think people are just kind of over those type of games now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, then again, I get all these invites for FarmVille too, so maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me do some quick Twitter topics here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked this tweet here, and I have to admit I'm not informed on the topic very much, but I'll try here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nijela tweeted us, don't know if the Florence Gate saga has made it on your radar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raises interesting questions about games journalism.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now apparently what happened, and he links us to something that's on Reddit, and here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to what I see on Reddit here,
[SPEAKER_05]: Robert Florence just stepped down from Eurogamer because of his column yesterday, Blasting Games Journalists and Their Relationship to PR.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he links to a tweet from the author that says, Yesterday was my last piece for Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is in amended form.
[SPEAKER_05]: I stand by every word of the original piece.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I remember reading this original piece.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody linked it to me because it was all around Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, why are all these people joking about Doritos and Mountain Dew?
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody fill me in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember reading this original piece.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I'm not sure I understand why this was so flippin' terrible, although I noticed there is an editor's note.
[SPEAKER_05]: Following receipt of a complaint from Lauren Wainwright, Eurogamer has removed part of this article, but without admission of any liability.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eurogamer apologizes for any distress caused to Ms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wainwright by the references to her.
[SPEAKER_05]: This article otherwise remains as originally published.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, because I don't have a photographic memory, I don't know what that means was cut from the article.
[SPEAKER_05]: My assumption, bolded, italicized, underlined, was that it probably had to do with a particular PR rep or PR firm that was kind of doing some things that might be considered questionable.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing's about basically...
[SPEAKER_05]: How tight of a hold does PR have on games journalism?
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you spell her last name?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hit the button on my iPad that takes me back to start.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there it is right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's the name for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I zoom in on that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because it's an iPad specific site.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking for the... BlackWolf says he quoted the public Twitter of Lauren Weinreich.
[SPEAKER_05]: Her outlet threatened libel, which is nasty in UK libel laws.
[SPEAKER_05]: They quoted her public Twitter about how she was okay with promoting hashtags to win a PlayStation 3 and then talked about how she was promoting Tomb Raider and then uncovered that she actually works as a freelancer for Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I need to call back in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe...
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a better memory than I, sir, because I remember looking at the original article and I was like, yeah, I could have told you that for a long time now, basically, that PR has its grip firmly on hold of a lot of games journalism.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I've always said indies are the best, because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though not everybody, you know, is, you know, some of these indie gamers are probably the first ones to do the, or indie folks are probably the first ones to do these hashtags to try and win a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of times that's where the most honesty is going to come from as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, thank you, Bobby, for setting us straight.
[SPEAKER_05]: That kind of sucks that it cost this guy his job, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a quote from Forbes, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go join Polygon.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sound like a group.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're like a Voltron of game people.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where you need to be, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently... Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has, okay, since then, Lauren Wainwright has had personal verbal attacks, sent to her Twitter, which she has now locked, her Steam account, and other networking sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now that's crossing the line ridiculousness.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is coming from other people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this was actually on Reddit, is where I'm finding this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to read a little bit of it, if you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robert Florence wrote an article calling out unprofessional behavior in gaming journalism.
[SPEAKER_02]: He then steps down from his job at Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so he quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wasn't fired.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because of this article, as he was told, he would be sued for libel against Lauren Wainwright since, in the uncensored version, he outed her for questionable behavior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since then, she's had personal attacks at her Twitter, her Steam account, other networking sites.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Forbes article states, it only takes a few bad apples to turn a conversation about free speech and journalism into one about misogyny.
[SPEAKER_02]: So apparently people have been taking this really seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was calling out integrity and people were turning it around as an attack, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf says, Ben Kuchera did a great article about this whole thing on Penny Arcade Report.
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's pretty good about taking these situations and putting them into perspective.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to admit, again, the core issue, we've all known about that for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this whole fallout, and especially now that part where people were threatening her on Twitter and shit, that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's stupid and that's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just trying to see if anybody's published the unedited.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyway, let me get some more of these tweets here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sertour tweeted us and said, I love Bobby Blackwolf and OLR so much and VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we love you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura sends kisses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Snotty ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt tweeted us and said, Hey folks, I just want to let you know you guys are keeping me company right now on my three-hour drive to Boston.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Three-hour drive?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a long drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger Claw tweets us, the Mass Effect movie moves forward with a new screenwriter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know y'all love your Mass Effect, especially if your name is Shane or DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let me read this link here that we got tweeted to from SlashFilm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, screenwriter Morgan Davis-Fole has been hired to make a new pass at the script for Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the first big movement on the project since 2010 when Legendary Pictures purchased the right to the franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: This writer, though, he has yet to have a script produced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I guess he wrote Alien Sleeper Cell and worked on Rescue Me as well as some Happy Madison films.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not sounding good so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he's a massive Mass Effect fan and producers liked his take after obviously deciding not to move forward with the original script by Mark Protosevich.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well as long as it's more Rescue Me and less Happy Madison, I'll be alright, because he actually is a fan of the games, but on behalf of the entire fan community, do not fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not, not fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw gives us one more tweet here about
[SPEAKER_05]: EA taking a part in American Cancer Society's Making Strides Against Breast Cancer Walk.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's nice to hear about the good things EA did.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's talk about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: He links us to a story from Game Politics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Team EA took part in the American Cancer Society's
[SPEAKER_05]: making strides against Breast Cancer Walk in San Francisco to raise funds for the fight against breast cancer.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA Chief Operating Officer Peter Moore was on hand to kick off the event and walked with the employees.
[SPEAKER_05]: So very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good on you, EA, for doing your public service for an important cause.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys very much for your tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yes, TigerClaw, I know there's one more tweet, but it's a two tweet maximum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, any other last minute stories you want to share tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, PopCap and EA are teaming up with the ADA to give you free Plants vs. Zombies for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got an email on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's stopzombiemouth.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you're trying to be cheap about giving out candy and stuff like that, you could be one of those people that gives out something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they have coupons that you can print off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, they have a code on there that can be used between October 30th and November 10th to redeem a free copy of the PC version of Plants vs. Zombies for PC or Mac.
[SPEAKER_03]: and um it's all the same code so you can print off sheets of those cut them up and give those out instead of candy if you want to or with candy or with candy um and so you can do that if you don't feel like going to and basically just go back to the stopzombiemouth.com website and then use the code p-hater p-e-a-h-a-t-r
[SPEAKER_02]: Peahatter.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the plants is a peahat.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a pee-hater because they don't like getting hit in the face with pee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not, you know, urine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, also this I was kind of talking about before I actually got to read the whole thing now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently there's going to be some updates to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember before how it was okay to jailbreak your iPods and iPhones and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not going to be the case anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, it's only legal to jailbreak phones or say unlocked prior to January 2013.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, after that, it is no longer legal to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, it's no longer legal to jailbreak tablet devices or root tablet devices.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of a big step backwards to the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's more websites running that whole Disney toy box thing, but we already know what that is, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta say, Disney Infinity has a great logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does have a nice logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very interesting that they have two different components of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of which would be, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pages not turning correctly.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of which was dubbed the Toy Box.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one, of course, is the actual characters, the play sets.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're the play sets in the Toy Box.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, tying in with Monsters U, Cars, The Lone Ranger, The Incredibles, Toy Story, and Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_03]: And like we talked about last week... It's two Johnny Depp movies, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is, because he's in a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got a picture here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The reader looks really different.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like, you know, say...
[SPEAKER_03]: Skylanders, but they've got these characters and these coins and then looks like boss characters, almost like they have that mech thing from The Incredibles, so you can team up with Buzz Lightyear and Mr. Incredible and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope the game's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it probably will be, I mean, considering how well Skylanders does, and Skylanders, to be honest, is a very new property versus...
[SPEAKER_03]: and Disney characters, which everybody fucking knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, before we wrap up the show tonight, I bet you thought I forgot, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to reveal the winners of tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just took me forever to tabulate the votes because there was a lot of participation tonight and I've been talking a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's reveal tonight's winners of the list list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is, the definitive list, the top three things scientifically proven that you guys want on G4 to get you to watch it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number three is a tie.
[SPEAKER_05]: The screensavers.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the Angry Video Game Nerd TV show.
[SPEAKER_05]: The number three answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: The number two thing that would most get you to watch G4 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starcade 2 Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly, the number one, the numero uno thing, the thing that G4 ought to book right now to get everybody to watch it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's Cosplay Challenge!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: At least I'll be getting paid!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's Cosplay Challenge is the thing you most want on G4 TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Signed, sealed, delivered, done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much for listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate all the support.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, all we ask, we don't ask for your money or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just tell a friend or seven about the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help us spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio and the whole Voice of Geeks Network and all the great shows that are on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and also starting November 1st voting for us each and every single day on the podcast awards podcastawards.com that's right and tell your friends that's right and tell your friends make your friends vote all unique IPs though don't break the rules do not get us disqualified because you're a dumbass and break the rules do not break the rules or I will break you hypothetically alright let's go around and get everybody's final thought for tonight Dark Sakura feel better for God's sake I want Pinkberry your final thought is I want Pinkberry
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought tonight is I hope we have enough time to go to the grocery store still.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one errand we still have to run this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alan's like, nope, not going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: My head hurts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, feel better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be hurty next week again.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Blackwolf says we should green light the earth.
[SPEAKER_05]: We may green light that for VOG.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's costume is not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to disappoint you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: The picture is closest you're going to get to the dream.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because really, what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never said you had to dress up as Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they seem to think that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does it for another week at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, an interview with Eddie from BomaniStyle.com and more.
[SPEAKER_05]: So be sure to tune in next week, November 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!