This week, GDC is come and gone and the future is bright for 2014. Microsoft has given a
date for more of the Xbox One's release and the VR space is growing. Valve added a VR
mode to Steam and Sony showed off its concept to GDC. All this and more on the show where
every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio live with this episode number
545 for March 23, 2014 from our brand new studio N7. That's number 7. My name is Rob
Roberts and joining me here in our new digs is the one and only DarkSakura or Jamie Sommers.
It's echoey. It is a little echoey. Hello from space. I'm hoping that doesn't get picked
up by the mics too much but we might have to dampen the noise in here a little more
because this is supposed to be like a dining room. I ain't dampening shit. I'm okay because
people will fuss at me now that I've been doing it like I did it all of twice and then
fussed out when I didn't do it the third time. So sup bitches. Sup. So do you like
the new digs? I do. I do. I really like this door behind me that no one can see me just
pointing to. I know because it is Orange Lounge Radio. I fucking love that door and I want
to steal it. I'm taking that door home. Now by the way Jamie I have to apologize in advance
tonight because I'm kind of stealing your M.O. I've been getting over a sinus infection
the past few days which I know is usually your thing to be sick. Girl. No. So if I sound
different that's not the new studio's fault. That is the fact that. That's Rob's disease.
Yeah I'm actually getting over like I was really bad like this is I've had this since
Tuesday and I still can't shake it. Well you know I've avoided my annual sinus infection,
my sort of springtime infection because I found that there's a corticosteroid that's
over the counter and I bought the fuck out of it. And now my face doesn't feel like death
like it normally does right about now. Hooray. So. You stick it up your nose and you squeeze
shit up there. That sounds gross. And then you snort it. That sounds gross. When I put
it that way yeah it does. Alright well joining us not on the Skype line tonight but here
in studio welcome back everybody tech master Loki live in the flesh. I'm I'm sitting here
I'm trying to find spots on the carpet and the floor that aren't. Wobbly for the. Wobbly
yes. Oh yeah good luck good luck with that. It's alright I think I figured it out. We
got to get used to the new digs and break them in a little bit. Well welcome back. Yeah
it's nice to actually be out of the kitchen. And in our kitchen. Well yeah it's it's it's
such it's so hard to like like I feel like seriously it's like mute mute mute mute mute
and just yeah yeah with all the kids and stuff in the background. So well I can make some
extra noise or something if it helps. I've been reading about the saga of Screamy. Yep
he also noticed what Captain Fuzzy Pants. I don't know about according to your lady.
He likes to scream. Well I don't say he likes his colicky so he screams himself to sleep
every night for a while which is why hopefully I'll be back next week because you know this
is the first night that the wife's put. Well she has her mom coming over to help but this
is the first time she's gonna be wrangling both kids at the same time you know. And so
tonight's a trial run with. She's not entirely happy with that but I was like it's like well
I'm gonna let you make this decision. I'm like I'm going sorry Nellie. But I'm like
it's been four months. Yeah I was just gonna say how did you like Dark Soccer's Christmas
present. You guys think I'm kidding but no he just opened it. Loki got to open his Christmas
present finally. I like it it's great. Share the chocolate with Nellie it sounds like she needs
it. Yeah there you go there you go butter her up with chocolate that always works. But you know
what I have to say I'm glad for people who can do the kid thing. Oh yeah. So glad I don't have any.
I have a cat. Yeah that's a you know parents my child is a cat. And Sanrio is finally getting
used to this whole new house you know she hid behind the toilet for a day and I posted. She
was trying to be one with the toilet. Well I posted that picture on Twitter where she was
trying to hide under the litter box. She doesn't like to be around other people at all. But now
she's kind of exploring a little more and actually she likes to jump up on the windowsill which was
something we never had in the apartment. Kitty cats need sunshine. Yeah absolutely absolutely.
Well believe it or not it is a show about video games gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle. We
do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby
Blackwell show at the Voice of Geeks Network. Live.vognetwork.com is the place where you can
join us live if you want to chat along with our show tonight. And let's see going to going to
our chat room VX Jason XV says I'm not hearing echo. Well that's a good thing. Jason would know.
And by the way I'm glad Jason said something because this reminds me to acknowledge Jason
because Jason has helped out Studio N7 from afar as well. You guys might remember now I'm not
gonna promise this is gonna fix everything but you guys might remember especially if you're a
live listener the show has a tendency to drop once in a while. Well Jason said I think I have
an idea how to fix that. So he got us a brand new cable modem so we no longer have to rely on a
rental from the cable company. So thank you Jason. Big round of applause for Jay. I mean as if he
doesn't do enough for the show. It helps. That was very kind. I know going from like a rental modem
to a you know my own modem it helps. Now that I said now that I said that we're gonna drop in
five seconds. Dan and I invested in our own about a year ago. It made all the difference. Yeah so
um well either way I appreciate the fact that I don't have to rent another one or the other one
anymore I can just take it back so that'll be great. Tech 2030 in chat says it sounds a little
different than the old studio. Well hopefully in a good way. We tried to rebalance the mics and
everything. There's just not enough fuzzy furniture in the room that's why it's not yet. I think that
my tablet just doesn't like the connection though because I keep popping in and out. Don't. Well
we'll try to we'll try to work. Basted. Um Loki had a great idea though for the studio. We should
get like try to go to a yard sale and get one of those really tacky orange couches and have it here
on the side wall for the guests. Actually that's something that you can do yourself you know. What?
If you can get a couch that's in decent shape all you have to do is buy the right kind of material
and you can just sort of over upholster it. Yeah but like an or just even like put an orange throw
on it or something. Well no I'd say over upholster it and you know make sure it's really good. But
yeah I know how to do all that stuff. I'm crafty. There you go. Awesome. All right um let's see.
Tech 2030 clarifies just different. I don't know how to explain it and saying it doesn't sound bad
at all. Well that's good. I'm glad. I'm glad to hear things are in good shape. So listen it's a
trade-off. You either get my crappy headset audio or you get a slight reverberation from the kind
of empty room. Which we'll work on. We're gonna add more stuff in here and then. Speaking of which
I got like I said I've got a a bar top arcade cabinet that I built that's just sitting collecting
dust and one of the spare desks you know and my work. Also have a signed poster from True Crime
New York signed by the entire voice cast that's framed. They just gave me the frame they're like
I don't want to take that thing out of the frame. It frames yours now. I'm like okay cool. You know
there's a night if we don't get that orange couch there's a nice spot here for either like an arcade
machine or maybe a pinball machine. Maybe I can finally get that baby pac-man machine I've always
wanted my entire life. You want to borrow World Cup? Don't get it. Don't tempt me. Come get it. No
we were sticking with our three. Yeah no I don't blame you. No but we know how to get you into this
but for the record this is not the time to get into pinball. Is it getting really expensive? It's
been getting really expensive for the past two years like my when we got a jackpot we made a
really good trade for it we traded our old what do we have before we traded something for it the
the I think it was Black Knight 2000 is one of the things we traded for it but now like the
Twilight Zone that we got the I think we got it for around three grand at the time easily is going
for upwards of five and six so it's really really just appreciated since then. Gosh it's almost
like the home market the pinball market you know. Try to do trades and work and learn to shop them
and then pick up something light start trading up. Yeah I'm not interested in building up the
massive collection well I mean well you guys don't have the massive collection. We had 13 at
one time which is pretty decent. That's pretty we know a guy who has like 30 there's almost all the
new Stearns. There's still a YouTube out there on our YouTube channel over at Orange Launch Radio
on YouTube which by the way you know not only does Jason do the enhanced episodes of the show
over there but if you go back in the archives a little bit we actually did a tour of Jamie's
house a few years ago when she had all of those 13 tables so that was that was a really impressive
site of course you don't live in the house anymore but no and we're probably gonna be moving before
the years out we're gonna be looking for a new house but I guess I'm new today I got some new
I got some new. Tell us about your new acquisition today. Well the the vibe my poor old vibe is gone.
I have a Fiat now and it's blue it is very fucking blue and it's little and cute and I may have
ordered an Alliance sticker for it because I didn't think the N7 sticker looked fine on it
so since it's all blue it's gonna be I don't know what's call it either we were gonna call
it the Ferrari at because Fiat owns Ferrari but they also in Dodge so then I guess not you can't
have it all so I don't know. I'm going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com. Tigerclaw by
the way linked that video. As long as I'm not in it you can show it. You're in it. You're
definitely in it but I'm looking at chat and the pagan Jew is in chat say who is my new
friend I was gonna say I have not seen that name in chat before but I love I love that I love that
name the pagan Jew says man I what I've always wanted are those table style miss pac-man it's
like the cocktail table machines right yeah what how wouldn't you love that for a little table
right here instead of well there is a tutorial out on building one of your own but building a
coffee table size so that you have the middle part is the gaming area and the other you know
places to set your drinks and stuff down on I just need to get a pac-man battle royale those
are only what $5,000 you can swing it steam what steam oh just get downloaded on steam and run it
on a computer or something yeah yeah yeah I got you I got you or or I'm sure you know I they can't
be that sophisticated I'm sure that they'll dump it eventually for the record because the pagan
Jew brought it up I actually did start thinking about calling my my little Fiat the Kodiak because
it's the same color as the yeah too much Mass Effect it's a really pretty color though it
really is it's little though like I think I would have to if like you and Alan were to both come
with me in that car someone would have to sit sideways and backseat yeah Alan and I would not
both fit in your car yeah it's little Dan fit in it but our buddy that we actually actually have a
friend that works at car max that's where we got my car from he was like I'm gonna sit behind Jamie
cuz Dan pushed the seat all the way and no so yeah all right well okay so we've talked about a
lot of non gaming things we've talked about Loki's coming back to the show we've talked about our new
studio we've talked about dark sacros car let's get back to what the show is all about it's video
games and we're gonna start off talking about our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we
have been playing this week so that you got a frame of reference where our heads are at this
week with video games dark Sakura well I am playing through Mass Effect 3 again because and I'm gonna
go ahead and put this out there for everybody if anyone besides me is doing mods and finds after
you update your in video drivers that text mod and you mod are not working it actually is a
conflict with the Nvidia drivers and I have put up old Nvidia drivers on Mass Effect thing I did it
like two days ago so you can download run the old drivers and your mods will work again and text mod
and you mod but I was I'm playing more Mass Effect 3 I'm trying to finish out run number 17 so that I
can finish run number 18 I might actually just completely start over and make a completely
different character I haven't decided yet I might actually finish the game with not with my weirdo
albino Shepherd I don't know anyway so um I am also I started doing hunting logs on Final Fantasy
17 17 fuck the fuck Wow 14 travel to the few yes I time child avatars no fort what the fuck is seven
is all well I mean if you think about it 11 was an MMO 11 teen there was 12 13 and 14 is an MMO so
15 16 17 will be the next MMO so maybe I do you know something Darcy are you did you just breach
an NDA no I didn't anyway I meant 14 so whatevs um so anyway um I I I figured out I'm basically
just running around doing as much of the hunting log as I can and I'm on the appropriate level for
myself now like I am halfway through the hunting log the level for hunting log so that's really I'm
happy I'm still playing Animal Crossing and I now have blue roses so if anyone wants blue roses I
could be persuaded to turn on my game tonight and give one lucky person in chat who messages me
first to blue roses if such a person desires and what's the big flippin deal about is they
take fucking forever it took me an entire year to get hybrid Reds and then and I had to do perfect
town to do it so now did you have to grind the bones of Ed in or yes I had to sacrifice Ed to
the gods of my village no what you have to do is you have to you know you start off with your white
red or yellow roses you have to breed orange roses then you have to breed purple roses then
you have to breed purple and orange roses together to get a hybrid red and you have to have two hybrid
Reds to eventually maybe breed a blue I have so many fucking flowers in my village but now I have
like a big clutch of blue roses and so I in fact I will tell you what I will be kind enough to give
two people in chat blue roses because I have enough to do that all right well there you go
like reverse bachelor style or is that no they don't give them or they give them a rose of their
stains yeah I don't watch the bachelors yeah they give him a rose of their study so it is bachelors
there was a girl from Sacramento apparently on that show I heard and she got she got she got
totally screwed over by the guy in the end that's what I heard but I hear all this stuff you know on
the radios because I don't watch you know I like survivor and big bro I love Big Brother but that's
about the most reality TV I was oh and RuPaul's Drag Race that's that's important too but RuPaul's
RuPaul's Drag Race just transcends all other television they should get interesting like
reality twists you know they think they're going on a show for bachelor but it's survivor haha well
I always said that the best season of Survivor would be when they cast a bunch of drag queens
I mean let's be real that's that is must-see TV right there come on now to tie it back to video
games though have you ever have you ever played some of those video games based on TV there's
like a bachelor video game on mobile oh yes there is on the Wii and there's yet that's right there
was that and there's like a survivor video game also on the Wii and there well there was like an
old-school one on PC they're all terrible they are so like how are they too bad how are these
games so bad like in the licensing like well like at least like Wheel of Fortune Jeopardy the game
should press your luck like at least you know what you're gonna get you are gonna get those games and
even though they might not be the most fluid presentation sometimes they work well enough
for what they are but oh my god like Survivor is just bad it's so bad but anyway sorry I don't know
how we got on a tangent somehow we were on Dark Soccer's gaming weeks just talking about blue
roses did you did you get people to join your village yet I have two people and I am going to
go plant two roses near my train station I mean sorry four roses near my train station and two
are gonna be for acts deft and two will be for Queen Simeon there you go and then if you want
to try and steal it from one of them get to her village quickly and start whapping people with
bug nets and only the survivor will win all right Loki while she does that how was your gaming week
didn't play that much this week I think I played a little bit South Park I played Call of Duty
modern warfare 2 because I actually picked that up because we're kind of we were getting bored
with just modern warfare 1 because we've played it before we actually started off in modern warfare
1 then we moved to modern warfare 3 when we were playing on Xbox and then you know they wanted to
kind of go back to modern warfare 1 because it was what we considered the best game that we played in
the series so far well then I picked up modern warfare 2 and I think that's the best game in the
series so far and then I started the grind you know because in modern warfare 1 I had the grind
quite a bit just to get leveled up but apparently there's a lot of hackers on modern warfare 2 so it
didn't take me it only took me five games before I got into a modded game and I'm already ranked 70
now so hackers yeah my Xbox live game no it this is PlayStation Network and then you think no this
is PlayStation Network I'm playing on PlayStation 3 right now so yes and sorry hackers on my internet
thing but here's the thing though and like I don't really understand you know the point of it but
it was kind of like generous but like I don't this is retarded at the same time because when he came
in the first thing that happened was he ranked everybody up to seven unlocked everything so I'm
like hey cool I got all my stuff unlocked and then he proceeded to kill everybody with an aimbot I'm
like okay well this is I guess I guess I'll let you kill me the name but because you did rank me
up to 70 but you know I just don't I don't know why I'm still in this game and eventually it
actually the server detected that he was cheating and then kicked him off but the hell kinda like
what is that I'm good I'm gonna bring you up up up up and then take you down I don't get it but
I'm like hey cool now I made you and now I'm gonna break you snap it kind of sucks because I was
enjoying you know kind of leveling up and grinding a little bit because I was you know enjoying you
figuring out the classes and stuff and then they got ranked up to 70 I'm like well I don't need to
play this anymore so I'll just wait until we play her actual private matches but technically I didn't
cheat somebody else I benefited well this happened to my co-worker on modern warfare one he got
ranked up to level 50 and so I you know he got everything unlocked because at one time I was
like hey why is your clan tag marked as something and he's like I don't know I don't know how to
change that so I played that I played more South Park the stick of truth and that game is hilarious
and what else they play a little bit 2048 just because you know it's addicting and how what else
I think that's actually it oh I played a little bit modern warfare one because we this Wednesday
we actually played a private game but that's probably gonna be the end of that so yeah lots
of modern warfare old modern warfare games and I don't know I don't have a lot of gaming time
anymore so it's it's kind of limited to that with two kids you don't have gaming time what are you
talking about oh yeah all right my gaming week I was also pressed for time a little bit this week
with you know the whole moving thing and in trying to get everything wrapped up with the other
apartment which finally took those keys over on Saturday and it felt so good to be rid of that
but anyway I did fit in a little gaming time and one game that's been taking up quite a bit of my
time besides besides Final Fantasy 14 that's always a given because I'm on a rating team in
Final Fantasy 14 so I'm always playing that you know at least one or two two nights a week but
I've been playing Diablo 3 again you know I know I've been talking about this on the show the past
couple weeks but with the expansion coming out this this Tuesday is the big day for the expansion
they were doing an experience boost they were doing 50% experience boost for a couple weeks
well they up the ante for this weekend only and it's a hundred percent experience boost so it's
like get my paragon levels get my paragon levels as fast I can because in Diablo if you didn't know
you level your character from 1 to 60 and then in the expansion that's going to be 70 but once you
hit max level you start grinding these things called paragon levels and the paragon levels go
from 1 to 500 which I know seems like wow you can level your character to 500 it doesn't really work
that way because the paragon levels all they do is they give you one stat boost and they rotate
through four categories it's like offensive defensive utility and a potpourri I don't know
there's some other thing but you you choose basically what you want to put your stats in
in those but the cool thing about the paragon levels is that they are for all of your characters
so let's say I am paragon level 26 which is where my character is at right now if I start a brand
new character she'll be level 1 but character level or paragon level 26 so I can still put
those 26 points and stat boosts into my level 1 character so that's pretty cool that's why a lot
of people get 26 per character or is it just you know it's 26 per character but it's not I mean
it's not the gigantic boost you it sounds like it is like 26 levels because like let me like okay
it cycles through the four and one of them is offensive and so I keep putting my points in
critical hit chance so each point is a tenth of a percent increase in critical hit chance so it's
not okay so it's like the Borderlands 2 system that they have for experience awesome points or
something I bet it is yeah I bet it's a very similar thing they probably won one probably
borrowed from the other and probably yeah I would be surprised at all so that's that's a big thing
everybody grinding because knowing that the expansion hits Tuesday now instead of paragon
leveling everybody's gonna be taking their characters to level 70 but they'll be able
to carry those paragon levels with them as they level through act 5 so it's you know people are
very busy with that so been we have a clan for Horde house my other show so you know just finding
other people to play with them their eyes they haven't given you a way to just pay to level up
to 70 yeah right or giving you a free boost with the pre-order for the expansion none of that yet
not yet not yet we can level up really fast now but anyway yeah also in Diablo news this week
the auction house shut down so that is done so if you were staying away from Diablo 3 because
you were waiting for the auction house to go away well here's a chance there's no more auction house
the icon is still there because people can claim their items and cash out everything through like
June but you can't list things anymore it's it's done so there you go so there's that the only
thing that makes me a little sour face at Diablo 3 is I was reading the FAQ for the expansion and
everything for the expansion on launch day and they're telling people what to expect and
everything right and so if you remember when Diablo 3 originally launched everybody was
hitting that error 37 right it was a big big thing and you know the game got a lot of shit
because you know back when Diablo 2 did not have mandatory online I didn't have to deal with this
fuckery well they're saying on the FAQ launch page you might hit a queue when logging into
Diablo 3 and you know if you hit the queue just wait and you'll be able to attack the monster and
I'm kind of thinking like that doesn't help the case that people do not like that this game has
mandatory online which by the way is not a problem in the PlayStation and Xbox versions still don't
know when the PlayStation 4 version is coming out but I imagine the holiday at this point they're
gonna bundle it with the expand they're waiting for all the PC people to buy the expansion I
thought they already they're gonna announce 30 or they said that the PlayStation 4 version was
gonna be that you know with the reaper of souls and stuff in there is I how can it not at this
point they may have but and I missed it but how can it not at this point but they wouldn't want
to announce that because that's gonna cut into PC sales of the people who want to play it now
so they're gonna wait until a month after and then they'll announce that the ps4 one officially
has both well watch I've been following Blizzard way too long it's exactly how it's gonna go down
so anyway God where was I with that whole mess yeah oh yes there's gonna be a queue to possibly
get into Diablo thumbs yeah a little a little ridiculous a little ridiculous so I am making
a little bit of stank face at the game for that but I'm also not the type of Diablo player where
I have to be in there day one like I'm not like that big on it so if I can't play right away then
what else I'm not not worried about it one other game I've been playing this week and I think a lot
of you all you all out there have been playing this as well I have been playing the Final Fantasy
10 HD remaster which does include 10 2 but I've only been playing 10 because you know I want to
play that first huh what what can I do for you no I'm not playing 10 2 yet I'm playing playing just
10 right now but um I it is what you would expect it is Final Fantasy 10 but it's in widescreen and
with with up bridge graphics you know Alan walked in when I was playing and he's like I can't really
tell the difference I could though like and I don't know if that's just the quality of TV has
gone up in the 10 years or no longer than that probably 15 years since Final Fantasy 10 was first
out but just like I'm like the colors are more vibrant things just look crisper and better this
soundtrack has been redone a little bit and I don't find the redo the redos of the songs are
faithful to the originals they didn't like like completely screw up the chocobo music or anything
like that like everything still stays faithful to the original the only thing I don't remember the
loading times being such a bear in the Final Fantasy 10 version on PlayStation 2 or loading
times yeah oh yeah like you know and it's just the put in the disc launch the game oh okay now
I'm on the main menu where I choose which game do I want to play all right pick FF 10 loading
all right gonna click load game loading gonna load my game loading this is kind of like all right
there's a lot of loading screens here and I was kind of surprised didn't do any type of like
install or anything to try and maybe minimize that a little bit but that's like my one little
bitch and you know what to be honest maybe it was that way and I just forgot after all these years
but I felt like on PlayStation 2 it seemed like I kind of got in there a little faster and got to
play my game or as you know you gotta say say your time aside go get your drink and your sandwich
before you play your game but that's my one one minor little bitch with Final Fantasy 10 otherwise
it's it's a great deal especially if you know I realized we have a lot of listeners that are
probably like 18 to 21 you know kind of in that range so you were probably too young when Final
Fantasy 10 first came out and maybe you've gone back and experienced it which you know thumbs up
good for you but if you somehow miss these games but you do kind of like Japanese RPGs and you like
those types of games or you're interested in them I think this is a great way to pick them up you
know it's only what it's like 40 bucks for the two games it's that's a great deal and it's not only
the two games they are the international versions for the first time in America so that's pretty
cool because you can do the alternate sphere grid I had I have the international version for
10-2 so okay there you go but you had to import that right yeah yeah I did but it played just
fine it also comes with the audio drama that plays over some credits there was like a Final
Fantasy 10 audio drama or something that came after 10-2 and then there's a another Final
Fantasy 10 like extended movie or something or is there am I thinking last mission oh no there's
like every bonus that goes with Final Fantasy 10 is all there I mean it's all with it I'm trying
to be that guy who goes through and plays one at a time but if it goes anything like Kingdom Hearts
did I'll get like a quarter of the way through the game and then be like oh my South Park game
is here time to go play that because I'm waiting on that now so it's fantastic yeah I'm going to
the chat room over at live.vognetwork.com act deft and chat says Final Fantasy 10 sucks anyway well
you know what that's what I have to say Syal in chat says I'll play Diablo 3 when offline mode
becomes a thing the PlayStation 3 version or Xbox 360 version are for you offline mode is a thing
in those games if you're curious so there you go s2100 Matt says kind of reminds me of the horrible
loading times for the Final Fantasy Chronicles disc Final Fantasy 4 and chrono trigger for ps1
well here's the good news it doesn't load for like battles and things like that I mean that
feels fluid like that was the annoying pain in the ass thing about those was like every time you
got into a random battle there was like a little loading time that was a bit much on those like old
PlayStation games but you don't you don't have that here it's not that bad so all right so that's
gonna do it for our gaming weeks so quickly our housekeeping I don't have a whole lot to say here
since you know we had our week off last week but I hope you got y'all enjoyed the tape show that we
ran over Loki's budgeted time sorry about that but we made it work sorry it was the baby crying
I understand but I'm glad we were able to do something for the listeners I saw there were a
lot of people that use the passphrase that's hidden in the show to check in so I know a lot
of you guys were checking it out one way or another so I'm glad we could do a little something for you
guys but now we're back to our form and and hopefully coming at you for the next next many
few weeks here solid twitter.com slash olr facebook.com slash orange launch radio or google.com
slash plus orange lounge radio all the different ways you can follow us on social media I should
throw this little a little teaser out there too we are thinking about what we're gonna do for a
new look at orange lounge radio.com because you know we've had that old website that we've kind
of neglected a little bit ever since vog network launched because a lot of the focus has been over
there and with good reason but we are gonna kind of take a look at what can we do to orange
lounge radio.com to kind of make it a real central hub for show related things and more
info about the show and you know the fact that this show does have a 12 year history behind it
and counting so you know kind of some of the historical things for our show and what we can
put on there so we're old don't remind me you know what these posters these posters keep me young you
see that that is some of these posters are older than some of our listeners that's a DDR second
mix marquee which which of these posters would be older than one of our listeners maybe the second
mix marquee second mix marquee that would be for one of the Silent Hill 3 poster baby I don't know
I would hope I would hope we don't have 12 11 come out it was 2005 so you were doing second mix yeah
anyway cloud here on a wall scroll um to give the visual to you guys there will I will probably do
a YouTube of it I'll do like a little YouTube to put for the channel and and have Jason make it
nice if he's willing to do that and put it up on our channels that way you guys can go check out
our YouTube channel we'll give you a little visual look of our studio once once we get a little more
in here I think it'll be really ready to show off so yeah there you go um okay so let's get into our
gaming news tonight Loki once you start us off so it was rumored that they were gonna do this and
of course they did it so Sony kind of announced their codenamed project Morpheus what that is is
basically their VR headset and spec wise it sounds kind of similar to the oculus rift it's you know
1080p 90 plus degrees field of view also kind of utilizes the PlayStation camera I guess it
sort of has like the same move motion sensors built into it and of course a bunch of support
from all sorts of middleware and development companies that unity havoc you know epic games
Autodesk crytek you know all the big guys and of course no information on price no information on
release date or anything like that they did show off some tech demos utilizing games that are
already out there like thief looks interesting I mean I'm kind of excited about VR actually
coming mainstream to consoles my only concern of course with anything that you know you have
like a new technology is the first few games that come out for it are gonna be very gimmicky
it's just like I don't know like even with the 3d stuff on the 3ds or with the motion controls
on the Wii and even the second screen on the DS it was just gimmick gimmick gimmick gimmick this
isn't really needed oh hey or hate the Kinect any games that have come out for the Kinect they
haven't been dancing game and pretty much gimmick gimmick gimmick gimmick so that's the only thing
I'm concerned about and probably price point because you know that's really expensive then
I don't really want to buy it well the cost of the technology may come down a little bit though
by the time this thing actually comes out I mean I really don't think you guys should expect to see
it this year I think we're talking out there I think they even said not this year yeah holiday
2015 maybe I mean and you guys have to remember it is game developers conference this announcement
was not an e3 type of announcement and that's where some people you know and Bobby gets into
this a lot more on his show where he you know and he kind of has that perspective because he does
develop games like flappy vlog and all that right so he does kind of have that perspective and and
that game developers conference is not e3 and we kind of have to remember that sometimes we get
thrown little tidbits you get thrown little things and you know to try and get excitement
and sure ever everybody wants the media to report on them so sometimes you're gonna get a little
bone thrown at you but you have to remember the news isn't really for you and something like this
especially for Sony to kind of say all right we are gonna do this for the PlayStation 4 can get
developers thinking all right what kind of game do I want to make because you can't really make
a PlayStation 4 game overnight you know people are working on now the stuff that's gonna come out
holiday 2015 holiday 2016 for heaven's sake you know things that are way way out that's how long
a video game takes to make so I mean by kind of announcing this publicly to the developers now
it's kind of like all right no more of this leaked stuff we all know this is something we're working
on here's the specs and you know good luck have fun with it I would love to see like something
like this being patched into like currently you know like games that are already out there even
like re-releasing them with this kind of like how they do with kind of the move stuff obviously you
know adding motion controls versus adding you know a whole second camera to make it stereoscopic
and all that stuff and head tracking and all that it's a lot more complicated but it'd be kind of
cool you know to be able to play like say Killzone or something like that in VR or even Minecraft in
VR I mean cuz obviously the oculus rift version was pretty cool so I would like to try that and
also you know if the price point is nice I'm going to our chat room real quick real quick
Ragingator in chat at live.vognetwork.com says will project Morpheus offer users the choice of
a red pill or a blue pill hahaha well let us not let us not forget project Morpheus won't be the
final name I mean there's all there's development names all the time yeah we're still playing the
revolution in ultra 64 y'all right yeah besides the project Morpheus that's something more I'd
see associated with the one fuck off all right but speaking of the choice I hate you so much go
back home all right I'm kidding all right it is good to have you back speaking of the choice
between the red pill and the blue pill now users are gonna be faced with a choice between project
Morpheus and oculus rift or are they and then also there's you know Microsoft what they're coming out
with remember that there's this whole roadmap thing that leaked out I want to say is it been
a year or two years now you know talking about the whole you know Kinect and Xbox one and you know
this whole project for tell fortaleza which I guess they're singing translates to fortress in
Portuguese if I don't know what the hell that's supposed to mean but they're saying it's supposed
to be like some sort of like augmented reality of VR type thing and it's something that they're
apparently working on this is now also being confirmed by like I guess a second source now
it's whatever happened to the the luma room thing that Microsoft was doing I thought that was their
thing um no that was something else but it apparently is just too costly right now with
you know what's out there I mean how you're asking someone to basically set up a projector
that's gonna project stuff on the walls I mean that sounds cool but it's just it's too expensive
and just imagine trying to sell that you need a very specific room for that it's just not something
that anybody could do I mean it'd be neat if they can actually do that and pull it off well now wait
a minute you dodged my question let's go back are you gonna are you do you feel like you're gonna
have to make a choice between oculus rift and project Morpheus or do you think there's room in
a gamer's house for both depends on the price and just you know once again like I haven't really been
jumping into just buying you know a PlayStation 4 and Xbox one or even a new gaming PC I'm just
gotta see what's gonna be for it I'm not gonna just jump in and buy you know a new console and
like you know $200 plus device and you know what were they gonna support with it I mean what kind
of games are gonna see cuz remember you know we did this with like the Kinect and stuff like oh
you need to get the Kinect to play all these games and then it's very limited way you can play it's
like okay I can play dancing games or I can play games that implement Kinect for really stupid
reasons you know you know I don't know it I gotta wait and see what they have for it I mean I think
I'd hope with VR that there's gonna be some cooler stuff with it but it's all gonna be also how
sensitive everything is you know is it gonna be able to pick up movements out you know obviously
with this these newer cameras and stuff they're a lot better than the original connector even the
PlayStation I was so I'm hoping that it will be a better experience but I have to see that I have
to see the reviews games all that stuff for me even though I I get the competitions healthy and
I think that'll be kind of a good thing in this case you know and I get that they are and they
aren't competing I mean the PC market and the console market are very different right and the
things that are gonna be good for oculus rift on PC versus Morpheus on ps4 is just like back to
those same adages about PlayStation 4 I see about console gaming in general versus PC gaming is that
you know with console gaming you have your sets of standards and you never have to worry about
that but at the same time you are stuck within those standards whereas PCs can kind of always
continuously upgrade right so that's you know there's gonna be pros and cons between the two
you know whatever and I'm sure you're gonna see some game overlap between the two for me the the
honest-to-god thing I'm having a hard time conceptualizing is how why would I want two
VR headsets in my house and maybe this is just like a I'm not like like I'm sure there was a
time in a day where people were going like you mean I need to have a Nintendo and a Sega in my
house I don't need both right or even way back in the day I need to have two television sets in my
house what am I gonna do with two television sets I only need one so maybe that's just I you know
again once like all the games are there it might but I just right now I'm like I don't want to buy
two VR sets the thing is like you know I kind of view a VR set is almost like having a TV it's like
well this is stupid that I should have a second TV to play a second game system on one this TV
could easily play both game systems they should just be able to switch back and forth and here's
the thing like they're even talking with the other project Morpheus headset they have a game
with the Eve Valkyrie I think is what it was that is a game that's being co-published by oculus so
that's kind of interesting right there that there's a little bit I don't know if it's being done by a
different company for you know for the PlayStation 4 but the fact that that's also coming to this
head says well it's like it would be nice if it was just all oculus or all one company together
making this device that could be used across everything but of course everybody wants their
own things so they can patent it and sue each other and all that fun stuff I'm going to our
chat room over at live dot vog network calm Akuma JP says in Japan no room to spare oh that's a good
point and you know I'm not I'm not were there Japanese developers in that list of people for
project Morpheus because now that I think about it you know again I don't follow oculus rift as
closely as say Bobby or some of the other fans will but our Japanese developers it wasn't it
wasn't necessarily developers it's more of like engines and middleware and that type of stuff so
like you know unity unity or even like you know unreal and stuff that's used by different
developers you know it could be you know from all all corners of the world so I don't think that's
I'm sure that especially you know being that I think that would take off from Japan if the
prices right because you know that is a big selling point not a lot of space VR could be
pretty cool well I'm curious if there's going to be like maybe a cultural difference you know
sometimes there are differences in the games that work in Japan versus that work here and vice versa
I'm curious if VR is something that's going to be on both sides you know because Sony obviously has
a big presence in Japan and America so I just I'm just kind of curious I mean I just I honestly
don't know how well VR is received in Japan maybe maybe Akuma or some of our other folks know well
Bobby Black Wolf's there saying in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com there are a lot of Asian
developers working on the rift that's where most of the porn is from actually I'm and that's what
I was gonna say I'm totally looking forward to all the you know all the not necessarily pornographic
but all the perverted games coming from Japan who never use this there's a there's a very big plus
in the oculus rift column I'm serious there's a very big plus in the oculus rift column you know
why because everything on the PlayStation one's gonna be controlled whereas the oculus rift you
can literally you know anybody that has a dev kit can make stuff for it and I'm not just you know
I'm not just talking about porn although you know hey but you know it's it's the other stuff as well
you're not gonna really be able to get that same homegrown stuff on the PlayStation 4 I mean yes I
know that PlayStation embraces the indie developers and so forth but it's it's so much different like
you know like Bobby Black Wolf can't put flappy vog on PlayStation 4 as easy as he put it out
there on the internet you know I mean that's that's like the difference what I'm saying so
anyway let's see Alan alchemy in our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com says VR porn is
terrifying because you have a helmet on like you can be jerking it and have three people watching
you with their cell phones out that is not a future I want to live in not only that but
because you know like something like this device would be utilizing a secondary camera you could
actually watch yourself jerking and have the VR camera on at the same time you'd have it like
you know picture-in-picture almost if you're into that sort of thing I guess Wow so like
would would cam sex have a whole new thing to it we're like I don't know I don't know it's
POB to the max wouldn't be camp starvation too much like hamster so I don't know people are
into hamsters let's see SSG 100 man our chair at live.vognetwork.com says the hardcore gamers
only compile a margin of the overall profits towards gaming sales while the hardcore gamers
might have interest in this it doesn't mean that the casual people will jump at this VR not just
the Sony thing but also the rift well it depends on if they can get Wii Sports on it or all tongue
and cheekiness aside if they can find that Wii Sports type of game that sells it I mean think
about it Wii Sports sold the Wii that is how you push a peripheral I has there ever in history been
a game that better sold a peripheral than Wii Sports I don't think there has Super Mario
Brothers that wasn't that's not really a peripheral that's the whole damn system I don't
well me I can't you might and I'm sure somebody's gonna say DDR but dude Wii Sports was million
DDR zillion for the master system I don't know about that because well I mean the whole hair
to Wii Sports come on not in that respect but zillion was pretty big for pushing master systems
because they based the whole light gun off of the zillion gun maybe centipede and a trackball
I'm reaching here but that that's a tempest that in the trackball that was a good point good point
that's what I'm saying though I mean we could we could name all these different types of things
here but that's what I'm saying is that oculus rift and project Morpheus need its Wii Sports
that's what's gonna really sell those things all right let's move on with some other news here
because it is only a three-hour show we could talk VR all night long I'm sure but I want to
talk a little bit about some really big retail news that broke I think it was around the same
time as game developers conference but this was not from game developers conference Walmart
announced that starting March 26 you can trade in your used games at more than 3100 Walmart stores
and in exchange you'll get a gift card that you can use at Walmart or Sam's Club all the exchange
products will be sent for refurbishment and then will be made available for purchase in like new
condition so Walmart don't fall for it don't fall for it you are you are already ready to hate on
this well I fucking hate Walmart I don't really try not to give them my business they're a highly
disreputable company uh-huh they're just just research their business practices before you
give them it I like GameStop better than Walmart oh that's it okay but here okay so the hate boner
is strong with this one but but your your hate boner for Walmart does that have anything to do
with the whole use or do you think there's something about this used game practice that
actually is going to be bad no I don't there's anything about the practice it's just that I think
that in terms of social morality they're about the lowest on the pole you can get so I don't support
them I would rather other people not support them I would rather just go to the mom-and-pop stores
go to games go to GameStop before you go there and definitely go to Costco before you go to Sam's
Club um just to give you an idea about how some things are going for Walmart right now the
PlayStation 4 you can trade in for three hundred and seventy five dollars the Xbox one three
hundred and ninety dollars the that's a pretty good trade-in value I'd have to say the Wii U
deluxe $120 a 3g Vita is $95 that's actually kind of tempting because I don't really need the 3g in
my Vita I've never used it Grand Theft Auto 5 do not give them money $27 I won't $27 72 cents
Super Mario 3d World $38 those really aren't bad values but I mean honestly at the end of the day
Dark Sakura what I prefer to do I cut out the middleman entirely well I mean I sell my games
on eBay I mean so I guess yeah eBay is the middleman but I feel like it does still put
me direct with the buyer and I get profit that way I would like to point out to Tiger Claw that
people of Walmart is really a very not everyone who goes to Walmart looks like that that's just
playing into stereotypes sure but the average person doesn't choose to educate themselves on
the business practices of the place that they go to so I really really would rather that people
actually put conscious effort into making the world a bit of a better place and not putting
money into the hands of the people who are trying to fuck it over well here's the thing though Dark
Sakura is that people you know the reality of the situation is Walmart is huge whether we like it or
not they're huge they're a behemoth out there and I I could really see where this is gonna be a big
thing I think it would have been a bigger thing five years ago I think Walmart's really late to
the game in this regard but you know if if you had been able to take your games in and get that
money that you could put towards groceries especially when the recession hit I think that
would have been huge for Walmart yeah but I think that I would still be able to find other ways to
get money there are there's a there's actually other places out there who will give you money
for your games we have dimple sure and you probably get as much well dimples a local chain
but a lot of places everybody's getting in on this Amazon you do their Amazon you can buy a lot of
groceries out from Amazon in some cities you can do this for through I think Best Buy was to you
but I think they ended it but there's there's definitely other places that you can go look you
probably know a few more to that I'm not thinking of but what's your thoughts on Walmart taking the
used games do you think it'll be successful for sure they'll do okay with it I don't know if it's
gonna be just like it all depends on what what their trade-in values are and what they're
reselling their used games at I mean that's really gonna decide how successful is because you know
all they're gonna do is you know someone's gonna come up with a metric where okay game
subs give me this Walmart's give me this here's where I'm gonna go you know especially if they're
looking just to turn it around and purchase games with it now I don't know if Walmart does pre-orders
on new games I mean I think that they do but I don't know no target does so I would think where
one does the other probably does too but see that that's the thing is I mean I'm sure they don't
really care because they're just looking at reselling that you know used stuff and making
more of a profit margin from it so they could care less about you know the people that usually go to
Walmart are looking for deals I mean and even the few time I don't really care to shop at Walmart
either but the few times I have gone there because I purposely need something cheaply made are the
only times I've gone to Walmart like I need a really shitty sheet for a theater production
and I actually need it to be so shitty that it see through when you put a light behind it I think
that was the last time I went to Walmart it was I actually needed a terrible sheet but it but anyway
that the people that you you usually are going to Walmart looking for deals I would think are gonna
really benefit from having to use games there because they're gonna be cheaper and people are
gonna be like hey I don't care that it's a minute they'll throw in a dump in and people eat it up
just like they eat up the cheap DVDs that they have yeah for real I don't know you can see that
happening act-def in our chat room at live that vog network comm says Walmart does pre-orders so
there you go I confirm that they do that do that I'm not surprised at all it doesn't seem like a
particularly difficult thing for a company to do and you know kind of gets gets a little bit of
their money and their customer loyalty from that all right anyway let's move on with some more news
dark soccer with some interesting news coming up as soon as I can get my connection till you know
to participate with the show live instead of participate five you know five hours from now
so this is I know I'm actually not super sad about this but you remember I met somebody who
was on my list of people to meet one year at e3 and it was this particular kind of rock star
fella it was a Igarashi Koji who designed most of the latest to Castlevania games and was one
of the developers for Symphony of the Night or as it was in Japan Nocturne in the Moonlight which
is I think a better name basically he left Konami his last day was on March 15th and I'm gonna go
ahead and read his quote because I actually like how he says it he said I've decided to break out
on my own to have the freedom to make the kind of games I really want to make the same kind I think
fans of my past games want as well leaving Konami was a big decision not one I took lightly I've
spent my entire career there made many friends had a lot of great opportunities but I hope all
the gamers and fans have supported me in the past will join me in being excited about what comes
next wish me luck and I just got to meet him I you know we he put up with my really at the time
awful Japanese and he's just a really neat guy I mean just you know to have met just once but I'm
actually not sad to see him leaving Konami I think that we're gonna see I would like to be able to
see his work with a lot more freedom because he's clearly very creative has fantastic ideas and I
think it's gonna be good for him and for the gaming community in general to see what else he
can come up with it's kind of interesting seeing that the reason one of the reasons I guess he left
it was the whole fact that Konami is now kind of focusing more on social gaming and kind of the
mobile scene you know basically he said you know the more hardcore the game the less suitable is
for the casual market unfortunately I'm good at making core experiences so it was two years of
making the game that leaned to hardcore for the social market so it was canceled then I'd try
again and be canceled and again and be canceled so this this is a very interesting read of sorts
on where Konami in general has been heading because you know I think we were even just a
couple weeks sitting here going what is really Konami got in their in their cards right now
besides Metal Gear these days on consoles the metal gear and Pro Evo that's they don't they
don't really push out a lot of the franchises like they used to back in the day when we had a show
that was half dedicated to one of their franchise a Konami franchise I mean that is not the same
Konami that's there now but yeah they really crank out social stuff mobile phones and let's not forget
and pachinko and really lucrative market for them actually Konami's in that business to listen
let's not forget that you go to a casino and you'll see the Konami logo on a lot of the slot
machines it's always cracked me up before the record where's my DDR slot machine I want to know
I would also like to point out to people who call the Castlevania games on the handhelds as
Metroidvania yeah she said when working on Symphony of the Night that his biggest influence was
actually the Legend of Zelda that Metroid didn't factor into it oh interesting that it was the
the exploration and finding and hidden things here and there that inspired part of the item
system for Symphony of the Night and the subsequent games go to our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Tigerclaw says how long before the former Castlevania developer starts a Kickstarter
for Castlevania like game who knows probably not long well I mean there was that story out there
about that he would be happy to go work on a Metroid game and I think I think somebody posted
that to my wall on Facebook and I responded with that picture of the cat that's all over
tumblr that has that look on its face it just has the caption heavy breathing because that's exactly
like yes yes how many times have I posted that on Facebook but I mean seriously like I would love
for him to go work on a Metroid game I mean the newer Castlevania games were kind of crap I don't
think he wasn't involved with the newer ones all right I don't think so because newer Castlevania
games weren't they kind of forced them to be Castlevania as it was yeah exactly originally
going to be a Castlevania game yeah so I mean I don't know like I don't know about how you
guys feel but I kind of think like Castlevania peaked a long time I tried to make Castlevania
several times with not quite Castlevania games you know with the Lords of Shadows and then there
was that one that was God and I can't remember the name now but it was you're fighting robots
and instead of blood it was oil or something and it it was nano breaker I think oh yes I do remember
you know what I remember that game when it was cyber bot it was nano break yes I remember them
yeah it was they were demoing that at e3 when you're a man I like cyber bots yeah I think I did it
for a classic game once already 3ds ones are awesome I don't know dark Tetsuya telling me
there is a beat mania slot machine I didn't know you said DDR yeah I did say DDR but I mean that's
still pretty cool although I'm sure they don't make it anymore cuz my money's dead would you
heard well that I think technically they're think technically they're still making you beat but
whatever hey the money lives on on on iPads don't you know huh cyber bots is Capcom's number one
game don't lie it's a quote it's a devil out quote from puzzle fighter that's oh that's right
that's old-school everyone here's like what cyber bots reaching into the archive for quotes there
all right he's not the only guy leaving lots of people are leaving different companies and for
pretty much the same reasons kind of move on and do their own thing another person that's actually
leaving Sony stig a moose and he's not working I guess at Sony Santa Monica he was kind of the
creative director of God war 3 and I get guests basically you know they canceled what his new
project and so you know he's basically left the company after being there for 11 years also along
with him at sucker punch was see here Jamie Grissom er and basically he left after working on
infamous second son but he's been there for quite a while as well a lot of these guys is kind of
moving on and doing their own thing going back India yes this has to be related to the layoff
news from a couple weeks ago what they laid off those people at Sony Santa Monica and this says
that his project got canceled so he left that that has to be tied together and this one I'm
kind of disappointed about but hopefully he's gonna be doing some great stuff on his own Tetsuya
Mizuguchi has departed Q entertainment and of course you may recognize that name from such
wonderful games including rez and rez like games like child of Eden basically saying that uh you
know I guess he's moving on to his own well I thought that there was news like about a year
ago that he was taking on another role anyway because I seem to remember morning the Mizuguchi
was gonna be making another game anytime soon before and I thought there was something I mean
I don't think the news was that he had left the company but that he was taking some type of like
other role within it so I mean and they're even kind of confused on that sucks though cuz I love
his work I guess there's like some anonymous sources they're saying that you know they're
kind of confused when he may have left that he's been keeping a secret that he's been gone and he
may have actually departed was it last year sometime so I don't know what the hell's Q
doing then that's interest no idea I haven't really seen anything developing so maybe there's
got they've got something in secret they're working on no big no where he would be pretty
awesome huh harmonics yeah I don't know in East meets West West kind of thing could be interesting
badass I kind of I think with like the visual styles that he's got with his games and stuff
that fit right in with you know was it uh their brand new shooter that they've got you know there
is a reality though that maybe he doesn't want to do video games anymore like the guy who did
Katamari Damacy right ended up making like kids rides yeah he came back and started making like
smaller video I mean he keeps coming back and making little videos here and there and he'll
come back hopefully we haven't seen the last of music and you caught a Mario fucking awesome
that's just that's a series that's been kind of quiet for a little while huh it's cuz he drove
it into the ground it's like hey it's a new game Oh psych it's just still the old levels again it's
another new ads kids old levels that it that is a series I'd like to see kind of come but that
that's something they could put on project Morpheus because that will make people sick
whatsoever can you imagine Katamari Damacy in VR it would make for an interesting like survival
mode where you're running away from the giant Katamari Akuma JP with a clarification on now
where Tetsuya Mizuguchi is gone Akuma JP says he was going to teach in a university and Q is doing
social games so I mean this is really like a running theme is I mean maybe not so much the
Sony one but we're seeing that companies shifts toward social games is driving the old guard and
some of these these faces that really developed the classic games we love out well they're taking
the safe route because it's it's a you know social gaming is where they're making a lot of money so
you can't fault them for wanting to you know keep their company profitable but at the same time it's
like yeah it does kind of suck that these guys are going but you know if the you know these
creative guys that are you know known for these fantastic games they're not necessarily needed
for a lot of these social games anymore because I mean you don't have to be too entirely creative
to come up with something that's gonna sell okay on you know mobile devices I could see them you
know going on to form their own you know spinning off to form their own companies and a lot of these
guys do that and you see a lot of stuff being kick-started or you know that's why there's a
whole indie resurgence again so I I don't know it's I'm hopeful that he'll make something cool
lots of very passionate comments in our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com game guru says
it is kind of sad that both Capcom and Konami are both essentially going to disappear for the mobile
market Jason with a little bit of a rant here saying people make social games with the same
boring-ass formula if there's one thing Nintendo got right it's the incredibly light use of
effective social elements Nintendo Network Super Mario 3d world low Nintendo is doing
non real-time social better than anyone else hmm dark Tetsuya supports that comment that she actually
do agree I don't know I do and I don't like I I don't I don't know like I do still enjoy those
elements that Nintendo puts in their games but yet I still yearn for like Nintendo to really push
that envelope further with online like where is my true online experience I don't even think like
the stuff that they have implemented in some of these games and you know with the whole you know
hey I could leave a comment here in this part of the game stuff that they do on the Wii U I don't
think that's if you didn't have that like you'd really miss it I would think I just think it's
kind of like oh that's gonna neat but it doesn't really add that much it doesn't say like wow I
need to get this version of the game because it has this feature in it that's never crossing
anyone's mind it just kind of something that I do that's like see you look hey we have internet
we understand social media we're hip we're cool you know I think the coolest thing that Mario
does is when it gets the ghosts in the levels that came from you know other people running it
that I think I think that's the coolest use of the social media and that's the kind of stuff
I would like to see like more of I think that's that's really cool that's not even social media
that's like shit they were doing from the DS like where you would you know get ghost data from
people and stuff I just don't it's not that new it's cool I like that they have that but it's I
wouldn't even go as far as saying it's like social media it's just you're sharing ghost data I mean
let's let let's not overly complicate things all right let's move on with some more news and that
has to do with the Xbox one which we haven't talked a whole lot about tonight but I know a
lot of people have been picking up Xbox ones because like there was a big sale this week on
that new Titanfall bundle right like I think Walmart marked it on 50 bucks and then Best Buy
was price matching it so a lot of people picking up an Xbox one right now and a lot more people
gonna be picking them up in September because the Xbox one will come to 26 more markets in September
eight of those were part of the original launch lineup that includes places like Denmark Russia
Sweden Switzerland they were cut from the original launch plans but now they will be launching there
in September one of the other big places of note where the game will be launching in September will
be Japan so finally Japan gets its Xbox one but the question is who cares will they care yeah
Akuma do you think other people will care it's all about the games right well it could I mean
let's see what happens at e3 because you know if you think about it okay if the system is coming
out in Japan in September this is the opportunity this e3 for Microsoft to get up on stage and say
hey XYZ Japanese developer who has been secretly working on an Xbox one exclusive this whole time
such as they weren't getting those some good support for the Xbox before for a lot of the
shooters so I wonder if that would be enough to you know if they start getting more local development
for like just those bullet hell games would that get people to buy to hell more RPGs I have a
tinfoil hat theory Akuma JP says don't care I have a tinfoil hat yeah well what's missed Walker
doing right now because we know remember they were big stuck in the bathroom with explosive diarrhea
no but they remember they they were a big start of the push for exclusives on the Xbox 360 when
they have Blue Dragon and Lost Odyssey which you know but the problem is again Lost Odyssey wasn't
exactly a huge sales behemoth which is criminal because that game is fucking amazing I thought
that Blue Dragon was really fun and on the Wii I know they did last story was on the Wii right
and I know they've done some DS games in between there but what are what's like their big project
they're doing right now hmm I don't see them working on something for the Wii U maybe maybe
maybe I don't know maybe yet did the last story sell better than Lost Odyssey did now miss Walker
didn't do Dragon Quest right there were no no that's I get confused because it's the same art
square enix well yeah but I mean think of the out source development no and well we never got
the Dragon Quest and Dragon Quest X is the MMO we never got that anyway which is weird I don't
think that would do that well over here I it's just it's one of those things is you know they
don't have a lot of people that have just you know you're cornering the Wii U market then you
have you know people that are gonna play an MMO on this thing it's just I don't know that it's
too risky to bring it over here Akuma JP says missed Walker is in social games too that's a
sad laugh um Akuma JP also says yeah like like Dart Sakura had quoted earlier they don't care
people who want to play Titanfall will buy that's kind of what's happening over here like five
people well I don't know I think it's more magic well me actually in Japan probably not a lot but
I should have to say after seeing Titanfall in action yeah III think it would be it would
actually be a decent selling factor it actually is pretty good yeah on Xbox I mean I mean not
Xbox but I saw the PC one yeah and it was it was pretty good but see that's the thing it's like if
they really want to play Titanfall I think they just pick it up on PC why wait you know almost
six months yeah all right um let's anyway lots and lots of regions that the Xbox will be coming to
other big places Argentina India Israel Korea Saudi Arabia Singapore South Africa those are
just some of the countries a lot lots and lots of places getting the Xbox one a little later this
year so please look forward to it to register participation for this week's episode of Orange
Laundry radio at vog network comm use the passphrase belt well how about something that has
nothing to do with actual gaming systems but does affect gaming systems let's hear it well Netflix
we've been talking about the whole deal with the net neutrality popping up and since the the ruling
past and just on top of that there were the other situations where we're seeing Netflix making deals
with Comcast and you know other companies trying to get a bandwidth deals well now Netflix is sort
of turning it over and their CEO Reed Hastings put on a blog post this past Thursday that that
uh basically they're just he's just completely they said that the original definition of net
neutrality isn't fitting and it needs to be changed to to basically describe better the
activities around customer activities and what's going to you know demand what's going to use more
services can use less this quote says without strong net neutrality companies like Comcast can
make these demands driving up cost and prices for everyone else which is basically what we've been
saying anyway yet they've gone and make that deal so is this you know a case of a little hypocrisy
or is it that this is something that was already in the works is it I just don't understand why
they would just switch over like that but it I mean but it's a correct statement we know we see
it's happening already and there's also a Comcast executive though who was saying that the Netflix
CEO was wrong this is the open internet rules never were designed to deal with peering and
internet connection providers like Netflix have always paid for their connection so we've got a
little bit of an argument here well obviously there's concern about net neutrality because
it's in some ways it's kind of a ticking time bomb when it comes to gaming specifically because you
know we don't know what might happen where you know I think what's ultimately gonna happen is
that you're gonna see that these these providers start to put their data caps out there and they
have the different plans and they're gonna try to sell these cheaper plans that are very stringent
on the data caps but yet there will be certain services that will not count towards the data cap
which I think already happens with Comcast and they're like Xfinity movies and things like that
I don't think count towards whatever I don't even know if they're enforcing data caps right now but
you know they had that thing I and but it's just a matter of time before we see will Xbox live count
towards that will PlayStation Network count towards that will something like on live or
one of those streaming gaming solutions will they try to be the ones that you know I get the free
pass on the bandwidth I don't know but I I just don't think like Comcast can be so bold as to
start telling these tiered internet things because it's gonna be a huge revolt it's not like customers
don't have the choice to go other places yes they may have not have other cable providers in your
area but shit I know people that would go back to DSL rather than put up with this tiered internet
bullshit well also I'd like to read what the pagans you just said and the theory behind the deal is
good marketing because of the upcoming merger they want sure they can play nice at least that's what
I heard on NPR and why did Alan say but when doesn't he say but he doesn't want the internet
to regulate the pictures of butts going on out there I think is the problem but anyway yeah I
think I think that's a good theory that Comcast is making nice nice with Netflix because that could
have been a thorn in their side with the merger coming up and you know they're gonna have to
show that it's not antitrust basically that they control too much so anyway also hmm I agree with
butts who doesn't agree with butts all right well coming soon to a gaming store near you let's see
if there's some video games that may feature butts Loki anything in the u.s. sorry no butts this time
cut the rope triple treat coming out on 3ds the witch in the hundred night on PlayStation 3
although the alternate artwork for that does feature I think her but Diablo 3 Reaper of Souls
I think there's a butter to in that on PC Dynasty Warriors 8 extreme legends on PlayStation 3 and
extreme legends complete edition on PlayStation Vita and PlayStation 4 deception for blood ties
on PlayStation 3 and on the Vita Cabela's big-game hunt her pro hunts on ps3 Xbox 360 and Wii U and
that is Alan alchemy by the way in our chat room clarifying his comment saying I said butts because
Comcast which actually is a perfectly valid explanation now that you say that Jamie do
you accept that explanation that's all the time well that's a game because before the show I said
that you liked big butts and you cannot lie you other brothers can't deny all right going to Japan
and talking about some of the releases over there hey on the PlayStation 3 biohazard 6 premium
edition L and Excel I don't I didn't even know that there was like a new like that game has
already been out so I don't know they're re-releasing it again for some reason on the
25th this week let's see also Hatsune Miku project diva f-second ooh I did not know this was the
thing that was coming out soon but yeah that's coming on the PlayStation 3 on the 27th and I'm
sure there'll be some people that are very excited about that one of the surviving music game
franchises there that's probably come out over here in the summer yeah in 2015 no no they released
the first one last summer did it come did it come out pretty quick that's come I think it's pretty
quick also some repackaging and re-releases for sleeping dogs Hong Kong Himitsu Keisatsu and Tomb
Raider game of the year edition are also out on the PlayStation 3 this week winning post 8 comes
out this week in regular and 20th anniversary premium box that is all on the PlayStation 3 in
Japan on the Xbox 360 this week Titanfall is released in Japan although I'm not sure if some
no it's not it may may be affecting Japan just like it is here so I think this list has been
updated but on the Xbox 360 you could get Yaiba Ninja Gaiden Z Ninja Gaiden Z was out on the Vita
this week there's actually a handful of games on the Vita this week there's a whole shit ton
of games on the Vita this week at layer Aisha Plus Kukan no Daichi no Rankin jutsu comes out I know
there's some at layer fans out there so there's that on the Vita this week golden time vivid
memories Hatsune Miku project Eva second is out there as well lovely quest unlimited in regular
and limited edition and roll kill bull and nice on the shutter chance comes out irregular limited
edition and winning post 8 that's a heck of a lot of Vita games this week and lastly on the Wii U
this week there is a new premium set coming out and we'll talk about that a little later in the
show and on the 3ds this week new love plus it's new love plus with a plus sign after it isn't that
redundant it's new love plus maybe is double plus new love double plus maybe they've been reading a
lot of brave new a lot of 1984 so everything is double plus are they actually releasing three
maybe these are stickers because there's actually a picture of like 3ds is with like skins of some
of the girls in the game on that so maybe that's the extra they all have the same expression maybe
yeah they do they all yellow concerned we're so concerned that you want to fuck us laughs
lastly they're dating them dating dating yeah you can also pay for dating lastly there is a special
3ds ll or XL Monster Hunter 4 edition it's a gold of 3ds that is coming out in Japan this week if
you really love your Monster Hunter you can get it just it just looks like gold flames or something
like it's not even and it says Monster Hunter 4 on it big fucking deal actually kind of good looking
right here the track the Triforce ones way that anytime I hear the 3ds ll it makes me think of
Leonardo Leonardo from the clerk's animated cartoon dark Sakura how about the UK there's
some stuff on the 25th we have Diablo 3 Reaper Reaper of Souls for Mac and PC we have quest of
dungeons and smite that's actually a fun name smite on the 26th we have Fez for anything with
a Sony name on it the 27th we have Warhammer 40k which I dumped somebody over once but it's coming
out for Android iPad iPhone and PC and on the 20th we have Professor Layton versus Phoenix Wright for
the 3ds you might dig smite by the way sorry my buddies over on a podcast called video game
realness which you all should check out if you haven't been listening to it it's a really fun
show but they've been talking a lot about smite it's it's kind of like a League of Legends style
game I know it does like more like you can do like first-person points of view or not not for
but like more like World of Warcraft looking because you know how League of Legends is kind
of like a like a top-down sort of thing but like I guess smites a little more like World of
Warcraft leading so I it's kind of one of those style games I would also like to point out for
people next month that goat simulator comes out next month and everyone needs this game I'm going
to be getting goat simulator the heat Loki's been talking sorry I'm great give it up for the goats
that it that is when I a I convinced my sister she doesn't even have steam or anything I'm like
dude you need to get that's coming out next and you know in two weeks and she's like okay well
we need to hook up Sean's computer and you know give it up for the goat see it looks great but
here's the best here's the but what here's the best part but yes the best part about goat
simulator besides the fact goat emulator beside the fact that it looks crazy is steam they're
gonna have the whole steam or workshop support so you're gonna be able to make your own shit
if you really want to I don't know if it would probably get voted off there because it's
inappropriate you could make your own goat say yeah I have this weird feeling that goat simulators
like the new minecraft like wait like I kind of think I it just I don't call it a hunch kind of
think goat simulators the new minecraft reginator says what about goat simulator to goat stimulator
oh I saw there like sirs you are a damn pervy I've been in the corner I've been following the
guys that you know they make the game and just like just basically trolling everywhere to try
to find you know some sort of new footage of the game and the best I could do with someone posted
a vine video that they had of playing goat simulator at GDC that cliffy B had that I don't
remember but it was something yeah where he had the tongue stuck to the back of the car and he
was being drunk around in circles like oh god I need this game now it's so amazing it does look
like a game that you you would have made it really did it's like you love you guys you guys know
Loki loves his sandbox games come on grand theft auto 5 he never shuts up about it Saints Row 4
he never shuts up about it he loves the sandbox game what is goat simulator it's just I just
stewed in parts with goats and it's not ridiculous over the top which is the other but I see you
know I would get this too because you know what my one of my favorite animals and all the entire
universe is goats because I love their eyes and goats are the best they're the most adorable
things ever and like the goats that are at fairy tale land here in Sacramento for when I have to
go with Becky and she takes Julian and I just hang out with goats say you love the goats say you do
I love cats yeah okay how's that you happy you ever have to do a new intro you know what you
guys can bite me and you're gonna say that you guys are awful okay here I am trying to support
independent gaming and you guys are being you know what that indie game yeah I know plenty of what's
pick that indie game is probably the first one in a long time where all three of us said pre-ordered
I don't know I think the game is pretty mad I like big goats and I cannot lie oh come on were
you raised in a barn no all right um that's it for the UK dates yes I'm seriously hoping that
they put goat boy in that that game somehow all right Loki why don't you reach on in and pull
out another story for us okay so um there was I guess Siliconera had asked Nintendo about you
know unity coming possibly to the 3ds because you know it's supported on the Wii U and hell that's
how a lot of those you know indie games are on the Wii U's because people are building them in
unity and porting them over using the unity export stuff and of course the generic answer that they
got I don't even know this is exactly news is we're definitely looking at it so there you go
they're definitely looking at something so I'm definitely looking at it yeah my eyes are in that
general direction what you're you have you already forgotten about the goats have not but I I heard
aren't they aren't there supposed to be like 50 games or something using this that are coming to
we use soon I thought there's a lot of games that are using it I'm not sure on the exact number but
I can imagine like 50 games that sounds about right makes everybody I mean a lot of people are
using unity especially because the Wii U doesn't really support a ton of different engines that
you know can be multi-platform so I can see it's one of the few that you know people are developing
games for that's easy to port to other systems how they added support for the Vita and you know
PlayStation 3 for it supports most of the consoles out there right now all right well as SSG 100 Matt
in our chat room says moving on to the next topic well apparently your boyfriend thinks we need Jesus
why don't you tell him a thing or two let me tell you a thing all right moving on let me tell you
about Unreal Engine 4 Unreal Engine 4 this is some other big news that came out of game developers
conference Unreal Engine 4 is gonna be out it's it's gonna be basically available to plenty more
people it's it's open to the public essentially for the low low cost of $19 a month but there is
a catch if you are going to profit off the game it will involve a royalty agreement asking for
5% in gross sales so you know but I mean you can do a lot with Unreal Engine so it might be worth
it to some people so yeah Unreal Engine 4 is gonna be available to the public it's a subscription
based service there this is the same thing that triple-a game developers have been using for lots
and lots of money but yeah it's big big news coming out of game developers conference direct
out of direct out of the mouth of Tim Sweeney who is the epic games founder so this is great because
you know assuming that developers are willing to take the you know 5% agreement a lot of indie
games can really focus on you know making that game and you know the engine will do a lot of
hopefully the legwork for them we see a lot a lot of games out there that use Unreal Engine 3 as it
is you know things like forget doesn't Final Fantasy 13 run on Unreal some of it like like
there's a lot of weird games out there you wouldn't think run on this engine that do I know the last
remnant ran on yeah real yeah there's just a lot of games out there that run on it like the Mortal
Kombat games do right pretty sure they do so you know this could be a great thing for Loki this
sounds like the type of thing where you might be raising an eyebrow going is this another thing I
should play with no I don't want to learn something else you don't want to learn something else ones
enough for you yeah maybe later fair enough all right well before we get to our break here we're
gonna go back to a classic time in gaming it's a classic time when there was no engine there was no
do-it-yourself you end up you want to make a video game you learned assembly language we've
bought a very expensive you had you had a Texas Instruments computer and programmed a little
bleeping ball that's right dark soccer is gonna take us to the classic game of the week archive
dark soccer what is a video game that you think the kids out there should be playing this week
speaking of things that come on he's fucking run into the ground nothing is as great as the
original Frogger what a what a timely choice unintentionally and I will tell you about Frogger
and my history with this game before I go further into it and to be clear this is the original
arcade game not the pot not the shit not the dumps that Konami took on the franchise so anyway I
imagine me around eight years old on roller skates playing Frogger it's damn hard to play Frogger on
roller skates it's hard to play almost any arcade game on roller skates and I did play a stand-up
pole position on roller skates as well I played the exact same Frogger machine at Babalu skating
rink in Dothan Alabama every summer for probably the next 11 years after that so and it still
worked it had some burnin it was old but damn machine still worked and now it's gone and I
mourn that particular Frogger but that was my Frogger anyway Frogger is a game we play as a
stupid frog and you were trying to get across the street and then across the pond into your little
froggy hole and sometimes crocodiles might try to eat you which I've never seen a crocodile eat a
frog but I have seen it grab a man by its leg this happened for now I've seen this having him
because I'm from the swamp anyway a Frogger came out in 1981 it was developed by Konami and licensed
by Sega and Gremlin at the time so basically you just have to navigate traffic you know keep from
getting run over by the damn front by the trucks and apparently a Formula One cars go on the street
in whatever town this is and all kinds of things it is you know one of the very classics of games
it also was one of the first games that used more than one CPU is choose 80 processors it is
basically still super popular and shush don't judge me for saying froggy hole okay I'm not the
one having an obsession with froggy don't get distracted by chat especially when they're being
perverts up so anyway by 2005 Frogger sold more than 20 million copies worldwide including 5
million in the u.s. so yeah you use a joystick you you know have to navigate the froggy around you can
send them up and the different types of vehicles that you can be smushed flat by our cars trucks
buses dune buggies bulldozers vans taxis bicyclists motors and or motorcycles that will just cut
through traffic and then in the next half you have crocodiles and turtles the turtles can sink
into the ground the crocodiles can eat you but you can land on their backs you can ride their ass the
entire way if you want and then you land in your frog home sorry not frog hole and the levels are
timed so different things will kill you make turning you into a little skull and crossbones
which the last time I saw a frog a frog skull it was when I was cutting into it when I was in ninth
grade in biology class so at any rate you could be hit by a car you could jump into the water run
into snakes otters or into crocodiles jaws you can jump into a home invaded by a crocodile you
can stay on a diving turtle that is submerged to ride a log crocodile turtle off the screen
jump onto a log a home already occupied by a frog jump into the side of a home or in the bush and
running out of time before getting your froggy home as far as other versions there have been
many others there have been clones as people in chat room are mentioning right now Sierra had the
magnetic media rights as far as cartridge versions Parker medic media as in discs Oh
okay Parker brothers licensed it from Sega for cartridges we've seen copies on the TRS 80 the
Sinclair 1000 and Sinclair 2068 sorry it has just clicked for me after all these years why
Frogger two three deep which was the one I loved on Commodore 64 was only ever on cartridge because
it was a Parker brothers game I just had an aha moment Thank You dark soccer I feel welcome
lightened we had Atari 2600 versions the multiple releases and there was a cassette for the
supercharger and Tommy there was a Tomy Tudor version that was also licensed from Konami
themselves but not it's not clear if it's been developed by Konami Parker brothers also did the
releases for 2600 and television Atari 5200 which I have the clique of vision which I have
Atari 8-bit computers the vic-20 and Commodore 64 as you mentioned Rob Sierra had the Commodore
64 disk versions which is why there were two versions on the Commodore 64 and there's Apple
to those the original 128 came Macintosh the IBM PC the Atari 2600 supercharger and then the versions
for the TRS 80 color computer and Sinclair did had a version developed by corn soft in the UK
about 10 million was spent on advertising for Frogger and it was advertised along with the
Empire Strikes Back there's your Star Wars thing Coleco also had a mini arcade tabletop version
that was released also along with Pac-Man Galaxian and Donkey Kong I have one of those taken apart
awesome now there were clones of it including froggy for the ZX spectrum hopper by anchor
anchor and soft for the BBC micro and the acorn electron there was another Frogger for the BBC
micro ZX spectrum there was Frogger for sharp MZ 700 in the UK and a version of done for the new
brand by the name of elite the Atari 2600 also had a game named freeway that its working title
was bloody human freeway awesome so I mean like I said there's just been like a bunch of different
versions I mean we have them by Hasbro we have them you know rereleases for PlayStation we have
there was a prototype based off a Frogger for the Sega Game Gear that was never released but
apparently I think there are leaks of the ROM set out there was a Porta Frogger for Xbox Live
Arcade and that was developed by Digital Eclipse and published by Konami so then you were right
the sequel to Frogger was Frogger 2 3 deep in 1984 there was another Frogger in 1997 Frogger
2 swap is revenge in 2000 and then a bunch of shit that Konami took on the franchise well
well that first Konami won the Frogger in 97 that was a huge game that was a huge that was on the
original PlayStation that was a huge game it was very different you know because it had the larger
kind of worlds you know that game I thought was incredibly boring I I owned it actually I didn't
I didn't mind it I thought it was cool well how about some pop culture references this time Frogger
had an animated series as part of the Saturday Supercade the CBS did it was included with it
was Frogger pitfall Harry and then their segments were replaced by kangaroo and space ace and there
was a segment on remember that show VR troopers they were beating a frog monster called amphibidor
based off of Frogger and it's been mentioned in that horrid horde show Seinfeld which I still
do not like to show MTV movie that was a really funny episode though okay well basically there
was a reference to a bunch of different early games in that one and Frogger was in wreck-it Ralph
hanging around a game central station and in 1982 and that's why I'm saying stay tuned to the very
end of the show tonight Buckner and Garcia did a song called froggies lament that was on the
Pac-Man fever soundtrack and as I recall for single wasn't it the b-side I don't know bad
religion did a song called Frogger where he says that Los Angeles is trying to play Frogger with
his life yeah there's basically quite a number of different references but the best of them ever in
2006 there's a group in Austin Texas that modified a Roomba dressed as a Frogger to do a real-life
version of the game that used a bitch a Bluetooth controller the Roomba was able to get across the
street 10 times 40 lanes and survived for 15 minutes before it was quote killed by an SUV a
game over you know and actually Frogger has been a nickname for disease as well I don't know if I
was it was a name given to the jumping gene for a particular family fruit fly okay then there you
go is that it there's all the highest by the way the highest Frogger score by Michael Smith
of Springfield Virginia and the world record was nine hundred and seventy thousand four hundred and
forty points and he beat Pat Lafayette on December 26 on 2099 and I'm guessing that's a some sort of
yeah it's a Twin Galaxies thing so whatever all right what evs there Frogger there it is your
konami shit there it is your classic game of the week Frogger which really is a real real classic
if you think about it yeah I mean all those references alone no Frogger will ever be as
awesome as me on my roller skates as a seven-year-old playing at Babalu skating rink in Dothan Alabama
well fair enough all right here then Rob uh-huh it was long and bored straight my hair when I
was seven went to my ass you will never see it be that long ever all right we're gonna take a break
Jamie's doctor I'm just looking at the related videos by the way to the Frogger video and
somebody recreated it of course in Grand Theft Auto Frogger of course they did that's hilarious
that seems like the type of thing Loki would have done all right we're gonna take a break guys when
we come back to plenty more orange launch radio including rapid-fire news the frugal question of
the week and plenty more coming out of game developers conference and more your emails your
calls we come back with more of orange launch radio right after this welcome back everybody
to orange lounge radio live here with episode number 545 of our show starting off the second
half from our brand-new studio and seven that's number seven because yes this is the seventh place
we have broadcast orange launch radio from in its 12-year history which just goes to show how
frequently I move although to be fair one of those places was where dark soccer was at so when you
had sure me at your feet for years that's right and now I have Sanrio who runs away because she
doesn't like people who's under the bed making evil single glowy eyes at me yes but she's she
kind of hides under the bed for half the day and then this is really weird in the old apartment she
would never get on top of the bed because she was afraid of the comforter she did not like the
comforter whatsoever well we didn't put the comforter on the bed this time and now she she loves the bed
she get hops up out there all the time in fact now she likes to jump up there when daddy got home at
4 30 in the morning last night she likes to jump on the bed at 10 a.m. kitty treat meow meow meow meow
kitty treat meow meow meow mmm like you little shit I'm gonna get the comforter I know Dan left
the door open today and Midna comes in and pounces on my face and then starts pawing at because we
have a big wide window over my bed so she's pawing at the blind so I open the blinds she gets up
there he runs out you know how she gallops yeah like that gotta love cats I love cats but
cats don't give a fuck and a story so yeah if I I'm not only a little bit sick but I was up until
4 30 last night because I went to San Francisco for a midnight movie last night that my shadow cast
group was doing on the road in San Francisco last night and so I drove home right after the show and
I'm so tired so I'm just I'm tired and I'm sick and I gotta go back to work tomorrow it's gonna be
a long day but I'm I'm happy to be doing this show with all of you guys and those of you listening
in chat this is how I spend my Sunday nights fun fun times SSG 100 Matt says she's getting she's
getting back at you for locking her in the bathroom for an hour during the move it was
one hour and it was for her own good and safety we didn't want her to run away hey not that she
would ever go outside but she would just she would have freaked out more outside all right
unfortunately this is not a podcast dedicated to cats although I don't know maybe I should
start a fourth podcast about cats but I could totally do a podcast about cats I'm gonna just
gonna call it old cat lady it'd be fun you never know I'm surprised they don't they probably do
have one called pod cats there's got to be there's got to be a show called pod cats if there's not
patent-ending all right let's uh let's do some rapid-fire news it's a video game podcast let's
talk about what's going on in games real quick Loki so looking forward to playing Titanfall
and 360 was supposed to be coming out this week but then at the last minute they're like hey it's
not ready and so it's now coming out on April 8th in North America and April 11th in Europe
and they said no we'll we see a few things that can be made even better and so we're giving
blue point a little bit more time to deliver an epic Titanfall experience for the 360 according
to the press release more like it's not done yet and that they they're working on epic day
one patch but you know that's neither here and there but yeah hopefully it's an awesome game
PlayStation 4 they announced that they're also offering in these some new development tools
to help with publishing games on their console including with that you know the ability to export
to PlayStation 4 on game maker studio as well as mono game which is I guess free to license
Sony computer entertainment developers and also of course you know unity does support PlayStation
3 and PlayStation 4 and I guess our PlayStation 3 and Vita and the PlayStation 4 version of the
export is coming for I guess some early access people in April and so that would be pretty cool
also they're authoring tools framework I guess this free open source available to download and
they use that you know in their first party games like you know last of us and beyond two souls and
that kind of stuff so pretty cool and then also they're going to be doing some more updates to the
PlayStation 4 firmware that's gonna allow you to do some game capture without HDCP restrictions
because right now you're kind of limited how you can capture on you know the PlayStation 4 but with
that you're gonna be able to I guess you know export clips and that kind of stuff you know you
can record and share longer clips of gameplay sessions and you know beyond I don't know if you
can yeah upping the resolution on ustream and twitch streams to 720p which is gonna be coming
in a later update so that's kind of cool that they're doing that and also the ability to save
videos and screenshots to a USB Drive so you know you want to edit them off your PlayStation 4 you
can do that as well instead of having to just export and stuff that's awesome all right well
moving on to some other news disregarding Mega Man Legends 3 you know it broke many hearts that
this game did not end up happening including the Mega Man creator KJ Inafune still wants Mega Man
Legends 3 to happen he said recently that if somebody asked even right now what's the game
you want to create most it's still Legends 3 I put so much effort into that game so much passion
into that game but it didn't happen it's always a regret in my mind even now we all know that it's
not gonna happen though as long as Capcom holds the IP but if they asked me to make the game I
could still gather most of the original team even right now so hey I'd be happy to see a mighty
number 9 legends if you know what I mean that by the way in comments to a US gamer moving on I
mentioned during the Japanese release dates that a new Nintendo Wii U was coming well it's just a
different type of bundle here what's happening is that the Wii U premium pack in Japan is being
replaced with a Wii Sports Club bundle hmm so yes a Wii Sports Club bundle is going on sale in Japan
starting on March 27th it will be a 32 gig Wii U premium console with a gamepad and then we use
our excuse me Wii Sports Club passes for events like bowling golf and tennis from Wii U Sports
Club because remember we use sports clubs that whole weird like free-to-play thing where you can
like demo it for 24 hours or you can buy one game or you can buy yeah so it comes with passes for
some of the games there and of course a Wiimote controller and a wrist strap all for the low low
price of 30,000 yen as you say they include a Wii remote with that that's just bullshit I know of
course there's a there's a Wii remote there so you can actually play the game and lastly also about
Nintendo a trademark for QOL in Japan for a number of products QOL quality of life and the trademarks
are covering things including portable gaming devices standalone gaming devices merchandise
beauty products so very interesting nobody knows though what exactly this could be about although
some people think it could be some type of new fitness initiative well yeah I remember they were
talking about that they wanted to kind of go in that direction in which I still don't I mean I
cool but once again I don't think this is gonna I don't know where they're going well I ranted a
few weeks ago about how Nintendo should have had the Fitbit craze and they lost it and maybe this
is their chance to try and still capture that although I kind of thought we you or we fit you
was supposed to kind of have that whole thing in it so I don't know what else they're enhancing to
the fitness thing but we'll see I just don't I don't get it right now I mean it to me this is
almost like how I didn't get the Wii vitality sensor and I still don't get that and it's cool
the app they want to you know do something where you can exercise and they can do all that sort of
tracking stuff but the problem is there's already stuff out there that does that and probably does
it better and just because it has my has a me in it doesn't mean I'm gonna fucking buy it or I'm
gonna buy a system for it so I'm I just wait and see what they're gonna do with this we'll see
dark soccer what do you have for us we have some stuff basically we've got going on and this is
kind of sad but all of the DLC for guitar hero DJ hero and band hero is going to be going away
as of March 31st so yeah I get it while the getting's good and guitar hero on iOS is going
to be discounted through the end of the month on the App Store in other news we have a new
character that has been revealed for ultra Street Fighter 4 and that's Decapra Decapra Decapra who's
one of bison's dolls or I should say Vega for the Japanese version she's the arch villain of the
doll guard and she is a clone of Cammy also and this one was really sad and Dan and I actually
talked about this because part of what put him in the hospital for congestive heart failure were
energy drinks and a Norwegian team teen I'm sorry basically was part of a he was 14 year old kid
named Henrik who was at his cafeteria school doing a Call of Duty land party that lasted 16
hours he said this is the quote I was playing Call of Duty then everything went dark and I passed
out he was sent to a hospital in Lillehammer who basically he was in a coma for several days his
kidney started to fail other organs started to fail and it was because he had been drinking
energy drinks the entire time the rest of the rest of his health had been pretty okay all up until
that point but it was the combination of lack of sleep focused attention and just drinking
consistent energy drinks for the period of 16 hours he drank four liters of energy drinks that's
a little excessive that's even you wouldn't drink that much that's just stupid that is also 14 which
goes along with you know stupid and that that's a good way to make your heart explode yeah but but
and the reason I'm saying the soup is more like an ignorant thing you think the human brains under
like 25 years old are not programmed to think about long-term effects they're programmed to
think about immediate reward so that is I need to stay awake let me drink another I need to stay
awake let me drink another and not putting any thought at all into what is this going to do to
my kidneys take a break my liver can't process this much taurine when you're when you're playing
games or you know doing anything like that take a break why do you think we take a break here at
OLR instead of doing three hours because people's gotta pee take a little break to you know drink
water and use the restroom and all that stuff so all right anyhow let us take a break on over to
our Facebook and Google Plus communities because when you slam those words together you get FUGL
Plus but we just call it FUGL for short in a segment we call the FUGL question of the week
heading on over to our communities we're gonna get some responses to this question tonight we
are sure that many of you have heard the news this week that Igarashi left Konami after many
years of working on the Castlevania series so we thought we'd use this as an excuse to ask our
audience about their thoughts on Castlevania the past and the present do you have a favorite game
in the series do you still play the new games or could you never get into the series and why
so we're gonna get people's thoughts on Castlevania tonight so let's start with over on
Facebook wicked from the nerdgasm Network who says the Castlevania series is a very personal
favorite of mine I originally cut my gaming teeth playing countless hours of Castlevania 2 just
trying to decipher what the hell the villagers were telling me I never did beat the game until
I was into my 20s though sorry guys I suddenly decided to get a case of the hiccups my favorite
game in the series fluctuates a lot especially after all of my game challenges over the past 18
months right now it's Aria of sorrow followed up by Symphony of the night sandwiched by dawn of
sorrow in third I fell in love with the Metroidvania style of Symphony growing up and I feel the sorrow
pair took the spirit of the game and ran with it I like the classic style side scrollers especially
Rondo of blood and super Castlevania 4 but I never could get into the 3d ones sour taste to
my mouth from Castlevania 64 I guess then I know a while back I think he went through and played
like every single stinking Castlevania game because they they do these like little challenges
on their show where they play every game in a series it's pretty impressive let's see dark
Tetsuya says favorite game in the series has got to be Symphony of the night games like that helped
inspire my favorite indie title ever wink what could that be as for egos future well if he follows
in the footsteps of KJ and ifune I'm very excited about the prospect of a similar game with his
influence yeah I'm sure that's just a matter of time our pal Jeremy from Koopa Club says I love
this series my faves are the original games the more action-oriented ones I like the Metroid style
games as well but those don't appeal to me as much as say super Castlevania 4 does the first
Lords of Shadow isn't all that bad but it's not really that great either I haven't played the
other two games in the series and maybe I will someday but right now I have no desire to really
reward Konami with any of my time oh snap I also don't see why anyone is sad that Ega left chances
are he'd never have made another Castlevania game anyway given that they had him working on social
games for the past few years and I'm adding into that and canceling them let him leave and make
something better I can agree with that Ian also from Koopa Club that's Koopa with a Q Club with
the K another great podcast says I remember liking Castlevania 64 a bunch and really got into the DS
games I'm not sad about him leaving either as that appears to be the trend that people are doing
I'm hoping the Silent Hill masterminds follow suit and we will get kickstarters out the ass
and vag for their respected games what do you think dark Sakura how about kickstarters out the ass and
vag don't know no no no no no no no no no no no no no SSJ 100 Matt giving us our favorite kind of
answer a haiku here we go are you ready for the haiku whipping vampires never get that's all you
already lost whipping vampire oh no I just kidding I can't count just kidding that whipping vampires
that's for no way whipping vampires I made the same mistake it's yeah um fam whipping higher
vampires vampires is two syllables Rob I'll let it slide whipping vampires never gets old except
when it is Simon's quest that is a lie Simon's quest is one of my favorites don't spread lies
on my show our friend Shane says Castlevania 3 only because it had a pirate named Grant
de nasty cracks me up every time I read it was that a mistranslation thing or is that really
was grant de nasty grant de nasty according to the website how many syllables calm vampire is two
syllables but what about vampires that would use syllables will be two syllables thought I'd try
unless you're from Texas or Alabama or somewhere vampires then it's got 50 all right and lastly
nemesis 47 on Facebook nemesis 47 says Castlevania Symphony the night on the old PlayStation one
still to this day one of my favorite games in the series I still remember the time I beat it and got
the good ending by exploring every nook and cranny in the castle remember getting that stinking
upside-down castle the first time in one of the top 10 moments in gaming ever when you unlock
that upside-down castle and you're like ah fuck no it's after you get through with with butthole
shaft which is what I called him related to the acid badge Kickstarter no no no butthole shaft
was yes the dark priest shaft I'm just talking about shaft shut your mouth um I still what I
always wanted to do that was I was trying to find because you know there was the hidden track for
Maria having been turned into or possessed by the succubus hmm but I never did find that in the
Japanese one which Dan imported before he and I got together wow that's actually pretty impressive
yeah all right let's see going to Google Plus and reading some of the answers over there act
deaf says super Castlevania 4 is definitely my favorite in the series that was a good one I love
that one on Super Nintendo and then there was Castlevania 5 on the Super Nintendo and I remember
thinking at the time this game is ass and it wasn't until much later I learned about how it's
because Castlevania 5 was it was um why can't the name slips me not symphony night but the one before
it Rondo blood blood oh blood crammed into a Super Nintendo cartridge and it wasn't Castlevania 5
it was actually listed as Dracula X Oh was it I thought they called it five here they it was
Dracula I think it made might have like given it a subtitle is Super Castlevania 5 yeah cuz Super
Castlevania 4 was the redo of the first one but it wasn't really a redo sort of it was first style
yeah but um but yeah Dracula X was in fact I've got the box and manual and everything but nothing
is as awesome as playing the damn game on the PC Engine because oh my god I remember you brought
fucking epic you brought that over to our we listen to the beginning in gothic German with
the when the girl gets stabbed oh god that game is awesome and oh my god playing through the game
is fucking Maria singing the entire time okay she gets a special attack wouldn't you get the the
him where I think what Richard does is throw it at people or some shit like that she starts singing
and her singing is so bad it kill things are you finished no that games fucking awesome alright
lastly Jason over on Google Plus says I tried playing Lords of Shadow the first one and I
wasn't pleased I made it through four distinct levels before giving up at the shadow of Colossus
ripoff lol I love Castlevania I've always loved Castlevania I got a late start on the series and
played Symphony of the Night before I even played the Nintendo and Super Nintendo versions but I
enjoyed them all I enjoyed practically every 2d Castlevania and have fond memories of Castlevania
64 what but any more modern 3d Castlevania than that just hasn't attracted me that is some by the
way I wasn't able to read them all tonight because we had a lot of long answers but please check out
all of our answers at our Facebook community facebook.com slash orange lounge radio and also
google.com slash plus orange lounge radio for the other answers over there thanks to everybody
that answered the question this week what a shit once and for all in chat what's that how many
syllables vampire has oh no remember Castlevania judgment um don't know no I don't it never
existed it never existed in my universe la la la la that was the beginning of the end you know what
you know what you know what we need to just like just completely play through Rondo blood at my
house break out the the turbo duo get some Rondo on it would be nice if we finally got one of these
gaming marathons I've been talking about doing for five years off the ground and they're right
all right let's move on we got more news to get to and your calls and emails pretty soon here but
starting off with Loki so the oh yeah has done a lot of weird made a lot of weird decisions lately
in making itself irrelevant but now they're doing I guess I want to call this almost like the final
nail in the coffin but they're now dropping the free to try requirement for developers because you
may remember when the OUYA came out all the games around the OUYA had a free component to them so
you can at least try them out now that's not required so now basically it's the Android
marketplace on a really shitty console that now you can also play those games on other things
including maybe soon PC so what's the point again tell me do you regret your decision to back that
Kickstarter ah yes I do but at least I got to try the console out for a while and I mean I made
most of my money back so hey ladies again extended rental it was a it was a rental it was a red box
but a silver box yeah it's like when I used to rent consoles and I got to try it too so it worked
out yeah so I got to laugh at it but yeah I don't know why they would do that but whatever um also
apparently Disney interactive they are scaling back and that story was left over from last week
oh I'm sorry how was my bad on the Cheryl tonight sorry fired I knew there'd be a mistake I knew we
would come to the new studio and there'd be some damn mistake well this it was just that not worse
the best part is we can edit that out we do it live here at all our fuck it we'll do it live
well I just want to reiterate from last week that Disney interactive is making less games
because you know what they made like what one game last year you know one console game Disney
infinity oh I'm sorry two games there's planes to like everybody else social so social is huge
on social yeah and so you know what's gonna happen now there's not gonna be planes this year so fuck
you people that like planes you're only getting get Disney infinity too if that ever comes out
which it probably will because it made a lot of money all right anyway moving on to more recent
news and things that are upcoming to the PlayStation 4 apparently pre-loading is supposed
to be a thing that's coming to the PlayStation 4 I thought this was something that was already
available on games but I guess not sucker punch which of course is the studio behind infamous
second son said on Twitter that this is a feature that's coming later in the spring there was a
tweet that said quote no preload until April this of course a response to all the people that wanted
to play infamous second son which I know none of us were able to talk about during our gaming
weeks none of us have played it I know my buddy Shane's been playing it a lot he really likes
it a lot he says he said it reminds him of crackdown it looks like it looks good I need to
try that I never really got into the other games but no no I it's making it sound really good so
I have to check that out but anyway yeah sucker punch said that in the tweet no preload until
April so this could mean that future games will be something you can digitally download and then
play on the launch day I don't know what big games are coming out in April I know there's
Final Fantasy 14 but that's a little different being an MMO so yeah I don't know I don't know
but that'll be cool that people can download the games and then play them at midnight on the launch
day as a lot of people will be doing with Diablo 3 this week I'm sure dark soccer so this is just
I really had to bring this article up just because of something that Bioware Montreal's game designer
Munvir Hare was bringing about he actually did a talk at game developers conference called
misogyny racism and homophobia where do video games stand basically challenging this whole we
only develop male characters because only guys or the majority of our market are guys he said
and this is a from here that it's cynical to assume that an audience isn't capable of embracing
a gay character in any way and that more exclusive female protagonists that aren't glorified sex
objects and have personalities beyond supporting the men in the game that it's a good thing I mean
basically is bringing up you know the female Shepherd who you know there's a yeah okay well
is it 15% of the players had a female Shepherd but still you got a lot more I think attention
with her in the third Mass Effect which was about the best thing about the game and I mean they're
basically saying you know the people are arguing that women weren't soldiers in medieval times but
there actually is plenty of historical evidence that women were would fight and that in other
cultures outside of our typical Eurocentric video game you know focus that there were plenty of
female warriors in other cultures so it was really really good you know but the best thing that I
think came out of this that he's quoted saying is let's not be scared to ruffle feathers and let's
be open and honest about our intentions let's push and engage in a new discourse as a result
of these dynamics and let's do all of this because we are current what we are currently doing is
absolutely not working it's about damn time I'm trying to see if some of our chatters have some
comments on this Seattle in our chat room says everybody loves Samus not counting other M hey
you know there's some people that like other M as well you know well I think that it's it's I mean
but but I mean he's right it's sad that it needs to be said it's not like females aren't accepted
as huge big important video game characters like you have you know Samus like you have Lara Croft
like you have I mean heck Princess Peach in a way you know is well I mean you know people were
excited to be able to play as her I know that might be a bit of a stretch but femshep and you
know so on well and I'm not I'm not like saying it's perfect by any means but I'm just saying
that like you know it's not like they can't there shouldn't be that fear to have the female lead
because there's plenty of very successful ones well and it's not just the female lead it's having
other sexual not just sexualities but having a gender sexuality of race you know even religion
I mean we finally have had a few Muslim characters pop up here and there we need more I think you
know I'm gonna say Co C's characters of color you know we need more people and we need to actually
have where I like being able to make have your character and make the choice but I like having
other characters that interact with it also have you know not just oh we're gonna do whatever
because you're the main character but I'd like to see other characters that are strictly like like
I hate to go back to Mass Effect 3 on this one but how are you had trainer or you had Steve you
know they were very firmly in their sexuality you know yet you had plenty of other characters
who didn't matter you know but my point is is that it needs to be recognized that you have people
coming from all sorts of walks and you know I really hate using the word preference because
it's something that's you're born with something that's ingrained and preference to me denotes a
choice you know so I've had a lot of people say identity yeah well but I look at identity
as yourself and not necessarily what you know organs you like to play with if that makes sense
well I like the church organ well you know what I hate organs so you'd like to play the piano
exactly anyway anyway now I'm a flautist cuz I flout it uh-huh but let's say they release I
don't know Halo 5 with a gay master or you know gay master chief or whatever like good I mean
this is what I would say no there's gonna be a lot of people out there that are gonna have
something to say it's not that I don't I don't hear me wrong on this I mean I would love something
like that but I also am a realist where there's a lot of people that would be like you know here
would be my problem with Master Chief as in the character that has existed through these games
there's a cannon established and I'm really fine with keeping a character cannon if say that there
was a much future Halo game much you know later on in the future and it's a new Master Chief and
he happened to light the cock fine I don't care that'd be great I don't really think people need
to be judged by you know what bits they like poking in their bits I don't think it should
matter and it's no one's fucking business yeah it really is no one's fucking business and I hate the
whole concept of closets and in and out of closets because who the fuck cares I don't care what parts
people like to play with well unfortunately there's too many people out there that do in
this people suck but my whole point is that I don't care if this X person has a wife or if she's got a
girlfriend on the side or if it's a big open marriage and there's a bunch of fucking going
on under what I don't give a shit don't give a shit and I would like to see more characters
or stuff like that it doesn't matter it doesn't matter what their sexuality is it doesn't matter
who they fuck I'd like to see a whole lot of fucking going on to you would you for no but I
think it doesn't matter it shouldn't matter it should matter what their skin color is what
matters is that yes this creates who this person is we respect that these are the things that make
this person who they are but it should just be a oh okay that's cool that's who you are I don't
need I don't care you know if you know what I mean not that it's not a doesn't matter kind of thing
but that it's a that's who they are I respect it let's keep moving all right I'm going to some first
a question from our chat room from our buddy Shana Lenko Jamie would you consider male Shep being
straight cannon since until Mass Effect 3 he never was interested in men just women which would mean
they fundamentally changed me I to tell Jason I didn't say what bits with their bits I said what
bits in their bits oh because some people like it in the ass and some people like it in the badge
okay some people like it in other things I don't care because you all right but what about Shane's
question god damn it would you consider male Shep being being straight cannon since until Mass
Effect 3 he never was interested in men just women which would mean they fundamentally changed him
that's kind of an interesting one because I think that they realized that it shouldn't have been a
thing to begin with technically your Shep doesn't have to have sex at all or doesn't have to have
your set you can have can be asexual I could totally have an asexual Shepherd except Garris
but you know what I mean if you if Rex was available I'd totally go for that if you could
resist Garris's temptations you could have a completely asexual Shepherd I tried once Rob I
really did try and I tried to play a bro Shep so I could get Caden uh-huh and I couldn't play him
because no all right going to s to 100 Matt because I like this day I like what see I'll just said
put my bits in your bites as she went under Matt says progress takes time it took a long time for
there to be female protagonists and film movies books etc video games with the in-depth storylines
are somewhat of a new media but what does what does bother me is that given how much we've
progressed as a society that it would be quicker but again progress takes time and I actually kind
of agree with us Joe and under Matt I think I think we'll get there and I I still I think the
only way we're going to get there is if we keep hooping and hollering and talking about it and
having this dialogue that's how we're going to get there but I just wish it wasn't necessary I have
faith that we will get there I mean but look at look at what the indie gaming scene is already I
mean you have things like gone home you have you say was here pitching Dominique Pamplemousse which
you know to tackle some very some issues you you don't really see in games otherwise you know and
so on so it's starting in the indie scene for the record by the way to add another thing to what
Shane asked in my own headcanon as far as I could get away with playing a broshep he was totally
whacking off to Caden it's a picture totally whacking it because honestly I like the Caden
romance with a broshep a lot more than I do with a female Shepherd Tiger Claw in chat says what
would Shepherd be like if he or she was transgender the same be Shepherd Shepherd with bits that don't
quite fit of course in the future hopefully they would have much better corrective surgery for that
I I'm wondering if maybe Tiger Claw means there could be a because you know how some folks prefer
to use gender-neutral language like neither he nor she you you they or Z you know a different term
but that's not really possible in Mass Effect but I think I think we also have to look at you know
like say on Facebook there's what 50 different ways you can identify your gender it might be a
bit much for a video game to have 50 different branching options I mean you know yeah you do
have to kind of and not that I'm saying that we shouldn't you know have transgender representation
I absolutely think that would be a great thing but as the designer does kind of have to choose
at some point you know what are the possible branches for these characters and I think down
the line we're definitely especially as technology catches up but for the most part and this is
another sad thing too I think that while the developers were trying really trying to be more
open and basically throw more of a bone to you know I really think trying to push some limits
they're trying to be a lot more respectful of people in their lives we still have a very binary
viewpoint when it comes to gender you know just in general it's hard to change you know having
centuries of that beaten into your culture and then have it turn around it's still pretty you
know instinctive to say he or she instead of realize that that what you see may not be what
you get so it's another thing that just has to be tackled but I'm saying that for now it's to be
expected but I don't think it should be expected much later on if that makes sense sure all right
well I'm sure there's plenty more comments on this but I would have to direct those to our email bag
which is participate at orange laundry calm if you'd like to participate further in the discussion
but in the meantime in the interest of time we're going to tackle some other news stories so going
over to Loki all right so this is kind of interesting kind of all part of the I guess
evolution to the steam service but they're adding a virtual reality mode to I guess the latest steam
beta and what that's gonna do originally you would have to add a command line dash VR to enable it
but now they actually have a button for it and it's I guess meant for head mounted displays like
the oculus rift and so it has an ear face I think is from what I hear is similar to like the big
picture mode but you know it's meant for VR displays so it's interesting I don't know I
guess obviously it's something they're gonna need you know if they're gonna be you know forward
thinking so be kind of curious to see what that looks like I don't know hmm well I guess this is
just in time for this headset craze that's growing right yeah well if I remember correctly I think
the valve was kind of working with you know oculus maybe a little bit and you know just some of their
ideas with I remember I read a comment about like they're saying increasing like the frame rate or
something or doing something with the it was some sort of different method for displaying pixels
that allowed you to get a lot less motion blur and basically involve them displaying an image
and then flashing to black almost so that you don't have that kind of streaking effect with
you know pixels being left on the screen or something of course I'm just talking out of my
ass right now but that I remember reading but Bobby says that there in in chat he's saying
that all these news sites that are running this story are getting it from a reddit post and so he
actually links us to the reddit post how funny it's his own it's his own post so Bobby Bobby's
the one that posted this to read it and yeah I said FYI steam beta now has a VR mode in view
menu no command-line argument needed how fight good job Bobby why didn't you break that news
over a vog network like oh I'd you have to give that one to read it it's fine it's funny though
but they didn't source them and they never source read it but my god now half of half of what
Facebook has on it like comes from like BuzzFeed they owe read it a lot of money let's be real it's
ridiculous what sites run I mean shit sometimes they run stories based on like random people's
Twitter posts I just don't understand it sometimes that's hilarious yeah well let me let me read the
rest of what Bobby submitted to the or the reddit here which he submitted oculus is reddit it's
still just big picture mode on a curved screen but it works pretty well for what it is when I
first tried it it required me to do some monitor trickery with the rift on an extended monitor and
it was very flaky now it works with my normal setup and works immediately for those that never
tried it you'll need to opt into the steam client beta and have steam VR installed from tools I'm
also opted into the beta branch of steam VR but I'm not positive if that's required for the new
version or not so hmm good job body he's going viral and not even he says is it says the logo
is that's true you do have the little vog logo next to your submission there that's pretty cool
all right well moving on to some other news this this I am NOT getting from reddit but directly
from the website of the creators of the game this kind of goes back to one of those the dangers of
kickstarters stories again the game was called super action squad that at one point was super
retro squad and coming from the website here exploding rabbit.com it says quote super action
squad is too big of a project for us to handle right now so we're putting it on hold to make
some smaller games first we will resume development on SAS or sass once we are in a better position to
make it the reasons for this decision including why the original Kickstarter was a bad idea in
the first place are explained in detail below not going to read the entire post but I'll read some
of the bullet points here it boiled down to inexperience lack of understanding and scope
unrealistic estimate of cost being part of an ineffective team which I thought was a pretty
ballsy thing to write about unity is not a good tool for 2d platformers which I don't know if I
agree with that I don't yeah I don't either because it's kind of one of those things where
it's like well you shouldn't have kickstarted a game that you didn't know that you should have
tested the system first I don't know if I buy that either well here's the thing it's like I think a
lot of it his main excuse was like he's used to programming in flash and then going to unity was
completely different but I think aside from creating the engine I wouldn't think it would
be that difficult to be able to port everything else so obviously it is I mean just because you
I don't know they had but yeah I mean going from taking you know creating was it Super Mario
crossover and just basically grabbing pre-made levels and pre-made assets and all that stuff to
creating your own stuff which let's be honest it's just kind of slight changes to the sprites of you
know Super Mario crossover it's Super Mario crossover retail version minus all the Mario
and Nintendo stuff because we'll get sued well there's also a section in the post called what
do differently and I think this is interesting just a little quote from this section quote the
thing is though knowing what I know now I would have never launched a Kickstarter for the game
as my first project it makes little sense for a team with little to no experience that has never
worked together to try and make a big game it would be much better to focus on something small
and simple after getting experience releasing small projects we would be able to work our way
up to bigger ones so they you know and no real word on what's gonna happen all those people that
gave money although they are saying you know they kind of say a little bit vaguely in the post you
know if you were a big donator contact us we'll work something out we're not unreasonable but
they're talking about they can't really do refunds right now probably because the money's already
been spent you know people in the Kickstarter comments are pretty bad yeah I will of course
but this is this is part of the dangers of Kickstarter this is why I've always been very
nervous to get in on that craze and there's still really only a hand for you to think
him I can probably count on one hand the number of projects I've given to so all right anyway I
could probably also count on one hand the number of emails we received this week but that's okay
we love hearing from our listeners even when it's only a couple of them I know when they're
wrong you can you cannot you oh you can email us anytime you like participate at orange lounge
radio.com oh what's coming up tonight our saga nothing all right hello LR I've listened to the
to the shortened episode this weekend I must say I appreciate you guys taking the time to record
something during your busy schedule I very much enjoyed listening to it and I think it's great
that snake was mentioned as it truly is a classic game I also very much appreciate you guys
mentioning snake 360 and it's still in development as you read this sequel however there was a yyr
however there was one big inaccuracy in what was said during the episode that simply cannot let
pass Oh cinnamon toast crust cereal is a hundred percent naturally flavored and does not contain
any fake cinnamon yes big red gum and other things containing fake cinnamon aren't the truly gross
gum in general is gross anyway but but only a hundred percent cinnamon and sugar present every
bite along with 15 essential vitamins and minerals it's true that some people who shower name
mainly seen as me are fully entitled to their incorrect to keep the fuck but let it be placed
on record that cinnamon toast crunch cereal is officially yummy and delicious keeping it real
yyr and you know what I still think it tastes like balls so I agree with the statement until
you put it in milk and then it just kind of dissolves and it just because yeah I think
it's the in milk part that really just made it very much with cinnamon and milk I mean it's
here's what I do a cinnamon toast I don't eat any cereal with milk I'm weird I I have one cup
like a giant cup we're talking like 40 ounce cup full of cinnamon toast crunch a second cup with
milk you just eat them separate it's still good but it's a way better than if it was soaking in
milk yyr I would you know I don't do this very often on the show but I would like to apologize
for dark soccer's behavior unless I would like you to sit and spin and golden grams golden
shit it is shit it is not shit it is the shit I I will I will not allow the woman to comment
on breakfast cereal again you know what okay but mind you mind you what did I say my favorite
breakfast cereals were as a child you liked great great night like weird total and crackling oat
bran but at least you pooped regularly I did poop regularly okay granted okay there were two kids
we know she's not full of shit see okay and by the way there were two shut up oh my god
yeah Rob but there were two kids cereals that I did like one was Apple Jack's which tasted
nothing like fucking apples Apple Jack's is kind of dumb I don't like it oh god you're a horrible
person who would eat like kicks I never understood that it's like eating packing peanuts I mean it's
seriously gross kicks is gross but what I'll agree with you there honeycomb fuck that shit
all right the other one was I really liked Rice Krispies I felt when they made Rice Krispies
treats a cereal okay but I would have to eat my Rice Krispies like super fast because I hated
that soggy shit at the bottom oh my god why are we talking about fucking sir I'm hungry now thanks
Rob I'm hungry you know what I saw at the store I couldn't free pizza today and it was great we
bought $200 worth of groceries today to stock our new house I saw you had food in your fridge for
change right and one of the one of the things we were looking at getting was you know Ritz crackers
or one of my favorite snacks right do you know they have bacon flavored Ritz cracker what it's
probably not very good you know what I found huh when I was at a total wine looking for I was going
to go get some frivolous and they were out of frivolous the fuckers bacon wine they had bacon
maple donut beer that sounds amazing I was like the fuck is this no so I bought sticky toffee
beer instead next email oh my god so it's very short it's from someone named Travis which I'm
not I don't have a nickname so I'm not gonna use that Travis Donovan no it's not Oh Disney
and Pixar sing let it go and we have a link we're not playing it I love you but no oh you
know what though that video was all over Facebook I saw that one I liked the one though where the
guy who does all the different Disney voices just as impersonations saying like in 20 different
characters voices that was pretty freaking cool yeah but I thought thanks regionator that's
fucking gross I think it's time however what did he say Apple Jack's plus dark soccer's grape
nuts crackling oat bran equals jack shit oh shut up damn it now I lost my train of thought I had
I had something to contribute oh yes okay thank you I think it is time to let go of let it go
like I'm officially sick of that song like let's stop stop it I was singing it in the middle of
Target and Berkeley no I'm done I'm done with all the parodies I'm done with all the knockoffs
I'm done you stop it she's a flawless goddess I don't know what it is then I haven't actually
heard this don't have children and you don't know what the frozen is I know a frozen is I
just haven't heard this song Dan hasn't watched it either and I need to fix that oh yeah we always
hang up on Loki before the fortune cookie when you've been playing knockoffs lately anyway I
didn't do in this time I did something for Frogger all right fine reginator you know what thank you
sit down you are you in the corner reginator because I don't think you are you need to get
back in the corner where you were you know what I'm I've decided from here on out the
Drew's joke book is retired you know I work with you now right yeah I do I've told our intern drew
I think we're about ready to promote him to a mailroom mm-hmm so he can just do the mail
for me mm-hmm reginator is now the holder of the toilet paper joke book reginator you're the
intern now that's quite the promotion all right you were the holder of the toilet paper either
speaking of the holder of toilet paper is there any more emails I need to go home and watch frozen
don't judge me part is why are you why do you have Mario on your butt it's a pillow and I'm
using it for my back leave me alone participate plus it's something my ex got me in Hong Kong I
don't exactly value this oh that ex yeah the Republican one that one well that wasn't the
main problem Jamie it was just one of many and as the Republican this yes who had this the yeah
well here's because I don't want to make it sound like I can't be friends with you if you think a
certain way politically is this totally not true but it's just the whole thing like he actually
ran for political office and all that stuff but anyway let's not talk about him because he's long
gone and they're better yeah let it go that's right let it go let it go down the drain all
right we'll bury Rob's ex in the snow I've been making up my own lyrics to the song
after the past month does live in Reno now no all right anyhow is that it for emails as every
notice yes participate at orange laundry comms a place to send emails let's get to the F use the
week
so I don't know because I've had a pretty fucking amazing day okay I just got my fiat and there's
an armrest and the armrest fell off I mean it's not a major thing and it's something that they'll
fix because I'm in like the first 30 days singing in Carmack Carmack's is pretty awesome but oh my
god fuck you too delicious gluten-free pizza and the fact that I want more of it and I was I had
no willpower I ate like shit yesterday and I had carby stuff and I had carby stuff today and I'm
just gonna have to go on a meat fest for the next week and I have to go back to the gym and I don't
like go to the gym by myself but I gotta I gotta go back to the gym who wants to spot for me at
the gym you are some lazy bitches I can't click on YouTube links to mama iPad bandwidth all right
is that it Loki I asked you if that was it I just thought of something you bitches need to see
prison so sucks it makes me feel more tired than I am that's it my F you of the week goes to sinus
infections because I've had one since Tuesday as I mentioned earlier in the show and it sucks it
is ruining my life and it needs to stop and I also want to give a second F you to dark Sakura hey I
didn't give you a sinus infection but you made them popular you know what the jazzling is popular
are you getting it done are you getting pea-jazzled you know I know about getting ass-jazzled but I
guess not well we'll talk to Exeter for about you know ass bleaching and stuff like that but it'd
be like be jazzled you don't say and this is your first time listening to orange does radio I'm
fucking sorry I'm sorry that you've had to put up with this shit it is so good for Loki to be back
in the studio I feel like this is I mean yes Skype works but it doesn't work the same I'm just saying
all right anyhow getting back into some gaming news Loki so speaking about Kickstarter and how
it's a terrible idea to back game projects you you Suzuki is researching the idea but not yet
decided if he's going to kickstart Shenmue 3 which I can tell you right now if that were to
be put on the Kickstarter would probably be approved immediately so research a little quicker
but yeah so I don't know that would be kind of neat to see him put you know Shenmue 3 on there
does he own the rights to that or is it still Sega I I don't know I think the license yeah I thought
we had a story just a couple that yeah we just had a story a couple weeks ago the the licensing
expired the trademark I don't know that so it is open season now all right moving on to one more
story about a game a lot of people are looking forward to in fact if this game doesn't show up
at e3 this year I don't know what Nintendo's gonna do it will be cut bitches III think so but it has
to do with the Wii U version version the Wii U version in order to save this system I'm gonna
need to sacrifice three virgins all right now the Wii U version of the Legend of Zelda and the
producer eg Anuma has made some interesting comments about the Wii U version of the Legend
of Zelda and that could be that there may be a top-down view in these future Zelda games because
you know top-down was the way the old Zelda game with at least the very first Zelda game was then
of course linked to the past and you know link between worlds is kind of brought that back a
little bit but we haven't I mean the console ones involved in 3d ever since you know ocarina so could
the top-down view return and let's see the official Nintendo magazine had an interview and the
question the interviewer asked what did you learn from making this game can you use any of these
ideas in future titles for example the merge with walls ability and is amazing and it would be a
shame if it was never used again and he says I think the top-down view made the ability to enter
the wall really interesting also in this game I feel we found a new direction in regards to the
potential use of the good old top-down view for Zelda it's the kind of point we will take in good
consideration when thinking about the next Zelda game I think people might be reading into that
quote a little too much but when you consider that there's a second screen I could definitely
see some sort of like maybe like top-down map view in addition to what you're seeing on the screen I
think would be a very logical extension or dungeon maps certainly on your or your Wii U screen I
think there's certainly potential for top-down things to come into that that map or in the the
second screen if nothing else so all right my game guru and Chad at live dot vog network
dot-com says oh god they're making a new four swords game aren't they hey you never know you
never know what you're pretty popular though weren't they yeah yeah I think so they're giving
it away for free on 3ds for a little bit twice oh my god I know we had another unicorn in chat
mmm Zuck is actually in chat he's in chat good times live that you should be in chat to live
dot vog network yeah everyone why aren't you there all right because they're listening during the
week while they're at work or on their commute or what have you which is fine but you know come join
us on some Sarah says some Saturday night who we won't be here on Saturday another show will be
which is fine but Sunday hey we are here and you should come join us for a live show sometime all
right anyhow let us get to that was the last story so we're gonna open up the skype line I
think now's the time one eight seven seven game olr our username on skype orange lounge radio and
while we wait for some calls to come in I don't know if Loki has any last-minute stories but I
can also go to our Twitter as well at twitter.com slash olr Loki not really much there's a rumor
that Rainbow Six Patriots isn't redesigned from the ground up three times so that doesn't mean
it's coming out anytime soon that I don't really have it's slow slow news week which is weird
because game developers conference was this week but then again that means that's that's because
you know again it's not a news conference so nobody's developing right now cuz they're all
at the conference not all of them I know seriously like one of the shows I watch cooking with unity
they've been off this week because he's at gay only I was about to like where are you guys you'd
be off a game developers conference if you give you do anyway we have a call hi you're on orange
launch radio who's this it is jammer Jay you guys hear me yeah hey jammer Jay what's up but nothing
nothing much I just actually I'm listening to the song I'm the show live it's been quite a
while listening to it live well welcome back thanks for being here hello well the darks occur
it's like what you want to share with our listeners tonight do you have a question or a statement or
what oh yeah it was like so here's a question I've been going over it cuz this happened to me
the other week so what happens when your backlog like you have something that's on your backlog
like basically I had like Final Fantasy x2 it was all my backlog for these two so long that they
didn't HD they did each HD remake I still haven't got to it but it's been like 14 years so when you
have all these games in your backlog does it just become like a collection or a vault it's like yeah
hi yeah I I have had games and I hate to admit this cuz I'm so gonna get judged for it I have
games that I bought the day they came out and they're still sealed because that's how bad my
gamer a DD is okay so that's what it takes I have the same thing too it's like I have games still
shrink wrapped and they're like from previous like there's stuff on ps2 that I think I would
get to one day but that one day hasn't happened like in ten years it's like wow yeah no you're
not alone I can tell you that I do it too I don't know if any of our chatters want to admit to that
as well over at live that vog network calm but dark soccer you're the most ultimate collector
of them all do you have games that you like you played once or like you've like never even played
but you just like hey I gotta have this remember the games I have that are still in shrink wrap so
yes yes do you remember any up top of your head um I don't think I've opened my copy of death
smiles and I have the special edition um feel my Saturn RPGs a couple PlayStation games I don't
actually I think that one of my copies of Space Channel five part two is still shrink wrapped
because I had the Japanese one and I haven't played my copy of Bayonetta yet so you're not
alone jammer Jay there's plenty of us that have the same problem now let me ask you this are you
gonna finally check out tend to and are you gonna check out your original PlayStation 2 version or
if you just said I forget it at this point I'll just play the the new HD remake I I think I'm
just gonna play the new HD remake because my actual x2 is like the international version but
I never got past the intro to see if the rest of the game was in English or not I think I do have
another x2 copy of 10 to Jamie bonkers over here it's not to give up too much information I am one
of dark sikora's now I'm one of her co-workers in the land of cubicles so land of cubes low cat in
the house yeah okay does it drive you then crazy when people say I asked I don't think if I could
I I hear people say it but that's not what it is and people drive me crazy when they do anything
X when it's supposed to be 10 I've gotten like and I blame Bobby for this now actually because
of this whole gif thing but I still call it gif because I can pronounce things properly yes but
now I hit stun says Mega Man x2 was a great game that one actually is an X because that's a legit
X yeah because it's a prototype yeah but like what gets nevermind I'm just not gonna say anything
else you almost had her going all right the jammer Jay is there anything else you want to share
with others tonight so now at this point it has become a collection I guess the backlog if it goes
back more than 10 years like that if it goes back more than 10 years you know if it's still shrink
wrapped you could consider selling it on eBay depending how common or uncommon it is otherwise
you know what hold on to it as a memory to quit wasting your freaking money I know there's like
some like C titles that I have like in the backlog doll I think like Dark Sector for 360 I think Loki
might have planned it I don't know no one else has ever heard of it I have a copy for some reason
haven't I haven't played it but I actually still have tchotchkes from like a few years ago from it
oh my gosh oh that's what I was gonna let you guys know I was gonna ask you about I was gonna
send a donation of like swag if I needed to downsize some video game swag so I was gonna
send it to you guys so you guys can give it away to listen listeners yeah get in touch with me
outside the show we'll work that out I think give you my address already oh good you'll have to send
it to me like in email or something like that or in chat in chat at low cat all right sounds good
all right I'm gonna I'm gonna let you go jammer so we can get more calls but they just call it in
and welcome welcome back to the live show get no problem take care buddy you too all right bye
one eight seven seven game olr or a username on Skype orange lounge radio all one word if you
want to call into the show and chat with us about whatever we've talked about tonight or maybe you
have your own topic Loki did you have anything else no all right let me see if I can pull up
the Twitter is really fast what stop stealing my diseases sorry I'm finding this longer the
show's going on the harder time I'm having with my voice so I may have to call it a little a little
earlier tonight but we'll see here moving on let's go to another call because it is lighting up here
hi you're on orange launch radio who's this yeah this is raging leader no if it isn't our newest
intern intern rage inator how you liking the new joke book loving it what's up buddy uh just two
questions but I'm willing to bet that the answers are gonna be kind of long-winded if my guess is
right um you know the first one have you ever been have you ever known you know people not to
basically we're like a better work petition three companies to get certain games onto steam and be
successful about it oh to get a game on steam and be successful about it um not not like green light
word you know where copies is basically say hey we're thinking about bring this game I would you
buy it whereas we we the consumer folks down well I think are you're talking probably about like
these Sega games they have a bunch of positions going on try to get a bunch of different Sega
games ported the PC and I think on steam but I think for most companies nowadays that aside
from EA but they probably want their game on steam and so it's not really an issue of oh I have to
convince you to put your already you know available PC game on steam usually they want to be on steam
with the exceptions of you know some of them are there on EA's origin service or you know like in
the case of like Mojang and stuff that has you know he's doing well enough by himself he doesn't
need steam oh all right yeah you know the reason I bring it up is because I was commenting to dr.
her the other day you know speech at that it's kind of a crying shame that aside from metal
gelt metal slug three there's not really anything by SNK on service so I thought there was a king of
fighters one of the recent king of fighters game oh oh yeah you're absolutely right you're
absolutely right I completely forgot about that that's all right it's a big store it's easy to
get lost in yeah really now as far as my second question you know it goes it's probably more
geared towards a Loki because he's more of the builder expert in some group now when you were
building your cabinets you know be your main campus or what have you what god you know like
joysticks and monitors aside what kind of materials did you use did you use like parker board or well
it's mainly MDF for it I mean depends on the size you know I my first main cabinet which was
an ultimate arcade to cabinet it was made with three quarters at MDF it was actually supposed
to have been I think 5 8 or something which made it a lot heavier than it needed to be so
is is basically MDF but I mean I don't know it all depends on how you're trying to you know what
you're doing with it like if you're painting it or if you're gonna you know put a laminate on it
or you know whatever but usually they're out of MDF or some sort of plywood just because you know
MDF does tend to be a little bit weak sometimes especially if you have really heavy the other
thing too is like you know if I were to go back and do it again I wouldn't have done like kind of
a classic arcade cabinet I would have wanted it more like you know the view Lex cabinets and stuff
where it's just control panel and HDTV because honestly trying to get stuff you know running on
low enough resolution though you know work with a TV or you know a monitor or something like that
it's just a pain in the ass it's a lot easier just to have a nice HD screen because then you can do a
lot more with it you can you play indie games on it or whatever and you know may not be as classic
as you you know you have it a main cabinet but it's a hell a lot cheaper and probably a hell a
lot easier to make I want to say I spent three grand on that first cabinet really wish I hadn't
built it yeah honestly no I've been kind of sort of toying with the idea of building y'all a
candidate but it you know if I do build ones could be like big the basic shell of the cabinet they
would look like basically like y'all your classic arcade candidate from the 80s or early 90s yeah
probably make it out so I kind of went for lemon on the sides and what that in for like a martyr I
would probably use like a flat screen LCD monitor or TV yeah off the shelf Bob you know fight stick
and then just so I don't like I get my computer to overheat because lack of circulation ever off
the side yeah no that way I can't really skip y'all play our key game especially if I were
played like something like Street Fighter 4 or what have you well the other thing you can do
too is actually just get an old arcade cabinet and just convert that over it might even be cheaper
and it's already been built up nice and there's a lot of people on you know not even necessarily
eBay bond Craigslist they're willing to get rid of those things for like a hundred bucks or less
or even you know a couple hundred dollars to pay on the condition dark soccer you guys had like a
pole position machine in your house at one point it was like a converted thing like that right we
did yeah we um made our yeah our main was built out of the pole position which for a while doubled
as Shermie's house that's awesome an arcade cabinet is a cat house it's actually kind of
because okay the stand-up one had the pedal so sure me would just walk in with where we had no
pedal yeah and that was just her house it's like I live in an arcade cabinet now you go Shermie
that is amazing all right and the rage inator by the way since we see him on video he's petting
his kitty right now is in the background there hi Anakin all right oh he looked all right
rage nader I'm gonna let you go buddy so we can wrap up the show but thanks for the call
yeah take care of you too bye I am actually gonna close up the Skype line I'm sorry I didn't end up
taking more calls tonight but I do kind of need to take a little break because I'm finding the
longer we're going on I'm like more sinus pressure that's not good I think it's time for pills so I
want to quickly shout out some of these tweets we got here at twitter.com slash olr by the way
if you didn't get through and you do have something to say please do email us we'd love to hear from
you I mean dark soccer only had like two emails to read tonight and one of them was like a line
long so give her work next week y'all participate whatever what let it go stop I'm gonna throw this
cell phone at you I don't even care all right just a few tweets here that I want to read a
few stories that were submitted s2100 Matt sent us a tweet about the ET 2600 game landfill site
dig documentary is put on hold by New Mexico authorities really oh the Popo is shutting it
down I guess they didn't like the idea of people going out there digging it all up hmm I think we
referenced this early in the show but Tiger Claw says this link to a story about how Nintendo has
50 unity games on their way to Wii U but can they can they sell well alongside Mario I mean is the
question absolutely can I think that I think they can too because what I buy Mario what else you're
gonna buy well well but I hear the games are doing really well on Wii U too because of the fact that
they don't get lost in the marketplace like they kind of do on the other systems so I mean there
is that and lastly Tiger Claw says this is a link Microsoft saying DirectX 12 will improve Xbox one
performance um that's that's not too surprising I mean you know sometimes these firmware updates
and things will help the systems run better right and so when we're talking about something like
DirectX which is basically you know Xbox that whole name Xbox comes from DirectX something
I mean that's no surprise that should help things but wouldn't that be akin to like a graphics
driver update or something like it might it might make a few things better here and there but it's
not gonna like radically change your experience um it's actually supposed to improve frame rate
is better and you know they're talking about fours of five and stuff and saying it was like 60 I
thought fours of five is already 60 frames per second but I guess they're talking about how you
know they use it to improve fours of fives performance and stuff and how it's supposed to
have a lot less overhead so you know a lot less processing power is required to do the same stuff
so that will help because you know a lot of these you know Xbox one games are having trouble hitting
1080p I mean it's a lot of the 720 you know upscale and they're having trouble hitting 60
frames per second so anything can help and hopefully DirectX you know 12 will get you
where it needs to be on par with like the PlayStation 4 all right sounds good well that
is going to wrap up another edition of orange lounge radio our first from the brand new studio
and seven and hopefully first of many many more episodes to come as we lead into probably our
next big show would be in June we will have our 12th anniversary episode here at studio and seven
so that'll be fun so anyway I want to thank all you guys for listening to the show tonight and
those of you that are listening live thanks for participating with our show we really appreciate
it those of you that are listening to us through whatever podcasting device you use be it your phone
the iTunes or Android apps such as stitcher or whatever it is we really want to appreciate you
guys for taking time out to listening to our show please help us spread the word about orange
entre do we don't ask for your money to do the show although you know I do we wouldn't turn down
but you know no but but in all seriousness we really don't ask for your money to do the show
and all we ask tell a friend or five or 20 about the show and help spread the word I do accept pink
berry of course you do of course you do they have a new flavor yet isn't it a new month right now
they had hot chocolate that's it's they key lime is a new flavor I was just there today too but
that's really good I want blood orange to be back now me too anyway they're not giving us money we
need to stop talking about them until they give us money we're holding our endorsements like that's
gonna happen right hey do you know how many of our listeners I I get emails and messages that
people try it because they hear it on our show so you know we've had it might be a small impact
we've had an impact so anyway and that that's all thanks to you guys who do listen and come out and
participate with the show we really appreciate it and yeah thank you so we'll be back to do it
again next week until then let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts Loki great to see
you back here in person I don't be back and I hope I'm back next I hope the wife gives you
permission to stay do you have any final thoughts for us tonight I hope the baby's not too screaming
right now okay hurry home and find out dark soccer your final thought tonight I won't sing
you sure I already sang ones on the show that's all the singing you get for a year and my final
thought tonight is I need to go sit in a hot steam to clear up my sinuses right now hot steam sounds
awesome not like steam like the video game service on PC's although you know that steam's pretty cool
too but I want some old-school steam and so I think I'm gonna go get some I want the live
listeners to stay tuned in I will see you next time as well Jamie as well Matt we'll see you
then bye you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of
OLR studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network calm Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific
9 p.m. Eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those
of the staff of orange lounge radio or fog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you