[SPEAKER_06]: Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
[SPEAKER_24]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_29]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_29]: Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_29]: In this episode... Hey, are there any boars down there?
That's the biggest fairy I've ever seen, Tinkle Fairy.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's your favorite security movie?
[SPEAKER_19]: Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolute fright.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's yours?
[SPEAKER_08]: There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't torture yourself.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my job.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now's the time where Spock can send me dogs!
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll get you, my pretty.
[SPEAKER_19]: And your little dog, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know Kung Fu.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why did they have to take the word gang?
[SPEAKER_17]: No one expects a punishing position.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's Kendo.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, Sky, Loki, Orange Lounge Radio,
S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_14]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a microphone check, and apparently the microphone is finally working.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think we had it plugged into the wrong place.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, sorry about the dead air earlier.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we're going to do the intro again.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we're live!
[SPEAKER_27]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe I'm dead, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I'm alive.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, I'm alive.
[SPEAKER_27]: They said that I was alive, so I guess I am.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, it's December 29th, 2002.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is sort of episode 26.
[SPEAKER_27]: Actually, uh...
[SPEAKER_27]: Two-thirds of our little group is sort of not here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Rob and Matt, sorry, Sky and Loki, they are currently in the car all the way back from Southern California because they went and didn't bring me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I was working, you know, kind of need to make money.
[SPEAKER_27]: So they might have a little bit of a dedication during the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: I've got two special guests with me in the studio, I guess, today.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let me go ahead and...
[SPEAKER_27]: Do a little introduction again.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have with us in studio Jessica and Ross, also known as Iguana Girl and Islander.
[SPEAKER_27]: So have them say a couple words.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yo, yo, Step Squad representing in this biz match.
[SPEAKER_29]: I really can't come up with anything after that marvelous intro.
[SPEAKER_29]: So hello, people.
[SPEAKER_29]: Let's go ahead.
[SPEAKER_29]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_27]: And, uh, that's, uh, that was stunning.
[SPEAKER_27]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_27]: I had to get my eyebrows.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go ahead and give shouts out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, again, Step Squad, of course.
[SPEAKER_27]: And hello to everybody in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: For anybody who is tuning in and has never even heard of our chat room, what hole have you been living in?
[SPEAKER_27]: You can find our chat room at orangelounge.skie.cx.
[SPEAKER_27]: So go there or we'll hunt you down and kick your ass because your information is on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_27]: We can find anybody that way.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_27]: I had just got done playing a song from Drum Mania, which was Miss You.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, a bunch of people probably know it from the English lyric version right on time.
[SPEAKER_27]: But we're going to go and play a song from Dance Mania Bass 10 and a song that's going to be in DDR Extreme called Speed Over Beethoven and something from Parappa.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go old school.
[SPEAKER_27]: So that's it for now.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't touch this You can't touch this
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: Kick, punch, it's all in the mind If you wanna test me, I'm sure you're finding the thing The teacher is sure to beat ya Nevertheless, you'll get a lesson from teacher now Kick, punch, jump, block Once more now, kick
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't get cocky, it's gonna get rocky, we're gonna move down to the next doggie now Jump, turn, pause, listen, can't believe, jump, pause, pause, jump, and turn I see you getting better, kick to the limit, in order to get to now, kick
[SPEAKER_16]: Chok Block Chok Kick Chok Kick Punch Block Gonna get harder now, Chok and Chok Chok Chok Turn and Pull Chok and Turn Chok and Pull
[SPEAKER_16]: I wanna see if you wanna see what it means to be the man With a master plan, are you the man now?
[SPEAKER_16]: Here we go now, kick, punch, block Kick, punch, lock Chop, kick, block Chop, kick, lock Lock back and kick it Lock, turn, kick Lock the punch Lock the punch
[SPEAKER_16]: Good job, Parappa!
You can go on to the next stage now.
Yahoo!
Alright!
[SPEAKER_14]: We are back from our little break and what you heard was, uh, yes, Bach.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, not Bach, Beethoven.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, what we, uh, had playing there is, um, to go ahead and clarify what I said, I said we were gonna play a song from, uh, Dance Mania Bass, and then a song from, uh, uh, DVR Extreme, which I actually even said the name, it was Speed Over Beethoven, but the first one we played was, um, You Can't Touch This, it was the bass mix from, uh, Dance Mania Bass 10, and then the last one we heard is Chop Chop Master Onions Rap, the first level of Parappa the Rapper.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, anyway, uh,
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sure that about everybody is familiar with DDR Extreme being released on Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_27]: And we even said that we didn't think it would be because who would have thought that it would have been so important in Japan to release a game on a holiday that's basically just a commercial holiday there.
[SPEAKER_27]: But apparently it was released and hopefully we'll be seeing that stateside.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, whenever we get an update of what locations have that, we'll be letting everyone know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Unfortunately, there's no official update yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_27]: But we've got some information on DDR Extreme actually taken directly from Konami's site.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can find the information at www.konami.co.jp slash am slash ddr slash extreme.
[SPEAKER_27]: The new songs that are going to be in DDR Extreme, we have a Cartoon Heroes Speedy Mix, I Do, I Do, I Do, Irresistible,
[SPEAKER_27]: La Copa de la Vida
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have Speed Over Beethoven, which I just played.
[SPEAKER_27]: Scenery the Speedy Mix, Jenny Wong, which should make JB very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_27]: We Are the Champions, Factory Team Remix.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm hoping that they didn't redo Queen.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are the champions, my friends.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have We Will Rock You.
[SPEAKER_27]: I guess they are going for a Queen theme.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we keep on fighting to the end.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, you know, I thought that it would be bad enough after that horrible version of Killer Queen.
[SPEAKER_27]: I mean, at least the music part was right, but whoever they had singing that just needed to be shot or fried or something.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_29]: Fried would be nice.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, shot, and then as they're bleeding to death, they fry so that they bleed fast.
[SPEAKER_27]: Deep fry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Deep fry them so that you can, like, eat them like a Twinkie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, we dip them in batter and then put powdered sugar on them when they're done.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was a good suggestion.
[SPEAKER_28]: See, there you go.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sorry about the microphone.
[SPEAKER_28]: Stop your microphone.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, another thing we have, we have 1998, Naoki.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know if anyone's seen it.
[SPEAKER_27]: There actually has been a picture floating around of a, there's a desktop available for people who have seen it of the Mecca from Brilliant to You.
[SPEAKER_27]: I actually knew who happens to read my live journal.
[SPEAKER_27]: You see a picture of that mecha that was taken from a background that was made for 1998.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have Bag by Revenge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Graduation, I'm not even going to bother to try reading the...
[SPEAKER_27]: Hiragana, because right now I can't make my brain think in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it's B for you, so it's gotta suck.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have Hyper Eurobeat, Naoki featuring DDR All-Stars.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, it's not Paula Terry, rejoice!
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: Ooh, it's Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have Love Shine, Paranoia Survivor, Tears, which is Naoki Underground.
[SPEAKER_27]: I've noticed Naoki Underground stuff is a little bit better than the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Legend of Max by ZZ, Trip Machine Survivor.
[SPEAKER_27]: More Trip Machine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Crash, Mr. Brian and the Final Band.
[SPEAKER_28]: What happened to the band before?
[SPEAKER_27]: I think they were sacked.
[SPEAKER_27]: They were deep fried.
[SPEAKER_27]: They were deep fried like a Twinkie and eaten by cannibals.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just another great treat from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: They were taken to the island of eyeball-eating cannibals, like the one who stole my Animal Crossing character's eyes.
[SPEAKER_27]: But that was last week.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have... Ah!
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: Politeary!
[SPEAKER_27]: At least Memories isn't a bad song, and she sort of holds the key there.
[SPEAKER_27]: She usually doesn't.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have Vanity Angel, which we've probably played on here before.
[SPEAKER_27]: If not, I'll see if I can sneak that in later.
[SPEAKER_27]: and 3P303 Bass Mix, which we've all heard if we bought Konomics.
[SPEAKER_27]: Cutie Chaser Morning Mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yay, Cutie Chaser!
[SPEAKER_27]: And it's the good one.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's the one from Ohasta.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do it right.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have a Do It Right Harmonized Two-Step Mix.
[SPEAKER_29]: From the American Macs.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, from the American Max.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Drop the Bomb System SF Mix.
[SPEAKER_27]: Pretty cool that we got these songs before Japan did, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, actually, that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's because we kick ass.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's fucking right.
[SPEAKER_27]: But then again, you know, they had everything first and we had to wait.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's about time we got some.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's kind of like the Bay Area versus Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, we have A-Style now.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're happy.
[SPEAKER_27]: And we have it on a nice plasma screen.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where the videos actually work.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, the videos work too.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was rather enjoying looking at some of those videos.
[SPEAKER_27]: Weren't you?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, the videos were quite enjoyable.
[SPEAKER_28]: Except for...
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_27]: Colors for Extreme.
[SPEAKER_27]: I guess that's probably a redone version just for DDR.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Happy Wedding, which makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_28]: All of that song's balls can die for all I care.
[SPEAKER_27]: What, Happy Wedding?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why?
[SPEAKER_27]: Why does Happy Wedding need to die?
[SPEAKER_12]: Happy, happy, happy, happy wedding!
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, you know, Ryan has a problem with that for a different reason.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let me actually pass off the mic for a second.
[SPEAKER_28]: Going on with the list, we have Namor e la Liberté, which is actually a DDR version of a 2DX song that was on 7th style.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we have Stoic Extreme version.
[SPEAKER_28]: Apparently they're doing a whole new version.
[SPEAKER_28]: Again, that's another 2DX song.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's V for Extreme.
[SPEAKER_28]: Most people know what V is.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's coming from 5th style.
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: I have no idea what that song is.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have no idea because it's in the... Go translate that for me, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can't remember which that is.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to do something here.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's going to take us just a minute to go ahead and... No, Babelfish sucks.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sorry for whoever just dropped.
[SPEAKER_27]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_27]: We love you anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to a little site called At Nifty Global Gate.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a really good little translation site.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to do this to translate all of that lovely kanji that I can't read because I can only read five kanji.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I read about 40 kanji maybe.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, back to... Was this the one?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, it's a Naoki song featuring Yuki, and by the way, chat room, I'm not really paying attention because I sort of have to manage the show, my bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: And that's incorrect.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's not a URL.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, it's not a URL.
[SPEAKER_27]: Goddamn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, this is lovely radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, it means a blue impulse.
[SPEAKER_28]: A blue impulse.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's better than, you know, like a white creamy one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you, Nostelon, for announcing your bathroom break, by the way.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, back to the list.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Destiny Lovers.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have by Kunita something.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, I'm Going to Get You by Kelly Cosmo.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Jet World, which we like Jet World.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jet World's a cool song.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have another one that I recognize the first kanji as being a three, but we're going to go ahead and run that through translator as well.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's part of three.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Tortoiseshell Catlock, which, Tortoiseshell Catlock, this is what it translates to, and then the group that does it is called Subtropical Muzzy Sky Bomb.
[SPEAKER_27]: La Bamba, Dance May Next, Jane Janna, Kiss Kiss Kiss, Kiss Me All Night Long, Mobomoga, Orange Lounge, Stay, Beatmania, 321 Stars, Air, Be Lovin', Feeling of Love, Miracle Moon,
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that the same thing?
[SPEAKER_27]: What song can you do?
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Love to Sugar by DJ Taka featuring Norio
[SPEAKER_27]: White Lover, um, White Lovers, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have, uh, well, Ten Something.
[SPEAKER_27]: God, all this kanji.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, Satoru Omi.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, we have... God damn!
[SPEAKER_27]: More kanji!
[SPEAKER_28]: They don't like honkies.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Door of Magic, Theme of Space Mako.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um...
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Frozen Ray, Pink Rose, we have Hold On Me from Pada Pada, which Paradise spelled with a C-E.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's put this up at English.com.
[SPEAKER_27]: Paradise.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then we have the returning songs.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Butterfly, Dum Dum Dee Dum, Captain Jack Grandal, El Ritmo Tropical, I Believe in Miracles, Get Up and Move.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ibelive, it's Ibelive in Miracles We have If You Were Here, Let's Get Down, Little Bitch, Rhythm and Police, K.O.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.G.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Synchronized Love, Red Monster, Hypermix, Telephone Operator, Club Mix, by Shelly Peter.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Afronova Primeval, After the Game of Love, Baby Baby Bigga Bigga Ba, Baby Baby Give Me Your Love, Cutie Chaser, Don't Stop, Electro-Tuned, Gentle Stress, AMD Sexual Mix, Great Music Cyber, which, by the way, is not graduistic.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was the one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, that was a...
[SPEAKER_27]: T.D.X.
[SPEAKER_27]: Song, Jam Jam Reggae, we have Keep On Movin', Senorita Virtual, Leading Cyber, Love This Feelin', Make It Better, Mr. T, Take Me Higher,
[SPEAKER_27]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Remember You, SP Trip Machine, Jungle Mix.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Trip Machine, Paranoia Eternal, Put Your Faith in Me, and Think You Better D. I'm not even going to bother reading the old songs because if you've been living in a box and you haven't seen anything that's on DDR Max, so enjoy your little box there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we're posting this in the chat room for everybody to see.
[SPEAKER_27]: And there you go.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's the link.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_27]: What's new else in the Bitmoney world?
[SPEAKER_27]: Anybody want to have a go?
[SPEAKER_27]: Don't look at me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Talk about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, talk about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess there's a tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's the 11th of January.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's a tournament at Fremont.
[SPEAKER_28]: Was it Ardenwood?
[SPEAKER_28]: Funtime Pizza.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's Funtime Pizza in Fremont, and if you're in the Bay Area or in Sacramento area or anywhere in NorCal, you probably know where it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: I believe it starts around 11 or noon.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can check out the details.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's a thread on it on ddrfreak.com.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, and you can get linked to the Killer Pals site, which is who is putting this on.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, um, it's looking like it's going to have Perfect Attack, um, Freestyle, and then also Freshness Freestyle, which is basically something kind of from the, from the
[SPEAKER_28]: from the Shaft A-Team Freestyle type of thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: So it should be a good time on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I would imagine that your best bet, though, would be to get the information from the site because I'm just remembering what I can remember off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_28]: But Jamie is getting us set for our next break.
[SPEAKER_28]: And she's trying to find some neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're actually taking over the airwaves because we've decided that...
[SPEAKER_28]: Korean Time
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, it's Big Booty Fun here on Originals Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to play what I have immediately available, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I might be playing, you know, even more bootylicious stuff here during one of our upcoming breaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we're going to get a break to gather ourselves.
[SPEAKER_27]: So the first thing you get is Tashani with a Gungo, also known as Caution.
[SPEAKER_27]: And please don't Caution drop it in your chair, because you could break it.
[SPEAKER_27]: It would hurt.
[SPEAKER_27]: It would hurt a lot, so here goes.
[SPEAKER_13]: B-Boost, I don't have a flat You can't stop me from smiling, Bonnie and Clyde Number 1, 2, 3, go, until the end of the night Your next chance is over, I told you It's easy to make you cry, it's like you don't want it I know what you did, now you're like another Now I'm the one who's coming, my lover Say goodbye to my baby one week, past you
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
[SPEAKER_22]: and 99, Prime Time Shine, baby hit me one more time
[SPEAKER_13]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: I miss you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm waiting for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I miss you.
Are you ready?
Let the music begin!
You move, move it!
[SPEAKER_16]: Can you hear the cheering?
Super Performance!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_25]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_26]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're back live.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was a collection of some stuff from DDR, third mix, Korean version.
[SPEAKER_27]: We had Gagai by Sharp, which was the second song.
[SPEAKER_27]: The first one we played was Tashani with Caution.
[SPEAKER_27]: I see that we had a few people caution dropping after I warned them not to.
[SPEAKER_27]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_27]: We also had from DDR Euromix 2 and also going to be in DDR Extreme, Vanity Angel.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then just for the hell of it, Erotic with Max Don't Have Sex With Your Ex.
[SPEAKER_27]: So that was it.
[SPEAKER_27]: We went ahead and did a little bit of research on new releases in the Beimani world.
[SPEAKER_27]: We also have the release of Pop Music 9, which I actually can't exactly find a date on, but there is some new stuff being incorporated into that game.
[SPEAKER_27]: According to the official Konami Papa Music 9, there's a few new modes introduced.
[SPEAKER_27]: I actually just posted a link to that page in chat, although unless you're fluent in Japanese or have a good translation program, you won't be able to really make any understanding of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: But one of the things that they mention in there is called Osasume Mode, which is basically easy mode.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're given an option when you start the game to say yes or no, and you can basically play the first level as bad as you want to without failing, which is good for the newbies, I guess.
[SPEAKER_27]: and then another neat thing, and they've actually got a few of the cards shown on the site, memory cards for pop and music.
[SPEAKER_27]: I guess it works similar to like the ones in the initial deracing game in Derby Owner's Club for all the crack, you know, sorry, horse addicts, I should say.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like somebody in this room that I'm not looking directly at and pointing to, and another person...
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, but, uh, apparently you can save your settings or game data on the card.
[SPEAKER_27]: I could read this in the really bad English that my translator put it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, well, just to give this a skim over, it basically says that you can save an expert course, the one that you design yourself.
[SPEAKER_27]: And, um, it says that it is convenient, and the game becomes pleasant further, even if it takes, right or wrong, an entry card using playing.
[SPEAKER_27]: That automatic registration will be made to the internet ranking if it plays using a Poppin Music 9 entry card.
[SPEAKER_27]: And.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, I am reading!
[SPEAKER_27]: I am reading directly from the page here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Actually, it says Hata and.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, so there's some new options.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wouldn't it be cool if they did that for DDR or let you program your own Oni courses at home and then bring your card in and play it on the machine?
[SPEAKER_27]: I mean, what type of stuff would you pick?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I'm thinking it might be even better, you know, because we already have memory card slots that we use regularly that we have to actually pay for ourselves.
[SPEAKER_28]: It would just be, you know, this great technology out there right now with this type of card system that they're just now starting to get into with Konami.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's cheap.
[SPEAKER_28]: You just toss in a buck or whatever and it pays for the card and it saves everything for you.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, why the heck not use it?
[SPEAKER_28]: It saves from having to have big, huge, expensive memory card slots.
[SPEAKER_28]: Instead, you just have a card reader and that's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: What they used to have, though, back in the day, I don't know if anyone ever watched the old, I think it was the GamePro show that used to come on.
[SPEAKER_27]: It had that guy hosting anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: They had, when they were showing the NeoGeo system way back when, the cartridge system, which, you see those big things?
[SPEAKER_27]: Those are NeoGeo cartridges.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're huge.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're basically the arcade game cartridges.
[SPEAKER_27]: And they had a card that you could take and put in on the Neo Geo Arcade system.
[SPEAKER_27]: Come home and play the same game on your AES.
[SPEAKER_27]: And you could start from where you left off in theory.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it's hard to find any of those that still have the cards.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sorry about the chair.
[SPEAKER_27]: I have a chair in here that's trying to systematically kill Ross.
[SPEAKER_27]: My bad.
Yeah, straddle on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you there?
[SPEAKER_27]: He's traveling the chair.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, this isn't liked by his girlfriend's suggestion.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, I was suggesting, you know, keep an eye open for those Neo Geo machines.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can see those card slots on them.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, you know, they could do that same thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's like you were saying, they're cheap.
[SPEAKER_27]: If they brought out a new home system that incorporated those little cards, you could save your data that way, too.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, J.D.
[SPEAKER_27]: Roth.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's who it was.
[SPEAKER_27]: J.D.
[SPEAKER_27]: Roth?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, he did Funhaus.
[SPEAKER_22]: J.D.
[SPEAKER_27]: Roth did Funhaus.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, he was dumb.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, no, we're not having Mr. Spanky's masturbation party.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, okay, Mr. Spanky, I mentioned what Mr. Spanky is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mr. Spanky comes on and gives sex tips on our show.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, really now?
[SPEAKER_29]: Do you think he might have a temperature for me?
[SPEAKER_27]: He told us how to have a masturbation party.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_27]: Make sure you have plenty of latex.
[SPEAKER_27]: That earned a burp from Jessica.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, the Neo Geo also has an outlet that you can plug your headphones in.
[SPEAKER_27]: That burp was brought to us just for Travis from Jessica as a token of her extreme belting.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, heaven forbid that I make anybody think about anything.
[SPEAKER_27]: But back to the subject at hand, you know, Konami is finally incorporating this.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, what if they start doing this for 2DX?
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_27]: So technically, the GameCube has a way to read those cards.
[SPEAKER_27]: And if they could do it that way, there's no reason that Konami should be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe they'll release something for the WonderSwan and have the WonderSwan compatible with the PS2.
[SPEAKER_27]: That would make them some money right there.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it's a thought.
[SPEAKER_27]: Think about it, Konami.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then again, like anyone, Konami's actually listening to us right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Remember, I'm not going to read anything unless it's over a private message, and go ahead and you can email that to orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com, which is all up and ready for me to check on.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, I'll tell you what, even though I can't, you know, play it while we're actually doing the Fuck You's of the Week...
[SPEAKER_27]: We're gonna pick songs for everyone's Fuck Yous of the Week, but because I'm special, I'm gonna go ahead and pick mine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because I always use the same song every week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, we'll go ahead and get this started, and the next song we're gonna pick is Jessica's song.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's a surprise, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: She gets a song, and then we'll have Ross's pick, and then we'll come back, so everybody starts sending me the, uh, F Yous of the Week.
[SPEAKER_27]: And if you don't send them, I don't read them, because I can't read something that doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can make one up, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I can make one up.
[SPEAKER_27]: But anyway, let's go ahead and get this started.
[SPEAKER_27]: So send them now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, now, now, now, now, now, now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Five minutes ago.
Thanks for watching!
When you say you do, baby, I love you, I just can't resist
[SPEAKER_14]: All you need is my arm, fill me with the joy, I can't say no now
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: S,
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio With the Ping Pong Ball Yes, this break was brought to you by the Swedish Chef And of course, Tack with the Psycho Duck Children
[SPEAKER_27]: During that break we played my theme music, Schlagwerk, because this is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then Jessica's request of Traces.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, it was Attack Attack.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then even though Paul Oteri is officially banned from Orange Sounds Radio until the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_29]: There is nothing wrong with Paul Oteri.
[SPEAKER_29]: I love Paul Oteri.
[SPEAKER_29]: Love you, girl.
[SPEAKER_27]: Even though she can't hold a tune to save her life.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go ahead, marry her.
[SPEAKER_28]: See if I care.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why would anybody want to?
[SPEAKER_27]: She looks anorexic and can't sing.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've gone off on Politary before.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is not the Fuck You Politary show.
[SPEAKER_27]: We also had the remix from DDR USA, Drop the Bomb.
[SPEAKER_27]: We had Tack with QQQ, again, the Psycho Duck Children.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we are, you know, because for some reason I can't play music in the background of my show while we're using the microphone because of the mixer on here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, don't marry Paul Terry, she's ugly.
[SPEAKER_28]: She's not very married.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm Maple, M-A-R-R-Y.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, she's unhappy.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's unhappy because we hate her.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, but I can't really play the music over, you know, with the microphone, so we get the silent fuck yous of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're a moment of silence in honor of being angsty.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, my fuck you of the week, you know, I don't really feel very bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: I mean, true, the other host went to SoCal without me.
[SPEAKER_27]: But that's okay, even though I had work and I was bored.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was just really, really alone.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I got peanuts for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_27]: Which were nice peanuts, they were quite tasty.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I got lots of chocolate.
[SPEAKER_27]: I got peanuts, I got nuts too.
[SPEAKER_27]: You got nuts?
[SPEAKER_27]: I got nuts.
[SPEAKER_27]: Were your nuts salty?
[SPEAKER_29]: Um, actually, yeah, actually they were fancy.
[SPEAKER_27]: You had fancy nuts?
[SPEAKER_27]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, um, other than that, you know, there's not really, you know, I'm pretty, pretty happy, I think.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, oh, fuck you to the 8th style machine for breaking my nail, but it's sort of a not really because I got to play it and we have ours.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, I have, uh, I have had a cry.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, um, the, uh, it was actually pretty nice to have that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also, uh, fuck you to cheese.
[SPEAKER_27]: We went to, uh, Old Spaghetti Factory, and they put a lot of cheese on their food.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is what I had.
[SPEAKER_27]: I had garlic cheese bread.
[SPEAKER_27]: With cheese.
[SPEAKER_27]: I had butter on my bread.
[SPEAKER_27]: I had cheese and spinach, ravioli with alfredo sauce, covered in cheese, the mithril cheese, by the way.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mithril cheese.
[SPEAKER_27]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Mizzithra.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mizzithra cheese.
[SPEAKER_27]: But the first time I saw it, I read it as mithril cheese.
[SPEAKER_27]: Made by the elves, who'd pawned their own mother to have it themselves.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then I had ice cream and a cream soda.
[SPEAKER_27]: We were in the freeway going to, uh, Scandia when I realized that I really had to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, fuck you to lactose intolerance.
[SPEAKER_28]: Which then spawned Fun Parappa.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, which then had us going into the Parappa funky flow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, um... Parappa funky funky flow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, uh, let's, uh, how about your FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm actually very, like, normal this week, so, um, I, I, uh, I have an F you from last week, maybe I could do that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, F you to everybody who waits until the last fucking minute to do their Christmas shopping, because they make people who are in retails' lives hell.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not to mention, not...
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, Mark.
[SPEAKER_28]: and all that fun crap.
[SPEAKER_28]: And F you to the coin slot on 8th style, but it's not really an F you because I love the machine and it's pretty and it's five minutes from my house.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ross?
[SPEAKER_29]: None.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're boring.
[SPEAKER_29]: I can't think of anything, no.
[SPEAKER_29]: I love everybody.
[SPEAKER_29]: Really.
[SPEAKER_29]: You're full of shit.
[SPEAKER_29]: Just cast Maple.
[SPEAKER_28]: Isn't that right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Maple's full of shit, too.
[SPEAKER_29]: Um, um, whatever.
[SPEAKER_27]: We could have Jessica step on your toe.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, then I could say I have a nephew, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Then he could say you're sleeping on the couch.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did we have a moment of silence in honor of that phrase?
[SPEAKER_27]: I think we've gotten most of the crap out of our system.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go ahead.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think you got props.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, let's go ahead and...
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, you can let us know.
[SPEAKER_27]: We actually have a new person in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll go ahead and give a shout to our new person in a minute.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go ahead and read the FUs of the week from our lovely, lovely and talented listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: First, let me have DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU to not having FUs.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was eloquent.
[SPEAKER_27]: Next, we have DVR Angel.
[SPEAKER_27]: My FU this week goes to DVR Max 2 Machine at Ronert Park.
[SPEAKER_27]: Scandia, again, for not taking tokens and the people that work there that are too lazy to fix it and say they're technicians that come in at 5pm need to fix it and not them.
[SPEAKER_27]: Didn't I get that from RVGL?
[SPEAKER_27]: That was my FU of the week last week, which I'm not even going to get into because they're still pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_27]: Next, we have 23Rangus who says, Big FU to my bed.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or his bed, not my bed.
[SPEAKER_27]: My bed's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: I have a California king.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, FU to his bed for causing great neck pain while still looking so fluffy and squishy and super sleepy time-ish.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU to learning pata pata because, damn, I can't learn a pata while uggling the all-stars.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU to Met Commander 2 for being too easy and a giant FU to a CD clock radio for not wanting to read my B-Money CD.
[SPEAKER_27]: Out.
[SPEAKER_27]: And, um, that was it from him.
[SPEAKER_27]: By the way, we now have people in here doing pata pata in their chair.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, I'll just, doing a yesterday.
[SPEAKER_27]: And now we're doing boom and fire.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, our new person, Ohaya Bemani, thank you, by the way, for coming into our chat room and tuning in.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, F you to people who hog new DDR machines and refuse to give others a try, who go out of their way just to see it.
[SPEAKER_27]: God, that's true.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, we didn't do that today.
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_27]: We have VidPower next.
[SPEAKER_27]: F you to free time, because I need more of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: F you to classical speed for only being 30 minutes, because it's got such great songs and there needs to be more of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Classical speed was interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: F you to not being able to pick out more happy hardcore CDs because I can't find any at the music store.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, and F you to Rob's OL auto schedule since it won't play the OL Rewind on Thursday afternoons.
[SPEAKER_27]: DSCS SoCalKicks
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, actually, it's, um, an F you from, uh, her and, uh, Mel B. It's for Jingle from Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_27]: He is such a bitch to find.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then you go and try to find a present from him, and Mel's only got one present in the hour and a half he's been trying.
[SPEAKER_27]: Friggin' punk-ass reindeer.
[SPEAKER_27]: He gets a fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mel says he wishes Grandma would run over Jingle.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, that's from Shark Skull, who, you know, both of them have been, I guess, on the show before, a couple times.
[SPEAKER_27]: The other one we have is from...
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck my friend and his dad for his DSL ruining the dial-up internet on the laptop for three days, which was over the period of the show time, so I missed the show and life sucked.
[SPEAKER_27]: and fuck his posture because it sucks and birthday for being on a Monday and having to have a party on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have a bigger fuck you then.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh oh, we're getting into another fuck you from Jessica.
[SPEAKER_27]: And missing the show, so fuck that.
[SPEAKER_27]: And one more, fuck projects over break because that destroys the whole break thing and they should just die.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_27]: Teachers just don't realize they need the time for relaxing stuff and projects make it sucky.
[SPEAKER_27]: Boo on teachers.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, boo, boo his.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jessica has another, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go ahead and pass the mic back.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is a mini FU for people who try to schedule things on other people's birthdays.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know who's... The person I'm talking to knows this one.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I love you, man.
[SPEAKER_28]: But that sucked.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyways, I'm trying to fix it.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I guess you'll be invited when it gets taken care of.
[SPEAKER_28]: But, yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_27]: That would just suck having an important event scheduled on your birthday, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, that person just needs to be ashamed.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know if you heard that person, but apparently all your balls need to die.
[SPEAKER_27]: But you're still loved, you're still loved.
[SPEAKER_27]: Whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, we have another FU of the week from Blackwab.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck headaches.
[SPEAKER_27]: Slept too long under the influence of painkillers.
[SPEAKER_27]: And fuck his girlfriend's little cousin for trying to kill him last night.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, if someone tried to kill me, I'd want to say fuck you to them too.
[SPEAKER_27]: And fuck oyster.
[SPEAKER_27]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_27]: It makes me sick.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nice English there.
[SPEAKER_27]: I hat yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: It makes me sick.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's hear it for Ingrish.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's loving Ingrish!
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_27]: And we have an FU from Maple.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU to his brother who wants the computer while he's trying to listen to OL Live.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_27]: There's things that are more important!
[SPEAKER_27]: Like having FUs written to you.
[SPEAKER_27]: And, uh... Dan!
[SPEAKER_27]: Got an FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_27]: My man is...
[SPEAKER_27]: My man does not have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, we're doing these at my house, and my fiancé is downstairs, apparently, playing Animal Crossing, which is our crack in this house.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: I can't think of anything to say right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm being honest with you all, so I'm going to go to break, because I have to pee.
[SPEAKER_27]: We want a special song.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll tell you what, we're going to go ahead and play a song for everybody listening, and
[SPEAKER_27]: which, and I'm going to apologize because this is off the CD so if it doesn't, there may be a moment of silence while I'm trying to get it to actually work so I apologize if that ends up being the case.
[SPEAKER_27]: What I'm going to play is a song that has been heard in, actually the home version of Beatmania 2DX, that's 8th, no 6th style, why did I say 8th style?
[SPEAKER_27]: But it's been in 7th style and 8th style.
[SPEAKER_27]: Should I play the remix or just the regular long?
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll play the remix.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is the remix version of Beautiful Days, and it may take me a moment to get this up and running, but be patient with us, and thank you for doing so.
Oh!
[SPEAKER_20]: Looking back when I was a child and dream, growth and maturity would come to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Having faith in you set me free and fly away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looking back when I was a child and dream, growth and maturity would come to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Having faith in you set me free and fly away to everywhere.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because Bongo Demands It
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, because Bongo demands it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I guess if you're hearing me say this, you're listening right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, the second song we played is Simple and Clean, which is the full English version of... Actually, I think it's the only song in English I've heard by Utada Hikaru, but that was the one from Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe later on I'll play the Planet B remix, but unfortunately I don't have the English one, I only have the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_27]: um we have a belated um fuck you of the week uh from Nost Island and we had Jessica falling over in the other chair waving her hands and going help and Ross is rescuing her um anyway um we have this belated fuck you of the week uh to Homestead for their crappy uh web servicing etc dot dot dot and that is a direct quote so uh
[SPEAKER_27]: We actually have some discussion about some older games in here.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have a discussion about Marble Madness 2.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you have hiccups?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Somebody needs to scare Jessica.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's play some more Politary.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_27]: I couldn't tell if you were in pain or laughing.
[SPEAKER_27]: I hiccup, and then I burp.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hiccup, and then I burp.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then I hiccup, and I burp.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have hiccuping and burping.
[SPEAKER_27]: It looks like we actually have some discussion going on about old school games in here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, 23rd Amagus is telling us about The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, which is my favorite Nintendo game ever.
[SPEAKER_27]: We had votes for Marble Madness.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe we'll do two listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: We actually had an idea for one, but maybe we'll do two.
[SPEAKER_29]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, why don't we actually, let's go ahead and start our first one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why don't we?
[SPEAKER_27]: As soon as Jessica stops hiccuping.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, baby, this will scare you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Vanilla Ice.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you burping still?
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, chat room, suggest a duck hunt.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, so what's scary enough to get rid of Jessica's hiccups?
[SPEAKER_27]: What would be scary enough to get rid of Jessica's hiccups?
[SPEAKER_29]: Rub that.
[SPEAKER_27]: That would be scary enough to kill people.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, think back to the Miggle 2 tournament.
[SPEAKER_27]: Think about to where we put Brad in your trunk.
[SPEAKER_27]: We put Brad in your trunk on the way to Lions.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh yeah, we did, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, isn't that scary?
[SPEAKER_27]: Because he flashed his pale skin to the world.
[SPEAKER_28]: That is kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you still hiccuping?
[SPEAKER_27]: Chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, the click of vision is not scary.
[SPEAKER_27]: Politary Prawn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's disturbing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, she would be the dildo.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's ugly.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's very ugly.
[SPEAKER_29]: The 250 BPM Satan fetus is pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_27]: I would not play that song for ages because of the Satan fetus.
[SPEAKER_27]: Foam bat porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Blink.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not foam bat.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's plastic bat.
[SPEAKER_27]: Plastic bat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Get it right.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's plastic and it's orange and it's been signed by practically everybody now.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think her hiccups went away.
[SPEAKER_27]: Her hiccups went away?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Travis did come up with the worst one.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I got a random message from... Some idiot.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, some idiot.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, um... Well, why don't we go ahead and try to do a listless, you know?
[SPEAKER_27]: True, I seem to be playing, like... Just ignore the person.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tons and tons and tons and tons of music the whole time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ignore!
[SPEAKER_28]: Just right-click ignore.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can't you?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, that's lovely.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, we're having an issue right now with the, uh, chat room, so I'll tell you what, let me go ahead and play a couple more songs, uh, until we, uh, get this settled, so, uh, let's play some stuff from, uh, Jet Set Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's Guitar Vader with Super Brothers.
... ...
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_14]: and Sipa Brazzers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, crisis averted.
[SPEAKER_14]: For the time being, right?
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, that song is actually from the first Jet Set Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was Super Brothers.
[SPEAKER_27]: The soundtrack for that game was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: When they brought it out for the US, though, they were supposed to have added some more tracks to that.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it was a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um...
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we're going to go ahead.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're not going to be doing the song battle this week because, of course, my other two hosts aren't here to put in their contributions.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we're going to go ahead and leave the playlist the way it is this week.
[SPEAKER_27]: But next week we actually should have the song battle.
[SPEAKER_27]: And because none of you voted for Knight Rider, hello, then I'm going to pick a new song.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you have to vote for it because anything that I pick, of course, is going to be instantly cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: They didn't vote for Knight Rider?
[SPEAKER_27]: I put in a nice remix of the Knight Rider theme.
[SPEAKER_27]: and nobody, and like, two people voted for it.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're all idiots.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it lasted for two, it actually made it through three weeks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, so, people had some taste for a while.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, um, thanks to, uh, DarkTessia, it was, uh, they put some Rob Zombie music in, uh, in, uh, Jet Set Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, um, we're gonna go ahead and, uh, go into one of our, uh, favorite segments, which is, uh, the, uh, listless.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're probably going to do two of them today because we're not having the Battle of Songs.
[SPEAKER_27]: And hey, don't you all love it?
[SPEAKER_27]: So this one is going to be... Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Should we do Best Old School Game?
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe Best 80s TV Show, perhaps?
[SPEAKER_27]: How about Best Sitcom or Tune?
[SPEAKER_27]: What would you suggest?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hmm... Sitcom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because Tune's going to be too hard.
[SPEAKER_27]: Best 80s Sitcom.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know how many of you are actually going to be old enough to get it.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, you know, think back.
[SPEAKER_27]: All of it for Propel.
[SPEAKER_27]: Propel was not an 80s sitcom.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, Stalin wants to hear you laugh again.
[SPEAKER_27]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_27]: You actually sound kind of evil when you laugh.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's my evil boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_29]: That's what I was trying to be evil.
[SPEAKER_27]: Actually, we have a suggestion for best 80s movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's too broad.
[SPEAKER_27]: It is pretty broad.
[SPEAKER_29]: Like, you'd have to break it down to best 80s comedy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because there's only three of us here, so maybe we'll pick four each.
[SPEAKER_27]: So maybe we could do it that way?
[SPEAKER_27]: Best live-action, non-animated 80s movie.
[SPEAKER_29]: Crap, there goes Transformers.
[SPEAKER_27]: Edwards Scissor Penis
[SPEAKER_28]: No, it's Penis Hands.
[SPEAKER_27]: Penis Hands.
[SPEAKER_27]: Edward Penis Hands.
[SPEAKER_27]: See, now our ratings are going to go up because we're talking about porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: See, look.
[SPEAKER_28]: You realize it's extremely sad that I know more about porn than my boyfriend does.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, owned.
[SPEAKER_29]: Whatever I have in my possession.
[SPEAKER_29]: Trace the Lord's first video.
[SPEAKER_29]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that has what basis?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: She was underage.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Child porn.
[SPEAKER_29]: You can't tell it was the 80s.
[SPEAKER_29]: She looked old enough.
[SPEAKER_27]: What, big hair and fake boobs?
[SPEAKER_27]: Was that the same excuse that you used for... I'm not even gonna ask.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to vote for four-piece.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to play more music because I can't think of anything else to talk about.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we're going to go ahead.
[SPEAKER_27]: We did actually have some requests for more Parappa music, so I'm going to go ahead and play the final song for Parappa the Rapper 2.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to go ahead and throw in some more Jet Set Radio stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see what else we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sweet Soul Brother Jet Start Radio
[SPEAKER_27]: So stick around, make sure that you keep your eyes open because we're going to go ahead and be voting for our songs and then we'll go ahead and let you know what we're up to.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yo, yo, yo, check this out, it's party time, party time in the house Everybody, I'm wondering how you're feeling out there, you feeling good?
[SPEAKER_14]: We're gonna put on a show out there for everybody Check this out Somebody say ho!
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatcha gonna do when they come?
[SPEAKER_14]: I gotta be seen!
[SPEAKER_14]: You gotta do what?
[SPEAKER_16]: I gotta believe!
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, yo, everybody!
[SPEAKER_16]: Just check out the way I lift everybody!
[SPEAKER_16]: Yo, yo, everybody!
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm trying to get the rest of the poor kids to party!
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-oh, uh-oh, here comes the dude!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: I gotta believe, what you're gonna do
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatcha gonna do when they come?
[SPEAKER_14]: You gotta do what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I gotta believe!
[SPEAKER_14]: X to the E to the R to the O And pick up your hero, here we go!
[SPEAKER_14]: X to the X to the R to the X
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_14]: I gotta believe, that you're gonna do when they come I gotta redeem, that you're gonna do when they come
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatcha gonna do when they come I gotta believe Whatcha gonna do when they come I gotta believe Whatcha gonna do when they come I gotta believe Whatcha gonna do when they come I gotta believe
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you everybody!
[SPEAKER_13]: And don't forget, you gotta believe!
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls!
and more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Me, me, quick, quick, oh, oh, oh
[SPEAKER_01]: Kwe, kwe, mi, o, mi, mi, o, o, mi, o, mi, mi, kwe, kwe, o, o, o, kwe, na, mi, kwe, o
[SPEAKER_01]: 2-2-2-oh-oh-me-oh, me-me-oh-way, oh-oh-oh, me-oh-me-oh 2-2-3-2-oh-oh-me-no, me-me-oh-way, oh-oh-way, oh-ah-oo-oh
Me, me, quid, quid, oh, oh, oh Quid, quid, me, oh, me, me, oh, oh, me, oh Me, me, quid, quid, oh, oh, oh Quid, nah, me, quid, oh
[SPEAKER_01]: Toot toot toot, oh oh bleep oh, bleep bleep oh bleep, oh oh oh, bleep oh bleep oh Toot toot toot, oh oh bleep now, bleep bleep oh bleep, oh oh bleep oh bleep oh Toot toot toot, oh oh bleep oh, bleep bleep oh bleep, oh oh oh, bleep oh bleep oh
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Niko Meow Niko Meow Niko Meow Meow Meow Meow
[SPEAKER_25]: This randomness could only be brought to you by Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: And so I hope we all have our answers ready for our list list.
[SPEAKER_27]: And Dan has decided to participate in this.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because there's only four of us, usually we do this with six or more, we all picked four songs, but we're still going to vote only for the top three.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I repeated one of my movies on here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Damn it, I'm dumb.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're choosing movies.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, well, I'm going to go ahead and do what I originally had on here.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, we're going to go ahead and start with me, because we can.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know, but let's go ahead and start with Jessica.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's your number four movie?
[SPEAKER_28]: Number four, we have Weird Science.
[SPEAKER_27]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: Number three?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, Weird Science?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, what other movie can you see two guys running around with bras on their heads and it seems completely normal-ish?
[SPEAKER_28]: Number three?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, passing off to Ross.
[SPEAKER_29]: Number four on my list was A Christmas Story.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, it's seasonal.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's still funny to this day, and god darn it, you'll shoot your eye out.
[SPEAKER_21]: My number four was Aliens, because that movie's hard like the rock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, my number four is Adventures in Babysitting.
[SPEAKER_27]: because of the part where they're singing and Thor.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: Adventures in Babysitting was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, let's go ahead and go to number three.
[SPEAKER_28]: Number three for me would be Clue, because, you know, you got three different endings, you never know which one you're going to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, here's Ross.
[SPEAKER_29]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_29]: My number three movie is Revenge of the Nerds.
[SPEAKER_29]: Why?
[SPEAKER_29]: Because I can consider myself one, and hey, any movie with boobies is a winner in my book.
[SPEAKER_21]: My number three movie is The Karate Kid because it's the only cool thing that Ralph Macchio ever did.
[SPEAKER_27]: Too true.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number three is Legend because it has a young Tom Cruise in chain mail.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, not in chain mail, in his outfit.
[SPEAKER_27]: And plus Tim Curry's a pimp.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, number two.
[SPEAKER_28]: Number two for me is the one that everybody's been asking about, Ferris Bueller's Day Off.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because, you know, when Cameron was in Egypt's land, let my Cameron go.
[SPEAKER_29]: My number two was Fast Times at Ridgemont High.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_29]: Phoebe Cates.
[SPEAKER_21]: My number two was The NeverEnding Story.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because that movie was like, cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know that my favorite is going to get voted off, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_27]: What other movie can you get?
[SPEAKER_27]: Leg warmers and roller skates with one of the Bee Gees.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, he looked like he belonged to the Bee Gees anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: And Don Bluth animation on top of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Rolling.
[SPEAKER_27]: and no, not Roller Babies.
[SPEAKER_27]: I actually like that movie and I admit that it's bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: But Xanadu was just like really cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Plus it had Olivia Newton-John in it and Electric Light Orchestra music.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, what do you mean?
[SPEAKER_27]: They're all positive.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, what's your number?
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, that's my number too then because I actually like the other movie better.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, number one.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is my personal number one because I'm a sap and, you know, like John Hughes movies are like the pimp shit and all that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Pretty in Pink.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because you, how can you not love John Cryer as Ducky?
[SPEAKER_28]: He is just too cute.
[SPEAKER_29]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_29]: My number one movie was another movie with Molly Ringwald in it.
[SPEAKER_29]: That would be Breakfast Club.
[SPEAKER_29]: Classic, classic movie about nothing but Saturday morning detention.
[SPEAKER_27]: and Judd Nelson was hot.
[SPEAKER_21]: My number one movie is Back to the Future because that DeLorean kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_21]: Christopher Lloyd is awesome and Michael J. Fox was even kind of cool at the time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Plus I've watched it like seven times in the last three days.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: So you must be going crazy.
[SPEAKER_27]: And here's my other fuck you of the week to Mystique for buying that for Dan.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because I've had nothing but Back to the Future playing on the TV.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number one... Yeah, the music was cool too.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number one is Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because it has David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, Dan, don't go...
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, no styling has pointed out something.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nobody named Superman.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was a 70s movie.
1978.
[SPEAKER_27]: Although, the second one was 80.
[SPEAKER_29]: The second one was not worth it.
[SPEAKER_28]: The second one had Zod.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it wasn't as cool as the first.
[SPEAKER_29]: When I was a kid, Superman 2 looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: When I watched it later on, I was like, that's the worst looking set I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then Superman 3 went all to hell because of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: We are going to offer you five minutes to vote for your song.
[SPEAKER_27]: So go ahead and start sending me...
[SPEAKER_27]: Movie Movie
[SPEAKER_28]: Hmm, I am going to vote off... I think I'm going to vote off Xanadu, just because I have issues against, you know, like, disco queens and shit.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm going to have to go knock off Adventures in Babysitting.
[SPEAKER_29]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Poor Jamie's tattoo of hers gone already.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pretty in Pink's gotta go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so, um, we have our songs, we're gonna vote for the, uh, song!
[SPEAKER_27]: Ugh, crap!
[SPEAKER_27]: Movies.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to vote for the, uh, top, uh, three movies.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I'm posting them to the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_27]: What we have on our list is Weird Science, A Christmas Story, Aliens, Clue, The Karate Kid, Legend, Ferris Bueller's Day Off, Fast Times at Ridgemont High, The NeverEnding Story, The Breakfast Club, Back to the Future, and Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_27]: Black Lab, I'm going to kick you.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know where you... Well, I don't know where you live.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, go ahead and start the voting now.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to...
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, whichever one of those was the best movie of the 80s, so we're going to go ahead and get started with a song.
[SPEAKER_27]: You have five minutes to send in your votes, and if I feel nice, you might get a little bit more time.
[SPEAKER_27]: But I don't normally feel nice, so go ahead.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
Je suis heureuse de vous retrouver à cet endroit à ce moment-là.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want you, I want you, I want you Even if you love someone else I don't care if you don't know why The clear sky is low But I want you to know why Why my tears are filled?
[SPEAKER_14]: Darling, darling I want you to be there, be there, be there
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Darlin', Darlin', where are you?
Can you see me?
Darlin', Darlin', can I forget what happened that day?
[SPEAKER_14]: Darlin', Darlin', I wonder if you can remember me?
[SPEAKER_14]: Look, you're walking towards me
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: It's ghetto promo time.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is No More Shows Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: I kill you!
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we have a winner.
[SPEAKER_27]: And the winner wins.
[SPEAKER_27]: But what does the winner win?
[SPEAKER_27]: The winner wins the distinction of being cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, let's have a drumroll please for number three.
[SPEAKER_27]: Number three is Clue.
[SPEAKER_27]: Clue.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tim, another, a very good Tim Curry movie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Madeline Kahn is awesome.
[SPEAKER_27]: It had Madeline Kahn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Flames on the sides of my face.
[SPEAKER_12]: Heaving, heaving breaths.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, actually, that was in, that line was in our, um, old intro.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was a Rob influence.
[SPEAKER_28]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, our number two was Dicey's Future by A Last Minute Vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: and Dan feels rather thrilled at that the number one by a resounding number of voids voids, voids, voids, votes Ferris Bueller's Day Off you know there were a lot of movies that didn't get Raiders of the Lost Ark was mentioned Superman, but Superman was the 70's
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: There were... But we... I'd say Ferris Bueller's Day Off, though, had to have been, like, one of the top movies of the 80s.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um... You know... It would be cool if they would put more 80s songs, though, in DDR and Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, we got The Reflex.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: And you have, like, a crop load of, like, songs that have been covered.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here...
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, like I said, you have a bunch of songs that have been covered.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, like Xanadu, like Have You Never Been Mellow, so... Yeah, but covers aren't nearly close to the same thing.
[SPEAKER_29]: True, but they're there, kind of.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, look at Smoke.
[SPEAKER_29]: That's from the 1973 Deep Purple song.
[SPEAKER_29]: Right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I shot the sheriff.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, I heard that on the radio just the other day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wasn't Boom Boom Dollar an 80s tune?
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe, you know, an 80s tune in Japan or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mighty Fine In Dollar.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I wish that there would be more 80s stuff, just if only to infuse the youngins with good... Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Goodness.
[SPEAKER_28]: Gosh, well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's...
[SPEAKER_29]: What's other 80s and 70s stuff, like all the Casey and the Sunshine Band stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for speaking with this great topic.
[SPEAKER_28]: 70s?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, disco, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Disco's cool and all, but, I mean, you're comparing apples and oranges.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're talking about, you know, like, Miracle versus Disco Inferno.
[SPEAKER_28]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not fair.
[SPEAKER_21]: All the disco stuff's awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm like trying to do the mic pass here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, it's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_21]: You probably heard about half what everyone says.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not your fault.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bad mic setup.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, and in case you guys hadn't quite caught it yet, Little Miss Jamie is in the poopy pot right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yet again.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yet again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because she has had too much Propel.
[SPEAKER_28]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Propel her into the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, she's being propelled onto the toilet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't believe y'all didn't vote for Back to the Future.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, come on, really.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, it's available in a nice trilogy box set now at finer stores everywhere.
[SPEAKER_28]: But is it fixed?
[SPEAKER_28]: Apparently there was an issue with the second and third movies not being available in widescreen.
[SPEAKER_21]: That seemed to work on mine.
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe you got the second set then, because they were supposed to re-release them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, that is actually a point of debate, though, people being concerned over widescreen over fullscreen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, there's no debate there.
[SPEAKER_21]: People over widescreen are mindless, idiotic zombies.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan, they can't hear that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want my stuff cut off.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't get why it is, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_27]: they had Steven Seagal wasn't on there but they had someone portraying Steven Seagal and they had super wide Steven vision Seagala vision that was it and they had the widescreen so wide that you could see like stuff that was like off the set you could see the guy over in the other room you know going to the bathroom or eating or something and then all of the extras over there getting food off the table but uh
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a... I don't see why people enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we can't all have mics because the splitter that I bought was not the right splitter and we couldn't find one.
[SPEAKER_27]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan said, dude, that's booty.
[SPEAKER_27]: I totally want a mic.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan wants a mic.
[SPEAKER_27]: See, Dan's got his taste of radio now.
[SPEAKER_27]: They said they can hear you.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: He likes the power.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm a pimp.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you hear him say that he's a pimp?
[SPEAKER_27]: He said you're loud.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, that's... He sticks out like a hitchhiker's thumb.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's not dumb.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan's gonna get kicked in a minute.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_27]: We actually, now we've got comments coming in about Alan Rickman movies, so that makes me feel all happy and joyous.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, as far as the sim update, I'm going to be fully honest, I don't keep up with the sims.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, some people keep up with the game, The Sims, but I don't keep up with the simulators or anything.
[SPEAKER_27]: I understand that the Tourney Mix 3 deal didn't go as well as some people had wished that it would.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to have a full update on that one next week when Loki is back on the radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hopefully though, he did mention something about having unlimited access to get all of those things hosted up on the site so we'll be able to let everybody know and we'll probably put something up on our webpage.
[SPEAKER_27]: By the way, again, for people who are wanting to participate in chat, just go to orangelounge.skie.cx and there is a link to our chat room located there on the site and you can participate in all the madness and
[SPEAKER_27]: We actually had a couple people saying that Tourney Mix 3 actually was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, what was good about it?
[SPEAKER_27]: What was good about Tourney Mix 3?
[SPEAKER_27]: I didn't participate in any of that.
[SPEAKER_27]: By the way, we also... There's a Matt's Edit contest, Make Edit Get Porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, it's called Make Edit Get Porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think that's going to be in a couple of weeks is when that's going to expire.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was supposed to be last week, but nobody... Well, we only had...
[SPEAKER_27]: We only had two entries from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_27]: So it's going to be anything that's in Max USA for the United States.
[SPEAKER_27]: Make your edit for that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Send it in to Matt one way or another.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can send it to me if you want to and I'll get it to him.
[SPEAKER_27]: But you win this contest.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's only one winner, by the way.
[SPEAKER_27]: But you win the contest.
[SPEAKER_27]: You get porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, it's not like hardcore stuff, but it's more like Skinamax-style porn and Playmate of the Year and crap like that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Girls Gone Wild, ooh!
[SPEAKER_29]: Snoop Dogg version.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, I'm wondering why they don't have, you know, Men Gone Wild.
[SPEAKER_27]: I would be all over that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, Dan.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you don't want to see the kind of guy who would just whoop out his dong.
[SPEAKER_27]: If it's big enough.
[SPEAKER_27]: If he's hot.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan, dear.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to leave the room.
[SPEAKER_21]: Only hot chicks take off their tops.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, mostly.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, seriously, if you're just not getting any and you need your porn fix, send in your edit.
[SPEAKER_27]: You might just get lucky.
[SPEAKER_27]: All five of your fingers will be lucky.
[SPEAKER_28]: Either in a fap or a schlicking.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, either in a fap.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can play fap fap revolution at home.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or schlick schlick if that's your thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or schlick schlick revolution if that's your thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, everybody wants porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did not mention the porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: According to Maple, everybody that wants porn is busy getting porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh, MP4 style.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, I think that it's time that, uh, I think it's time that, uh, maybe we went to another break, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't have to go to the bathroom again.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yet, but I'm on my second bottle of Propel, who knows.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know, what do we want to listen to today?
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you have any requests?
[SPEAKER_27]: We don't want to listen to Satan Rock.
[SPEAKER_27]: What track is it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Hold on for a second.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's the original one.
[SPEAKER_28]: So you can play one of the originals.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're trying to figure out songs to play, so we're like...
[SPEAKER_28]: We have a request for Boom Boom Dollar, but I don't know if Jamie's going to circumvent that or not.
[SPEAKER_28]: So Jamie's playing with tracks.
[SPEAKER_28]: She's having fun and just kind of tossing things around.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're sitting in a car between two guys, is it okay to get wood?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not even okay to ask.
[SPEAKER_28]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're uber fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those are the free songs.
[SPEAKER_28]: The free song solo cake.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're running out of things to sing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Help!
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie's playing with music.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually, do me a favor.
[SPEAKER_29]: Throw in one of those.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, one is the originals, and one is the free song.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: We had a request for Beautiful 21C, and I thought it was on one of these discs, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't have Beautiful 21C, but I will, eventually.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, let's go back to... Yeah, next week on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're gonna...
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to go ahead and look for a song that was requested.
[SPEAKER_27]: What style?
[SPEAKER_27]: Third.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, from third style, Beat Me Into Dicks third style, we're going to, assuming that I have the song, we're going to go ahead and start it off with a request.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't have it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't have Macho Gang.
[SPEAKER_27]: Second style, I have...
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we are playing Macho Gang.
[SPEAKER_27]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, anal fighter.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: SOS, The Tigers Took My Family
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're back and we're on the home stretch of the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: We did get a request for a very funny song, and unfortunately I haven't been able to quite get it just yet, but I can't promise anything.
[SPEAKER_27]: We may be able to have that ready for the afterbirth of the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ross was bringing up something very interesting earlier about Japanese video games, about some of these weird ones.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you mind telling us about it?
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, I mean, you've seen some of the stuff, like the ones where you have to walk the dog.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, come on now.
[SPEAKER_29]: Goodness, South End Mall in Hayward had the one where they had the butt, and you had to have the paddle, and you had to spank it.
[SPEAKER_29]: It didn't last too long.
[SPEAKER_29]: Let's just say that.
[SPEAKER_29]: When I had, you know, some friends of mine walking up behind it and trying to mount it.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, it's not going to last long.
[SPEAKER_29]: South End Mall did have something cool, though.
[SPEAKER_29]: They did have the Monkey Ball arcade game, which had a banana for a joystick.
[SPEAKER_29]: We don't have them here anymore.
[SPEAKER_29]: Just do a search on Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_29]: And Jamie is over here playing with stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: I tried going to 3brain.com to try to find this song to play by request.
[SPEAKER_27]: And when you click on the low HTML version of the page, it gives you a smiley face done in text.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie, you were saying about those games.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tell about the lobster game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_29]: There's a site where I saw, basically, you know one of those crane games where you win stuffed animals and stuff?
[SPEAKER_29]: They had live lobster.
[SPEAKER_29]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, they're, you know, the claws are all taped up and you just plop in your money and if you're lucky, you'll have dinner that night.
[SPEAKER_29]: Lobster.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_29]: How can you lose?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, it's a little inhumane, but this is Japan.
[SPEAKER_29]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_29]: Really.
[SPEAKER_27]: I do.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, yeah, that is a little inhumane.
[SPEAKER_29]: A little?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, it's a little.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, okay, look at this.
[SPEAKER_29]: Walk the dog.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why not just go out and walk the dog?
[SPEAKER_29]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_29]: I guess, you know, for people who live in apartment complexes with no dogs and no pets, this is the only thing that they can really do.
[SPEAKER_29]: They'd be remotely close to walking the dog.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're watching Jamie go through 3Brain.com right now, and she can't find it.
[SPEAKER_27]: The song is not up on 3Brain.com, so I'm going to have to find it a different way.
[SPEAKER_27]: I had it probably burned off, but if all else fails, I'll try to have it for next week, for next week's little fortune cookie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, we're needing new material for our fortune cookie.
[SPEAKER_27]: So if anybody happens to have anything that you think is funny, save it for us.
[SPEAKER_27]: And who knows, maybe your little comedy clip might make it on for one of our fortune cookies of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: But you know, there were some of those really interesting games that I really wish that they'd bring out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_27]: I like playing that photo game.
[SPEAKER_27]: That photo game was cool, as I suck at it.
[SPEAKER_29]: They have one at Burt's Place.
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a bunch of different Japanese games, like the Walking the Dog game.
[SPEAKER_27]: But the game that I want to play is Taiko War.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tycho, for anyone who doesn't know, is a type of Japanese drumming.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, I've actually got two of those drums in my Animal Crossing house by my fire.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, but this is one where basically you play the drum.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, actually, I think it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't have the links immediately with me, but I'll try to find them for next week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Namco has done a series of music games.
[SPEAKER_27]: Really?
[SPEAKER_27]: They've done a guitar simulation game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Every single one of them.
[SPEAKER_27]: They've done... We just sued them over.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I could...
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, Dan was saying that every single which one, Konami sued them over.
[SPEAKER_27]: But they've done a guitar game, they've done a keyboard game that actually looks like it might kick Keyboard Mania's ass, because it actually goes with music, so you have to read the music and play it.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's an auto-harp game, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm still waiting for them to make Sax Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want Boner Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Boner Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want Boner Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, you play Trombone.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can't make that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dead.
[SPEAKER_27]: Boner Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Stroke Mania.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want Beat It Mania.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whack Off Mania.
[SPEAKER_27]: Masturbation Freaks We have a suggestion from Namco Panty Raider Okay You know Trumpet Ska Session Mode That's actually a suggestion from more than Jake Flute Namco And we actually We actually would Uh
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, actually, welcome to, uh, Rob, who has joined the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm in charge!
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jack off me!
[SPEAKER_27]: This is not a train wreck!
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm doing a good job hosting, dammit!
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm doing a good job!
[SPEAKER_29]: I can't do it!
[SPEAKER_29]: I cry.
[SPEAKER_29]: Riverdance mania.
[SPEAKER_29]: Riverdance mania!
[SPEAKER_28]: Dude, no, all you have to do...
[SPEAKER_27]: The Lord of the Dance!
[SPEAKER_27]: I am the Führer of the Dance!
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: River Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, um, they need the Kunio version, River City Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, um, well, you know, really, if you want a River Dance to DDR, all you have to do is play, uh, Captain Jack Basic.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_27]: We're having some discussion here now on old school games.
[SPEAKER_27]: River City Ransom, it's called Hot-Blooded Downtown Story.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then there was the... Dan's just going off on making up neat little meat mania.
[SPEAKER_27]: Meet Mania.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm actually imagining that now as like, you know, Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_27]: They should have an Iron Chef video game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Apparently there are Iron Chef video games on Saturn.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what, let's go ahead and check our good friends at eBay.com.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've got two Saturns.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Iron Chef Saturn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see if we find any.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, there are none posted.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's look up Iron Chef Game.
[SPEAKER_27]: I love eBay.
[SPEAKER_27]: There are no Iron Chef Games.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's look up Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Greatest Game Company of All Time.
[SPEAKER_27]: And there are none posted on right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll look up Chef.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have South Park.
[SPEAKER_29]: Chef's Love Shack.
[SPEAKER_27]: And a Disney Chinese Chef Goofy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, this is cute!
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe Sega put it out for their plushie line.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Your Mom Revolution, Particle Man Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want Triangle Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: With a giant triangle and a big, like, pole, and you bang the sides of the triangle to a triangular screen.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, Fish Fish Revolution would be like the Swedish Chef game where you try to hit targets with a fish.
Wark, wark, wark, woo!
Wark, wark, wark!
[SPEAKER_27]: No, that would be Chef's Chocolate Salty Balls.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, Chocolate Salty Ball.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're having a hoedown.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yee-haw.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, we could just, we should actually make our own video game company.
[SPEAKER_27]: And just, there'll be eight, Namten to come.
[SPEAKER_12]: How about, how about, uh... I like Tengenami.
[SPEAKER_27]: Then it would be Sonygen.
[SPEAKER_27]: Speaking of corrupt and evil.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was corrupt and evil.
[SPEAKER_27]: Combine them with Sony and you have the ultimate evil empire.
[SPEAKER_27]: And that if their games were all distributed at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nintendo Graphics.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's that for?
[SPEAKER_29]: That's for the Sega Nintendo Turbo Graphics.
[SPEAKER_29]: Dude, I would play that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ross Ross Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's nobody playing Ross but me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just for the record.
[SPEAKER_28]: I am the only person that gets to play Ross.
[SPEAKER_26]: Do you stomp to his beat?
[SPEAKER_27]: I stomp to his beat.
[SPEAKER_27]: Beatmania, huh?
[SPEAKER_27]: White Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you think she's going to do?
[SPEAKER_27]: Team up with the other golden girls and eat cheesecake?
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe one of them is going to have a heart attack?
[SPEAKER_29]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_29]: If we had our own video game company, what would we specialize in?
[SPEAKER_28]: Simulations.
[SPEAKER_27]: We would do real life sim where it's like... I want to simulate making a bowl of cereal.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, cooking.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's what I want to say.
[SPEAKER_28]: Cooking.
[SPEAKER_28]: A cooking simulation.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_27]: They actually have a game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Again, it's another one of those goofy Japanese games where you work in a restaurant and you have to make people's orders.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like sandwiches and stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tapper.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, it's not... Tapper.
[SPEAKER_27]: But no, in this game, if you don't make their order exactly the way they want it, then you lose points.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, there's also the egg-flipping game that was at AI, where you flip the pan and try to catch the thing, but it was broken.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, that actually is another thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: They could sell, you know they have those live dolls?
[SPEAKER_27]: They could sell, like, the Ultimate Sim version.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, you hook it up to your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because the Xbox isn't good for hardly anything else anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: It makes a great paperweight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jump Rope Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jump Rope Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, actually, if they did a square dancing game for DDR, like, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where you actually play with a partner.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, that would be pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan Dan Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: I play that every day, yo.
[SPEAKER_27]: Not Jumper Revolution, Square Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Grab your partner and buy the toast.
[SPEAKER_12]: We can rent a casino.
No.
Shut up.
[SPEAKER_27]: The redneck hit comes out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where's something I can throw at Dan?
What?
[SPEAKER_27]: Throw it at Dan?
[SPEAKER_27]: I didn't bring it up.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know, but I can't hit you.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can hit Dan.
[SPEAKER_27]: And Dan blocks the cat toy with Charmander.
[SPEAKER_21]: Charmander, I choose you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh oh, Charmander's tearing up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Cat toy revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Shermie Shermie Mania.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where you just sit around and pet Shermie.
[SPEAKER_27]: And she eats and flops on the floor.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's not stupid.
[SPEAKER_27]: My cat is not stupid.
[SPEAKER_29]: Cow milking.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Cow milking.
[SPEAKER_29]: How perverted is that?
[SPEAKER_27]: And you have to milk it in a certain rhythm so you have the bars that come down that corresponds to a different udder.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here, I'll pull out this teat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Squirt.
[SPEAKER_28]: It'll end up being kind of like those stupid crab games that you have to hit the crabs before they make it across.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whack-a-mole.
[SPEAKER_28]: The whack-a-mole type of thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: You have to grab the other before it moves out of the way, so you gotta keep up with the other.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's one twitchy cow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Give that cow some Prozac.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, we're not having DDR upskirt revolution.
[SPEAKER_29]: You know?
[SPEAKER_27]: DDR Upskirt, this little weird site had a camera put in the middle of a DDR machine and had little schoolgirls dancing on it.
[SPEAKER_27]: So it's a picture of their underwear.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan, you freaking pervert.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll find it for you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we've had a request for DDR Upskirt cam.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, someone find me a link to DDR Upskirt.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, not 3Ds.
[SPEAKER_27]: Upskirt.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to do a search for this.
[SPEAKER_27]: DDR Upskirt.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can't believe I'm doing a search for this.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, people look on the list of everything that I've been looking up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, we find Lolita Preteen Sax.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Um... Maybe this is it?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_27]: GDR Manskirt Revolution!
[SPEAKER_27]: No, that would be Kilt Freaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Kilt Mania!
[SPEAKER_29]: Bagpipes.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: That would be bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're not having Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_27]: Revolution, by the way, because Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_27]: sucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, we're not having Dildo Revolution.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, we need, Ross needs to see the upskirt cam.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jessica says he doesn't.
[SPEAKER_29]: It does exist.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, I don't know, no, that one's down, thank God.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we found the live sex cam and free pick amateurs with DVD tits.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Banana boobs!
[SPEAKER_27]: Banana boobs.com Ah, shit!
[SPEAKER_27]: I lost it.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, we're not going to the banana boobs.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, banana boobs is so funny.
[SPEAKER_27]: BananaBoobs.com Didn't we say this show was adult?
[SPEAKER_11]: But no, they, uh... This is not M-rated.
[SPEAKER_21]: Those are the ugliest boobs in the world.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan wants to use his adult check code password.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, you know what, I think that's a bit much for the boobs.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, we're not going to the Goatsy site, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_29]: Goatsy CX.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what that is?
[SPEAKER_27]: It's the one of the ass.
[SPEAKER_28]: the stretched open ass so we as moderators on DDR Freak have seen quite a bit that we've seen that about 5 billion times before it's old get over it, learn something new on the internet, thank you there is the pay picture find me the DDR upskirt um he wants to see the mulletsgalore.com
[SPEAKER_27]: Dan said it would only be awesome if Solid Snake is there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Which, uh, you know, actually they did make a mention of that on Naked Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, guess what?
[SPEAKER_27]: It's about that time, so we're gonna go off and look for porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh, prawn.
[SPEAKER_27]: We don't need seafood, Dan.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dude, prawns are awesome.
[SPEAKER_27]: We do not need DDR lesbian porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, that's it for this little lovely bit of train wreck.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, soiree.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, this is a soiree.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, we're going to go because we have other stuff to do.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, do you have any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's start with the farthest away, Dan.
[SPEAKER_29]: No.
[SPEAKER_29]: I second that, no.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to go play Ross Ross Revolution.
[SPEAKER_27]: I said thoughts as if any of us are busy thinking.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, my final thought is if you want to have an upskirt cam, be sneaky.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_24]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_24]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now, the buffoons date at the drive-in with the school's valedictorian.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really appreciate your asking me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most people are intimidated by my high academic achievement.
[SPEAKER_06]: This movie sucks shit!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Eber gave it thumbs up, but Siskel thought it was too preachy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I enjoyed the director's last film immensely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kathleen Turner has big fucking tits!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, well, she recently had a child.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think her maternal biology may play a role in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: She looks fabulous for a woman her age, doesn't she?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a firecracker in a bullfrog's mouth and blew his fucking head off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, in psychology we learn that it's not uncommon for male adolescents to commit savage acts on animals as part of their maturing process.
[SPEAKER_06]: That girl in the fucking car in front of us, she gives everybody head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess she's starved for attention and she feels promiscuity is the only way to obtain it.
[SPEAKER_08]: These popcorn's fucking terrible!
[SPEAKER_08]: It tastes like someone jizzed all over it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the thought of semen on this popcorn is certainly disturbing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps the staff in the refreshment stand was overcome by the monotony of their work and decided to play a childish prank.
[SPEAKER_08]: I looked at my asshole in the mirror today!
[SPEAKER_08]: It blew my fucking mind!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's ironic that parts of one's own body can seem odd and unusual because you don't see them on a day-to-day basis.
[SPEAKER_02]: My father's shit stinks up the bathroom all fucking day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's puzzling why one person's fecal odor can be more overpowering than another's.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder whether it is a function of the food digested or that person's internal metabolism.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna go get head from that fucking girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: While I'm sorry to see the date come to such an abrupt conclusion, I do appreciate the time you've spent with me and look forward to a future rendezvous.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like to piss in that guy's fucking gas tank!
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye-bye, have fun.
[SPEAKER_27]: And another addition to this little fortune cookie message, if you go to understudationlive.org, you can see the news there that Understudation Live is going to be returning on January 11th, so grab the details there, and I now return you to the rest of the outro.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.