No! Message for you sir! Attention!
lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex in this episode.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gay?
No!
What I expect for Spanish exposition is kendo.
Hey!
And find that funny Orange Lounge Radio
We are live and this is episode number 23 for December the 8th of 2002 but actually
we're taping the show a day early on December 7th of 2002 because we've all decided to go
out and get a life this Sunday night Because we can
Because we can You have to clean
You get to clean? Joy, joy
I'm going to a concert, I'm going to see Cher You're barely even laughing
That's like a horse.
Actually, Cindy Lauper's opening, and that's what I really want to see, so...
Uh, you are tuned into the Bimani scene's most hilarious radio station of all things
Bimani.
My name is Rob Robertsby, you might know me as Sky.
Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts in this corner of the Happiest Bunny on the
Farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
You know her better as Dark Sakura.
And in that corner, it is our Tech Massa Loki.
And we have with us tonight in the studio, nobody else.
There's nobody else here, because Brad and Irene are out in the front, but they're playing Animal Crossing, because they suck.
Quit hitting people with bugmets and get in here, we're doing a show.
Pit balls, don't forget the pit balls.
We'll be talking to everybody a bit more later. First we're going to take a quick break, we're going to do a bunch of popin' music songs this break, won't that be fun?
Any other opening thoughts from you kids?
I just made a treble clef with the microphone cord.
That's special, thank you.
Also on tonight's show, the usual talk of nothing, and a new game. We'll be doing a new game tonight. That'll be fun.
And I don't know what else. So, enjoy this opening, I have no idea how we're going to go three hours tonight, but we'll make it. We'll manage somehow.
Thank you guys for listening. We're going to do some pop music stuff, and we'll be right back. This is all from Popin' Music 6, so especially the pop music club that wrote us a letter a couple weeks back saying we need to play more pop music.
top music. That'll make them happy. Oh, hello Irene!
How can we get there tonight?
I'm sorry, I'm being talked to on the phone. I think now is a very good time to go to break.
What do you guys think?
Don't let your roots bring you down Live in a foundation of a dream
I'm so in love with you, whatever you wanna do it, follow with me
You make me feel so proud of you, you're the one I need you my
I don't wish upon a star, this love is for you, let's stay together
Don't let those calling distance stay, from heaven soon you'll find
Can you hear it?
And this is all that it is, all that's right
We can be so lucky
Wow
Don't let your roots bring you down
Live in the foundation of the land
Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that you are not allowed to play with your
Today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter
A, and the number 59.
Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
Hello boys and girls, you're... hello, no, we don't want another song yet, oh that's
what I get for having the thing on repeat, my bad, my bad.
But I hope you enjoyed the pre-show that we did tonight of all the Beatmania 6th Mix music.
It was super.
So how are you kids doing tonight?
I'm fine.
Yes, we're extra special on a Saturday tonight for no real good reason.
No, I mean, we're not going to be here tomorrow night, so we had to do the show sometime.
And when we tend to pre-tape the shows at another location, well, that's just too much
work for me.
This is much easier.
I'd have been stupid on a Saturday night like anywhere, like Golf Land or Scandi, you have
all these kids around.
Oh my God, it would have been nuts.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Why do you have the microphone? What are you doing?
It's like, go away.
I hate kids. I really do.
We should sacrifice them to the Dark Lord.
Jamie's especially evil tonight.
Yeah, I went over to Golf Land the other day to play some games, and there really wasn't anything to play
because 5 key was broken, because Heart Freaks was broken,
This is the sound of me putting my finger down my throat in honor of RVGL.
Yes, but of course those of you out there listening that aren't from this area have
no idea what we're talking about, but it just gets really frustrating when you have all
these bimani games at your local arcade and none of them work.
None of them.
We should send copies of the show to Steve and say, this is the bad press that we're
giving you.
Fix it.
He'd probably just ignore it like everything else we've given him.
I'm going to go and prove the laser tag.
Okay, let's see.
First start by making the guns not look like a giant wad of crap wrapped around with electrical
tape a thousand times.
They can improve it by making it a Qsar.
Damn right they could.
I'd play it if it was a Qsar, but it's not so I don't touch it or go near it or even
think about it.
These are kind of like the supreme of laser tag, huh?
There is no other?
There can be only one?
There is only one because they keep closing the fucking centers down.
I don't know.
There's like one in Concord and that was like the closest one.
Then there's one in San Fran, I think, and then there's some down south.
Pleasanton?
Pleasanton.
Yeah, Pleasanton.
They've got one.
I haven't been there in a while.
So how was your week?
What did you do this week, Jamie?
I worked.
And then what?
The only movie I ever saw more than like twice in the theater I saw, well, besides Rocky Horror, because you know, you see that every week.
Um, Moulin Rouge I saw three times, just because that movie was so awesome.
I saw Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles four times.
Yes, indeed.
That's so old. I need to get that on DVD.
I saw Bill & Ted twice. Well, Bill & Ted's Bogus Journey. I saw that twice.
Cool.
In the theater. And I saw The Wrath of Khan twice during its original run in the theater.
Wow.
Neat.
burned down smells like burning and how was your week
Logan I work well I guess you could call it working I was on the computer
downloading shit as usual but this time I was downloading please the hell's that
noise I don't know my computer farted just ignore it it was weird I don't
think a truck backing up in there just ignore it it was that weird hum we had
last week coming back for a little bit. Yeah, but anyways. Nobody move! It's the alien implanted
chip in my head that's interfering with the speakers. Maybe. Yeah, but, uh, so I was downloading
PlayStation utilities to attempt to hack a DDR Max 2 disc. This was a short-lived attempt
seen as I... This is the one you yacked about a couple weeks ago about how you're gonna
have the ultimate DDR mix, but no, too tough. It wasn't too tough as I know jack about
programming kind of you need to know how to hack something to be able to hack a
DDR max 2 machine but since I don't know how to do that that's obviously not
going to work all I have to say is there's some weird shit in there I mean
the way they do things on the max 2 disk doesn't make any sense and I don't know
why they do it because they have like for instance the banners for the songs
and everything they have them stored in there three times they have the
executable for max 2 stored in there about 19 times and then they have like
a copy of the actual card that it flashes once. I was like, why store all this excess
data? I can't find the backgrounds. I'm not even going to look anymore because I'm just
fed up with it. Tired. Not worth it. The videos, I know where the videos are. I know where
the music is. I can't decode it worth shit, so I said forget it. I just don't care.
No illegal mixes from Loki. No, nothing. You know, if it's going to ever come down
to it, I'll just buy a machine and run my sim on it. It's going to be 100 times easier
to maintain and work and you're just going to just have to buy the giant metal pads and
just do it that way. Because really actually I was looking at it, you would, there is a
limit to how many songs you can put on there because it actually stores a lot of the data
on the flashcard itself and the flashcard is only 32 megs. And I mean I'm sure you could
probably cram more stuff on there but it looked pretty full as it was. I'm thinking, that's
That's why I'm thinking after Xtreme comes out, they're going to do something else the
way they store stuff on there because there's no way that they're going to be able to fit
anything else on Xtreme because it's all stuck on a stupid flash card and it's pretty dumb
because all the graphics are on that stupid flash card.
Yeah, I'm in the chat room right now and EOSFBB agrees that you should just put a computer
with a SIM inside a DDR cabinet.
If you do want to join our chatroom, by the way, just go to our website, orangelounge.skie.cx,
and then click on Chat, and it tells you how to do it right there.
Of course, since we're taping a day early this week, if you go in there on Sunday night,
well, there's still quite a few people in there listening to this for the first time
on Sunday night, because people are just used to that.
Brad, tell me about your week.
You're over there in the corner.
What's going on?
What's up?
What's up, my brother?
I have a job now.
You have a job now?
Congratulations.
Yay.
Isn't that fun?
Everybody enjoys that.
Well, but I get money now, so that's always good.
Money's good! What do you spend all your money on?
Rent, bills...
I saw you digging through the couch for tokens the other day and it was pretty sad.
Fuck you.
No, I gamble for tokens.
We play poker for tokens.
What else did you do this week?
Did you do anything fun?
See any good movies? Go out and do anything fun?
Go play any DDR?
the guitar freaks
but the guitar freaks is broken now I hear
yep
fucking dolphin
no but I just saw harry potter too that was pretty good
harry potter
I played metroid prime yesterday that's good
nothing really see I have no life you know
I wanted to buy metroid prime today but I'm holding off
you should buy it
well I have a gift card at target that will give me money off so I figure I'll just use
my gift card
yeah you should that's the that's the next best gamecube game you should get
I want games now that I have some money I can go buy games.
but cool. Well, OHA is cool, but OHA only has like seven songs on it. So they need to
do like a 70 song DDR OHA for GameCube. You and that damn ferret.
I can lend you monkey balls. You can lend me monkey balls?
Yeah. That's okay, I was in here eating nuts. This conversation has turned dreadfully perverted.
We have no idea what we're going to be talking about tonight.
So wait, I came in late. I know this is going to be boring for everybody else, but...
That's right.
Did Matt get a... he got the flashcard finally, or what?
You were looking at the flashcard, or...?
He's basically given up on the sim. He got... he got... he obtained super secret copies of the MAX2 discs.
Oh...
And was able to look at them, and then thought,
God, this really sucks. This is hard to hack, so fuck it.
Maybe we should enlist a certain person whose name starts with R-I and ends with a C-K.
He's good at programming and coding and you can look at it.
Yeah, I'm serious.
What do you think, Matt?
Do you think you can give it a try?
I don't care, whatever.
He just gave up.
I just don't give a crap anymore.
I mean, I did get something good out of it that I already kind of had.
I got high-res banners for everything that's in Max 2.
I mean, Max 2 and all the old songs.
So I have super high-res banners now for that, which is kind of cool.
And um, I did find out a little bit how Max 2 works, but I really just don't care.
Now, the person that gave me the disc said he had some friends in places that know how
to do this kind of cracking stuff and said he was going to give it to them and let them
go at it.
But, I mean, I haven't heard of anything I would have to ask him to see if he's going
to do that.
Because if he did that and they figured it out, then yeah, I could go ahead and do it.
But, right now, stop it.
Oops.
Stop that. Just now.
God. Anyways, aside from trying to
get that thing to work, I was watching Taken
all week long. That would be good. I'm talking into
this girl's penis.
It's just as much of a train wreck as our other pre-taped shows, what can we say?
We just don't have the magic when it's not Sunday.
It's not my fault they didn't do anything to the Bimani community.
Everyone's freaking lazy and shopping instead.
Oh yeah, out shopping.
All their fault.
It's not my fault.
Which by the way is going to tie into our list list topic tonight.
But uh, yeah, stuff did happen, it's just, you know, minor stuff.
What, stupid stuff?
Yeah, stupid stuff.
Some stupid news that doesn't apply to anyone here in the United States.
Euromix too, they finally figured out the speed modifier code because the retards at
you know, Kami of Europe or whatever, decided, hey, you know what, putting in a menu where
you can select options is so not European. Let's just have it where you just do the nice
little arrow combinations on the pad and that way you can get, you know, codes that way.
So they didn't really tell them what the codes were, you know, for speed modifiers. They
knew they were there, they just couldn't access them. And finally someone figured out what
it is and now they have like you know 1.5 speed and 2 speed like we have over here which
is retarded stupid Europeans you know what can I say hey now be nice a rogue was just
going to tell you the same thing they figured out that you're only like speed codes today
so almost beat you to it if there wasn't that delay which oh my gosh Jamie has a hole in
her crotch no I think it happened when I got I got snagged when I was getting out of the
The car. My car.
They gave it this way. Easy access.
Okay, it's on the front by the zipper, okay?
Not anywhere near low enough.
This means that I gotta go buy new jeans.
People give me money.
I got a penny.
So do I. That's it.
What was I taking up a collection for? We were at a party, a small little party last night, and I remember I was taking up a collection for something.
I need the dead baby fund for Tokyo.
What?
Dead baby fund?
You're gross.
Never mind.
Oh my god, you are awful.
That's an inside joke we're going to tell off here.
No, I'm sorry, I'm in a semi-foul mood, which is perfect for radio.
Why is this?
Why are you in a foul mood?
I'm none of anyone's business.
I'm allowed.
I'm a chick.
Are you PMSing?
No.
are you pregnant no thank God I got the ferret thrown at me no well I can
understand she's got a hole in her jeans pretty soon to be bigger you know are
Are you building an interocitor in there? No!
I don't know that reference.
I didn't see it.
Are you boys playing nice in there? No! Are you building an interocitor? No!
Uh, let's see. Let's go to the mailbag.
Why don't I do that? Let's open up the mailbag.
I'm going to play some mohawk next break because the chat room demands it.
And now the ferret will entertain you.
Hold on, I'm going to our mailbag.
Stop looking a DDR freak.
I don't go to that noob site. What are you talking about?
There's a couple FUs in here, we'll do those later. Oh, here's one.
I do have an email to read. What do you know? Let's get the email reading music, shall we?
Hunting for music. Hunting for music! Here, I will read a page out of Harry Potter.
Hunting for music!
I will read a page out of this book.
Oh, are you going to read a page out of Harry Potter? Not really.
Okay, because seeing as how I sat here during the pre-show and read the whole book.
Alright, here we go, here we go.
We've got an email.
And it's from the OMGPMTHPSOGTHP network.
Word.
And it reads as follows.
Loki should have his own show where he sets fire to the French.
Damn those French.
They annoy me so with their Frenchness.
Your show rocks. We here at the OMGPMTHPSOGTHP Network are very pleased. We will continue to show support to your show and we'll sacrifice one virgin every week so that we may hear you play Instant Love again. Play Instant Love you must. We demand it or Kung Fu Squirrels will rain upon you. Thank you. The proceeded message was brought to you by the Oh My God Please Make the Horrible Pain Stop Oh God the Horrible Pain Network.
I think we should give in to their demands.
That was beautiful.
Well, we just played Instant Love last week, but you know what we should do?
I don't care. We'll play it again.
You know what we should do? Why don't we put Instant Love in the normal rotation?
The music rotation for when we're not here.
Because our show is special.
Are you saying that our music show is not special?
No wonder no one listens to it, because you told them that it's not special.
Special enough for the Olympics.
Hey!
Our show is special, but Instant Love is special.
Fine, we'll play Instant Love.
God.
God damn.
You guys are such bitches.
bitches. And that's all the email we got.
So that's all I'm reading for you. That's, of course, one more email than we
got last week, so
actually, no it's not. We did get an email last week. But if you want to send us an email, go ahead and send us to
an email to orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com
Sign up for our LiveJournal community before I hunt you down
and sacrifice your balls to... Because
we like to be nosy and read all your journals. Were you just strangling
The squirrel ferret thing with the mic cord?
No, the squirrel was doing it itself. It was autoerotic asphyxiation.
Oh my! Excuse me, I'm still breathing.
Okay! That's just a nice term. It just rolls off the tongue to say.
Autoerotic asphyxiation.
We're gonna take a really quick break at this point, and we're gonna come back,
and we're gonna play a brand new game. I also like vehicular manslaughter.
You guys are weird.
Okay, we're going to take a quick break and we're going to play a brand new game.
However, I need two contestants for this game, so we're going to take contestants from the
chat room.
We're going to all be the celebrities.
Loki, you get to be a celebrity tonight.
You don't get to be a contestant.
You're a celebrity.
Yay.
Does that mean I get a chair?
Okay, so.
No.
This is the question.
Okay, the first two people to private message me with the right answer to this question
will get to play our new game, our new secret game.
Who was the artist that did the song Young Forever?
Who was the artist that did that song in 4th Mix?
First two people to PM me the answer, get to play.
Alright, so that's it, and we will be right back.
Who PM'd the correct answer?
Huh?
Yeah, you have to PM me the correct answer.
It's a game show.
Just not an answer.
Like, you can't PM...
Oh, it was Bob!
And expect to play.
Yes, you have to PM me the correct answer.
Who was the artist that did Young Forever?
Because a lot of people forget some of the dance
media artists sometimes.
So I figure that's a good one to ask you guys.
OK, I'm going to take a quick break.
As requested by the chat room, the chat room demands it.
We're going to hear some oh-ha.
We'll be back.
Oh
I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go
The early bird gets the worm
We will, we will be young forever
We are the ones who make it right We are the people of our time
We hold the future in our hands We have the love to build upon
Together we can have it all
With every step we're moving on and on
Standing up for everyone
And for you to run around
You will be forever free
With all this love around
We will, we will be young forever
Forever, we will, we will sing forever
People give you my life, you need me
We will give you my life in intake
You've been waiting tonight, now you can say
Ba da ba da deep in my heart
I must've took your superstar
And what I give you love, you give me energy
When I'm facing the stage, you make me feel free
There's a devotion and desire
I'll kiss you every night
Oh baby, la di, la di, la di
Singing glory, glory
Ba da ba da singing on my feet
Loli loli loli
Baby got me slurring
Lord, but I'm using baby to see higher
Loli loli loli
I will fabricate and dy articulating
Power is it a gift to be human being?
Loli loli loli
Baby got me slurring
Light up my light music
Baby, light my fire
Hey there, it's your friend the Megaskin
Warning me to listen to Orange Clown
every Sunday.
Not just because it's the best eeeeee money radio out there, but because
if you don't, I will personally come to your house
and do a nori nori nori routine. And believe me,
nobody wants to see that.
Listen to Orange Lounge, because I don't want to have to have anyone suffer through this.
Goldwave and up the volume about 500% otherwise it was beautiful they're
getting better we love it okay so now we're gonna play a brand new game here
on orange on radio and I have to say this is inspired by Jamie do you want to
do you want to talk about inspiration for this bit no okay then I'll talk
about it this bits inspired by the radio show that I used to do on Saturday
nights from 639 30 which is what time we're doing tonight so we thought we'd
steal a bit from that show no this is inspired by them we're gonna do the
The Orange Lounge Match Game, ladies and gentlemen.
This is the Orange Lounge Match Game.
We have our two contestants, the winners who knew that Rebecca was the artist of Sang Young
Forever, EOSVB and Rogue will be our two contestants tonight.
So you guys are going to PM me your answers, and this is how the game is played.
Quite simply, we're going to read a little sentence, a little phrase, we're going to
tell a little story, and there'll be a blank at the end, and you guys will have to fill
in the blank so but what you want to do is you're gonna want to match the
celebrities in the studio because everybody else in the studio is going to
answer the question too and we're gonna have to introduce our fabulous
celebrities here hold on I gotta I gotta find the music for introducing fabulous
celebrities yes that's right everybody it's the orange lounge match game all
All right, celebrity number one is the lovely,
the beautiful, Dark Sakura.
Thank you.
Wonderful celebrity number two, say hello
to the Rice Princess, the anti-mirror woman herself,
Irene.
A harl.
OK, and celebrity number three is the wonderful Tech
Masa Loki.
Yes, it is.
And celebrity number five can be seen in a brand new,
or I'm sorry, celebrity number four can be seen.
Celebrity number four can be yours if the price is right.
Celebrity number four can be seen in a brand new porno
coming up this week.
It's called Derek Does Dallas.
It's Brad.
I am not gay.
And, the fifth celebrity is me! You get me! Uh oh, one of our contestants quit the chat
room. One of our contestants ran away. That's scary. So, we're going to have to take the
next person that clocked in, which I don't know now because I closed out on the windows.
Okay, I'm taking, I believe the next person who logged in with the answer was 23rd Magus,
so we're going to take him instead. Sorry rogue, you lose. All right, so now it's the
OSBB and 23rd Magus. Okay, so what you guys are going to do, you're going to private message
me your answers. Don't say them in the chat room, you guys. Okay, here we go. The first
Next question. Is everybody in the room have a pen? Okay. Here we go. This is the first
one. Nelson the newbie was so excited to be playing Dance Dance Revolution for the very
first time. He had to play the game because he'd heard that everyone else who played it
was really blank. Nelson the newbie was so excited to be playing Dance Dance Revolution
for the very first time. He had to play the game because he'd heard that everyone else
who played it was really blank. Everybody's thinking. I still need answers
from both contestants. Yo, answer now. Before I poke your eye out with a spoon. Okay. Let's
get a little more thinking time. No, I'm still missing one. He's probably trying to come
up with something clever. Okay, he's clocked in. Okay, he had quite a little bit of an
answer there. Okay, so let's see what the answers were. Our contestant said, EOSvb says,
Nelson the newbie was so excited to be playing Dance Dance Revolution for the very first
time. He had to play the game because he'd heard that everyone else who played it was
really thin almost to the point where they look like they were strung out on
heroin but it was from all the cardio Wow all right 23rd Magus's answer is he
had to play the game because he'd heard that everyone else who played it was
really popular popular okay so we have popular and look like they were strung
out on heroin Jamie what was your answer super cool pimpin smooth like butter
Super Cool Pippins Move Like Butter. Awwww, I'm sorry, that doesn't match.
Rice Princess, what was your answer?
Uh, Asian.
Was really Asian? I'm sorry, that doesn't match.
Loki, your answer. Everyone that played the game was really...
Super! Really super!
Sorry, doesn't match.
Brad, your answer. Everyone else who played the game was really...
No, just kidding. I thought my answer was greasy.
It was really greasy!
I'm sorry. That doesn't match either.
Okay, and my answer was
he had to play the game because he heard that everyone else who played it was really
gay. I did put gay, actually.
So that means it's all tied up at zero to zero.
They're both losers so far, but that's okay because we've got four more
questions to go.
And by the way, the winner of tonight's competition, as their prize, will have their name displayed
in lights on the website.
How's that?
And a crack pipe.
Okay.
Yeah, you have to get your own crack pipe.
Okay, so here we go.
Here's the next question.
All right, the next question is, Freddy the Freestyler was the leadest freestyler in all
of Florida.
He did Matrix Walks, Bar Hops, Caution Drops, and he even did, blank.
Freddy the Freestyler was the leadest freestyler in all of Florida.
He did Matrix Walks, Bar Hops, Caution Drops, and he even did blank.
Here we go with the game.
Matrix Walks, Bar Hops, Caution Drops, and he even did this.
I have mine.
Freddy the Freestyler was the leadest freestyler in all of Florida. He did Matrix Walks, Bar Hops, Caution Drops, and he even did this.
Me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me-me.
Okay. Is all- celebrities, are you all clocked in? Yes, everybody's in? Okay. Let's- let's-
Let's see our answers from the, uh, contestants. EOSVB says,
He did matrix walks, bar hops, caution drops, and he even did cough drops!
Cough drops!
Haha!
That's kind of like, oh, he says ri-co-la.
That's kind of like what happens when you go to the doctor.
Drop him and cough.
23rd Magus says, he did matrix walks, bar hops, caution drops, and he even did dynamite
rave.
Ooh.
So let's see if either of those are a match.
Jamie, what was your answer?
He did an interpretive dance wearing a schoolgirl's uniform with the upskirt cam.
An interpretive dance with the upskirt cam, ehhh, sorry.
Alright.
Irene, he did matrix walks, bar hops, caution drops, and he even did...
Uh, seppuku, because he's so not innovative.
Seppuku, no, I'm sorry, ehhh.
That does not match up either.
Loki, what was your answer?
Pelvic thrusts.
Pelvic thrusts, very good answer.
But no, no matches, sorry.
Brad, Freddy the Freestyler, he even did,
I wanted to say knit crochet, but no, he did yoga.
Oh, he did yoga.
Very good, but eh, I'm sorry, that's not a match.
And my answer, he did matric walks, bar hops,
caution drops, and he even did the chicken dance.
I'm sorry, no matches.
The score is still tied at zero to zero.
Alright, moving on to the next question.
I think I have new think music, wouldn't that be fabulous you guys?
Yes.
Hold on, let me see if I got it correctly here.
Let's see.
No Animal Crossing town theme.
Damn.
Okay, new music.
Okay, next question is, Penny the perfect attacker was all ready to beat Tigger, Eugene,
in the latest tournament.
She knew she could win because she was wearing her lucky blank.
Penny the perfect attacker was all ready to beat Tigger Eugene in the latest tournament.
kostjamrh Are all the celebrities clocked in here?
i need an answer from the OSFBB still
Is this just the same music in a different key?
That's all the songs were on the show, it was always the same song.
Okay, I've got to answer.
Are all the celebrities checked in?
Yes, okay.
Here we go, I'm going to read them the other way around this time.
23rd Magus says,
Penny, the perfect attacker was all ready to beat Ticker Eugene in the latest tournament.
She knew she could win because she was wearing her lucky shoes.
Oh, a logical answer. Will Logic win? Who knows?
EOSFBB says,
Penny, the perfect attacker, was all ready to beat Tigger Eugene in the latest tournament.
She knew she could win because she was wearing her lucky Supa Dupa Raver socks.
All I have to say to that...
I need a hug.
Alright, alright.
Let's see what the celebrities said.
Okay, we got super duper raver socks and shoes.
Pretty close, pretty close answers, but we shall see.
Jamie, what was your answer?
She knew she could win
because she was wearing her lucky flank.
Freaking laser beam strapped to her head.
I'm sorry, that is not a match.
Irene, your answer.
Ass.
She was just wearing a lucky ass?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, we never said the celebrities were well-educated.
I'm sorry that's not a match.
Loki, your answer, please.
She knew she could win because she was wearing her lucky...
Tampon.
Her lucky tampon!
No, I'm sorry, that's not a match.
Brad, your answer, please. She knew she could win because she was wearing her
lucky... Strap-on. Come on. Strap-on! Get it, baby, yeah! Oh, I'm sorry.
That was going to be mine. So close yet so far.
My answer. Penny the Perfect Attacker was all ready to beat Tigger Eugene in the
latest tournament she knew she could win because she was wearing her lucky panties
none of you guessed that the score is still 0 to 0 we were all around the
pelvic area come on I mean I had a laser beam shot to her head okay you guys
don't realize how perverted and sick our minds are come on listeners okay we're
gonna keep going we got two more questions for you guys so here's a
chance to catch up all right EOS FBB versus the 23rd Magus here is the next
question lovable Lucy loves para para more than any other game in the land
she's short Asian cute has big boobs and she's also really really blank
lovable Lucy loves para para more than any other game in the land she's short
Short, Asian, cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really, blank.
Lovable Lucy loves Parapara more than any other game in the land.
She's short, Asian, cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really blank.
Alright.
I'm getting some funny answers from other contestants.
We shall see.
Okay, are all the celebrities in?
Yes.
Alright, as soon as I'm answered, I'm sorry.
Okay, here we go.
I should now read the answers from the contestants.
Lovable Lucy loves Para Para more than any other game in the land.
She's short, Asian-cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really, 23rd Magus says,
good at shaking her ass to deluxe.
Again, a logical answer from 23rd Magus. He's sure to lose.
The OSFBB says, Asian-cute, has big boobs, and also really, really, firm.
She's also really firm.
Okay, let's see what our celebrities said.
Jamie.
Lovable Lucy loves Para Para more than any other game in the land.
She's short, Asian, cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really...
Addicted to speed.
I'm sorry, that's not a match.
Irene.
Oh, well, I think she's pretty lucky if she looks like that.
I mean, there's not a whole lot of player players that look like that.
Oh, okay, so she's lucky. Oh, that's cute. Okay.
Alright.
Loki said she's also really, really...
Loose?
Hello?
Lovable Lucy?
Yeah, just...
Lovable Lucy, now appearing on stage B. Lovable Lucy, the stage B.
She's also really loose.
No, I'm sorry, that's not a match.
Brad, your answer.
She's short, Asian, cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really...
Hairy.
Outrageously so.
Hairy!
She's also hairy.
I said lovable Lucy loves Para Para more than any other game in the land. She's short,
Asian, cute, has big boobs, and she's also really, really a guy.
Which would have matched a couple other people in the chat room, but unfortunately neither
of our contestants guessed that she was a guy.
Yeah, I would have almost been a match.
Okay, here we go. This is the last question, guys. Let's total the scores here. EOSVB has
zero and 23rd Magus also has zero. If they are unable to get a match on this last one,
we're just going to have to post on the website that they both lost, that they're both losers.
I suggest you get this one right. Okay. I'm getting mean now. Let's go back to the first
music. Okay, that's better. It's a better key. Alright. You like this key better? Okay,
here's the last question. Bradley the Bully was the best Beatmania player at the whole
arcade. But if you distracted him to talk about DDR, he'd call you a blank. Bradley
the bully was the best Beatmania player at the whole arcade, but if you distracted him
to talk about DDR, he'd call you a blank. Everybody's thinking. I have one contestant
in?
Bradley the Bully was the best Beatmania player at the whole arcade, but if you distracted
them to talk about DDR, he'd call you a blank.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'm going to start with the OSFBB. Are all the celebrities in? No. No, we still got one thinking. Okay.
The OSFBB specifically stated that he's pulling to get your answer on this one.
He's trying to match you on this one.
He's trying to think. Oh, did you get it?
You in? Oh, is everybody in?
Loki, you in? Okay, here we go.
Bradley the Bully was the best BeatMania player at the whole arcade, but if you distracted him to talk about DDR, he'd call you a...
EOS of Eevee says he'd call you a propel.
What?
Well, he said he was trying to match you.
Alright, 23rd Magus says, but if you distracted him to talk about DDR, he'd call you a fag.
Heaven forbid.
Alright, Jamie, let's see if V.O. said V.B. got that match he was hoping for.
Bradley the Bully was the best B-Mania player at the whole arcade, but if you distracted him to talk about DDR, he'd call you a...
Propel! Wow! No, I'm kidding.
He'd call you a blank.
He'd call you a blank?
Yes. I decided not to answer. He'd call you a blank.
Boo! The audience is booing Jamie, boo!
And I have a smiley face.
Oh.
Next!
Alright, next.
Um, he would call him a cab so he'd have a chance to get away before he beats his ass.
Ah, call him a cab! I'm sorry, that doesn't match.
Alright. We have some funny answers from the chat room. Jabberwocky says he'd call you later that night for a date.
or he'd call you a Michael Jackson wannabe with a nose and no baby
and he'd call you a cheese, windmill
Carl Sagan pocket watch, ass blaster
What an ass bandit. A pansy ass stupid fuck okay
let's moving on moving on trying to match our contestants we have
we have a propel and we have a fact I did
that's moving on let's moving on
that's moving on
well you know that
okay if you distracted him to talk about the are low key he'd call you a
well you know i had to but at this is this was my first answer was bag
all
my second answer was firing monkey pirate but which way to go with
are going to thank you going with that over so all my gosh we have a match
dignity
any
okay twenty-third maggots is ahead by one he did get a match
so
somebody had to have said propel for yosef vivi to win
lead me
okay he'd call you a
propel no just kidding
i
bradley would call him a cock smoking clerk a cock smoking clerk i'm sorry
that isn't a match
and brad gets the kevin smith award
eosvb wants to change his answer to animal crossing
too late
okay my answer
bradley the bully was the best beatmania player at the whole arcade
but if you distracted him to talk about ddr
he'd call you a
sacramental
no that's more of the chibi mentality
wow this game was a blank
alright so our winner was twenty third magus with a score of zero to one yay
yay congratulations
you know what that means
he gets to play the bonus round
yay
I'm gonna have to give everybody the back of their pants.
really, really blank. Everybody have an answer? I'm just waiting for our contestant. OK, here
we go. The bonus round. This segment on Orange Lounge according to 23rd Magus was really,
really, really random. Good answer, good logical answer. You will probably lose. Alright, Jamie,
this segment on Orange Lounge was really, really random. Random! A match! Very good,
very good. Alright, logic prevails. 23 Megas gets a point. That's a hundred dollars of
monopoly money. That you're not going to get. That you're not going to get. Okay, this segment
balls. I have colitis. And my answer was this segment on Orange Lounge was really, really
propel. Some people in the chatroom got it. Oh well. So 23rd Magus won $100 of Monopoly
money. So congratulations. Oh, he's going to get some propel.
And I'll beat him with the variant. A surprise. Alright. Congratulations. Thank you, you guys.
We're going to take a quick break and we'll come back to talk about some more Bimani stuff.
In the meantime, you demanded it, the chat room demanded it, the studio demanded it,
by request.
Colic balls?
No, not colic balls.
It's a new hack song, colic.
Hey everyone, this is DJ Konami.
I know you all know BeatMania, but I want to go back and teach you the basics.
Hey everyone, this is DJ Konami!
I know you all know Beatmania, but I want to go back and teach you the basics.
Listen carefully and try to follow.
The objects will come down from the top.
When it hits the red line, push the button.
When it hits the red line, turn the table.
You get it? Alright, let's practice.
First, hit the white key.
Now, hit the black key.
Okay, now a combination of both white and black keys.
Easy, huh?
All right, let's go on to the scratch game.
All right, let's go on to the Scratch game, when the objects reach the red line, Scratch!
With the fast note, the technique is to scratch fast.
Now it's all the keys and the turntable.
It's hard, but you can do it!
Okay, effector time!
Here's the stick of the new beatmania!
Look, way below, do you see the foot switch?
That's the effect on and on switch.
With this trimmer, you can choose your effect.
I'll show you, so trim with me, alright?
Hey, do you hear the variety of effects?
With this trimmer, you can change the strength and the depth of the effect.
All right, Loki, please introduce this next song, because it's kind of weird.
Okay, before I came over today, I found one of the strangest Paranoia remixes ever.
It's the first, probably only, all-Spanish
Latin Paranoia remix. It's Paranoia
Aku Eka, or whatever that means, I don't know.
And there's a DGI for it, too.
...
Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because Real Radio makes Captain Jack cry.
in its entirety on Sunday night at the normal time, just so people don't get too confused.
But if you're in the chat room wondering why you can't really participate live with the show tonight,
that's why, because we tape today early. We're on Saturday.
So, we're back, and don't have a lot to talk about, so this is the point where we usually would let Loki do a Sim update.
So, Loki, what's going on in the Sim world this week?
Not too much. They're wrapping up with the submissions for Turning Mix 3. Those are due next Sunday. That will be, I believe, the 15th, so make sure they have your stuff in by, I would say by 9pm at the latest.
Definitely wait before that though, but try to get your stuff in for Turning Mix 3, and then I believe a week after that, they will be having actual submissions up on the web.
to be up for about one whole week. So you want to get them then while you still can.
Aside from that, there's a few other things to know. In DDArmaniaX, they've got in their
user submitted files for them. They have a nice little list of every single site that
has DWIs on it. And that's where actually that Paranoia Remix came from because there
is a DWI out there for that Paranoia Remix. So check that out and you can always increase
your collection that way. And just do watch that forum. They have some pretty good files
that have come out recently. I just got one for Baby Got Back. You got to love that song.
So, definitely keep an eye on that. And also, nothing really new with StepMania. I have
checked their site and it looks like that they are in preparations for starting betas
Um, I don't really know what these are. I mean, Reggie looks like he's got his giant
dunce hat on and he's holding the dog with a bow. And then there's Sabrina who's in a
bunny costume.
Didn't they figure out, aren't they on their way to hacking the PC characters just about?
You were referencing something like on one of the boards that they found a way somehow
to hack the PC characters or you can load them in a program or something?
I did look at that. All that you get from looking at the one file they're talking about,
the bin file, I believe, is you just get a nice little shot of their face. That's it.
Sabrina the Teenage Bitch.
Yes, so you've got this dog fucker and you've got some vampire bunny. That's what your characters
are this week, dog fucker and vampire bunny.
Nothing compares to Mr. Spanky. Maybe we should have Mr. Spanky back on the show.
show.
Why not?
I think we'll have Mr. Spanky back on the show a little later.
Yeah, so if you're still playing DDRPC, and to be honest I don't know why you would, do
check those out because really I think DDRPC lost its, I don't know, interest a couple
days after it came out.
Oh, I've played all these songs before.
Yeah, it's like, oh wait, this was fourth mix.
I'll wait until we can hack this and put new songs in.
Um, other things that should be noticed, there was, uh, I guess you could call them preview versions of Bag and Paranoia Survivor on the net.
Actually, I should say, really ass copies of, uh, you know, Bag and Paranoia Survivor that were on Bimani style, they were...
Hey, guess what, Loki? I've got them right here. Wanna hear, wanna hear a little bit of Bag?
Oh, yeah, let's hear it.
Alright, here's a little bit of bag if you guys haven't heard it yet. Now it's really, really quiet, so bear with us. Here it is.
You can kind of hear the bagpipe.
It's Riverdance Yeah, woohoo
What do you think?
I think it's crap.
What it sounds like is it's going to be like Orion 78, except it's going to be with bagpipes.
It's pretty much that they have the speed down to 65 for the steps to be really close
together.
It's just going to be Orion.
That's all it is.
It's actually the kind of music I listen to when I'm trying to relax and calm down, so
I like it.
I have all kinds of CDs like that at home, so it's right up my alley.
okay one here uh... paranoid survivor i don't i don't even think you can really
hear this one ball play a little bit of it all thing that you know i really are
in the video
you barely here
they really are it so uh... yeah i would get the videos but i i can't play videos
over the air, because we get a lot of droppage. So, that was a little bit.
From what I gather from the videos, it was a pretty cool sounding song. You can't really
listen to it on the videos, because they don't have anyone that can rip it yet, because the
Konami stuff is like, no, don't do that. So, yeah, not too much to see there either.
Yeah, really been kind of a slow week in the whole Bomani community, just nothing going on.
It's just kind of that time of year, there's really not anything to really do between Thanksgiving and Christmas except shop, so there's probably not going to be.
I mean, DER Max USA came out for the holiday season, that was really the last thing.
We're probably not going to see anything until the beginning of the new year unless, you know, you've got BeatMania 7th Mix coming out for PlayStation on Christmas Eve.
But that's about the only Bomani release coming up.
coming up, and then in the new year we're going to see Max 2 for Japanese PlayStation
2, and uh, um, what the hell, 2DX7 style, yes. Probably next year. Probably also Max
2 USA at some point, but I don't know, we have to, I haven't, I don't even know what,
I haven't heard anything as far as how well Max USA actually sold. I think we probably
won't get any numbers until actually after the holidays. We can look into that. I can
Cool. Also a couple of pop music games came out. They're working on a pop music best hits. I know that, and I believe 7 just came out, if I'm not mistaken. I could be wrong, but I think 7 just came out for PS2. I know it was the first pop music for PS2 just came out.
But... I don't know too much about that, unfortunately.
Yeah, I did notice that they have, you know, like a DDR, they have the $2,000 metal pads,
which are kind of a rip-off, but they also have, you know, as people are aware of, the
2DX arcade controllers, and they also have a Poppy Music arcade controller, too.
Yes.
Question from Chat Room.
When is DDR Extreme going to be released?
Ooh, Brad brings back toys for us, yay.
Propel and food and drinks, anyway.
When is Xtreme going to be released?
A rumor is it's going to debut at some tournament, but I don't possibly see how that could be
the case because it's a Japanese game, so if it's going to debut anywhere, it's going
to debut somewhere in Japan, and places in America will just get it whenever their distributors
get it.
So I don't think there's any particular way that you can debut a game.
Now that particular arcade might debut their game at the tournament, but you really can't
control the rest of the U.S. that way.
I got it. Alright. So that's hopefully answers about Extreme. Well, also right now the betas
are only up to like 55 or 60 percent done. It's probably because they don't have many
of the Dance Media tracks in them. They have some, but not many. Yes, I mean, we've still
gotten plenty of songs that they have to add and test first, I mean, before that even happens.
so it's still a ways away.
Okay, Chateroom's been talking a lot about this and I thought maybe we would too. Upcoming tournaments.
There are a few tournaments coming up.
I thought I'd mention a few of them.
This Friday, if I'm not mistaken, yes, is this Friday,
is the Miggle Milpitas Golfland Evil Tournament Part 2, the aftermath. Yes, the arcade that
just got Derby's Owner's Club this week.
doing a tournament and that should be a lot of fun it's on a Friday night so
it's kind of like a big giant Friday night party and they're doing the
typical perfect attack and freestyle competitions however they're trying some
new things with both of them so there's some new things that they're doing and
if you want to visit their website it's www.monkeysfly.net slash MGLT
please go to that one and perfect attack rules let's see they're gonna announce
the qualifying song that day and they're gonna be doing the brackets a little bit
of a different way freestyle is going to be doing this tower system it's a brand
new way of judging freestyle so that should be interesting they're gonna be
doing some new innovative judging and ranking at that tournament so check it
out also coming up we've got the cyber beat tournament that's gonna be
happening I'm sorry the cyber beat nation tournament in LA that's going to
be February 14th through the 16th that's a Thursday through a Saturday if I'm not
mistaken orange lounge radio will be covering this tournament for sure
unfortunately I'm not gonna be able to make it to Milpitas on Friday Jamie I
don't think you're gonna be able to go because you got work you got the work
thing Loki you too right we all work unfortunately so we can't get there in
time so we're not gonna be able to cover Milpitas but if anybody any of you fans
out there listening to the show, got yourself a tape recorder and a microphone, go talk
to some people for us and send me stuff, that would be fun. CyberBeatNation in LA, February
14th through 16th, huge, huge tournament. They're giving away a Max2 machine in freestyle.
They are giving away a Max2 machine in freestyle. A couple rounds of freestyle they'll be doing.
It might be on a DDR Extreme machine, the competition, if it's out by them. Perfect
Attack, they're going to give away a BeatMania 2DX arcade style controller for the winner
of Perfect Attack. So, I'm sorry, but they're not calling it Perfect Attack. They're calling
it Stepping, Stepping Category or Stepping Challenge? Stepping Attack, Step Attack? I
don't know. Sorry, I'm messing it up. I'm running through these very quickly. I don't
really have a lot of time to read into detail in this tournament. But if you want more information
on that tournament, it will be coming to ddrspot.com in the next few days. They're going to take
some pre-registration there, so keep an eye on that. Or there is a thread in the DDR Freak
DDR Freak Tourney Forum. Early next year in Fremont there's going to be a
competition at a pizza joint and that's run by one of our fans DCB. He's a cool guy
so I'm sure that's going to be a kick butt tourney. Outside of California, I'm
trying to find some well-responded to threads, there's going to be a tournament
on December 21st in Baltimore, the town that doesn't listen to Orange Lounge
according to our rankings, but there is going to be a tournament at East Point
a great mall on December 21st in Baltimore, so if you're in that area you should check
it out. December 7th, I know I shouldn't promote that because I don't listen to this show,
but you know, you never know. Springfield has a tournament the other day, so that's
already done. We don't have results for that yet, my bad. My bad. There's a dancing stage
tournament in Sweden coming up yay that should be fun that should be a fun
tournament that will be good of course there's no location get all I gotta say
is Swedish chicks and DDR Swedish chicks and DDR amen to that you know what this
this um hey you know what I still like watching can I get a hallelujah hallelujah
you know you know what I will give you since we're talking about DDR tournaments
this is sweet and this is what i will give you
there's nothing to do with that
radio
with the ping pong ball
sweetest chef
yes i can squawk like a chicken
there's going to be a a tournament on the fourteenth of december in wales in england
it's going to be an english tournament
horrible horrible no loss access to the good the different my bad
mother-in-law section two funny
anyone with a good example of the well shacks and listen to the parents catch
i don't think i'm going to have to look at it but he is doing a well shacks
all right
is fighting for the field
it
uh... it's on the other side of the oh i mean it's pushing up crazy haha
somebody just so i did a chat room really huge
jabberwocka abba
that'll be a cool sweetest her what
we should probably place
erotic abba i think that's a damn good idea of the next break we're gonna do a
tribute to have other than swedish chicks india r
in roanoke park on december twenty first they're gonna be doing a winter charity
Perfect Attack Tournament for a Red Octane 2 mat.
Word.
Yes, bring canned goods.
The charity is for a Red Octane 2 mat.
Buy me a Red Octane 2 mat.
No, it's called the Winter Charity Tournament.
I don't know.
I'm assuming that part of the money goes to buy the mat,
and the other part goes to charity.
That's how it works.
Gasp.
Gosh, you guys.
Well, maybe it's another tournament
this Red Octane sponsored because Red Octane owns your soul if you play DDR and they sponsor
every tournament except the ones that are... From what I heard is Red Octane is actually
going to be selling some of their products like their ignition pads and Gamestops now.
Woo! So... Um, I can get confirmation on that, hello? Um, by the way, nothing like that's
been told to me and I'm always told everything that happens for Bemani in relation to Gamestop.
I don't care! I have medal stages! So there! Ha ha!
So those were some upcoming tournaments. Enjoy.
I would love to go to the Swedish one.
I want to go...
Yeah, I know. Bikini babes. Big boner. Alright.
First of all, playing DDR with no chest support sucks.
I can say this safely as the resolution.
Oh, I've always wondered. Let's ask a girl about their boobs.
Jamie, if you were to DDR in the nude, would that really hurt?
Would you get slapped in the face?
Well, first of all, I haven't, but I have played in my pajamas.
Just imagine it.
No, imagine having large amounts of your skin pulled away from your flesh and stuffed, and
then imagine jumping up and down like that.
Ouch!
Come on, every boy wants to know this.
What's DDR with boobies like?
Painful!
What is the best way to- do you like having your boobs restrained when you play DDR?
It's like, you want to tie them down?
Shut up.
Shush.
No, I have to do the quote.
Penfold.
Shush.
Anyone who gets that is cool.
What if we reduced ourselves to series?
I tried, ladies and gentlemen.
I don't know, does it hurt being able to play DDR naked?
Do you like your balls pop around or something?
No.
Actually!
Alright, no.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, my balls aren't D-sized, though, so I would know, they're not even C or B.
You'd be a ball bra!
Only a coco-
Who's got the biggest balls of them all?
Only a coconut ball bra.
Yeah.
So nobody in the studio will admit to playing DR in the new-
to be an athletic supporter.
Nobody in the studio is going to admit to playing DDR in the nude.
Well, I don't play DDR at home.
That involves pulling out 45-pound stages, setting them on the ground.
Yeah, like I'm going to take the extra time to strip down naked to play DDR in my front room.
Why the hell did I do that?
That's stupid.
Not to mention that that room is actually kind of small.
You've got furniture in there.
Yeah, the dogs rain around.
And there's seven on the fucking Chihuahua, I mean, it's not a pretty picture.
Oh, Brad's back in the room.
Brad, have you ever played DDR in the nude?
That's for me to know and you to find out.
Um, actually, honestly, no, I haven't.
I've thought about it.
I thought about doing intercourse while playing DDR, too.
That would be interesting.
It's like a couple, it's a whole new meaning to the couple dance.
Oh, we had somebody in the chatroom admit to doing it at home.
Bombay plays DDR on the nude at home.
Okay, I definitely can...
I believe that, yeah.
Why am I not surprised?
Why am I scared?
Ow, my freaking ears!
Is anybody else submitting to playing DDR on the nude? No, nobody else. Okay.
I played DDR on my pajamas before, though.
How was that?
Painful.
Was it breezy?
Well, seeing as how my pajamas usually consist of, you know, big flannel pants and a tank top, then no, not very.
Okay.
Alright, we're going to stop being perverted now.
It's my old house in the hood.
Oh, it's your old house in the hood. Your house in the hood was cool.
Okay.
Uh, oh yes, I need to make the announcement, we're not going to be doing the cage match tonight because last week's song didn't get in until very late in the week
the week and we have the marathon going on all weekend long so it's not hardly
getting played at all plus we don't have all of our regular listeners so
tonight's cage match is postponed well can we put both in the rotation no no we
can't you lose okay so let's see I'm trying to find my Abba covers and I
I think I only have one, but it's a good one.
So we will play that one, if I can find it.
However, when we do come back from this break,
we are going to do the FUs of the week.
So send those to me over a private message in the channel
right now.
Or email them.
Or email them to orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
We're going to do all of your FUs of the week
right after this break.
I wasn't jealous before we met Now every woman I see is a potential friend
Another says if it isn't nice You caught me saying that smoking was my only fight
Now it isn't true, now everything is new And all I've learned has all the turns I think of you
Don't go wasting your emotion
Lay all your love on me
It was like shooting a certain light
A little small time is mine and baby, I'm stuck
I still don't know what you've done with me
I've grown up old but you've never felt so easily
You're the kind of fear
And I don't have it near
I'm satisfied, I keep my pride
I beg you dear
Don't come wasting your emotion
Play all your love for me
Don't come sharing your devotion
Lay all your love on me
I've had a few little love affairs
They didn't last very long
And they've been pretty scarce
I used to think that there's something but It takes the truth even more incomprehensible
Cause everything is new And everything is new
And all I've learned has overdone What can I do
Don't come wasting your devotion Lay all your love on me
Don't go sharing your devotion
Lay all your love on me
What in the world is wrong with me?
Oh, it's time to come back to the sky
Ah, you have seven days left
What's left of everything?
You can't take me away
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Glance adapts to the lifelong
Even if it doesn't look right
Asakara mama de
Maisatsu mo tsukuku
Itoshii aroku wa
Asu mou konai
Saron de onai dori
Ko higa kutayo
Jumon no shina wo mou konai
Mou mou mou konai
Itoshii karo jamou mou konai
Let's go somebody!
We'll go somewhere!
Bitch, get a new song, an open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
That's right, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, a special taped edition tonight.
We are taping on Saturday, but we've got a lot of people, a lot of our regulars are joining
us here on Saturday night, but if unfortunately you weren't able to listen until Sunday night,
that's okay too.
We forgive you.
We're all going out and getting a life this week, so we had to change a few things.
Now comes that part of the show that's everybody's favorite.
Jamie, please explain the F.U. of the Week, why it was created, what it's here for.
We're pissed and we're not gonna take it anymore.
We're not gonna take it.
No!
That's the song. You know what? That's what my new F.U. song ought to be. I don't give a shit if it has nothing to do
with Bomani. That's the song I want.
Okay.
Here we go. Jamie's gonna start it off because she's the most angsty.
So here we go, the FUs of the week.
Okay, the first thing that gets the big fuck you is my computer.
My hard drive died.
As in broken.
As in, it wouldn't even reformat.
My computer wouldn't boot one morning, so as your fam was off work, so he was gonna put the restore dust in and
fix everything and make it happy again, and it didn't make it happy.
It said, C drive is damaged.
So I'm sitting here going, oh crap, oh crap, oh crap all day at work.
Um, basically, as it turned out, I didn't have to buy a new hard drive.
Although, the good thing that came out of it is that I now have a 120 gigabyte hard drive
with the 8 megabyte cache, so it's pretty cool.
But still, I lost about 60 gigabytes worth of information
and some photographs that I can't get replaced because my mom's ex-husband destroyed them.
Fuck you, Michael.
Not her current husband Michael, but her ex-husband Michael.
Her current husband's cool. Anyway, that's the best point.
It's just distressing, because I have, like I said, a lot of stuff on there, but I just can't get again.
And the ironic thing is that I was going to be backing everything up today, so... that sucks.
That's better.
That's your only...
That and RO again.
My grandpa and mine.
All right.
Dad, there's nobody for me to play Phantasy Star Online with.
As soon as I can, I will. I'm buying that game as soon as it comes out.
Or as soon as I can get it.
All right? Cool. All right, Matt, Matt's turn.
My first idea goes to the creators of TGR Max 2
and the fact that
they have to program so complexly that
a simple peon like myself who has no programming knowledge will ever play packet. Why?
why? Why won't you let me mess with this like everyone else does? Anyway, so, yeah, F.U.
does a stupid max 2-disc because it's gonna suck and I can't do anything with him. Um,
F.U. does a sub splash even though I'm going there tonight, um, for having all the games
broken because they don't give a damn, and F.U. the fucking kid was playing Speed Demon
all night on Thursday because I couldn't play Speed Demon because the fucker was taking
it over. Kick his ass. F you that stupid kid who's a speed demon. And aside from that,
you know, not too much stuff I'm mad at, other than stupid people, stupid drivers, people
ask dumb questions, that kind of thing. So, that's all.
Alright, thank you for that angsty little rant.
My FU of the Week goes out to people that you go out on dates with that don't return your phone calls.
How fucked up is that? I hate you.
My other FU of the Week... I don't know if I want to get into it.
I have another pretty long FU to lead.
My other FU of the week goes to immaturity.
And people that try to send cryptic little messages that are really stupid and immature
and try to make things into contests that aren't contests that are much more than contests.
FU to stupid boys.
p0k3smot42o
fucking rat. I don't care what you say. Any song that has a groovy little dance to go
with it. Rules. But those other step songs, yeah, they all suck, I'm sorry.
YOSFVB says, F you to traffic and to people with microwaves creating interference which
disabled my telepathic waves from reaching Jamie to answer Propel. And fuck you to all
those people now trying to use Propel as an adjective. And fuck you to Orange Lounge for
for what seems to be porn talk prohibition.
When did we ever stop talking about porn on here?
In fact, I think we've had an increase in it.
Actually, I've got more I can talk to about that later.
No, you're banned.
Orange Beanie says,
F you to Naoki for getting to spend
so much time for Polteri.
Orange Beanie, by the way, actually being a Polteri fan.
And F you to The Point for making my fifth mixed dreams dead.
Dead, I tell you.
FU to the point, go to Crestview, they have 5th.
Oh my lord, 23rd Magus says, I have a continued FU to Nori Nori Nori, as usual, a big FU to
being broke, which eliminates my chances of going to Scandi RVGL until January, cough,
donate to the United Magus College Fund, and a family sized FU to Nero's interface.
I accidentally moved a folder while making a CD and produced 5 coasters until I found
out what happened.
Fuck you ahead.
Your program sucks, you bitches.
Go learn English, you fuckers.
I'm punishing you with those FUs for not agreeing with me in the match game.
Bwah!
Supper!
Brak2000 says, FU to Captain Jack for not doing a cover of Oh Nick Please Not So Quick.
I agree, I agree.
Dang!
Lots of FUs from Stresa, FU'd who his ex, she dumped me the day after my 20th birthday,
but we're still so hung up on each other and she's killing me, but I'll survive, and I'd
I'd also like to throw an F.U. at my parents.
They've been plotting against me to kick out since June, and I'd like to shove a horse-sized F.U. in my mommy's booty.
Why does my mom deserve a horse-sized F.U., especially in the booty?
For finding ways to throw my flaws back at my face for childish reasons. Oh my.
Too bad Sally Jessy's not still around, because that would sound like something you need to go talk to Sally Jessy about.
Maybe you could go to Dr. Phil.
twen says at you within thirty minutes i found out the girl i love the got into a
major car accident and is engaged and has a two-year-old in a six months on
well that's
what happened to the lesbian
i'm sorry to hear about
the car accident that's that's a bummer
well i would say
if you did that
if it was a lesbian and i'd say it's karma coming back to play
no it's not
Let's check the old mailbag.
Some people sent in their FUs because they knew we wouldn't be on on Sunday.
Vidpower says, for the third week in a row, my main FU still goes to germs.
My cough has gotten worse this week and my throat is sore because of it. Also, FU to reading
boring schoolbooks and FU to the dark environments in Metroid Prime. I literally can't
see a Waldus a few inches away from my face, but a very fun game nonetheless.
You know what that cough is? It's the Ebola. You're gonna die. Bye.
F-E-B-O-L-A
not letting me go to rvgl on friday night just because i threw up thank you for sharing to my
mom again for getting me a fubu sweatshirt for hanukkah not knowing what fubu meant
what does fubu mean for us by us huh okay and to probably f you to my mom again for probably not
wanting to take me to tourney next friday but it's not a definite fu yet because i don't know for
for sure okay see you guys next time
thousand
beautiful
what's wrong
it would be totally
god i always get the chair of the city so it's there
all you know said he'd be sent us one more pocketed power for being conscious
of the fact that he is sick
yet still serving food is restaurant
old nights
okay kill some
that was our lovely at the use of the week thank you everybody for
participating we do appreciate it that reminds me yes yes we do have dates now
for make edit get porn oh cool yes let's talk about make edit get porn ah
let's see no problem is I don't remember the dates are right now because I can't
remember what I type on these boards I'd look at so many of them every week but
um yeah make edit get porn we've got um the date set for it I believe if I
Fuck you. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck you, babe. You're beautiful. Fucking beautiful. A big F-you to you, Rob.
Oh, I'm sorry. You were talking about pornography.
Okay. All the entries are due by Sunday, December 22nd at midnight.
And where must they submit them?
They must send them to my email or give them to me in person.
They can be in any format as long as there's some way I can see the step file or step chart
or have an edit file for it.
That's all I really need.
nightmare underscore
so it's nightmare hunter
yahoo dot com
uh... make sure you put the nice little underscore there between nightmare and hunter
and uh...
other than that you know
if you're local you know give it to me in person and all entries will be judged
on uh... january the fifth
that's a sunday
and they're gonna be announced on right here on orange island radio the winners right yes cool
And I have quite a bit of porn to grant, so there might actually be for a second.
Now very briefly, for those new to the show, what is Make Edit Get Porn?
Well, I've held many edit contests before.
I decided to do one that's a little different, just exclusive to the home version of Max
USA.
This time around, instead of giving out my normal prizes, which would be videos and DVDs
and stuff, I'm giving out pornography!
Porno tapes!
Yay!
And so we have Make It Get Porn, just like the title says.
And you'll get a big box of, you know, porno tapes, pretty much that consist of mostly
Playboy movies.
I mean, I don't really consider them porn, I mean, they're kind of skidimax, they're
kind of porn, but they're not, I don't know, it's hard to say.
But you know, you'll get those, and I mean, those are pretty expensive, actually, they're
about $22.98 a piece, so you are saving quite a bit of money to be able to go out and buy
those tapes and find out that they're crap.
If a woman wins, then we'll just have to find some boy porn to throw in the box.
Yes.
Pun intended.
Anyways, so that's going on, and like I said, you've got no time to do it.
So get your Trini Mix 3 stuff done this week, and then get your Make It Again Porn stuff
done next week.
All right, that was Make It Again Porn.
Let's talk about some new shit that's coming out in Japan soon.
We've got the Dance Mania series, you hear some of their tracks here right here on Orange
Lawn's radio.
They've got some new albums coming out very soon.
On December 11th, Classical Speed comes out.
That's all your favorite classical tunes on fucking crack.
Oh, we even have some real audio clips we can play for you.
This is the Radetsky March by Strauss.
We're going to listen to a clip of that.
This is from the Classical Speed album.
This is track number two.
Hopefully this works.
Perform a speed orchestra.
This is by the Speed Orchestra.
It's queuing up here.
Give it a minute.
preview of classical speed right here on Orange Lawn's radio, which is timing out
on me. Wait, here we go. Loading, loading, here we go.
That was the Rydetsky March.
That was done by the Speed Orchestra.
Other ones that should be noted, they have the Saber Dance.
No, we don't have a clip of Saber Dance, unfortunately.
Swan Lake, Marchy, Military, Victory March.
Want to hear a Victory March?
Or how about, how about let's hear a clip of Ode to Joy.
This is a Beethoven song, so let's hear this clip of Ode to Joy.
Everybody knows this song.
Everybody who ever took piano had to play this song at one point or another.
Another?
Let's hear this one.
by the way
Hey Tobin! Hey Tobin! Hey Tobin! Hey Tobin!
Very nice. Somebody in the shower room says, oh, that's kind of like end of the century.
Yes. First of all, End of the Century is kind of like Ode to Joy, get it right.
It's a little bit similar, yes. There's a brand new Captain Jack album coming out.
Rock the Fuck On. It's called Party Warriors. Fucking rock, that's all I had to say.
We only have a clip of one song, but it's got a great name, so I'm sure it's awesome.
This is a song called Centerfold, and actually it looks like this album is just a bunch of remixes.
So we got Heya, Iko Iko, Party Warriors, and this one, Centerfold.
Hey, hey, it's a bag!
Oh my gosh, it's Centerfold.
Dude, I'm gonna be 80 to make you into that.
Go captain, go captain, go captain, alright that was a centerfold, a little bit of a clip
there.
And also coming out, Dance Mania Speed 10.
And this is going to scare a lot of you.
The very first track is Nancy and the Boys, and they're covering everybody's favorite
artist these days. They're doing a cover of an Avril Lavigne song. Let's hear how awful
it is.
I can be on a speed album, jesus!
Oh, the OSF-EB wants a cover of Dirty on Speed 10. No, unfortunately that's not going to happen.
But we do get some other cool stuff. We have A Little Less Conversation. That was the Elvis song that made a big comeback. We have a clip of that.
That's the second track on the album. Done by the CJ Crew.
who did some
yeah i don't really like this what else is on the album
uh... wild child privatized give it up relax
masque nada i do i do i do i wonder if that's the other song
he got hooked up by jenny rom
champagne supernova hope god the oasis pong
get the party started
sweet fly with you
although i was a place i don't think that's not that you do you know some
please tell me didn't ruin that song
i opened her every day
joy to the world saber dance drop-top heaven
of god i hope that's not a cover of the deejays sammy song
we might be in for some real hell on speed ten yeah i know which cover brian
Radio Rockin', Want Your Love, Here To Stay, and we have another clip of Sectember by DJ Speedo. Love the name.
It's almost as lovely as DJ Mangu.
I know this song. This is probably going to be like a DVR.
So those are some new things that we can look forward to from the
Toshiba EMI series is coming out very soon.
And since we never really talked about it, let's talk about some other things that we've
had come out recently.
DanceMania EX-1 just came out not too long ago, had some good stuff on it.
The return of Smile DK, Captain Jack and Erotic all on a DanceMania album, that was pretty
cool.
And Lollipop, actually I do have Lollipop on my CD that I brought today.
Oh, cool.
I do have Lollipop actually on the drive somewhere.
I'll be perfectly happy if I don't have to hear that song, thank you.
I also have doggy style.
That sounds scary.
Weird, I didn't realize people left the house here.
I just had somebody come online who I thought was here at the house.
Uh, let's...
I guess we're going to go to a break, and when we come back we're going to do a list list.
I don't know if we have enough people to do a list list. Do we still have one person here?
I think she's still playing
Animal Crossing. We'll see if we have enough people to do listless.
We'll try to do that. If not, we'll think of something. We'll just do a three-person
listless if we have to.
We'll do a three-person listless if we have to. Fine.
In the meantime, we're going to take a break, and I had a request for something, and I don't even remember what it was.
I could talk about NewTek porn.
Okay, talk about what you want to talk about.
hold on let me see if we have anybody else in the front room to do
I get the chair
No you don't, I get the chair
Comfy
He's
looking semi-orgasmic now
It feels so good
Is it squishy?
Anyways, NewTek. NewTek's a new
studio we actually start distributing at my company now
they're an adult anime studio
and they were so kindly enough to send me three samples of their products.
So, here today
I am going to review three different titles. We have Leather Man
volume three,
we have DNA Hunters volume one, and we also have one called
uh... shut out, I don't remember the last one. I think Kelly or Katie, I can't remember what the name is.
I'll just call it Katie.
So, start off with DNA Hunter volume one.
uh... this is a story about
reviewing an important
the other it's a basically about there's this woman her husband died
and she really wants to have a and
problem is that she was ever husband's baby so
in order to do that she has to kind of cloned his DNA or something like that
anyways
so in order to get the money to do this she has to become a DNA hunter now what
DNA hunter is is basically
it's a woman
Women come to this company, and they say, I want this man's baby.
So in order to do that, they have to have these women that work for this company go
and have sex with these people, and then they collect the DNA, or semen, from these people,
and then turn sell it to the women that want to have those, you know, celebrities' babies.
Thus, DNA Hunter.
I have to say that this was an utter disappointment.
The title sucked ass.
It really was boring as hell.
Um, the very first, um, the thing that she has to act, the guy she has to have sex with is her, like, old boss from her previous job who's, like, this really old guy.
And no one wants to see some hot chick screw in an old guy, even if it is animated, so.
Really awful. I hear the rest of the series is good, but no. Awful, awful, awful.
Leather Man Volume 3.
Pretty interesting, um, title since I have to start watching it in the middle.
It's basically this guy carrying around a sack of money.
I don't know why he's carrying around a sack of money, because obviously I haven't seen the first episode, so I don't really know.
And he's going around and people just start having sex with him for no apparent reason whatsoever.
They're trying to steal the money, and it's kind of like Golden Boy, but X-rated.
You've got the guy, he's making women feel better about themselves, giving them more confidence and stuff, yet has sex with them and stuff like that.
I don't know. It's pretty good. No real plot to get in the way. Lots of sex. Fun, fun, fun.
The other one, I believe it was called Katie. I can't remember what the actual name was.
It's about this kind of cheerleader, not really a cheerleader, but she's like the head of the, kind of the pep team or whatever.
And she is being blackmailed by the rest of her team to do all these things like, you know, do cheers with, like, a vibrant strap dinner and stuff, and kind of stuff like that.
And she ends up at the very end turning into a slut. So you get to watch this, you know, cute girl get transformed into a slut at the end of the movie.
So, of course, everyone likes that. That's it. That's all I've got.
Beautiful.
a quick break and we'll be back to talk about something bimani related and maybe actually we're
gonna do a list list when we come back by request this break this is the only song we're gonna play
this break because it's kind of long it's six minutes long but it's very cool it's out phase
doing 0.59 live so uh it starts off a little bit quiet though so don't think that we dropped or
anything it just has a quiet intro it's got one of those windy noises things so uh enjoy this song
and we'll be back.
Oh
Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
Do you want to be accepted by Hollywood?
No!
Do we care what people think of us?
Do we want people to kiss our ass?
Yes!
of us? No! Do we want people to kiss our ass? Yeah! Extreme Bimani Radio, that's us, Orange
Lounge Radio. Hello once again my friends, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio pre-taped
this week. We're live on Saturday night, December the 7th, but this is actually technically
the show for December the 8th. It'll be played both nights. So we're gonna do a
little segment called List List. It's everybody's favorite. Tonight the topic
is, and those of you in the chat room will get to assist us with voting on the
winners of this, tonight's topic is the top three things I hate about Christmas.
Yes, it's the top things that we hate about Christmas.
The way the list works, the list list segment works is that we're going to compile a list.
Our fabulous in-studio celebrities will compile a list of their top things that they hate about Christmas.
And then one by one we'll each eliminate something that we hate about Christmas,
or that we might actually like about Christmas, someone else hates.
Things that should not be on the list.
And then the chat room will vote on the ultimate list of things that they hate about Christmas.
Let's start off. Who started last time?
Jamie, did you start last week? I don't remember. Let's start with Loki.
Let's start with Loki.
Loki, what is the number three thing that you hate about Christmas?
Gotti Christmas decorations.
Basically, you know, the white trash light setups, you know, in front of people's houses.
Gotti Christmas Decorations is number three on...
Does it look like Christmas threw up all over the houses?
Exactly.
We were just driving down the street the other day and Jamie said,
Christmas barfed on that house. Christmas barfed on that house.
So, Gotti Christmas Decorations, Loki's number three answer.
We have the Rice Princess in the studio. She's helping us out tonight with Listless.
Irene, what is your number three pick for Thing You Hate About Christmas?
Well, you have to say dumb, nosy relatives.
When you have to see those relatives you never see but Christmas time and they always want
to know what you're doing.
It's like, well, if I wanted you to know, I would have told you.
I would have sent you a letter or called you or something.
Dumb, nosy relatives, Irene's number three answer.
Very nice, very nice.
Thank you.
My number three answer would be parking lots.
I hate parking lots normally and around Christmas time, it gets ten times as worse.
People cannot drive in a parking lot, they are cutthroat going for each other's spaces,
they stay and they park their car in the middle of the aisle, so when you're trying to go
around to get a spot, you're trapped there, that shit pisses me off more than anything
else in the whole world.
Jamie, you're number three pick for something you hate about Christmas.
Decorations going up before Halloween.
Oh, decorations that go up before Halloween, very nice.
What about decorations that stay up after Valentine's Day?
I don't know what to steal out there, I just don't like them going up for my favorite holiday.
Alright, what if they're orange lights though?
If it's for Halloween, then sure.
Cool.
Alright.
Loki, your number two answer for a thing that pisses you off about Christmas.
Christmas music.
All of it.
All of it must go.
Don't change your music programming.
the artist that made it. Hunt them down. I will pay ransom. Actually, bounty. A bounty
for everybody that makes Christmas music. I want them all dead.
Okay. All right, Christmas music. Irene, your number two answer.
Having no money or resources to buy or make gifts.
Sex. Anything else you want to elaborate on there?
All right.
My number two answer is political correctness.
Because somewhere right now there's probably somebody that would be whining about how we
shouldn't say Christmas because it's the winter holiday season and everybody celebrates something
different.
But you know what?
There are some people out there that don't even celebrate holidays.
So you know what?
Just Christmas for all practical purposes means everything, okay?
I'm not like a Bible-thumper religious person, but I just say, Christmas, it's presents,
you get stuff.
I don't care what other people celebrate, but don't freakin' get all huffy and puffy
when somebody else, you know, celebrates something you don't.
You don't have to try so damn hard to be different.
Just go with it.
Rawr!
I hate political correctness.
And this, the thing that kind of triggered this was that we have this thing at work that
we do every winter, and we're not even allowed to call it, we can't call it a Christmas party,
You can't call it a Hanukkah party.
We can't call it a Kwanzaa party.
We can't even call it a holiday party because not everyone celebrates holidays.
We have to call it a winter appreciation party.
That is so stupid.
Jamie, your number two thing that you hate about Christmas?
I have one that's more personal, so I'm not going to say that one.
Okay.
I'll mention it.
like being away from my family for the fourth Christmas in a row, you know, since they're
all out in Alabama, so I'll put it this way.
I think that what I don't like about the whole holiday season is just that, how over commercialized
it is.
Over commercialized, all right.
You know, it's always buy, buy, buy, buy, and people don't seem to realize that there's
supposed to be more meaning to the season than just, I mean, I like shopping for gifts
like giving them because that's just how I am but there's when it's being used as
an excuse for more people to put money in their pockets I don't like that
all right that's a very good rant I like that all right Loki number one thing
that pisses you off about Christmas those people dressed up like Santa
Claus outside of grocery stores outside of malls everything working for the
The Salvation Army. F you to the Salvation Army. They don't need my money any time of
the year, nor during Christmas, and they aren't getting a penny of it.
Thank you, Mr. Grinch.
Thank you.
Gosh, Scrooge.
I hope you see the three ghosts.
All right.
I'm kidding.
Irene, the number one thing you hate about Christmas.
Not knowing what to get people for Christmas. I hate it. Just tell me what you want, what
you really, really want, and I'll get it for you.
Not knowing what to give people, alright, good answer.
My number one answer is already on the list, but I'll just say it anyway, we'll just have
a duplicate.
My number one thing I hate about Christmas is Christmas carols, so that goes right along
with Christmas music.
You can pick something other than Christmas carols on the line.
Okay, how about Christmas carolers?
Like the beginning of the Addams Family movie? That's the best thing ever.
I hate, okay, I was going to say you could have used this one. Christmas TV specials.
No, because the Grinch is cool. No, no, no. I'm not talking about the Grinch.
Grinch is cool, keep the Grinch. If I'm talking about like they have this one here, it's a
musical special with John Ritter hosting. John Ritter should not be on TV.
Not since Three's Company anyway. Yeah, Three's Company was cool.
All right, Jamie, the number one answer.
Misinterpretation of the holiday, as in all these, and I have to give background, I was
born Southern Baptist, you know, I still believe in God in general, but I lean more toward
the pagan side of my beliefs, and I love it when people go, oh, Jesus was born on Christmas
Day.
That's bullshit!
He was born in like June, okay?
This is a pagan holiday, okay?
The yule tree, the log, you know, the candles, all of it is a pagan holiday.
Get it right.
If you want dates and proof and everything, I can go grab all of my college books and
pull that right up where that tradition started.
I actually think that somebody posted a link in the chat room if you want more information
on that.
Thank you.
I think.
I am so sick of this, and that's part of the reason why I stopped going to the specials
at church was because of this.
Oh, Christmas Day, blah, blah, no!
You're wrong, you're stupid.
You're buying into what you've been fed all of your life.
Try thinking for yourself.
I don't like that.
No, that's my number one pet peeve about Christmas.
Alright.
I just stopped going to church because it was damn boring, and I didn't really care.
Except there was this one priest that looked like Weirdo Yankovic, and that entertained
myself enough to stay away for about half of it.
All right. Boy, not a single Balmani-related thing on this list. I'm really proud of you
guys. Okay. You know what? I don't know. I'm going to entertain something here in the studio
here. I don't think I feel comfortable eliminating any of these, because they're all things that
really suck about Christmas. So I think as a Christmas present, we should let our chat
room pick from all of these options. What do you guys think?
Sure.
All right. So we're not going to eliminate anything. You guys can pick anything from
this list, because I don't know about the others, but I don't...
We're extra bitter today.
i don't uh... i can't i don't see anything on this list i really feel
comfortable getting rid of so i can't even at the list i hate the stupid like
people that come around working on the wedding
the boy scouts and girl scouts want me to buy shit
i didn't need to know gracias
but but but
i love it
the adams family is like the best christmas movie
uh... some things that the uh... channel girl scout chat room suggestions that
that we missed.
Blood chip flavor.
Things in the chatroom that we missed.
Eggnog.
I like eggnog.
I know, I like eggnog too.
I like alcoholic eggnog.
Getting socks and underwear.
Hey, I could use that, okay?
My socks and underwear just disappear.
They just like, whoa, whoa, damn underpants gnomes.
Underpants gnomes.
And let's see, what else did they say?
and they were saying Silent Hill owns you.
I guess that's it.
Those are the only two things.
Okay, so send in your votes now
over private message in the channel.
And to celebrate, how about a little Christmas cheer
for all of you here on Orange Lounge Radio.
You got one minute to send in your votes right now.
That's all the I will do, I'll see you tomorrow I will be drinking a toast to you, it's such
A special day
Tonight is the night for our lovers
We wish we could have
This feeling
Through the weather here
Christmas is here
If you, I want you, I want you, I want you
Night falls on you
And if you want me and you
You can buy me what you want
Night, nightfall, it's the start of a new year
Oh, I'm falling, no, I can't, I must love you to be here
Just how did you know Christmas is here?
Can you hear me from above?
Do you feel the face of me?
What's been through?
We do in the air
Just in time
No one cares to stop Can you see me from above?
Do you share my frozen memories? Set it down
Let it in, let it out, let it out
Let us love, let it in
Please give me a new star tonight
To create a world full
Let's not face me Please give me back my yesterday
It's not for me Take my hand
Let's not face me
Oh
We indeed do have a list.
Here is the final list of the top three things you all hate about Christmas.
We helped, you voted, here it is.
The number three thing that you hate about Christmas is Christmas carolers.
The number two thing you hate about Christmas is that it's over commercialized, with hallmarks
stamped on the back.
And the number one thing that everybody in the chat room and we all hate about Christmas
is political correctness.
Yeah.
And that's correct spelled with one R.
Shut up, shut up.
Just shut up.
Correct.
Oh, they're saying I should use the movie, they're saying I should use the movie phone
voice.
and welcome to orange lounge radio if you want to hear a listless segment
press 1 now if you want to hear Jamie rant about something press 2 now if you
want a sim update press 3 now if you hate orange lounge hang up now you're
listening forever if you hate orange lounge shove this phone up your ass now
some people might do that we talk to me ask let's just ask mr. spanky about that
Oh, yes, we haven't heard from Mr. Spanky yet tonight.
I do believe we're going to do a Mr. Spanky update a little later.
Oh, now you're not so sure?
We need good porn tips.
We need good porn tips?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, we'll get Mr. Spanky back on the show right before it's over.
How's that sound?
Okay.
All right, cool.
Jamie, you've got to explain.
I noticed one F.U. you left out.
I don't remember if you talked about it last week, but you've got these Leet Max 2 shoes
and they're breaking.
I bought these vans, they're black and they have flames going up the sides and they're
already starting to tear up.
My last pair of vans lost to me like a whole freaking year and these are just falling to
bits so I got to get new man shoes.
But I'm going to wear these until they die, damn it.
Okay, I'm being asked to read a paper that 23rd Magus wrote that he got an A on.
It better be Bimani related or I'm not going to do it.
Oh yeah, there's an article in the paper, tell us about that, Matt.
Fuckin' vinyl, I haven't read it.
Anyways, my friend Eric, also known as Punkknight, he wrote an article in, I don't remember what
the magazine is.
Oh, it's a local paper here, uh, help me, don't, uh, Wired Herd or something like that?
Wired Head, I bet.
Yeah, something like that. Anyways, Wired Head magazine, and it's about DDR. I think Rob gets quoted on it.
Yeah, apparently. I haven't even seen it yet. I need to find a copy of it.
I know that there's a few down where my friend works, if you're local, down in Folsom at
uh, at um, shit, Pizza Place, um, Ciro's Pizza Place at um, Bloorveen and Prairie City Road.
So if you're local in Folsom, you can check it out there, otherwise, wherever Wired heads
at.
it like it enjoy it there I'm sorry well Matt was talking about wirehead Jamie is
noticing that if you shake a bottle or propel like a lot and then let it sit
there it looks like cum tasty this looks like it could do a lot of damage to some
sort of bodily orifice this propel bottle and and well Jamie what was your
comment as soon as you took a sip of that shake and water it ain't salty
That's right, it ain't salty.
Alright.
Let's...
HP...
Your HP tastes good.
Okay, here we go.
We're going to talk now.
We're going to read this paper.
It is Bemani-related because it's about Shaft.
That tournament.
So, 23rd Magus wrote this paper for one of his classes,
so I thought we'd read it,
and I'll give our little smart-ass comments on it.
How's that sound?
Here we go.
Yes, that's right.
Reading the paper, reading the paper.
Stand by to win.
I went to Shaft and all I got was this lousy roast beef.
One of my favorite and strangest hobbies is playing Dance Dance Revolution,
an arcade game in which you must step on arrow panels in time to the music.
Many people, such as myself, go further than the game requires,
working the arrows into a dance routine, in other words, weave freestyle.
Recently...
Not if you're white.
What?
Keep reading.
What are you laughing at, Logan?
Recently, Scandia Fun Center hosted a DDR tournament for those playing accuracy at...
What?
Read!
No, I want to know what the joke is.
Read.
Here, you shut it down.
Alright.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Can I finish?
Thank you.
Yes.
Okay, moving on with 23 Magus's Paper.
Recently, Scandia Fun Center hosted a DER tournament for those playing accuracy and freestylers.
The organizers decided to call it SHAPT. Sacramento hosts another fabulous tournament.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, Sacbimani hosts another fabulous tournament. Oh, you get docked three points for that.
He said Sacramento, not Sacbimani, so he gets docked three points.
It was quite witty, if I do say so myself.
I suppose I should go into detail about the three types of competition and exactly why they are important.
I've never seen anyone talk in an English paper.
Well, I suppose I ought to talk about this.
I suppose I ought to do my assignment.
Alright.
That way I don't leave non-DDR players, you unfortunate souls, you in the dust.
Accuracy attack is your standard play of DDR.
The object of the game is to hit every arrow step with the right timing.
I was not present during this competition, so you, dear reader, will be spared the agonizing details. Consider yourself lucky.
Regular freestyle players take the steps for a song and work them into a dance routine.
The routine always varies depending on the song and freestyler.
Some amazing feats have taken place in this competition, and their excitement levels rivals
that of any extreme sport.
A-Team Freestyle, also known as Old School Freestyle, is a demonstration of freestyling
techniques from several years back.
These routines utilize the safety bars at the back of the arcade machine, and incorporate
moves such as hand plants, hitting an arrow with hands instead of feet, and knee drops,
landing on an arrow with knees.
These often cause great pain to the performo- performo-
Nowadays, A-Team routines are generally considered childish and not cool anymore.
Personally, I think that A-Team routines have their biggest wow factor, but many don't share
my opinion.
Now that we're done with the background, let's get into the real meat of this.
I am, of course, talking about how I fit into this whole picture.
Through a little negotiating, green-whining, I managed to get into Shaft as an observer,
so I thought... or so I thought.
Instead, I participated in the most embarrassing and the most fun activity of my life, competing
in freestyles.
Uh, here's the rundown.
Midway through the freestyle competition, Rob and Janie, the MC and tournament organizer,
noticed that not enough people had signed up for competition.
I then decided to make an improv as a national freestyle category, which was one-third of the normal $15 entry fee.
Having only $10 on me, I decided to go for it.
Here was the catch.
Since it was improv, the machine was set to roulette mode, which selects a song at random.
If I had been able to pick my own song, things would have been momentally different.
Monumentally different.
Momentally, monumentally different.
Damn you, big words.
Namely, I probably would have had a routine set up, which defeats the purpose of improv.
As it was, I embarrassed myself royally, doing rave moves to a bubblegum pop song.
It was entertaining in its incognuity, but it was not a winner.
Not a winner.
Stand by to lose.
Boom.
Anyway, the wild part of my experience was not in my improv entry, but in what happened while waiting.
It was chaos incarnate.
Good friend Justin was going crazy with the deep fryer, dropping in everything he thought
he could get away with.
I still remember stuffing my face with deep fried Twinkies and candy corn.
It was fun, albeit messy.
Much of the time I was in the party room slash broadcast booth, talking with my friends and
helping out with the Orange Lounge Radio broadcast.
The broadcast was full of inside jokes, all of which were too rude and obscure to mention.
I do remember Justin taking over the airwaves, telling me to stop hitting them, although
Although I was doing no such thing, it was so moderately funny.
A few times I came out of the party room to watch some freestylers work their magic on
the stage.
It is from one of the routines that my story gets its name.
Mr. Wendell, a popular freestyler, was doing a comedy routine to Orion 7-8, one of the
more annoying songs.
One of his friends was holding up a hot roast beef sandwich, playing keep away with poor
Wendell.
At certain points in the song, the crowd, scooping the song lyrics, chanted, Roast beef!
Roast beef!
Hot!
The whole routine had me literally on the floor laughing, especially at the end, where
Wendell finally snatched the sandwich, took a bite, then backhanded his buddy, who was
sneaking up behind him.
That was Holland, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Applause.
Applause. Rob, always the charmer, stood on stage and declared,
I love stories with happy endings, don't you?
More applause accompanied by laughter and wolf whistles, a few of which I must admit were mine.
Aww, that was a beautiful paper. Thank you for sharing that with us. That was the end, right?
Oops, I did it again. I closed the window.
Oh well, I'm assuming that was the end of the paper. Oh, here it is.
Yes, that was the end of the paper.
Very well written. How do you guys think he did on that? What kind of grade?
It was out of 36 points, I'll tell you that. What do you think he got?
I give it a 34.
34. Out of 36 points. What would you give it, Logie?
It was grammatically correct.
Yes.
What grade's he in?
I don't know. In high school.
I think he's freshman or sophomore. That's a guess.
I guess it was alright. It started going off topic towards the end though.
I mean, you were explaining the different categories in DDR and then all of a sudden you just saw something else. I don't know.
It sounds a lot like my senior project.
No.
See, what happens, I think what happens is you procrastinate and you wait till the last
minute to write your paper and it ends up coming out like this.
So what do you think, Rob?
You guys have got to give me grades.
What did you get?
Grades?
Hold on, Matt.
What did you get?
I have 36 points.
34.0596 points.
All right, very nice.
For grammatical correctness, yes, I guess I'll give it to you.
Oh, my bad.
He's a senior.
My bad.
He's a senior in high school.
That's bad. He's getting pissed.
In that case, F.
In that case, F, you should know better.
There's not much difference between freshmen and seniors when it comes to curriculum when I was in high school.
Your grade, Brad?
I'd say 31.
31? No, you give him a B.
I give him 59. I give him 59 points for that. That was beautiful.
There is no 59, you fuckhead.
No, but this is what's funny. You know how many points he did get? 33. He got 33 points.
three points for missing the Sac-Pomani thing, just like we said.
You know what? I only learned two things in high school.
What's that? How to avoid people, and then a mole of 6.02 times 10 to the negative 23rd power.
I'm doing the way over my head thing right now where I put my hand up.
I took AP chemistry.
gave that paper a double S. That's winner. Oh, I'm vibrating. It's vibrating, but it's
a restricted vibrate, so I don't want to answer restricted numbers. Okay, um, wow, we've still
got about a good fifteen minutes to fill in the show. No, no ferret filling. What else
can we talk about? You brat, you wanna rant about something? Hey, fucking guy! This is
Gurbal. Your daughter, she come to my house, and she kicked my dog. I wanna tell a joke.
I wanna tell a joke. Okay. I need joke music. I need the... You guys all bit it over. The
Salakun. You guys all bit it over on the, uh, thing. Hey, I'm talking to you. Let me
Let me tell you something from keyboard mania. Something happy.
No keyboard for you.
Amongst the full coffee in my boots!
Okay, that kind of fits.
Anyway, the guy was walking in the woods, and he was lost and lost and lost for days.
So he chances upon this house, and he notices that there are telephone wires coming out of the house, so he knocks on the door.
and this ancient old man answers the door.
He goes, please sir, please, can I use your telephone?
I'm lost in the woods.
The guy goes, sure, you can use my telephone
and you can stay at my house, too,
until someone can come get you.
But my one rule is that you cannot sleep with my daughter.
OK.
So he goes in the house, uses the telephone,
has dinner with the family, and the guy's daughter was really hot.
He couldn't help it, she just weren't mad
and played the tune of the table.
So, late at night, the guy speaks out of his room and goes and, you know, has his way with her, and then goes to bed.
He wakes up in the morning with a gigantic rock on his chest.
And there's a note attached to it.
First greatest of all tortures, a gigantic rock stuck on your chest.
Then he goes, well, shit.
Throws it out the window.
And then he feels a searing pain, and another note appears.
Second greatest torture, right testicles tied to rock.
So, the guy leaps out of the window after it. He finds another note.
Third grade is torture. Left testicle tied to bedpost.
The end.
Ouch.
That was a nice joke.
Being a girl, I don't think you can completely appreciate the pain that I just felt right there.
What do you think, Matt?
I don't care. I heard that one lightning.
Fifth grade?
Well, fuck you then.
is there any another joke
this guy was in jail
he had been in jail for so long and hadn't gotten laid
he hadn't even been anyone's bitch
so he gets out of jail
and they give him his suit of clothing and twenty bucks
first thing he wants to do
is get laid
so he goes to a brothel
and he talks to the madam there and she's like well
our women are at least a hundred and twenty and up
He's like, do you have anyone that I can get for 20 bucks?
He's like, well, we can give you to Bertha.
So he gives him Bertha.
And Bertha's this woman with like one leg,
she has a peg leg, she's missing one arm,
and she's got a glass eye.
So the guy is trying his hardest
and he just can't get anything with Bertha.
She's like, look, why don't we do this?
So she takes out her glass eye, says, try this one.
So he goes out her eye, her eye socket,
and it's been the best lay he ever had in his life.
And he tells us, like, you know, next time I need to get some, I'm coming to you.
I, you know, you were the best ever.
He's like, okay, honey, I'll keep an eye out for you.
Ha ha ha ha.
Oh, dear good lord.
Okay, on that note, I think we're gonna take a quick break,
and then we're gonna come back and wrap up the show.
Sound good to you guys?
Yes?
We can wrap it up in ribbons and bows.
Oh, you want booty music? I'm sorry.
Well, I have this request, though, so I gotta play this first.
All right, I'm gonna play this, then we'll do something booty.
Okay, here we go.
We'll be right back.
Oh
It's Mr. Spanky, as promised, I'm here on the air to give you some tips.
Tonight I'm gonna read you a letter, because I don't know much about, well I do know a
thing or two about it, I have to admit you guys, not that there's anything wrong with
But today, we're going to be talking about fellatio tips.
So I'm going to read a letter for you guys.
You might need a translation of that, Mr. Spanky.
I'm sorry? Oh, fellatio. That's a blowjob.
Okay.
Fellatio means a blowjob.
All right.
This letter comes to us from a girl named Emmy.
She says,
My husband and I have been married ten years, and during this time,
my enjoyment for giving head has increased tremendously.
I have found the more I turn him on, the more it turns me off.
I'm sorry, the more it turns me on, I can't read today.
I start off by teasing him a little, flicking the head with my tongue, and licking the underside slowly from bottom to top.
I have also learned he likes me to deductively look at him while I'm doing this. It adds to the teasing.
One problem I had from taking his cock all the way, because I enjoy giving pleasure to him, so much I wanted to be able to deep throat.
I could do it once in a while, but most of the time I would gag, so I thought that if I could just numb my throat somehow, I would stop gagging.
That's when I figured it out. I bought some chloroceptic throat spray and put it in my nightstand.
The next time I gave him head, I had no problem swallowing his entire cock.
I can't tell you how turned on he was, and how turned on I was.
You can also use children's teething cream, but it doesn't have a pleasant taste, and it's harder to apply.
That's my tip. It works great for us.
There is nothing that you can do which more clearly shows your love for him than adoring his talk.
Well, thank you! That was Mr. Spanky Sex Tip of the Week.
You guys should look for me. I'm in DDR PC. I'm in a character expansion pack.
Bye everybody! See you next time!
Peanut butter jelly Peanut butter jelly
Peanut butter jelly with a big brains
Swing that back, turn your back, and see where it's at
Throw them all up, swing that back, turn your back, and see where it's at
Palm Beach, Peanut Butter, Dank County, Jell-A, Orlando
Peanut Butter, Tallahassee, Jell-A
Hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up
Man, shit, man, what time is it, dawg?
I don't know what time it is, Reylo
Peanut butter jelly top!
Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song.
Orange Lounge Radio.
You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio
And we're here to wrap up tonight's show, because we're just about at the end.
We're going to wrap it up in cellophane.
We're going to wrap it up in a nice little bow.
And sell it on eBay.
And give it to somebody for Christmas.
So, anything else you guys want to talk about on the show tonight that we haven't gotten
out yet?
Bree South.
I've mentioned it before.
Funny show.
Gotta love it.
On MTV.
Any more rants in you, Jamie?
are you barking
i'm feeling restless now
you're feeling restless so you just kinda
you need to go out and play some DDR? I'm feeling boar, yes
i'm going to sun splash tonight i'll be there until close
you can come with me, Jamie
So what are you guys going to play, because everything there is Para-para?
Para-para.
Para-para. You know what this town needs? We need a Para-para team.
No.
Come on!
I am no Para-less. I know maybe
six of them, and I only do four regularly. You know what pisses me off?
And I'm pretty sure... No, this isn't just specific to Roseville Golf Land.
I know most golf lands have this problem.
The kids that tease people playing Para-para.
I mean, fucking... I had one of them kicked out. God, I fucking hate those kids. I hate kids that
think they're better than everybody else that shit pisses me off it's like you
know at least we can memorize something you can memorize maybe like what beer
tastes good or whatever but it's just like God kids who think they're better
than everybody else is just really piss me off I want to kick kick so much ass
you've seen me go off on them I had one of them kicked out and the other one I
said okay I'll pay free to play do it dance yeah I know that was like the one
that uh we had that on DDR once too I remember that that was pretty cool yeah
Uh, I'm just looking.
And no, Orange Beanie, I'm not picking you up because you're in the other direction. Sorry.
Aw, I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, oh, and don't forget, Initial D.
Oh, Initial D is cool.
Initial D.
But yeah, kids piss me off, and there's a lot of them at Golf Land, and they're all rich and snobby, and they think they're better than everyone else.
They suck.
They piss me off, they suck.
And they suck.
They suck. No, they don't suck.
No, because...
They blow.
They don't suck, they don't blow. The fact that they exist is worse enough.
Oh God, I think I actually might have just created a pair of Parasax stars with my statement.
My bad, my bad, sorry guys, my bad.
Oh, for the four that I know. Or for six that I know.
Yeah, I'll join for the three that I know. I'll join just so that we have a big group
of people.
You have to teach me like a virgin correctly.
We need to do trick- okay, I'll teach you how to do like a virgin, that's fine.
And I'll teach you...
You can teach me the one you know that I know.
Ashimatsu.
But you know what I need to brush up on? I need to brush up on Light of Fire.
Okay. I need to remember how to do Eurobeat.
Yeah, teach me Eurobeat. Learn Eurobeat and then teach me.
So I'll get you my Max 300 Para Para going here.
No, I'll tell you what will be great about a Para team.
The thing that I want to learn though is Osolemio.
For that one day that I do feel like playing Para Para, what we need to do, we need to trick the assholes.
We'll just have everybody on the Para Para team sitting in the little booths and like one person up on the machine.
on the machine, and then when somebody starts teasing them, just get everybody to get up
and surround them and just start glaring, and then like, para para in their face or
something.
Everyone get up there and mirror.
That's right.
Wow, that's so 80s.
Kick kids in the butt.
How about I just inject them with the AIDS virus?
Try Drano, it kills them more painfully.
Imagine being injected into something that starts eating at your insides.
Or you just inject somebody with air.
Hey, I eat McDonald's too, okay?
I don't. My point stays.
Okay, so I think that we should just go.
You think we're going to end this show now? You want to end this show now?
Well, no. We have three minutes.
We have enough time to do final thoughts. You guys want to give your final thoughts?
Jamie, what is your final thought of today?
That's it?
Where's Brad? Get Brad back in here. He needs to do a final thought.
My final thought is, I need more man porn.
I need man sex.
Thank you.
You need man sex.
Brad, do you have a final thought for me?
I need man sex.
Well now...
And we have that on tape now.
Yes we do.
Hey, I'm going to play that last week on Orange Launch Rio.
I need man sex.
Tune in every Sunday night.
Hello to those people listening to us in Japan.
I heard at our station to people listening in Japan, they were Orange Lounge fans.
Orange Lounge the group, not the radio.
So they're tricked.
Haha, now we got you.
Yeah.
We got you good.
Well, I don't know, maybe we should offer them something a little bit different than
just saying, haha, we tricked you.
Okay, what?
Say, arigato gozaimasu.
What's that mean?
Thank you very much.
Oh, okay.
You should know what that means.
No, I don't.
I'm too white.
What are the Orange Lounge tracks for the rotation?
What do the kids have to look forward to next week on Orange Lounge Radio?
we're going to sacrifice low-key to the gods live on air
hey low-key is a guy who have written their guide okay
but i think i played by jim carrey
and i've had to meet
hey i like to carry a day
that'd be an honor
students like watch the mask at my place on this
i have not been
elise it is just a cooler
cd coasters
but i'm not
Oh, oh, oh, my half.com thing is going to arrive sometime next week.
What's that?
I ordered Sense and Sensibility on widescreen laserdiscs, so I can watch more Alan Rickman.
You're a hopeless case.
If you go to Jamie's friends page now, it is filled up with the Slytherin community,
the Draco community, the Alan Rickman community.
Alright, I am on, I am on, I'm in the Alan Rickman community, the Slytherin community,
the Professor Snape community, and I'm in the Animal Crossing community.
was uh...
i hate boys a place
well then we'll get you some pretty
i'm confused tuna
red bull there
now i need to turn tables i have the microphone turn tables and a mac
following the case you know if it's not going
jimmy actually i let me see how close the other week or the other day and i
was laughing at our shoes eating tacos
actually one of the action i got a second five controller now for the
And it's a lot better than the other one.
And I'm gonna...
No, I have the old ASCII pad.
It's the BeatCon or whatever that is.
It's better than the other one.
But I'm modding them.
But they're all like that.
They're all like that.
There's a one with piano keys which is somewhat decent.
I have the official ASCII one which sucks ass.
But I've been hearing that NCSX was dropping their 2DS controllers to 50 bucks. So I'm checking that out.
Well I'm doing a mod on mine that actually I'm making a brand new mod for 5 key.
I'm going to actually put ball bearings underneath the turntable to make it spin better.
Because it has room for it and they have these two really crappy plastic things that it spins on.
There's room for barbarians inside there, so we'll put that on there, and maybe a little rubber mat on top of it so that you have grip on the turntable, because their keys and everything is fine, but yeah, just the turntable sucks.
Make me a 2DX controller.
Should you?
No.
Okay.
I'll pay you.
Maybe.
One more, one more thought.
Which dysfunctional Sesame Street character are you?
I got Burton Ernie's gay relationship.
Surprisingly enough, I got Grover on E.
I'm Grouch's heroin addiction.
And what about you, Brad? I didn't participate in this
dorky thing. What are you talking about? Then you're transsexual Elmo.
I have a thought, actually. I thought it was kind of weird how...
Hey, Jamie. Yes, I can think. Anyway,
I thought it was kind of weird how Rob disappeared from our studio when Mr.
Spanky came in.
And why did Mr. Spanky sound like he was related to Triumph the Insult Comic Dog?
That sexual tip was good for me to poop on.
I hate you.
He was scaring me that he kept grabbing my ass.
Mr. Spanky, that was.
Oh, I thought he was talking about me. I guess he doesn't mind when I do it.
Alright, we're running over. We gotta go. Take care, you guys. Have a great night.
Yeah, we're running over the show.
over the show. Thanks for tuning in and supporting Orange Lounge Radio. We love you. My bad. Bye.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio. Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Skye, and Loki. If you'd like to leave us
a comment, send us an email at Orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com. And now, here's your fortune
Here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
And now a buffoons meeting with the dean of admissions at a prestigious college.
Well Michael, I'd like to extend my warmest congratulations on your upcoming graduation
and I understand you're interested in matriculating here in the fall.
I got a snake, man!
Yes, pets are welcome here on campus, be it the traditional dog or cat or even the occasional
reptile.
One time I feted some beer, Mank! It was slivering this way and that! It was all fucked up!
I'm sure it was. Well, we discourage inappropriate drinking among both students and pets here on campus.
Fuckin' shit!
Yes, that's a not uncommon reaction to this policy. So tell me a little bit more about your background.
My father's a fuckin' asshole, Mank!
Hmm, I see. Your feelings of rebellion are not unusual at your age, son.
My mother's a piece of shit, too!
Well, I hope you can find an outlet for your hostility over the summer,
so you can come to school in the fall relaxed and ready to learn.
My teacher in high school was a stupid bitch, man! She had her head way up her ass!
Well, the quality of the faculty at a university such as ours far exceeds that of a local public high school.
Your secretary's a real fat bitch, man!
Guess she's tried many diets over the years with minimal success.
I had diarrhea last month! I had to shit all fucking day!
Uh-huh. Well, we all get the occasional stomach bug. Never a pleasurable experience.
So, have you given any thought to your choice of major?
I've got a big fucking boner right now!
Hmm, I see. Well, sexual arousal is not uncommon during periods of nervous tension. I do not take offense.
One time I ate my neighbor's shit!
That's understandable. Well, I enjoyed meeting you, and we'll be sending you our decision by the end of the month.
I bet you got really hairy balls!
Yes, it's a veritable force down there. Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.