[SPEAKER_00]: and I, October 25th, 2009.
[SPEAKER_00]: A major new store burns computer games while you wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have an interview about the upcoming charity event, Umlaut, and some crappy little podcast once an obscure Japanese title released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard any good jokes lately?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, and welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gamer lifestyle, and of course, kittens!
[SPEAKER_08]: Cute, adorable, fluffy kittens!
[SPEAKER_08]: My name is Rob Roberts, joining you for the next few hours, of course, as with me as always, say hello to the one and only Secretary of Catnip, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, the one and only Secretary of Defense, TechMasterLoki.
[SPEAKER_10]: He cleans the cat box.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you guys doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been an interesting week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Been a very interesting week.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a unique week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a very unique week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to say in the seven and a half years we've been doing Orange Lounge Radio, I haven't quite seen anything like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually at Orange Lounge Radio we start off the show talking about our gaming weeks, but you know, in spite of things going on, we thought we might change that up a little bit and start off tonight with some news.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to head over to Joystick with a Q. Of course, we like them over at Joystick.
[SPEAKER_08]: They run lots of fun little game stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: They ran a story this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fans campaigning for President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Against all odds, a completely random Japanese Wii game starring a cat blogger has become a hot topic among some fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tsukiban Satchu Rena Wii stars a cat named Rena from a popular Japanese blog as the CEO of Cat Queen Inc.
[SPEAKER_08]: You play as a cat going through the initiation into the company, performing various minigames to earn Rena's respect.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not really true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't play a cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: You play a person.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really now?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Orange Lounge Radio Podcast discovered the game, which they have dubbed President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that, that we just dubbed it that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, they like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I shall call it President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then began tweeting the Wii game's official account.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fans started sending messages of encouragement and support to the President Cat hashtag, and the Rena account has started responding in both Japanese and English, revealing that the publisher is excited and a little confused about all this sudden attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be hilarious if this grassroots movement resulted in the localization of a weird licensed game.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, it would also be pretty sad if the publisher turned out to lose money on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's definitely something we want to play, but we're not exactly representative of the mainstream audience.
[SPEAKER_08]: That story coming from JC Fletcher over at Joystick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to dodge flying cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, we're a little surprised, probably like most people, that this actually made game blogs this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: A number of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people might think it was like a grab for attention, but no, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've done far worse desperate cries for attention on this show in the past.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's also interesting about this is that...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: GoNintendo and Destructoid
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously saw something in it, I think, that wasn't in some of the games we've talked about in the past.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just goes to show the moral of the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: America... Loves cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loves cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when I say America, I mean collectively the world that listens to this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just happen to be in America, but our friends in Australia, Canada, Mexico, Europe, they all fucking love cats too.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I think it just goes to show that people would like to see a game like this not everybody wants to see a game like this of course you look at the comments on this and you know the other sites that ran the article and there's people saying this game looks stupid yeah they probably also like Madden well yeah and my point would be there are some people that look at games like Madden and go well that's stupid
[SPEAKER_10]: Like me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I go a lot stupid to Madden.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think Madden is stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a waste of my time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I bet there are people out there that would say Uncharted 2 is stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: This game that gets critical praise, lavish, left and right upon it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody thinks it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't, but somebody out there probably does.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will say it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: You haven't even played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just want to be controversial.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, that's that desperate cry for attention people talk about.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am unique, just like everyone else.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: The point behind this, and if you go back on the show weeks and weeks, years and years, months and months, whatever, we've talked about this for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has to do with risk-taking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: and so they didn't really take a big risk I mean sure they I guess took a little risk in putting the game out over here which paid off for them with DDR yeah you know Beatmania not so much but a lot of Japanese companies I think are afraid to take risks sometimes because they think Americans don't get it or we're not gonna get it
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let this past week be a lesson.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of people over here that get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or else this story would have... Nobody would have cared.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like the past other hundred games we've talked about on this show that should be over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking about doing a Shermie blog as tribute.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what are your thoughts on this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: You actually got the game this week, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what did you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it worth all our hype?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did this get out of hand, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: How much of it is spoken?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not really spoken, it's just kind of in text boxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely would pick it up if it came out over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, as I posted in Twitter and stuff, there's been a few other cat games that have come out over here, more like the cat raising systems like, you know, Nintendogs kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Imagine Cats, and they also have like Purr Pals and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have to understand, even though
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people don't get these kind of games on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii has so many units out there, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: It takes such a small percentage of the people out there to sell a lot of units of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, those other cat games.
[SPEAKER_03]: 200,000 units and 400,000 units.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they were shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were absolute shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But people will buy anything that comes out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you put President Cat on the front of that box...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the fear of putting a game like this out in the US?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, there's plenty.
[SPEAKER_08]: We read off Japanese releases every week, and many of them don't come over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do they just think we don't get it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not the kind of game that would do well here?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the fear?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that it's just a lot of money that goes into localizing the game, and if they don't feel that they're going to sell enough units, then they're just not going to bother with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then I look at companies like Atlus or even Axis Game Localization or even Ignition, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of their games that come out over here that they decided to put out on the Wii...
[SPEAKER_03]: or even like the DS and stuff don't sell that many units.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Atlus especially, they don't sell a lot of units, maybe 200,000 on a good title.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, they only have a limited run.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've really cut their budget that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think that something like this, given the right marketing behind it, and I'm sure there would be, you know, a lot of praise for it, I think it would do pretty well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when you consider like these games like Pets, Cats 2 and Purr Pals, they have no marketing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have zero marketing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the chat room, our always present other guests here on the program, chat.orangehauntsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya in chat asks, yeah, who would we contact about localizing this, if anyone?
[SPEAKER_08]: And this kind of, you know, leading into the next question, what happens from here with our little mission to get this game localized?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a thought, but go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would contact kind of the usual bunch of people that are out there playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Localizing Weird-Ass Games
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess they're picking these properties cheap enough or something that they decide, you know, that it's worth putting it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they put out, I forget if it was like Go Minion or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ended up coming out as Domino Rally over here or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Go Go Minion, I think was the name of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's a really obscure title, but they went ahead and brought it over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Axis Game Localization does the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been doing a little bit more mainstream stuff lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been doing the Guilty Gear series, a lot of stuff from that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's a few other things that they bring over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then if you want to talk to other publishers, there's Zoo Games that brings out a lot of, like, kind of bargain bin stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do a lot of localization for UK games that get released over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're willing to bring over properties that no one has any idea what the hell they are over here, like Kokuto, which is some sort of demon character that's popular, I guess, in the UK or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: So should our listeners that feel passionate about the game email these guys, tweet them?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think it'd be a good idea to maybe...
[SPEAKER_03]: I would bring it up to maybe, I would go with like UFO Interactive and maybe Triaxis, maybe even like D3 or something, because remember D3, they brought over Defense Force, which is sweet and weird, Onishambara, plus they have the Simple Series in Japan, so they're used to weird ass games, but it's just, I don't know, it couldn't hurt to hit up more people than less.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't think game developers have already noticed when several major, major gaming blogs picked up the story... Yeah, and really what it comes down to is what kind of units are they looking to sell?
[SPEAKER_03]: What would make it worthwhile for them to bring it over here?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, obviously something like this is not going to sell a million units.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's not going to be... I don't think it's going to be the next Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't need it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Katamari was going to be the next Katamari.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it's good you bring that up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind, Katamari Damacy was a big risk, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game was released for $20 several years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was weird, and everyone loved it because it was different.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to read this comment, and I don't know if you have anything else you want to say on this, DarkSakura, but another comment from chat, Bochikawa in chat, Sky, the best jokes are those that we all can relate to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think you hit the nail on the head there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's part the Twitter thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that speaks volumes about Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's part the Twitter thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think it's part the fact that people looked at this and went, oh my God, this does look really cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why isn't there like a lolcats game with this as big as, you know, and maybe that wasn't the point behind this game, but that's what a lot of us are kind of interpreting it as, is cats in funny situations, cat wearing cat masks and the whole like stealing money game I saw a video of with the cats and the cat driving the car.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is ridiculous and preposterous like lolcats and fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that the best kind of fun is the ones you don't expect to be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: The ones that surprise you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta read this comment from Actdeft in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: And who says that Twitter is useless?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was actually listening to the show before last week's show, and I had said I was done and fed up with Twitter and I didn't get the point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boy, did I get told.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did I get shown?
[SPEAKER_10]: What is our purpose?
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever we determined it is at the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think our purpose was to show that more Japanese developers should think about bringing their quirky little games over here because there's an audience for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shoot, where was it that we would always go to at E3?
[SPEAKER_10]: We would go to the small little developers, to the ones that were looking... Kensha frickin' Hall.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or the back corner where Natsume had their little walk around thinking you could get... Look, my sheep is right over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: My Harvest Moon sheep.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know...
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I was thinking, Matt made some good suggestions, but I think also look for that company, see if they've released any other games that have been released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: and see who their marketer was.
[SPEAKER_08]: But certainly, though, after the antics of last week, you know in a boardroom somewhere in Japan this got brought up.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So that was pretty much... So maybe developers, when you localize this, a little less Bing?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about a cute meow noise instead of a Bing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Something I actually noticed from the screenshots is that it's actually in very simple Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: But part of the reason I was wondering is how much of it was actually spoken dialogue is because it would be much easier to follow if it's spoken.
[SPEAKER_03]: There wasn't really any spoken.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a lot of meows and lots of text boxes.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I will render services.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other thoughts on President Cat for now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if there's anything left to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: In a way, I kind of think our mission was successful.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if there's a lot else that can be done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ultimately, it's out of our hands at this point, and it is who's going to take a risk.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can keep the awareness up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we can keep the awareness up, and we can alert the potential risk takers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep that hashtag going.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, keep the hashtag going.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tweet the companies that you think ought to bring it over, and who knows what may happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially those of you that felt the need to email, because I know this came from tips from listeners, these various game blogs around the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that we've got that, I guess, start emailing some of the developers and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the worst that happens, they're going to delete it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I got their email address, the people over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've just been trying to get a hold of one of my friends in Japan to translate it for me, and she's been less than forthcoming because she has, a mutual friend is over there visiting, so I might see if, any of our Japanese listeners who's really good with your translation, let me know, because I wanted to let them know exactly how we came across them, so shoot an email at the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we'll work together.
[SPEAKER_10]: There may be some lucrative opportunity for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's get back into our regular show here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, we've taken a 20-minute detour to talk about President Cap, but that kind of thing happens when we tend to get spotlighted for a week for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to move into our regular show now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our ego swell and we turn into big divas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I asked for a Diet Coke.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, how have you had your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Peggle!
[SPEAKER_10]: Lots and lots of Peggle.
[SPEAKER_10]: My goal in Peggle has been to beat some of the levels on the first try.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I beat that freaking hard DNA level on the first try, and I was very proud of myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, one of the last ones with the spirals going up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have also really not been playing much of anything else, just simply because I had my midterms last week, and migraines all last week, and just...
[SPEAKER_10]: The Son of Crap All Week Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually played, well, like I mentioned earlier, President Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I played a little bit of the new Rena game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got through... It starts off, it kind of breaks it up, like there's three mini-games you have to do, and then three more after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I got past the first three mini-games, which is tough, because the last one was some question-answer thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't read any of that, so I just kept hitting random buttons, and yet somehow I was getting it correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I managed to get past that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the piano portion, which, even though I was hitting it in time, I guess I wasn't doing it well enough, and so they're getting pissed off.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, the car driving, which is weird, because you're controlling the cat in the back of the car that's sucking up what look like stars or clouds or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and then also play the cat dodging which was kind of fun but yeah the game is weird and fun so definitely worth checking out the other thing of course I played tons of was DJ Hero just knocked out most of the songs in the game I think I've actually played through everything now
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and then finally of course Grand Theft Auto 4 played some more Lost and Damned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also found a way around their patch to get rid of the mods but I haven't really done much with that because it's not working correct because apparently if you've ever modded the Grand Theft Auto on PC if you change too much it becomes unstable and then each save file actually saves some of the
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuff that you change.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if I try to change certain weapons or whatever, they'll kind of disappear from the save, and it's a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I found a way around all that, but unfortunately the modded disc I made was very unstable, so I have to go back to the drawing board.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really care, though, because a new expansion's coming out at the end of next week, so I may just hold off on modding everything until I can maybe get my hands on the Episodes of Liberty City disc instead, because that might be a little more fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were even just playing the new expansion because that's just going to be all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, I moved the arcade cabinet into the house this afternoon, so hopefully going to be done with that soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm downloading some front-end stuff for this program called Hyper Spin.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be running on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been downloading themes for a bunch of different games that I have in MAME.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been playing mostly World of Warcraft this week because, you know, I'm sucked into WoWcrack, but I did try out one new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say game in quotes because it wasn't really a game, but I checked out a game on PlayStation Network this week called Dot Detuned, or just Detuned, I guess you could call the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was something I think that was brought up at the very end of our show last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say one of the callers alerted us to it or
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I saw it on Twitter during the week, but I saw it was $3, and I was like, wow, what a deal for a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I went ahead and downloaded it and checked it out, and yeah, it wasn't quite what I was expecting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I heard that you could use custom soundtracks in the game, and I finally figured out why my songs weren't copying over on my USB card to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to go in there and do all or whatever, hit the triangle button, and was finally able to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love music games.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I'm all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's check out this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You sit there and you press the buttons and it kind of does different things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I imagine it's a lot more impactful if you're on drugs or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not on drugs, so I didn't quite see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, it was just interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not saying it was bad because it was $3 and it's certainly something different.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying it's not a game, so be careful.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yet it awards trophies even though it's not a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I will tell you this, if you want the easiest trophies,
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, easier than those achievements in the Avatar game on 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just pay the three bucks for this game and you can have like a gold trophy, like three silvers and a handful of bronze in like seconds.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't even look at what the trophies were and I had all but one of them unlocked in five minutes in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was incredibly simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's, of course, I wouldn't recommend downloading a game just for trophies, but I know there's some people out there that are, you know, EPing whores and want to see that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise,
[SPEAKER_08]: This is kind of one of those things, like, I don't know if you ever go to, like, the Museum of Modern Art, and you see some things in there that are really, really cool, like Andy Warhol paintings, you're like, oh, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that Marilyn Monroe painting's kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then, like, you see that other piece on the wall that just looks like someone threw a paint can against the canvas and called it art.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's art!
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is, okay, well, this is what that game, this is the art equivalent of...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the video game equivalent of that art piece.
[SPEAKER_08]: You kind of look at it and go, okay, I guess there's art in here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what, it does add to the very interesting debate that is, are video games art or not?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very, very strange.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm going to link this in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: But look at this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that art?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen that before.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's not what one would conventionally...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, so that's not the most bizarre thing ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to the chat room, Alpha Cananogram is in caps.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe I said that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But keep in mind, they're selling it in the game section of the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_08]: So just, you know, be forewarned.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is not a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it awards trophies like a game would do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, games usually have objectives and there are objectives with the trophy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's not a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: at www.twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also on tonight's show, we actually have a pretty full show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to be interviewing later on in the show, in part B, our pal Seg.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is putting on a big part of this Oom Loud event that's going on in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a charity event for Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we think these kinds of things that are very creative and involve video games and, you know, raise money for good causes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Things that give gamers a good name as opposed to, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: Kid shoots up neighbors, says he was inspired by Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love covering things like this that really offset the crap stuff that's in the media.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is a great cause.
[SPEAKER_08]: We hope our friends in the Bay Area will show up to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to talk to Seg a little later in the show, talk about Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I'm going.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Jamie's going to go because I'll give her a ride.
[SPEAKER_08]: She said all she needed was a ride.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki will try to get to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: If all of us can go, we could have a band.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we'll get into that a little later on in Part B of our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Start us off tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, recently Microsoft opened their first Microsoft store in Scottsdale, Arizona.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, one of the big things about the store, other than kind of being sort of a copy of an Apple store, is that they have the ability to basically print their own Windows games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the way this is done is you actually order it from a kiosk.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then give your name to one of the representatives in the stores and then basically wait a few minutes and you'll actually have the game with the label on the game printed, the case and inserts as well as the manual all printed for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of like that whole...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, they have a kiosk out there that will print, or I guess will make custom DVDs for you as well, like movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is kind of cool, actually, because you can't really knock it since games, like for PC at least, there's not really a used market for them, at least not one that you would see in a GameStop or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you're looking for a case and stuff, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have to have inventory in the store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be kind of curious to see if they could do something like this with Xbox Live Arcade games or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Boss Kiosks
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess I get the idea of putting out-of-print or catalog games into this kind of system, but as far as new games go, isn't the whole reason to walk into a store and buy a video game as opposed to just going onto Steam or Direct to Drive or one of those companies online, isn't the whole point of having the box, having the manual and that kind of new game smell that comes when you open up the box?
[SPEAKER_03]: They still get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they get the manual and everything printed.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just they won't get the big, giant cardboard box that goes with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I guess saves trees.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess you could look at it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get a disc and you don't have to worry about it being out of stock because they're just burning the game for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: But I guess this might be cool for like parents going Christmas shopping, wanting to buy computer games for the kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, you could see what the game looks like on a monitor in front of you, kind of see if it's appropriate for kids or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like if it's, you know, Lego that you're getting or if it's, you know, Demon Slayers from hell with boobies or whatever that, you know, you don't want to get the kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can kind of see what it is in the kiosk before you actually buy it and then have it printed right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that would be the target audience for this kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Question mark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: and some comments from our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com GameGuru says, besides, you can buy DVD cases and print out box art.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: The homemade stuff just isn't the same to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the same and they actually, obviously, since it's games for Windows stuff, they have this stuff licensed.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the actual manufacturers giving them the artwork for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have probably the process to I'm sure it's not just going to be like an inkjet printer printing out a piece of crappy artwork that's going to be on
[SPEAKER_03]: Paper that looks like cheap crap that you would make at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think this is going to be a little bit better than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be interested to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of people that reported on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And obviously a lot of people that visited the store.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how is the software that's burned off that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it look good?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it look cheap and knocked off?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it something that you could probably do at home for a lot less?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything Working Designs Did
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to see them in their store
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to see this in other stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you can buy Microsoft Points and stuff like that and go purchase your own Xbox Live Arcade games, but I want actual cards for each individual game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something that I can print out and say, I want to give the gift of, and why I would never punish someone like this, give someone the gift of the Warriors game that they put out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, okay, Jamie brought in an epic manual that came to her mind, and it's for Sega Ages on the Sega Saturn, and it's fancy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got, like, raised print and, like, the foil writing for Sega Ages.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a working designs game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I know, could we make cards for Yaris and get those printed, and I can give those to, like, it's like giving someone a fruitcake for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's free.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But even, like, you know, not necessarily that, but, like, custom...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: and, by the way, this is coming out here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is being localized.
[SPEAKER_08]: By whom is it being localized?
[SPEAKER_10]: Some brave, brave soul.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be honest, I think Axe AK Sis is the name of the company.
[SPEAKER_03]: Axe is game localization.
[SPEAKER_03]: The company I was talking about that localizes obscure shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, this would be a perfect candidate.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Joe Aniki Zero being localized for the US as if there's an audience for this because a lot of people look at this and go LOL WTF because yes if you don't already know it's all about like muscle bound guys wearing thong and all this muscle man-tastic voyage I believe that press reliefs even said about it I mean this is a ludicrous freaking game
[SPEAKER_08]: And the SNES one came out in Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_08]: but there's an audience for this so I just can't it's funny to me that there's an audience for this yet President Cat you know doesn't apparently have an audience over here and it's going to end up in bargain bins across America so it's just interesting so yeah as Loki said there's your perfect candidate company for someone to bring the kitty cat games over with we'll see
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how about something that is no surprise to anybody?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Microsoft has poo-pooed on any thoughts of having Blu-ray on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which we sort of knew.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were talking about, Microsoft was actually talking about Blu-ray accessories for the PC, but not for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think some interview some dude did with some website earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's so professional.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some dude at some website.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty much the boss, Steve Ballmer, said, uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a lot of people interpreted him to say that these Blu-ray... Oh, Blu-ray for Xbox 360 imminent.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw that all over Twitter that night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blu-ray's coming to Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was me rolling my eyes and going, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why would Microsoft put out a Sony product?
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially... And you know, they kind of make a good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's funny enough because, yet again, here's something we just talked about two weeks ago on the show or even last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think before all that cat madness started, we were talking about how...
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing that Sony has that Microsoft doesn't have is Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if Microsoft was smart, they would be selling the streaming video, the Netflix.
[SPEAKER_08]: And sure enough, when they kind of backpedaled on what the dude had said earlier in the week, they said, hey, we're going to be the only system with streaming 1080p very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they're kind of saying you don't need Blu-ray when you have streaming video.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the Netflix Instant Queue stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Netflix Instant Queue, but at the same time, I'm very proud this week of one of my purchases.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought the box collection of the Star Trek Next Generation movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All four movies with Captain Picard and a bonus disc.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: On Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's not something I would have wanted to download.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're bringing that over, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: We could totally have a nerd-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am all over.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually haven't seen Insurrection.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: And I've got it on Laserdisc, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should totally have a Blu-ray next Genathon with booze.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have first contact on Laserdisc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we drink?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to have a nerdy slumber party.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Booze Mahal.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, I don't know how we got off topic.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for me, it's kind of the same thing going back to the story we were talking about earlier with the games being printed on demand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would not have downloaded the Star Trek collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: And even though I could probably get a lot of these on Instant Netflix, it's just not the same as having the collection in your house anytime you want, put in the disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but it's easier for me to watch stuff on my computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it just me or are Blu-rays seeming to get a little cheaper?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're getting a little cheaper, not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're finding used ones more often.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm finding a lot of sales now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm seeing a lot of Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was at Best Buy this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: One game I didn't talk about during my gaming week because we've talked about it at length the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I finally played the DJ Hero demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was at Best Buy, and I was looking at Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a lot of Blu-rays available for $10, $15.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, they're starting to come the way of DVDs.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're still a little more expensive than DVDs.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get DVDs for $4 at Walmart, but they're coming down a little bit, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get to release dates very soon and see if there's anything wacky coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, some more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know about another President Cat, but I'm all campaigned out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so Xbox Live, the preview for the new fall update, they have sent out their first Wave 1 invites.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, actually, I got one of those, so I have the new update.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't gotten a chance to play with a lot of the stuff on there, but I did do the Twitter thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the problem I see is I don't think I'm going to use half this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the Twitter and the Facebook stuff, it's neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know how many tweets I saw this week that were, Hey, I'm posted from my 360!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just like, eye roll.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, we totally saw this coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody's going to have to do that mandatory tweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey guys, I got in the preview program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's my tweet from 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I want to tell you guys a secret.
[SPEAKER_08]: Almost everybody who signs up for these preview programs gets in.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's Microsoft's little way now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember when their system crashed a couple years ago when they rolled out one of these updates because everybody was freaking downloading it at once?
[SPEAKER_08]: This little preview program is their way of doing a rolling release for these updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except they're going to have to re-download it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the full thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the music store isn't working yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they have Lips on there and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, so apparently a lot of people got in on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they did have a lot of cool stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, if you're in the UK, you got to check out the Sky Player and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, over here in North America, you know, they had, of course, the Last.fm, you know, Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you check out the Last.fm by chance?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the one thing I am kind of curious about because I am a Last.fm user.
[SPEAKER_08]: I prefer it to Pandora and the other services available out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're great because the way it kind of syncs up with your iPod and everything with the Scrabbler.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the recommendations have been, for the most part, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm really curious to see what the Last.fm...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ DarkKnight and GoldAnthro both saying you can't play them with your games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last.fm does not work with your game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Synthpop and Spice Girls Mixed Together Epic
[SPEAKER_08]: Very epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Tiger Claw also confirms that the music stops playing when you exit out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it sounds like it's kind of like an independent application, kind of like Netflix is, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the movies stop when you leave Netflix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, all the programs are kind of like that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, the Twitter and stuff, it kind of goes into its own program thing, and then you actually back out to the main menu when you're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if I really am that desperate to check Twitter and stuff, I guess that would be handy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be useful, like, if I...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: That is a very good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is one thing that Xbox is sorely lacking, and these are the people that make Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there not... Unless, you know, because Internet Explorer is, you know, kind of a magnet for bugs and all sorts of exploits and whatnot, that they're worried that somehow they're going to find a way around it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, people playing, like, emulated games, like Nintendo games in a Flash browser or something, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that what they're worried about, maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I would think that with maybe Facebook or something, you might be able to kind of exploit something, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I never even thought to do that on the PlayStation, because the PlayStation has a decent web browser.
[SPEAKER_08]: But is it just me, or are both the PlayStation and the Wii, their web browsers, just kind of clunky?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, they just don't work like it does on a computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, I don't know, especially when I'm using the YouTube TV site, they're so slow to load.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's been the hang-up of any type of web system on a console.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: You think?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, but isn't the PS3 supposed to be a computer?
[SPEAKER_10]: So they said.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they did it just for the tax cut, remember?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: They seem a little clunky to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys have been to my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I have a lot of people over, we'll fire up YouTube and watch funny things.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really good to be able to do it on the Wii or the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that new YouTube channel, but it's slow and clunky.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I say?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to run anything off the internet on your TV, build a multimedia box.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess, but... Especially now with an HDTV, it's so cheap and easy to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Dark Knight does say in chat, I do like how on Last.fm they do have video game music stations.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wasn't aware of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to have to check this out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know I'm going on like 60 days since I've played an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I've been all PlayStation 3 lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, speaking of PlayStation 3, I signed into Home and there were like six requests to join our club, so I approved them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you want to join the Sony Home Club for Orange Lounge Radio, look for us on the search and add us before we fill up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fable 3
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this is starting to get a little cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's getting silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my problem with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Fable 3, and I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to bypass the whole game altogether.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless there's something that's really awesome that I must play in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess it's where we're going to be going with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the trend that's showing up that I'm getting really nervous about.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the bottom line is, if you don't like it, don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Show them that you're not going to support it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really what it boils down to in the end.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's just kind of sad that it's going there in the first place.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still going to buy Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I loved Fable 2 and the first Fable was good too.
[SPEAKER_08]: No matter what, I'm going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just get my upgrades naturally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It totally sucks when something like that happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I totally agree with their stance.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you buy gold online, you suck because you're supporting this practice of hacking accounts like mine and supporting keyloggers and funding this, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: So don't buy gold online.
[SPEAKER_08]: One other thing I wanted to state, although Matt kind of stated it, it was circulated also this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Project Natal will be supported in Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: That, of course, should come as no surprise at all since Peter Molyneux was, of course, out there at E3 this year kind of promoting Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there will be support for it in Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: What will it do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait till the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it does.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, there's something else going on that's, I think, a little stinky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very much like the weapon upgrade business.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a game that's called Parachute Panic that's on iPhone and iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm allergic to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, there's dust in the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now, on the last version that came out, you can pay 99 cents to unlock another five lives.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's a 99 cent game already.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, you can just do it in-game, but for the impatient people who want more lives, then you just pay for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's really just encouraging gamer laziness really.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like EA and their cheat codes, remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuff that normally would be in a game for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: But hey, now we can sell it for two bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have as much of a problem with it if it's something that you can achieve in the game otherwise, especially single player.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind when I ranted about WoW, that's a multiplayer experience and much different.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a single player game, you know what, if you want to use cheats to your heart's content in a single player game where you're not interacting with other people going online or what have you, go for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you want to pay two bucks because you're too lazy to get it yourself, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But as long as the option is there for you to still get it yourself and work towards it, I think it's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not something I would probably do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's more fun if you... I think anything worth having is worth working for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even if it's in a game or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am behind on some chatroom comments, so I want to read some comments from our chatroom, chat.orangeloungeradio.com Salacious Pop says, it could just be rose-colored glasses, but Dreamcast's browser was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of going back a ways back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was decent.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, you have to kind of say, okay, well, you know, that was 1999, this is before kind of web browsers were standard like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did Dreamcast's browser have to compete with, WebTV?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, I think for its time, it was certainly pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, Redertainment says the store in Fable 3 will be good, but the store in Fable 4 will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hope that it's not more of this nickel and diming stuff, but I'm sure it will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also a question from Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: If Natal gets delayed, will Fable 3 get delayed?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Seg replies with his thought, maybe not unless Microsoft wants it as a launch product.
[SPEAKER_08]: I assume Fable 3 is an add-on support for Natal rather than a requirement.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess, yeah, that's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: It depends on how much Natal is integrated into this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's like a required part of the game, then yeah, Natal delay is going to affect the game, but
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's just kind of a, hey, a bonus little game or a bonus little quest, then maybe not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see that kind of being the case, is that there's a download expansion that uses Natal or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be kind of interesting, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, moving right along into some release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, take us through the US releases this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Hero
[SPEAKER_03]: Also coming out this week, we've got Tekken 6 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, as well as the Fight Sick bundles for those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hasbro Family Game Night 2 on the DS and on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: World of Zoo coming out this week on the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: SpongeBob's Truth or Square on DS, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've also got...
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not for many of our listeners, but ni hao, Kylan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super game day on the Wii for your Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_03]: fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: You read a lot of game releases that I don't think a single one of OLR listeners care about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, they may have kids that watch Nick Jr., and that is important.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, The Backyard Again is another Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_03]: program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nerf N-Strike Elite with the scope.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out in a bundle for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Borderlands on PC, also making its way out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: RE Smarter Than a Fifth Grader Game Time on the Wii and DS and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pets, Dolphins, Encounters on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once again, another game series that puts out tons of games, and I'm sure they don't sell very well, but hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're putting them out, and people pick them up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Barbie and the Three Musketeers on DS and Wii Monster 4x4 Stunt Racer with a pack-in wheel coming to the Wii Drawn to Life the next chapter also on Wii and DS this time Diner Dash Flow on the Go still the best title for the DS title wow
[SPEAKER_10]: Ben 10, Alien Force, Vilgax Attacks on PS2, Wii, DS, PSP
[SPEAKER_03]: Forza Motorsports 3 on Xbox 360 CSI Deadly Intent on DS and Wii I think PS3 and Xbox 360 as well this one's for Rob Press Your Luck 2010 coming out on PC, Wii, and I believe DS as well but if it's not Peter Tamarkin then I don't give a crap and I don't see how that'll be possible because he's kind of dead
[SPEAKER_08]: What's his name?
[SPEAKER_08]: Todd Newton?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't stand him.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's like the worst game show host ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Reanimation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ruined whammy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And going back to the roots of this show, Dance Dance Revolution Hot Party 3 making its way out from Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, all these games now kind of blend together because they all kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe also to kind of go with that, DDRX2 will be coming out as well in the bundle on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: They only sell these games in a bundle now because they want you to buy those crappy dance pads to go with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Hamster's Bunch on PSP because God forbid if the PSP be devoid of crappy pet games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Dream Salon on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And finally, stuff coming out a week from now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rabbids Go Home would be the last.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Ratchet and Clank, Crack in Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's another title that will be coming out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got to read some comments from chat if you're done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTituya says, Sky, three words, Zombie Peter Tamarkin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, what else was said here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, SalaciousPop says, I'd play a Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eureka's Castle FPS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, where are the Nickelodeon games for me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Screw the children!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want my Nickelodeon games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for instance, can I get like a You Can't Do That on Television minigame collection?
[SPEAKER_08]: or like, Hey Dude, Explore the Ranch Game, or Salute Your Shorts, you know, so Are You Afraid of the Dark?
[SPEAKER_03]: The best episode of Salute Your Shorts had to have been, was it, the Water Balloon Capture the Flag episode, my favorite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank You, Seg, Legends of the Hidden Temple.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, they did have a Guts game on Super Nintendo, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nick Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about reviving one of these old, like, classic frickin'... For all I care, do a fuckin' today's special video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just give me something I remember from my childhood.
[SPEAKER_03]: David the Gnome?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, David the Gnome was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turkey Television.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me you wouldn't play a Turkey Television, like, shooting game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'd be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they do have Chicken Shoot.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kinda close.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything that's going to make us go crazy this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably not, because Japan's getting a lot of the titles that are big and expected for us over here this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Japanese releases this week on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bayonetta makes its way to the Xbox 360 on October 29th, as well as Tekken 6, of course, is a big deal over there, just as it is over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those both coming out to the Xbox 360, and of course, just in time for Tekken 6, another Hori arcade stick with the Tekken 6 design on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you'd care to import one of those from Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you can just get them here in the bundle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or on the PlayStation 3, you could get Bayonetta there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or the, again, Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also a game getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Samurai Do 3 Plus getting a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So those are the big releases on the 360 PS3 combo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dipping into Nintendo Wii, we have some different alternate titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another Dragon Ball title.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, that's a US date.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chin Sports makes its way to Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is kind of a minigame collection that's wacky and weird sports.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the one that has the extreme ironing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this came up on the show a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: It came out last month.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, for here in the US.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Japanese are getting their own version of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably what people care a little more about would be Sin and Punishment 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is finally being released on Nintendo Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Robot Taisen Neo comes out as well because there just wasn't enough Super Robot Taisen games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hikari no 4 Senshi Final Fantasy Gaiden Side Story
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and it's that same style of like Final Fantasy 3 DS and the Final Fantasy 12 spin-off game, but don't expect it to play like your other Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I miss as far as Final Fantasy spin-off games go?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what my favorite, like seriously my favorite Final Fantasy spin-off game was?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tease Me All You Want.
[SPEAKER_08]: I fucking love Chocobo Racing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I know a lot of people who love that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish they would make another one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was perfect for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or give me my extreme chocobo racing on the PlayStation 3 just in time for Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you reminded me, I forgot two major titles and I don't understand how I did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fairytale Fights was coming out on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, how did I forget this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto Episodes of Liberty City on Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think most people think of that as a download title.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fairytale Fighters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that what it sounds like?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Fairytale Fights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think of it as like Castle Crashers but with fairytale characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's brutal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like blood and guts everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you talked about this on a previous show.
[SPEAKER_08]: This sounded awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it cheap or is it like 60 bucks?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's like 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll wait for the bargain bin, because that's... You want to talk about a game that'll end up in the bargain bin?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't really sell this game to children, and adults probably won't take it very seriously either.
[SPEAKER_08]: We could market this to the people that bought the Red Riding Hood zombie game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's probably the target market for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got to be the same company, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Zoo Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It did...
[SPEAKER_03]: Red Riding Hood Zombie BBQ Yeah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it at PAX, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was either PAX or E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was PAX.
[SPEAKER_08]: And SalaciousPop reminded me in chat there saying I only got maybe 7-8 hours in the Tactics titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I suppose Final Fantasy Tactics is a pretty notable spin-off of the Final Fantasy series.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what's sad?
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably spent more time playing Chocobo Racing than the Final Fantasy Tactics games.
[SPEAKER_08]: that's for sure quickly I wanted to mention on the PSP just because I think this name is hilarious it's R-Type Tactics 2 yes the R-Type Tactical game remember that is actually getting a sequel and the sequel is called Operation Bitter Chocolate I can't make that up that is the real name of the game Operation Bitter Chocolate so would that be Dark Chocolate?
[SPEAKER_08]: Baker's Chocolate?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know that's what it's called Operation Semi-Sweet Chocolate with a little bit of nuts Operation I don't get it
[SPEAKER_08]: Grand Theft Auto IV, The Ballad of Gay Tony, Aggressed Generations of War, Borderlands, DJ Hero, Fallout 3 Game of the Year Edition, Football Manager 2010, Tekken 6, Feel, Wii Fit Plus, and Yoga for Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we're going to get to the classic game of the week very, very soon here, but just two more stories for you guys real quick, and then the break, and then our interview with our pal Seg about Umlaut right after the break tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, since we were talking a little bit about fairytale fights, they did have an achievement at one point for killing children in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: So not to be outdone, of course, Dante's Inferno, the game full of great ideas and awesome promotions.
[SPEAKER_03]: is now getting some flack for an achievement called Bad Nanny.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this achievement is... You've been a very bad nanny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can just see Super Nanny.
[SPEAKER_08]: This achievement is... You need to go and sit on the naughty step.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been very naughty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently this achievement is for killing unbaptized babies in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they not have a sense of humor?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this isn't saying that, like, you know, bad International Nanny Association or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: My mom was a nanny, actually, for many, many years, and I can verify they do not have a sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, my mom's hilarious, but I don't think she'd find that funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your mom's a hoot.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a video game about hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they've got walls made out of writhing naked people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this isn't exactly... This isn't saying you should go kill babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just demon babies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you saying we should go kill babies?
[SPEAKER_03]: Demon babies, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, look at Silent Hill with the smoke babies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, yes, you need to kill them because they're not human.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're trying to eat you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cats aren't human.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you kill them?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't kill them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're not demon babies either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sometimes they are, but most of the time they're not.
[SPEAKER_08]: a comment from xlink in chat chat.orange.radio.com they say no to this but you can shoot kids in Fallout 3 hmm those kids had it coming shut up
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, speaking of things I told you were coming before too long on a completely different note.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember when I said don't discount Facebook gaming?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't discount.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a big, big new game coming to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Civilization Network has been announced for Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in my opinion, this is huge because this is what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a major PC beloved franchise colliding with the world of Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_08]: and some of you are preparing your block application thing on Facebook right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, by the way, tangent warning.
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell is up with those changes on Facebook?
[SPEAKER_08]: What changes?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now they've changed it so when you log in you get like a news feed that seems to be like a random sampling of the stuff that you would see before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the popular stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to see the live feed you have to click into that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now the live feed shows not just people's updates but like who became friends with who and all this stuff that you really don't want to see.
[SPEAKER_10]: All the stuff we don't care about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, more stuff we get to block.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't block it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if you block it, then you block the person that did the friending.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, Facebook didn't think that one through very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, sorry, I digress.
[SPEAKER_08]: Civilization Network is making its way to Facebook and it's supposed to be out sometime in 2010.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actually a Facebook page already set up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on facebook.com slash civnetwork, C-I-V network.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're going to be on the lookout for beta testers very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sid Meier himself has said that the game will offer everything that people love about Civ...
[SPEAKER_08]: in a quote, fully persistent environment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Best of all, the game will be free.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brian Reynolds, who is behind Civilization 2 and Alpha Centauri, has the job of chief designer at the social gaming developer site Zynga.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of an interesting little coincidence.
[SPEAKER_08]: He has nothing to do with this game, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: it's interesting that he did so much with that now he's at this other company so you think maybe old friends maybe got together at dinner talking about this who knows but Facebook gaming dude it's common this is going to be something we're going to see in the next few months just get bigger and bigger
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, now we're going to get into a section of the show that we like to get into every week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a section for DarkSakura to open up the gaming vault and take a travel through gaming's past.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what video game do you think the kids should be playing this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: For those in the U.S., it is Galactic Attack.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has been known by many other names.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Japan, in the arcade, it was called Rayforce, but because of licensing, it came out as Layer Section on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got it as Galactic Attack, and in Europe, they got it as Gunlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is in the Ray series, Rayforce, Raystorm, and Raycrisis.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's pretty freaking amazing shooting game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the way that it plays because not only do you have the stuff coming from you from right above, you also target below your ship and can launch missiles at targets in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or as it should be, toward the bottom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I add something to that?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you want to hear some of the lovely little shooting sound effects here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: The music's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely sounds like a shooting game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just bullets, bullets, and more bullets.
[SPEAKER_10]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it is just one of the, you know, regular old, you know, shooting games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think it's one of Taito's best.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, especially, I love the entire series.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, Raystorm and Ray Crisis were fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this, to me, I think is what really gave it to us.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's, to this day, one of my favorite shooters and one of the reasons to have a rotating widescreen monitor.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It goes by several different names, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: We have Galactic Attack in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gunlock in Europe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Layer Section for the Japanese home version.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in the arcade, it was Ray Force.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why couldn't they just pick one name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because of licensing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was fully licensing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well there you have it, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Many, many different names for that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out on the Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie loves her Sega games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, she does.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's going to do it for this Part A of our podcast, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to be right back with plenty more in Part B. We have a lot coming up on deck in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not only do we have some news, some quick little stories here about what's coming out on Rock Band and Xbox Live and some news on Star Trek Online and Beatles Rock Band and so forth, but we have an interview coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our pal Seg is the man behind a charity event coming up in the Bay Area very soon known as Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to be talking to him about what's going to go down in December.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a few weeks away, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The year's almost up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's all for a great cause.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to talk to Seg all about it right after this quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: So don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio here on this lovely Sunday evening, October the 25th of 2009, where we are taping the 342nd episode of our podcast, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course you can tune in every week and listen to us tape live at www.allgamesradio.com, or if you just want the radio feed, it's allgamesradio.com, that's how I usually go in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: or there's also a radio app that you can get on your iPhone if you just search for All Games in the Store.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are the folks who we steal our bandwidth from every week and we really, really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, we're going to move into something a little different here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We usually be doing Twitter topics about now, but we're actually going to invite a friend of the program on the show and he goes by Seg Online, but his name is John Segerson.
[SPEAKER_08]: He actually goes by the nickname Seg and he is one of the minds behind Umlaut, which is a charity event that is happening in San Francisco at the DNA Lounge in
[SPEAKER_08]: Wednesday, December 9th of this year, 7pm to 2am.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a rock band event for Child's Play Charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: We like to talk about charity events and gamers doing good things.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to give Seg a call and get him on the show to talk to us a little bit about Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to go ahead and ring him up on Skype right now and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an umlaut, but louder.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a charity event for Child's Play charity, which provides video games, toys, and other financial support to children's hospitals around the globe.
[SPEAKER_01]: And our event is we play rock band as a catalyst for people donating money to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now, is Rock Band the only thing that's going on at this event, or is this kind of like just a big party where Rock Band's kind of in the corner?
[SPEAKER_08]: How's this work?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, this is going to be a very different kind of Rock Band night than most Rock Band nights.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, usually when people go out to do Rock Band at a bar or something, it's there, but it's just everyone playing to a projector and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're doing something a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have one area of just regular rock band play, no fuss or anything, in the upstairs lounge area.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for the main event, you're playing rock band on the DNA Lounge stage, a San Francisco concert venue.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you will be performing rock band as a band on a concert stage to an audience.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's more than just...
[SPEAKER_01]: Just playing rock band to the projector and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You are putting on a rock concert for people.
[SPEAKER_01]: And depending on what kind of band package you donate to, you can really get the ultimate rock concert performance experience with the lighting, band introduction, the whole nine yards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell us a little more about some of these different experiences that rock band wannabes, or however you want to phrase it, because you talk about how you can actually get up on a real stage that quote-unquote real bands have performed up on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that something that's accessible to everybody, or what are the different options for my band to showcase at this event?
[SPEAKER_01]: so first of all I do want to say that we do have two stages and one stage is free for anybody to show up and we'll get in a little later of what everybody can do but if you and three of your friends
[SPEAKER_01]: really want to perform on the main stage, we have two packages to perform on the main stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a standard band package, which we're going to ask for a $40 donation, but if you order online, it's $35.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's the whole band.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you split that up to four people, that's $8.75 a person.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for the standard band package, you get to play on the stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just play on the stage regularly, but you're still playing to the crowd on a major San Francisco stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, if you want to rock harder, that's where our ultimate band package comes in.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to put some extra oomph in your oomph loud.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're asking for $120 for the donation, but again, that's the band package, so it amounts to $30.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you get...
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Every song on Rock Band available.
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually partnered up with Harmonix with this and they will be providing stuff that can be played on Rock Band 2, but all of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's those few songs on Rock Band 1 that won't be included.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Beatles doesn't count for the main stage because it's just hard to get people through without switching discs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you don't want to have to switch discs all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it still like, what, a thousand songs to pick from?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's about a thousand songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we feel we're comfortable in doing this because it'd be pretty lame to have the same song played again.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you're in the ultimate band package, you get to reserve it ahead of time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also get, each member of your band will get lanyards, that sort of VIP pass thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: that's a nice little take home memento you also get you'll get a gift bag for each band member four bags and when you're about to go on stage you'll be introduced as your band you have to pick a name for your band and we'll make an introduction for you and we get the lighting guy involved and it just really makes it the kind of experience you really can't really can't get anywhere with it did you get the rock band Fog Machine?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who needs the fog machine?
[SPEAKER_01]: You'll have the full lighting setup of the DNA Lounge's concert venue stage.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess true enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get industrial strength.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you get the industrial strength concert.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for those folks that are thinking, oh my gosh, $120, that's a lot of money, keep in mind, this is, you know, A, a once-in-a-never type experience that you can get getting to play on the stage, and B, the fact that it's going to charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's not like going in SAG's pocket, it's going to a great charity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it's going to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_01]: We really want to stress that this is a donation, and the money that you give is going to Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you stood back and just saw it as the value of just like, what would I pay just to play rock band, you're kind of thinking it a little wrong in this context.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a donation to which we are thanking you by giving you this experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: All ages show at DNA Lounge
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: We are asking for a $10 donation because this is a charity event.
[SPEAKER_01]: But no one will be turned away.
[SPEAKER_01]: And even if you don't do the donation, you will get two raffle tickets for our prize raffle.
[SPEAKER_01]: And our prize raffle is stuff that we've been...
[SPEAKER_01]: my cohorts Chris Kohler, Joe Marquette have been collecting throughout the year of all this swag and all this stuff and they've been piling up in their apartments and we're going to give this stuff away as prizes in this free raffle
[SPEAKER_01]: so there's a lot of incentive there and actually Chris is doing a prize a day on our blog at umloud.org that's U-M-L-O-U-D dot org where he'll take a photo of some of the things that he'll have and post it so you can see the kinds of things that we'll be giving away on that night
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I know this is an event that's being hosted at the DNA Lounge, which is on 11th Street in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, the date and time, if you missed it, December 9th, 2009.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a Wednesday, 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: till 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like most bars are open till 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what if we have listeners all over the globe, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: How can people help out if they can't be there in San Francisco on that night?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I know our event is around San Francisco and all that, but if you can't make it to San Francisco or any of the other kinds of events that are happening, please consider a donation to Child's Play Charity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just go directly to them, they're childsplaycharity.org, and just consider a donation direct to them.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're doing this thing here in San Francisco because of the success of Foombrowser last year, and a lot of people liked it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's the kind of thing that we know that a lot of people come to, and we want to facilitate that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But what we're really here is to create awareness to Child's Play Charity as a whole.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is one microchasm of the many things going on in the gaming community to help Child's Play Charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I think it's a great cause and it's a really fun event.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, if nothing else, even if people are like shy, you know, one thing that should be said is that this isn't just, you know, for people that love attention of getting up on stage and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you just kind of want to come hang with, you know, cool people, come to this event because I'm going to be there and I believe DarkSakura is going to be there and we're trying to get Loki there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So hopefully we'll all be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So come hang with us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, and we'll definitely have more.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's stuff that we're working on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't really say right now, but don't feel that just because you didn't get the band package thing that there's nothing for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: There will be plenty of things for you to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will have a good time just showing up.
[SPEAKER_01]: So please, please come by.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'd love to have you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's, again, for all the information of this, there are many, many other things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please come to our website, umloud.org.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's U-M-L-O-U-D dot org.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we hope to see you there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just wanted to mention this real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of glancing through chat here and I see Tigerclaw in chat says something about DNA Lounge seems to have like a live video stream.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, there will be a live video stream that will be turned on during our events.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you can also see us rock out all the bands.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be centered on the main stage, I believe.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can view it from anywhere during the night as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_01]: Get on the boat soon to do the band packages.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have a few of the standard on hand, but that's sort of our release valve to make sure that everyone who's paid for a package gets to play on the stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're also increasing the price a little more on the night of for the standard package.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you really want to do that, if you really want to do this, please order soon than later.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So once again, this is Umlaut happening Wednesday, December 9th of this year, 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: to 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: at the DNA Lounge on 11th Street in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: More information is available on their website, umlaut.org.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's U-M-L-O-U-D.org.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you guys are on the Twitter and the Facebook and all those fun spots too, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it's amazing how many things can and cannot use the umlauted U. And that's so important for an event like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so important.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't worry, you don't have to figure out how to type it into your computer to get to the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a normal U will do just fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, a normal U will work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seg, thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Best of luck with the event.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: We had to rebrand this event a week and a half ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we really appreciate any word coming out of this event since it's a new name and everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we will have a great event for you guys to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hey, yeah, listeners, definitely follow these guys on Facebook or Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even if you're not in San Francisco, you might have a friend or relative or someone who likes video games that might see you following this and check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get the word out about Umlaut and a great event for Child's Play Charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Seg, thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to get mullet wigs I'm all for dressing up We need the rock mullet
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, come on, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see if I can make it down there.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least we got upgraded from I don't know to a we'll see, so that's usually good.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we'll get to more Skype calls a little later on in the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to thank our buddy, Seg, for tuning in live and being here with us live.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got plenty more show for you, including some rapid-fire news, and I believe right into a story about Rock Band and maybe some more songs you can play at this event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob Zombie, Pac-1
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I gotta say has got some sweet songs in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely something I'm going to be purchasing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Including Burn, Dragula, and Super Beast.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about frickin' time Dragula's in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: What song are we going to sing?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be a perfect song.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to do Dragula?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can get up on there and do my best Rob Zombie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have to get a big curly wig or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wolfmother Pack 1 New Moon Rising, Pilgrim, Sundial, White Unicorn, Woman Liz Fair, Rock Me, Morning Wood, Best of Me, Sugar Baby
[SPEAKER_03]: and each of those are available.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually the Morning Wood tracks are half off so it's only a buck or 80 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything else individually is $1.99 or 200 Wii points or 160 Microsoft points and of course the packs are a little bit cheaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Rob Zombie pack is $5.49 or 440 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_03]: $6.80 Microsoft points for the Wolf Mother pack or $8.49 in real money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're getting Sonic Youth, Cool Thing, and Steely Dan, My Old School.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both of those for $2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then to go along with releases here, Konami has confirmed that they're going to be releasing a port of Shadow of Destiny, which came out, I believe, on PlayStation 2 not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember it being a pretty decent game when it came out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well speaking of release dates, it's not very often we're talking about a game coming out early.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, this year it's been talking about all these games getting delayed to 2010.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Need for Speed Nitro, that's the new Need for Speed entry on the Nintendo Wii and DS, has had its release bumped up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was originally going to come out November 17th, but guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's now coming out November 3rd here in the US and November 6th over in Europe.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it actually got out a little early.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually checked this out at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty cool for a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know that sounds kind of harsh, but
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: On Xbox Live, Rainbow Islands Towering Adventure is coming out on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that would be Rainbow Islands, that game that kind of was once inspired by Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of like a sequel to Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was still Bub and Bob, but they were shooting rainbows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I noticed in the screenshots for this game, I don't see Bub and Bob.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like a new little guy here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is some new little spin-off game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Rainbow Islands Towering Adventure.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is actually a port of a WiiWare game that came out a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's coming out very, very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also for those who are in Europe and can make it and are interested, there's going to be playable Star Trek Online at Eurogamer Expo.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're almost out of tickets too, but that's on Wednesday the 28th in Leeds.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, they're almost sold out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you can actually play on one of the gaming PCs there and...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's different level demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can do ship-to-ship and planet combat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can shoot Klingons in space.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually, I think, play as Klingons in that one, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, you can go visit the giant lopsided donut.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the Guardian of Forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it should be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bayonetta has done something major.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is the first Xbox 360 game that got a perfect score from Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_10]: It got a perfect 40-40.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although now Bayonetta is cross-platform.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just happens that Xbox 360 is one of the platforms it's on, correct?
[SPEAKER_10]: And also the better version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the other one got 38.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, so they did review both.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know that Famitsu did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there are... If you actually...
[SPEAKER_10]: Look for movies on YouTube of them side by side.
[SPEAKER_10]: You will see a noticeable difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Famitsu Magazine doesn't hand out 40s very often, although it seems like we've had a few of these stories in the past few years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes you kind of raise an eyebrow at the games they give 40s to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe Nintendogs was one of their 40 titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's a lot of really, really great games in the past, like Final Fantasy XII and so forth, that got this as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it definitely is a distinction.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think only, what, a dozen games in the history of the magazine have had it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: For me, it's really tough.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Bayonetta, getting that is a big like, whoa, whoa, hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm totally getting Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any word on what it was they loved about the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or just we're only hearing about the 40s right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's just the 40s so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me double check.
[SPEAKER_08]: Salacious Pop clarifies, by the way, they gave the PS3 version a 38 because the port is muddy and bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks brown and is missing quite a bit of particles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they're not really saying why, but yeah, just seriously, look at them side by side.
[SPEAKER_03]: 38's still not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's intense.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, oh, it's crappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think President Cat got, what, like a 24 from Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's harsh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they're used to seeing these games a lot, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's a lot different for them than it was for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe like a generic party game coming out over here on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, those are a dime a dozen, whereas Cat games, there's two.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: No word on what the hell this is going to be used for, possibly a design for their new remote, their motion controller device, sans ice cream, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it sort of looks like a sex toy, too, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds kind of gross.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this is not like these are actually coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is just a list of this is what could have been or what is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a design.
[SPEAKER_03]: They may go with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They may not go with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like Nintendo with their inflatable chair of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just an idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought everything was sold on the whole lights thing or the changing light dot beam looking thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I thought that's what we were going at.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe they decided to change...
[SPEAKER_03]: The way they look.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe there's a light on here that we don't see or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, it looks like a plastic cylinder that has four buttons on top.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a lot of faith in Sony when it comes to controller design because I still love the PlayStation controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although then again, I say that and then at the same time I think, yeah, but then they did take DualShock out of the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that was a whole different reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: That wasn't really a design thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was because they didn't want to pay royalties.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, the PlayStation 3 controller is still a rock solid controller, especially, you know, and I took some crap last week for saying this, but especially compared to the 360 controller, which, you know, the D-pad leaves a lot to be desired on the 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: The PS3 is a pretty slick controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially the newer ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I kind of trust their judgment when it comes to making controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: They usually don't make bad ones, except that boomerang thing was really weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that never did come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was only a concept thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, maybe that light thing went the way of the boomerang.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thankfully, we do live in the day and the age of the internet, because if this was like, you know, the mid-90s where all we had were gaming magazines, that boomerang would have come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they wouldn't have heard the horrible feedback.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like a debate that's years old at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't know if the boomerang was necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd have to feel it in my hands.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it felt fine to control with, I would have been okay with the weird design.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just think at the same time, the PlayStation controllers are one of the best controllers ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why ruin a good thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at the PS1, PS2, PS3 controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've all been pretty much the same, and there's a reason for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Granted, they added Rumble to it at some point along the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: They added DualShock and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty much though it stayed consistent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on to another news story having to do with Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beatles Rock Band has actually beaten Guitar Hero 5 on the sales chart.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is based on U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: September sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: Believe it or not, the Beatles was released September 9th and Guitar Hero 5 was released September 1st.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Beatles has moved 595,000 units to 499 units of Guitar Hero 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: Granted, that's really close
[SPEAKER_08]: but also it should be noted that the All You Need Is Love download track 100,000 downloads in September so this is only considering September it's not considering the important Christmas period I don't want to start all this like OMG Guitar Hero 5 got his butt kicked but it is a little surprising considering Beatles Rock Band to some was kind of a niche title
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it is I'm not remotely surprised, I'm surprised it didn't sell more
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people are actually surprised the Beatles game didn't sell more.
[SPEAKER_08]: But of course, you know, this game will move throughout Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, both of these games are still going to continue to move, but it is a very... I mean, doesn't Guitar Hero... I mean, just taking the whole Beatles thing out of it, doesn't Guitar Hero usually tend to beat Rock Band on sales chart?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it depends who you're asking because...
[SPEAKER_03]: they say yeah we've sold more units well yeah you have like 5 times as many games coming out so yes you've sold more units so you can't really trust those numbers I mean look at even the Guitar Hero platform you've still got 2 more games coming out this year in Guitar Hero well Band Hero but come on it's Guitar Hero it's just E10 and then Van Halen that's still coming out too so it's a little oversaturation right now
[SPEAKER_08]: Enough already!
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you go see it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like the last few because it's just hard to follow what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this one actually took place after the last movie in chronology, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they kind of explained a lot of things and I thought it was actually pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_08]: But do you know what it got beat by?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did it explain why people like it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where the wild things are, I'm guessing.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: It got beat by a little indie title that has made it big called Paranormal Activity.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I should have figured.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was the number one movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that...
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually get to see that for free pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that movie's made a lot of buzz based off of the internet and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, funny enough, we're 10 years, believe it or not, after the Blair Witch Project, which is a very similar kind of marketing, although technology's changed in the past 10 years.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Paranormal Activity is sort of 2009's Blair Witch Project in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're marketing it like the Wii, whereas...
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not going to put it out everywhere and you're going to hear how awesome this movie is and you're going to be like, I wish I could see it, but it's not in my town.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we're going to flood the market with it and then everyone goes and sees it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what they did this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft in chat says, enough is enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've had it with these motherfucking saws in my motherfucking movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that apparently might be what some people are saying about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Except for the fact that maybe they just put out too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, here's what comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what comes down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think the Van Halen game was needed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think in the Metallica game and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't need to buy them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Guitar Hero fans do buy them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the reason you keep putting them out is because you keep buying them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Quick question chat and then we'll get into the next story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xlink asks, speaking of Saw basically, how many people have bought Saw the video game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any idea, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: How that game's moving?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Saw video game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, but I can find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look that up while Jamie brings us the next story.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we can move on there and then we'll figure that out later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for people who are playing Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2, there actually is a future character coming up for download.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Cable.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right now he's an NPC, but he will be downloadable to be playable.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that's a pay to unlock type of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I hope he's not overly imbalanced.
[SPEAKER_10]: But also, for more missions, there's a Psylocke mission coming out too, which will be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you played the Ultimate Alliance game yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: The new one?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's still sitting right here on my desk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's not great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It only came out a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is only showing in the first two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it has dropped in half versus week one, week two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it'll bump up again with the new movie out and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halloween and all that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halloween, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 3 version sold only 20,000 units.
[SPEAKER_03]: So 50,000 total.
[SPEAKER_03]: But once again, I bring up the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: These publishers are putting out games that are only selling under 100,000 units or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: President Cat could do quite well over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if their expectations are just to sell maybe a few hundred thousand units, if that, or even like a hundred thousand units, it's easy on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Easy to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of curiosity, and I apologize because I know we don't have the answer right in front of you, but how does this compare to Silent Hill Homecoming?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I know at one point they were talking about Saw was supposed to be like Konami's new series that...
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess was going to coexist with Silent Hill, but you kind of get the weird feeling, are they going to try and replace Silent Hill with Saw?
[SPEAKER_08]: Silent Hill Homecoming kind of took a lot of crap from the reviewers and the fact that they just outright cancelled the game for Japan, which kind of says something about their faith in the game as it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think the game was terrible by any means.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was different from the other games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could tell it was developed somewhere else, but I don't think it was bad at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: In comparison, for example...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360 version now of Saw only sold 20,000 units in the first week.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360 version of Silent Hill sold 47,000 units in the first week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, about almost 30,000 more units and then continued to sell and still continuing to sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, once again, it's a little early to see, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: And you don't just pull these numbers out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you do a little bit, but keep in mind, for those that may not have listened to the show before, Loki, you work in distribution, so you have a pretty good thumbprint on, you know, who's ordering what.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, and I'm also looking at, there's a website, VGCharts, that pulls stuff from MPD numbers, so I'm looking at what the actual numbers were each week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Silent Hill on PS3 sold 41,000 units in the first week versus the 20 that sold, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: Not even 20, you know, probably like 15 for Saw, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Complete random-ass question I'm going to put out there, and maybe you don't even know the answer to this, but is there any highly anticipated game coming out this season that you're just noticing is not selling?
[SPEAKER_08]: That you're just not selling copies of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not selling copies of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm putting you on the spot a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rabbids Go Home isn't doing very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a lot of people are picking that up in large quantities like the other Rabbids games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're kind of getting worn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they've worn out their welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say maybe...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to beg and plead for Demon's Souls.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then everybody after the fact was scrambling for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, dude, I told you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should have listened to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So is that game actually moving now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, it's moving.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're sold out at Atlus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they keep selling out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's probably the fastest moving Atlus title I've seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd say probably this fall, the one title that's not going to do as well as the company's hoping, I'm guessing, would be Avatar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's going to do that well, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the one based on the movie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that movie's going to bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that movie's going to be a big fucking bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not knocking it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually looks kind of neat, but I just think it's going to be one of those movies that is, especially considering who's behind it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The hype is too high.
[SPEAKER_08]: The hype is way too high.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that movie's going to bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, watch me be wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is something, you know, that may not sell a lot, but I think this looks freaking phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you guys know what a Microsoft... Oh, I know one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is really sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles The Crystal Bearers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a tough sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one wants to buy it because the last one was a port of a DS title and everybody hated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they're like, oh, Crystal Chronicles, I'm not bringing that shit in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Dungeons and Dragons, essentially.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's using the surface table, get this, you can actually plot out little pieces on the map, and they actually show you a little tour of this, you can put pieces on the grid, so you can actually, you know how people get out their big charts and their pen and paper to move characters around?
[SPEAKER_08]: Imagine being able to do all that on the surface, and look at that, D20 flying in, that you can actually roll there virtually.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can't cheat!
[SPEAKER_08]: You can do that virtually there on the Microsoft Surface, and you can actually move these little pieces around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now this is going to make the nerds want to have one of these in their home.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is pretty cool having this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is just a proof of concept for right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think a lot of people have looked at these surfaces going, what do you do with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's not a lot to do here, but this is starting to get really expensive too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I've never seen one outside of that one hotel.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it seems like that's where you're going to see them is in the lobbies of hotels for people to find coffee shops and expensive restaurants they want to go to and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Salacious Pop in chat says some casinos in Vegas are starting to use it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I can see that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Entertainment says Microsoft Surface is a cool thing to play around with.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like watching TV while high without actually being high.
[SPEAKER_08]: It certainly is something a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a cool little device.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it just might be a little ahead of its time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not the kind of thing people are going to have in their homes.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not going to be replacing your coffee table with a surface at any time soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then again, I don't have a coffee table.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't spill a drink on it, though, or you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's the other nervous thing about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, then again, I've dropped my iPhone I don't know how many times, and it still works, but I also put a protective case on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've dropped mine on concrete.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, me too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it hasn't broken, and I don't have a case on mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I have a big, thick case on mine because when I got my iPhone, I said, okay, I know this guy's going to get dropped, so I need to figure out a case I can put on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, you don't even have a protective screen on it, do you?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at the back of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not bad at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again... Yours is silver.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't even know they made them.
[SPEAKER_08]: The original ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an old-school iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which I'm going to auction off when I get my 3GS for a holiday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think those things are pretty waterproof because it looks like they have a picture, like a fancy picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like someone in a casino that have their drinks set on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that because the monitor is actually so inside of it, you know, and the table goes way beyond the actual monitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you spilled something, it would just drip over the edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more comment from Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: NBC News used Surface during their 2008 election coverage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and also that probably has a lot to do with that Microsoft and NBC collaborate on a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, MSNBC, hello.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then, you know, I like watching election year coverage because that's when all the channels try to roll out their new technology to get you to watch them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember when CNN did the holograms?
[SPEAKER_08]: I dropped my iPhone the other night and totally cracked the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how many times I dropped it before and it had been fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan did his first time he got his.
[SPEAKER_10]: He cracked it in his pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: So careful, careful, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't think I'll be buying one of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're $12,500.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know, like in five years, that price is going to... Remember when HDTVs were $8,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, it's still way too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get an HDTV, put a nice touchscreen interface on it, surface, done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you don't really... I don't understand why this stuff's so expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a $12,000 unit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Salacious Pop was just asking as we were talking about it on air because there's a little delay.
[SPEAKER_08]: LOL, what channel did the Princess Leia shit?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great way to describe what CNN did that year.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Red Entertainment follows up with Wolf Blitzer, I am your father.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Funny, funny, funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: uh let's see really random topic and then we're going to get it into the mailbag your emails at mailbag at orange loss radio.com DarkSakura will read here in a moment but I'm going to throw out this completely random question from chat it's like throw random questions at Loki night I swear uh Deakman is asking Loki did you see this announcement that a custom firmware for the PSP 3000 is supposed to be released next week
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm gonna go look at this up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, you look it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, DarkSakura's gonna dive into the mailbag at mailbag at orangelaundrater.com and read your emails, cause dang it, you send us emails and show us a little love, so we show you some love back in a little segment we call the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, um, hi LLR, thanks for reading my Twitter questions while playing on the short show about the official Konami DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_10]: Following up on it, I was wondering what you guys thought about the age restrictions on Konami's official DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have enclosed a snippet about it on the official summary.
[SPEAKER_10]: All registrants must be between the ages of 13 and 32 years as of April 1st, 2009.
[SPEAKER_10]: According to these rules, I actually would be ineligible to compete next year if there was another tournament.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure what to think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they are thinking someone hits 32, they fall apart.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, give it the good work, peace out, and triple A. That's from Jammer J. I think that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's incredibly stupid and kind of insulting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially to the fanbase that kind of helped DDR get big.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is exactly why I had no idea about this until you mentioned it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I stopped following it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then again?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe that's why I'm not allowed to participate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Next year I won't be allowed to participate.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was 32 April 1st of 2009.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to alienate some of your potential fans that way, go for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need a new nose, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am and I'm not over the DDR thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some days I go, I'm so done with DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not cool anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then I go, I kind of want that new one on the 360 PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: My sheet metal came in the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what that's for, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, for your little DDR project.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you're still in your 20s, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, barely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: You young whippersnapper in your DDR mat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our way so far is getting official Konami stickers from the arcade machine that are going to go on this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's how awesome it's going to look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how do you feel that in four years or whatever, you're dead to Konami?
[SPEAKER_08]: Deadman Walking, Deadman Dancing Deadman Dancing
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, over DDR, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is just a scam to get you to buy more dance mats.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we have a lot of listeners that are still attached to the music games, and yes, we founded the station on it, but I guess now that some of us are getting that 32 threshold, I guess we are officially too old for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, look at their game releases for DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not doing...
[SPEAKER_03]: Game only releases, not until like way later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to really stick with DDR and buy a new release each year, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to get Softmat to go with that release.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be $10 more than it would normally be by itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: If Beatmania 2DX or whatever goes to PlayStation 3, I'm very interested in what's next for that franchise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I've always loved Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if it goes to the PlayStation 3, you can import that shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, I didn't even think of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point, my man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: More emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I'm kind of feeling like crap right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one is a Kingdom Hearts 358 two-day mini-review.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, well, I'm saying this because you guys probably aren't going to play the game, so I thought that writing a review would help motivate you guys to buy it or at least rent it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I beat it in a week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, please use punctuation and capitalize your thing, because...
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw a commercial for the game on TV today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just random thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never made it through the first game or played the second game or played the DS game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I glitched my second game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or played the PlayStation 2 port of the Game Boy Advance game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm so lost in it right now that I'm just not going to even bother.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to sum this up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You play as Roxas and he gives it an 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know who Roxas is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know who he is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I know who he is because I've heard about the second game, but this character means nothing to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rewrite your review with proper grammar and spelling and everything, and I'll put it up on the site.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do love the Kingdom Hearts games, but I'm just not interested in these handheld ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this all goes back to my whole, like, I'm just not as big of a fan of handheld games as I am playing them on my big TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll wait until the next big official Kingdom Hearts 3 comes out and leave all these side stories on the side.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, this one comes from AZHP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey OLR, I was listening to one of your September podcasts catching up on the backlog you flooded the feed with and I remembered hearing that Rob said he got food poisoning from a sandwich chain that toasts its subs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_10]: I used to work at Century Theater to save up for Nintendo Wii near one such store of that chain.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of those stores are franchised anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: One by my work is super clean.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they closed one not far from here.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one that was in the Target lot closed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I don't work over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not all doing great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, we got an angry letter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Angry letter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love angry emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: and thankfully I sound like crap now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dear OLR, I listened to the podcast of the October 18th show and was honestly astounded at what I heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Upon reflection, what did I expect to come out of the mouths of people who live in the liberal enclave that is California?
[SPEAKER_10]: How can you stand behind the possible presidency of Cat?
[SPEAKER_10]: Cat has little foreign animal experience and no executive experience and likes the coherent strategy to deal with the growing threat presented by radical fundamental fleets.
[SPEAKER_10]: I even doubt that Cat is even from this country.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard that Cat is a Persian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any rational person knows that the true and correct choice for president is Dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dog has expressed his bath-based strategy for dealing with the threat of fleas once and for all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dog has a steady paw and is loyal to her previous president, President Burrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Dog has chased cars in the past, but after accepting Jesus as his Lord and Master, I can assure you that Dog will never chase cars again.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you step into the gaming arena on Tuesday, remember who has stuck by you like a loyal friend who treats you like you are its pet and not the dominant person you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Vote for Dog for President.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it or the fleas win.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for letting me listen from the conservative Eden that is Utah Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: This message has been brought to you by Glenn Beck, a smart, rational, and sane voice for the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: If that isn't proof that I'm clearly kidding, what else can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'd have to say that Dog has been known to eat poop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, Dog thinks I threw something when I just faked him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't really know if I can trust Dog to not drool on the issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can rely on Cat to be self-sufficient.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except for Shermie, who's just fat and lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, Kat has eaten hair, so that's not as bad as poop, but still, both candidates have their flaws.
[SPEAKER_08]: Redertainment, you ignorant slut.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, that was like the email of the century.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loved it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the best ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm saving it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gold star for you, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that is worthy of the gold star email bag segment recipient.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't you agree, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was proper grammar and punctuation all that used?
[SPEAKER_10]: Quite.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gold star recipient.
[SPEAKER_08]: Applause to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Close the fanfare, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I close the fanfare.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do-do-do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's your fanfare.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well done there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does my fanfare get a gold star?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your fanfare gets a...
[SPEAKER_08]: My God, you're like really sick over there, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the dust in the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Open the window.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is dust in the room?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's... I opened up my old laptop case to try to find my SD card reader, and it kicked up a crap ton of dust.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All we are is dust in the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the official campaign song, by the way, of President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that it for emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send your email for possible reading on the air next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much of that is getting picked up by the mics?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate my nose.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alert the media.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to my nose.
[SPEAKER_10]: And dust.
[SPEAKER_10]: And did I mention my nose?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because F you to my fucking nose.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the fucking dust.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to people that have a story about everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I mean, like, we were watching people on the subway.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, riding Bart this weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was, on the way there, a woman who was talking about... For some reason...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe he's into recycling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe he's rich in cans, because cans is the new currency.
[SPEAKER_08]: Under the regime of President Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Catnip is the new currency.
[SPEAKER_03]: These people, though, just annoy the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_03]: They try to one-up everybody's stories and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how they have
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, oh yeah, my cousin lives there, and oh my, I went there and did sheet metal work, and oh, and my dog was from that country and stuff, and like, isn't there a character like that on Saturday Night Live?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had ten baby cows.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't believe Loki just did a great impression of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do impressions of that woman all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when we see people like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we were doing that too while she was talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, and yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we had Miley Cyrus follow us.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we were making fun of her the entire day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Miley Cyrus followed us, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And she was playing music for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we went to our house on the moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Miley Cyrus followed us because she's our slave.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I hate people who have stories better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh god, I can't follow that up, that's amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I guess my only FU would go to stress, because I have quite a lot of it at work right now, but, you know, it happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: And FU to the fact that I haven't updated LiveJournal in like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'm seriously falling behind on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't like feeling behind on my life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kristen Wiig, that's... Oh yeah, she's like the only woman on that show right now, isn't she?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they ever fire the one that dropped the F-bomb on air?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Some new chick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember her first show?
[SPEAKER_08]: She dropped the F-bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they gave her a character that said frickin', frickin', frickin' every other word.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one time she just slipped and said, Fuckin', I would have done the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've kind of felt bad for her.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Red Entertainment would like to point out the name of that character is Penelope, the one-upper.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the chat room is saying bless you to Jamie because they can all hear her nose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry it happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: A couple more news stories for you guys, then the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, personally, I haven't played this game yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I acquired it for my MAME cabinet earlier today.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the game is Toki.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a 2D side-scrolling game starring an ape.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently it's getting the HD treatment.
[SPEAKER_03]: The French developer Golgoth Studio is taking the game and completely redoing all the graphics in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it actually looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hope the game's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it looks like it's all hand-drawn now and...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's the stuff you would normally expect on BoxArt, but it's all in motion now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently it'll be coming out for games for Windows Live and Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's not like a full retail game, it's kind of more of a mini-game if it's coming out on Arcade, but it looked kind of neat from the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could still be a full game, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, here's some games that didn't do so great when they came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: This story kind of caught our attention, and I don't like a whole lot of these top ten kind of lists, but this particular piece on GamesRadar.com, I thought was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: They ran a piece earlier this week called 18 Awesome Games That Died at Retail.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what I thought about reading this list is I wanted to see how many of these games, Jamie, being the collector of obscure-ass video games, was going to pipe up and say, that game was awesome!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one of those big games on GameTap, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were really selling that when that first came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, this is a list from GamesRadar.
[SPEAKER_08]: 18 games that died at retail.
[SPEAKER_08]: Grand Theft Auto Chinatown War is a more recent game coming out because folks saying there's not enough mature games for the system, but at the same time, not enough Nintendo fans wanting mature games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did this die, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't really care to... I didn't like the way it played just because it was a top-down game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I prefer more of like the
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP versions and stuff that are more the 3D stuff you'd see on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand why they did it that way because the system might not be able to handle that.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, now we see that Cop of the Recruit is coming out from Ubisoft and looks like what the PlayStation Portable versions of Grand Theft Auto were so it is possible to do it that way but they decided not to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it'll have a better chance on the PSP probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on with the list from GamesRadar.com, Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, I'm sure a list like this just wouldn't be complete without Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_08]: It gets a lot of praise all around.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was something that was originally supposed to be an exclusive for Microsoft but then got killed and brought back and just didn't really have a serious marketing push behind it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Jamie will get behind this one, Jet Grind Radio on the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the 18 games that tanked here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, just being the fact that it was on the Dreamcast console put a damper in it there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Metal Storm is on this list.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is an old-ass NES side-scrolling game, like on the old-school 8-bit NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty sweet, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1991, but unfortunately, it didn't really sell very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying it might have something to do with the fact that it was a crappy localization process and the cutscenes were taken out when it was brought over and it screwed with the color palette.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shenmue 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I have that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I have that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Earth Defense Force Oddworld, Stranger's Wrath on the Xbox is on the list Armed and Dangerous for the PC
[SPEAKER_08]: Otogi 2 Immortal Warriors I never even heard of this game but it was a Japanese hack and slasher about like an ancient swordsman it was a sequel to a game that apparently didn't do too well in the first place Space Station Silicon Valley on the N64 it was kind of a whimsical little platformer robot animal type of game that just got lost in the whole N64 not being one of Nintendo's greatest systems Panzer Dragoon Orta from 2003 is on the list that was a good game
[SPEAKER_08]: The Last Express Bionic Commando
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Grim Fandango, also on the list, getting down towards the end here.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Neverhood, from 1996, on the list.
[SPEAKER_08]: And last but not least, Okami made the list, which isn't surprising at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the reason why Okami kind of got burned, it was out on the PlayStation 2, kind of when the next generation of games was already starting.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, and the PS2 was already dying out for a lot of hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that was one of the biggest problems with Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it came out too late.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the time Final Fantasy XII came out, it should have been on the next-gen system.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's just me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess we're getting to that part of the show where we're going to open up the Skype line and hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number you want to call if you want to get on the show or you can just Skype us directly at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do want to give a little disclaimer first.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been having problems with Skype the past couple weeks where we've been randomly hanging up on callers.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did upgrade to a new version of Skype.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hola, bienvenidos a Orange Launch Radio, quien es?
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, you should always check your microphone connection calling Echo 123 on Skype before you give us a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise, it may not work.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I could swear I heard somebody breathing there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they just couldn't hear us for some reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard someone breathing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know what the hell was going on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So somebody was not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know what happened there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have any other... Actually, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it's Mr.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, SSJ100 Matt, how are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm doing well, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what's going on, but what are you up to tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I just got out of Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Video Games Live?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it in New York City tonight?
It was.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went to other...
[SPEAKER_06]: I went to the Dear Friends concert a while back when it was done, and this was a lot better.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the first one I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think the best one was when he did the encore, it was Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just want to point out, we realize SSJ100Mad is breaking up.
[SPEAKER_08]: His connection is kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that's because of the new Skype or what's going on, but we're going to try and get through this because I want to talk about Video Games Live a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Chrono Trigger piece, we were there the night that debuted in Oakland.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was an awesome night, so a good piece.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad that came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any lowlights?
[SPEAKER_08]: Were there songs that they were playing where you were kind of like, they could have bumped this for something else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was cool that they brought in Mega Man, which I don't think they brought in previous shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: But to Jamie's surprise, they did play Castlevania songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they have any guests show up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because sometimes they have random guests show up at these things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they did have a kid from YouTube that played Mario songs blindfolded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, on the piano?
[SPEAKER_08]: He was there when we went.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think Tommy has him on the payroll or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: He follows him everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, they called in, I'm trying to think of his name, Ross Baer, the creator of Pong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on to more calls and more last-minute stories here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope that was just an isolated thing and not something that's going to continue.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said he was somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was cutting out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think he said he was at a game or something, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll try to get a couple more calls here.
[SPEAKER_08]: 877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, do you have any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: DS Master 25 What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, kind of a sad story today.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: As soon as I get done... What the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there an argument?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is somebody breaking a dish behind you?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: My mother.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is she yelling at you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, my DS... Who are you talking to?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on the radio, Mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's 11 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, the L button on my DSI died, and it's only been like a few months.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't know if any of our listeners have had that problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is your mom mad that you're calling in so late?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: You shouldn't say Jesus in front of your mother like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's usually frowned upon, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: you realize your whole call has just been shot because now everybody's just saying mom I'm on the radio sorry but basically my DSI the stupid L button stopped working in the middle of 3D pinball of all things I'm sorry to hear it but mom's not going to buy you a new one if you keep staying up late to call stupid internet radio programs
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyways, I do have a good game review, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts, Jaren Fitgate, over two days.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say here, I've been a long-time Square fan, even though I kind of despised them on the first Kingdom Hearts, because I'm like, what the hell are you thinking, Square?
[SPEAKER_04]: Combining with Disney?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, and then a friend told me, don't knock it till you try it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, and I fell in love with this series right then and there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when Kairi left, I kind of cried.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically now I'm still on the search for in this one, which is supposed to be the real link between 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So unfortunately I had to sell my PlayStation 2 off because of the overdraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm planning on getting one again just to play the rest of the Kingdom Hearts series again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your mom didn't see you crying in a video game, did she?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, my girlfriend did, though, and she kind of cried along.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, no, Kyrie, don't leave.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, chicks seeing you cry, that just scores you points with them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you don't want your mom to see you cry because then she thinks you're a wimp.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm surprised my father is already bashing the whole Hannah Montana stuff and saying, at least you're playing good music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, are you a Hannah Montana fan?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was the one who sent in that angry message.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, remember, leave Hannah alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I try every day to forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 271.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, don't look it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would have only been like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't going to get any better.
[SPEAKER_08]: DS Master 25 or 26 or whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's way past your bedtime, young man.
[SPEAKER_08]: But any other last minute thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Beatmania 2DX17 for PS3 is going to rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm importing it with a PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's indefinite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to bed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like
[SPEAKER_03]: and then it got worse and then it got worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to admit that call was pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of feel bad for him, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, this is Ray or Ray Force, whatever you go on in Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up, Ray?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this past week, I managed to get my hands on a Street Fighter 4 5-in-6 tournament edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had a big stick with the real arcade parts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what did you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I thought... I was playing mostly, like, shooter-type games, like... Riding Fires and such with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes some time getting used to it, especially with the square well, but... Instead of, like, having an octagonal well or a circular one, but once you get used to it, like... Playing a...
[SPEAKER_05]: How expensive is this thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that kind of stuff tends to go down in price, though, after just a little bit of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because haven't those been out a little while?
[SPEAKER_08]: Since February.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they've been out for nearly a year now, and I believe the friars around me are starting to run out of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, if you're going to build your own, it's a lot cheaper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I actually thought about getting one of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we're thinking of the same device.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking about getting one of those a while ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can basically, if you get the encoder board for it, which they're not that expensive, the actual buttons and everything, it'll cost anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't build my own stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would I be able to do this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It plugs in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Switch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be very surprised.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Ray, was it worth the money?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it worth the money?
[SPEAKER_08]: What I kind of like about what you're saying is that you're not actually using this to play Street Fighter 4, but that you're using it to play, like, other games, like shooters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I think, seriously, if I were to get one of these, I'd actually use it to play, like, Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I suck horribly at fighters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm mostly, I'm a schmuck person first, and a fighting game person, like, way further down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, buddy, do you have anything else you want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other games you've been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm playing Space Invaders Extreme too, but I haven't played it for long, so I'll probably call in by next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, please do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very curious to hear about that game, because I did enjoy the first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to hear about what's new in the second one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'll have that later when there's more time to talk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of my calls this time are on my arcade stick, so any other people who can't be called.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll arrange something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, you're in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any chance we're going to see you at Umlaut?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: If on a Wednesday, I'm not sure if I'll be able to make it on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's past 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's in San Jose, not San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're in the South Bay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a weeknight.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's tough.
[SPEAKER_08]: But hopefully we'll see some of our Bay Area friends able to get up there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's going to be a fun night.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, see ya Later
[SPEAKER_03]: Just real quick, there's a new indie game that's on Xbox Live Indie Games called Pumpkin Shop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, this would be the perfect time of the year to release a pumpkin carving sim.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can do just that without the mess and have your own virtual pumpkin that no one can smash against your porch.
[SPEAKER_03]: No word on how expensive that is, but that is called Pumpkin Shop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds a little ridiculous to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be cool if you could share it with your friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to carve a pumpkin, carve a pumpkin.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised there's not a Facebook app to do that and you share it with your friends so that you get annoying little notices and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm kind of surprised there isn't that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now that you said it, there'll probably be one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a shame that there's not millions of dollars coming into my mailbox each day because that would be tragic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could start your own game company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Release the pumpkin carving Facebook app.
[SPEAKER_08]: Release President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd be a rich man.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what we can do with President Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just a matter of giving... That sounds like a threat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't release that many games a year, so I think that their budget might be really low.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd say both them and UFO Interactive would be good candidates to bug about releasing the game over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then followed by maybe... I'm not sure about Ignition or...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, who was the other one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, like Ignition, because they really only release certain types of games over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, really a lot of the RPGs and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that wouldn't really fit with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Axis Game Localization, man, it's all sorts of weird shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Graffiti Interactive would be good too, but they're really low budget and it takes forever for them to get stuff out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if you guys send out emails out there, we definitely want to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send your responses, the responses you get back from companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll post something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll post something.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there's a thread in our forums for it, we'll post the information of where we need to go with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I loved the excuse me, I loved the way people used the photo stream last week to show pictures of President Cat and their fan art.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would like to encourage people this week, you know, we're still a little bit on our President Cat kick.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll think of a new theme maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But continuing on that, I would really like to see in the photo stream and email your pics to pics at orange lingerie dot com.
[SPEAKER_08]: They go right up on our website when you do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I would like to see conceptual box art for this game if released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe an online petition might not hurt because at least it shows, okay, look, there's a few hundred people interested in getting this game over here to see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gives people focus to make their mark or something like that, and we'll go from there.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if that's it for Last Minute Stories tonight, then we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: my final thought is I have my arcade cabinet in my house and now I gotta finish it my final thought is I want chicken
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll play a loco to be exact, which reminds me of this week's episode of South Park, which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyhow, that's going to do it for this week's episode of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a word to the wise out there, those folks that are listening live.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have Daylight Savings Time kicking in next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's spring forward, fall back.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we will be moving the clocks back an hour here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you don't celebrate Daylight Savings Time in your country or where you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're looking at you, Arizona.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, please plan accordingly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's Arizona that doesn't have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So please plan accordingly for those of you folks that don't have daylight savings time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my  I guess that was it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I get my final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're good to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always like to say also if you enjoyed Orange Lounge Radio, please tell two friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Help spread the word because remember we have no big magazine backing us up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have no advertising dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: We rely strictly on word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do the show for free, no ads.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not even 9 o'clock yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of early tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still been an almost three-hour show, maybe two and a half.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's time to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio on November 1st.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't believe it's almost the end of the year already.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're getting into the very, very busy game season.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!