[SPEAKER_05]: Is that Simtoplus?
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the deal over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have naked Sims on your computer?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, he's not naked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, hi, we're live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, we're live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, we're not live.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're taped tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little special edition of Morison's Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a voice from the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, scary ghost of Christmas past.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we're pre-taping tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, if you've been following OLR, we're out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_05]: As you guys are hearing this live on All Games Radio, I am far, far away in a strange, mystical land that they call La.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_05]: Not here tonight is the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're taping Not Live on a Tuesday night, and Loki just isn't here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He didn't show up, and to be fair, I didn't call him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say, shouldn't you have called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, probably I should have, but here's the thing, is that then we'd have to wait 30 minutes for him to show up, and I'm just like, I want to get the hell out of here and get some dinner tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: He missed the boat.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Should we call Matt and see where he's at?
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you pre-tape?
[SPEAKER_05]: Silly little... That's what they call it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's industry speak for... Silly little prefixes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I think we were going to do like a best of tonight or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're going to roll that over until later because one of our listeners slash staff members, in other words, he listens so long we decided to just make him a staff member, Dark Tetsuya, is like putting something together out of some really old episodes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And of course this wouldn't be...
[SPEAKER_05]: It just wouldn't be OLR if the music I didn't intend to play started playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: How does that happen even when we're not live?
[SPEAKER_05]: I had two songs queued up tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The open and the Twitter topic song which we'll get into a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Simps3 and Peggle
[SPEAKER_01]: I never really got into it, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you think you never were able to get into WoW?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, certainly there's plenty of our listeners who don't play Warcraft and there's some that do.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it that made you not really want to stick with it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd hit around level seven and go, what the hell am I doing with my time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's what I hear from a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, like when I was, I had a fun time playing with Tiara a while back.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's like, I'm not a get up and quest-o-rama type person and zip through them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like to explore a little bit and take it, you know, kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it was like, this is kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: It almost sounds like you're talking about something dirty.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like to take my time and explore a little bit slow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I have a good time if I'm playing with people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you talking about WoW or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: In regards to World of Warcraft, I have a better time playing with a friend when I've got something to... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: But what I was saying is it's more fun when I have other people to participate in the game with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of all the things in this room, you threw a box of Kleenex at me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: You almost hit Shermie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I figured if it landed on Shermie, it wouldn't hurt her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: You notice who did not budge?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shermie, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: She just parks her fat ass there next to the very warm computer for pretty much the night.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's her little fortress of solitude.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well on tonight's show, oh, I actually did play one new game I want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll give them something new.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Luminous for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you say Bluminous?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Luminous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought so, but... Or Lumines, as some people call it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Luminous!
[SPEAKER_05]: Luminous.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the puzzle game that, of course, was hugely, disgustingly popular on the PSP, and rightfully so.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then had a sequel come out on the PSP that I don't think was quite as well received, even though it had Hollaback Girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then it had versions on the PlayStation Network as well as Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Xbox Live version, of course, was highly criticized for being kind of the first microtransaction-y game where there was just lots and lots of little things to download and add to the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's out on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Luminous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, Luminous is one of my favorite puzzle games ever because, you know, I love music games and I love the whole infusion and all that, kind of like how the music plays a part in the puzzle game where, you know, if you've never played Luminous before, basically you're trying to make blocks of varying size out of four by four blocks of different colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the bar that sweeps across the field moves in time to the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as you move the blocks around, the beats that it makes kind of fit in with the music.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it worth the purchase to you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the iPhone, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: The version of Luminous that I played on my old Sprint cell phone that had a four directional key and stuff was more fun to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let me tell you why.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: and the reason why is that they made one key design flaw and that flaw is that in order to move the bricks you touch the screen and you move your finger left or you move your finger right but to drop it you move your finger down so what do you think happens when I'm playing keep dropping it exactly
[SPEAKER_05]: Pebble is so beautiful on iPhones.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: So, if you are a fan of Luminous, avoid, avoid, avoid until they get this control scheme fixed.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I don't care if they put this shitty touch control thing in as an option, but what they need to do is have it so you can turn drops off, or that there's a specific little button in the right-hand corner or something where my thumb could rest that would drop the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the only way you would drop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would make it so much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura has been browsing the MMO world and has found quite a bit going on apparently in the land of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, for the people looking forward to Star Trek Online, namely me, if you get the Season 3 Blu-ray that's going to be coming out, then you will be actually receiving an Admiral's outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really think they're trying to push the game, especially with using champions to do it and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah...
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like they're really trying to get the fans of the series into the MMO even if they're not necessarily gamers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is smart, but the problem is, as weird as it sounds, I am kind of a bit of a Trekkie, but I don't really have an interest in those Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_05]: The original series Blu-rays, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, like, original series season three?
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, wait, no, there was no third season.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there a third season?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there were only two, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure there were, yeah, because third season is when you really started noticing the toupee.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not really into the original series anyway, as much of a Trekkie as I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all about, yeah, I mean, I get that, but it was all about the, it was all about Next Generation and Voyager and Deep Space Nine.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all about DS9.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess that's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, a little bonus perk tie-in, but sorry, I'm not going to spend like $80 on a Blu-ray box set season just to get some one little dumb little item.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully it'll be unlockable some other ways.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, then again, it's like the admirals, all they do is sit in a chair and be important.
[SPEAKER_01]: The captain's seat is what everyone joins Starfleet for, you know, to sort of paraphrase a DS9 episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still very, very curious about Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a little jealous of those that went to PAX and got to get a little sneak peek of it because I definitely am curious where this game is headed.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of great MMOs on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XIV, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hate on XI all you want, but XIV looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really interested in where this game goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, by the time I play it, a lot could change, but the trailer looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even WoW's next expansion looks really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also some news about Final Fantasy XI since you brought it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are still playing Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: In October, there's going to be a new expansion titled Shantotto Ascension that's supposed to...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually they say that the next free version update is going to be in November.
[SPEAKER_01]: But other than that, we're looking for October for the expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will have the new Wings of the Goddess Nation quests, the Moblin Maze Monger's dungeon crawling system, and it's also the final part in a series of stories that was written by the guy who wrote the story for Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_01]: Masato Kato.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is going to stick out for a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it was written by the guy who did Chrono Trigger, there's going to be fanboys that are like, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the trilogy of the stories, I'm trying to pull up that information.
[SPEAKER_01]: But seriously, I don't think that
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I remember hearing about these.
[SPEAKER_05]: These were the very small mini expansions they released that are like online only that you would get for the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they pretty much stopped with the in-store ones, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they have 14 on the horizon, development for 11 is probably going to slow up significantly and remain things like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens to a game like Final Fantasy 11 when Final Fantasy 14 comes out?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's probably going to go the way of PSO.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you look at EverQuest and EverQuest 2, I think there's more people still playing the original EverQuest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I think that doesn't always happen, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, then again, there are still a bunch of people playing Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we haven't had a lot of MMOs get sequels yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Diablo 3 is still not out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the Ragnarok one was still going on, and a lot of people were still preferring the 2D over the 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I totally forgot about Ragnarok 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if that... So that finally came out at some point?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I stopped paying attention to it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't touched Ragnarok in like a month, so... A whole month?
[SPEAKER_01]: I couldn't really get back into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sort of was going through the same thing that I went through, you know, with World... Like, what am I doing with my time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well... So you went back to Sims instead.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is actually the first time I've opened Sims in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just giving you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except to remodel a character.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's something about a game that you like, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Aion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aion, you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never did end up buying the full game because I heard about all the problems they were having.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I don't need to be the very first person in an MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to give Aion a few months to let the dust settle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's been having a lot of issues.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this is actually more news for our European listeners anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are opening two European servers.
[SPEAKER_01]: One is a French language server called Deltris and an English server called Karun.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be available for character transfers from the different servers in a couple of months.
[SPEAKER_01]: They haven't said exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's on its way.
[SPEAKER_01]: They say that everything should...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, I've got some other news for you guys that doesn't have to do with MMOs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually been a few things that have happened over the past couple days.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii got a system update.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has a brand new 4.2 release software, and you might be asking, oh, what cool new feature do I get with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: And the answer is nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least there's nothing that they're touting that is big about this release.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, the Wii system update 4.2 really only did some things behind the scenes, and it's also supposed to improve...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: also big big and confirmed this week there were some rumors about this and we talked about it on the show but Super Street Fighter 4 was confirmed earlier this week it apparently was revealed by GameSpot has released the first details on the game T-Hawk and DJ are coming back in the game and there's also going to be a brand new female character named Juri that is coming back to Street Fighter 4 Super Street Fighter 4 is it spelled J-U-R-I?
[SPEAKER_05]: yeah
[SPEAKER_01]: It could also be one of the alpha characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember Judy and Junie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Street Fighter 4 Super Street Fighter 4
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a little back and forth going on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love the graphic style in this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah, it doesn't look like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks like just another Ken vs. Ryu little epic battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's really going to show any new people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy, what if this is what the fighting actually looked like in the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the same freaking font and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: For Super?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course you know I'd notice the font.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, there's going to be...
[SPEAKER_05]: 8 new characters, 3 of them probably familiar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently though, Capcom will not charge full price for the title.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure what that means.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm assuming that means it's probably going to be in the realm of $40 for this as opposed to a full $60 game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another thing to consider, did they say that it was going to be hard copy or did they say it's going to be a download?
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe this is an all-new release that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not some type of download expansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we'll get some answers to that in the next few days.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's certainly, I think it would be too big for a download, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eight new characters and all this character balancing, that's big.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm pretty sure it's going to be... Does this mean that they're going to make Seth less of an ass?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, even the guys that made the game said he's way too powerful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that coming up on a previous episode of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: One other story I've got for you guys about Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Squeenix apparently earlier this week, of course, that's my lovely name for Square Enix, which now is Square Enix Eidos.
[SPEAKER_05]: All that stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So would they be Squino... Squino-dos.
[SPEAKER_01]: Squindos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon Quest, Kingdom Hearts, Final Fantasy 8 flagship IPs
[SPEAKER_05]: If each one of these games has a two year development cycle for a new game in the franchise, then that means every quarter they could release a two million selling game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you could certainly see that happening with series like Final Fantasy, Dragon Quest, Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the question is, where the hell are the other games going to come from?
[SPEAKER_00]: Star Ocean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that a two million selling title every time?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Tales games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Batman and Kingdom Hearts!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's possible, but that would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up, Sora.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm Batman.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm Batman.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you one of the heartless... I'm Batman.
[SPEAKER_00]: Batman!
[SPEAKER_05]: You almost... You know what you remind me of there?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Eddie Murphy from 80s Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Gumby.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm Gumby, damn it.
Remember that?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's old school.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very old school.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's older than most of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's older than most schools.
[SPEAKER_01]: That joke right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well Jamie wants to tell you guys about one other thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is actually in regards to Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Crash Course is actually out on Steam and Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's actually a price point on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually was released at a higher price point, but ended up being an error.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is actually going to be out for, well is out I should say, for 560 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now, but it is, like I said, an error.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you think it's worth the money to spend a little bit more on it, go for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But just keep in mind, it is going to be dropped.
[SPEAKER_01]: And of course, if you have it on PC, then the Crash Course actually isn't really available from Steam yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to bridge the gap between the Death Toll and No Mercy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is very strange that it wouldn't even be on Valve's own service yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: On Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure it's just a little holdup.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just says that the download content is not available yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, we're going to get into a little segment we do here on Orange Launch Radio called Twitter Topics because...
[SPEAKER_05]: because we can because we can basically that's what it boils down to we're bored and don't really know what else to talk about here on the show tonight because it's only been a couple days since our last show we go to twitter and we say hey guys what do you guys want us to talk about tonight because you know it's where every gamer has a voice and
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, we can't do calls tonight because we're not actually live.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's another show going on on All Games right now, so we couldn't, you know, we don't have our own radio station anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can't just bust down the door and say, hey, guys, we're live.
[SPEAKER_00]: We could just go, hey, chat room, someone call us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess we could go bust down the door on All Games, but I don't think the VGO fans would appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no, they can call our line.
[SPEAKER_05]: We only have a couple people in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've been soliciting questions from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we got plenty and plenty of questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: By all means, Mr. Rob Kerski.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tweets and chatters and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blue Swim is our first tweeter tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a lot of tweet questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got more.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got like twice as many as we usually do on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blue Swim on the Twitter asks, What do you guys think of the natural disaster survival genre?
[SPEAKER_05]: Twister the game with a flying cow and digital Helen Hunt tits equals epic win.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what though?
[SPEAKER_05]: If Loki were here, he would diss that game that Konami was showing at E3, which was something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like a natural disaster game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was one of those on Xbox Live not that long ago, too, and neither one of those games was exactly as awesome as you would think.
[SPEAKER_05]: And neither one had digital Helen Hunt tits, either.
[SPEAKER_01]: The closest I've ever played that had natural disasters in it that I could stand was the tornado area in Sonic the Hedgehog on Dreamcast, because that was pretty freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other than that, SUCK!
[SPEAKER_05]: BlueSwim goes on to say in a second tweet, After playing the PlayStation 2 game Raw Danger, I'm convinced that the disaster genre has huge amounts of untapped potential.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't leave that untapped, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not a game I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that something newer?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: GamerGirl on the Twitter asks, What was the first game anyone's ever played?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, that's tough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta go way back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's two.
[SPEAKER_05]: My earliest memories, because I don't remember, unfortunately, far enough back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard, because when you're that young, you don't remember everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would say I kind of have a memory of two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of them would be Spider-Man on the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was one of the first games I ever remember playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And at the arcade, Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember going to my sister's wedding reception once.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember being four and playing Pong on an arcade machine
[SPEAKER_01]: I grew up playing pinball, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as early memories, I remember being six and going to play the Odyssey 2 at my friend's house next door and playing Casey Munchkin and Casey Crazy Chase.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a ColecoVision when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Who enabled your gaming addiction?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it doesn't sound like your mom was really that much into video games, but yet you had all these systems that I never heard of.
[SPEAKER_01]: My mom actually was kind of into games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because keep in mind, when I was four, my mom was still in her early 20s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of my childhood was spent with my mom in her 20s.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so she liked to go out and have fun and liked games and played some pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when we'd go get pizza, she'd give me a few quarters and leave me in the little game area so I could play the Mario one or play Kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kangaroo was... I was the shit at Kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, over at Godfather's Pizza back in the day in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been a gamer practically since I knew that turn this knob, the bar moves this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have very early memories of Atari 2600 in much the same way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember who got one for the family or how we got it, but we had an Atari 2600, and my dad hooked it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was hooked up in my mom's room, which I always thought was weird, but I think that was so that if my dad wanted to watch TV or somebody wanted to watch a real show, then I wouldn't be monopolizing the big television with video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I would always have to go in my mom's room to play, and then she'd get mad if I don't ask first.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also played a lot of Apple II games.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of Kix, Lode Runner.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also grew up on the Carmen Sandiego games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I played those too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mousetrap
[SPEAKER_01]: and, you know, her stupid ex-husband, Craphead, playing... He was really good at Carnival.
[SPEAKER_05]: GORF GORF GORF
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to hook up the old ass systems and see how long some of those games can hold our attention today.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's the point of actually having a TV that will run some of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep in mind, my Odyssey 2, we don't have a TV it works on.
[SPEAKER_05]: They take the old coaxial cable thing, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: The little hooky things.
[SPEAKER_05]: They go with the coaxial cable, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like hooking up cable.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: My Nintendo had one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, those TVs are going to actually be really easy to find now because a lot of them, because of the whole digital TV transition, they're obsolete.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what else are they good for but playing video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's move on with some other questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Takeo Ray wanted to plug his Extra Life donation page.
[SPEAKER_05]: The URL is very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll go ahead and read it here because obviously Extra Life was something we wanted to be involved with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, we had to
[SPEAKER_05]: Backout is shared on the last show, which sucks, but we are still supporting the cause, certainly.
[SPEAKER_05]: TKL Ray's page is at ways2give.texaschildrens.org slash netcommunity slash allen, A-L-L-E-N, Ray, R-E-Y.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all one word, A-L-L-E-N, R-E-Y.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to say, though, if you just want to check out what Extra Life's all about in general, I'm sure TKL Ray would not mind if you just donate to somebody that's participating, extralife.sarcastiggamer.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sarkastic Gamer
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how to pronounce this name, but I'll try.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sponchtwang?
[SPEAKER_05]: S-P-O-N-C-H-T-W-A-N-G Sponchtwang?
[SPEAKER_00]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you guys think about Konami rolling out the official DDR tourney?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Konami announced they are doing an official DDR tournament that is going to be in certain cities across the US and it all kind of comes to a head at an official Vegas tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: But in order to go to the one in Vegas, you have to win one of the satellite competitions that's happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: Qualifiers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think there is one happening in NorCal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the closest one is in the LA area.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a shame, because a bunch of the really good... I may be wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have the slide up in front of me, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think a lot of the... I mean, this comes from watching a lot of videos and seeing a lot of people, but I really do think that some of the best players were in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's good that Konami's finally doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're honestly, sadly, about five years too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this is something they should have done when Extreme was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to promote some of their new DDR games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the one mistake they're making, they didn't give a lot of notice before this tournament happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was literally like, hey, this is going to start in Texas next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that's probably one of the biggest mistakes they made.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whereas if they just would have given it a little time, like maybe a month, and maybe they did have it out and I just didn't hear about it until a week before, but I don't think there was a lot of notice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I want to say the first thing I read on DDR Freak said it was like this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: But
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Mario 3 It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Von Johnson on Twitter wants to know, what do you guys think about Borderlands?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I don't know much about this game, but I did a little bit of research, just because of your Twitter question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently this is a first-person shooter, but it also has RPG elements mixed in.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's being made by Gearbox, and 2K is publishing it, and it's coming out on PC, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want to make a franchise out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, when I'm first looking at this, just the box art and even some of the screenshots, I'm kind of like, they're kind of going for the Fallout audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: This looks a lot like kind of what Fallout is all about.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I want a Fallout game, I'll play Fallout.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, it's certainly... And then I'll throw up because I get motion sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the other thing you should know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does do random level generation.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of got something like Diablo.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're kind of saying it was like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, certainly this has its own merits.
[SPEAKER_05]: So things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: A content creation system, which will influence some of the weapons that you see in-game in the game world and the map.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it sounds like this is something that's going to kind of develop uniquely for each person.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially for an RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well...
[SPEAKER_01]: Weren't some of the dungeons in Phantasy Star, the earlier Phantasy Star games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fight to the Death
[SPEAKER_05]: So this certainly sounds like kind of an original game, you know, even though we're making jokes that it sounds a lot like Fallout.
[SPEAKER_05]: It definitely sounds like it has some unique features that try to make it set it apart.
[SPEAKER_05]: So hopefully they release a demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be my biggest thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I probably still wouldn't try it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you have the whole motion sick thing going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just don't play first person shooters in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't play a lot, but there are a few that I got really into.
[SPEAKER_05]: But most of them are old.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they're going to be anytime soon as long as Dan's got ODST.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quake, Duke Nukem, 3D those are the games I'm talking about that I got into I haven't gotten into a shooter I played a little bit of Halo the last one I played any severe amount of was Hexen now that is an old school shooting I wish there would be a game like that again like the whole magical mystical first person shooter type of thing that was a rad game Hexen was great just the whole problem being that was still sprite based and you know I think wasn't Heretic 2 the one that they did
[SPEAKER_05]: DoctorOfWarC or DoctorOfWork on Twitter who has a cute little chibi squirtle icon wants to know the last CD or song you bought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said anything goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last CD or song you bought.
[SPEAKER_01]: Physical CD?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, I can't even remember the last physical CD I bought.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was too long ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: The World's Greatest Mashups Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as an actual song, I bought actually what my cage match pick was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which didn't win, I'm sorry to tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki picked some song out of thin air and we both lost by one vote.
[SPEAKER_01]: He pulled it out of his ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: He did.
[SPEAKER_05]: He always does.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was all the Kylie stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say the last song I bought, funny enough, there's a story behind this.
[SPEAKER_05]: The last song I bought was Limbo Rock by Chubby Checker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: No joke, go back, it's in my iTunes receipt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish I had it on this computer, I'd play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was actually, it was for Rocky.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought it because there was a new little pre-showed game we did that was the limbo, so I had to get the song for that, but that's the last song I bought.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was your last physical CD?
[SPEAKER_05]: Regina Spector
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually think the last physical CD I bought was Flavors of Entanglement by Alanis Morissette and that came out like a year ago I just don't really buy physical CDs I'm pretty sure that it wasn't the mashups disc was the last one that I bought but I'll be damned if I can remember what it is I know what it was, Video Games Live I bought it at the concert
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's a great place to get physical CDs, is at concerts, because sometimes you need to sign them there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Simslova wants to know, what games are you excited about for next month?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still catching up on last month.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't been able to play crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were out because of your hand.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, I am still kind of out on my hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never even played Marvel Ultimate Alliance, did you?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, in fact, look, right here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, a sealed copy.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I really freaking want to play it so I can get my Deadpool on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Poor thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think my team is going to be Deadpool and uh uh Ms.
[SPEAKER_01]: Marvel and uh
[SPEAKER_05]: Phoenix, and Captain America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, in looking at the releases, DJ Hero clearly is a game I want to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, kind of slipping under the radar, I mean, there's a lot of big releases between Gran Turismo, PSP, Uncharted 2 certainly is going to be worth a look.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I do want to point out Demon's Souls is coming out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a game I checked out at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's been out in Japan for a little while, but they're adapting it over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like an RPG, but it's supposed to be super hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And especially with White Knight Chronicles getting pushed back to next year, I think I do want to pick up Demon's Souls and check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually a PlayStation 3 exclusive, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um... Nutman wants to know in chat... Yes, that's the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, not chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Twitter again.
[SPEAKER_05]: For Rob, a question just for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you go straight for Alicia Keys?
[SPEAKER_05]: Be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have to say no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not for Alicia Keys.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I could get into this whole tirade about I don't really believe there is going straight in quotes or going gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is just liking who you want to like, as I call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I go ahead and classify myself gay because I like guys mostly, but I'm not going to say I would never, ever, ever, ever, ever want to kiss a girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Like my soul!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Forest Green.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually really fond of dark, dark red.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually an in-joke amongst a lot of my friends that I always wear earth colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I pretty much always am wearing brown, green, black, you know, like earthy colors.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny enough, today I'm wearing all blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a little blue stripy shirt and blue jeans on today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm wearing gray.
[SPEAKER_01]: Acrylic is a bitch to wash out
[SPEAKER_05]: I got one more question on the Twitter that just came in a little bit ago while we've been taping and I'll give this one more reload before we sign off tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like this for a random show when there's not a lot of news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Soda or Pop?
[SPEAKER_05]: Asks Spazinator PSN on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate Pop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate it when people call it Pop.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just bugs me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like nails on a chalkboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pop is what you do to bubble gum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pop is what you do to bubbles when somebody blows them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technically, the name is Soda Pop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get that, but it just sounds weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm okay with that, even though I prefer Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pepsi is so much better because Coke tastes like poo.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now, when I go into a restaurant, and it throws people off so much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can I get you a drink?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd like a Diet Cola.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, cola.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's when you don't hear a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I don't like, I don't really care for the Sprite type drinks, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'll say, I would like a diet cola, whichever one you have.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that way they won't do, is Coke okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is Pepsi okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: I just said whichever one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know there's a, you know they have to do that though because plenty of people bitch about it when it's not the right one.
[SPEAKER_01]: But,
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's why I specify.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you've heard me do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will take a diet cola whichever one you have.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a blanket permission.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you don't have Coke or Pepsi but you have RC Cola, by all means, give me the RC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, I was going to say, when I hear the word cola, I think of RC Cola and I think of Shasta Cola, which I don't even think they probably sell outside of Markel.
[SPEAKER_01]: You remember Faygo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: I drink diet soda Rob, I have to give up my diet soda and my coffee and black tea I can have green tea Can you have Sprite?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_01]: Caffeine.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only type of caffeinated drink I'm supposed to have is green tea.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, the hell with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm having coffee.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'll have my one cup of coffee in the morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: One.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had really good Chinese food.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Asen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to see him again.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's a good guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish his show would come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a slick show that this day in gaming that he had.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it was T-Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to remember what it stood for.
[SPEAKER_05]: This day in gaming that he had that he... It was a slick show.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has a really good voice for radio and the guy that edited it did a really good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, Rob D asks in chat, first thing he said, what is your favorite Japanese media depiction of an American?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine is and will forever be Terry Bogard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one I'd really have to get some thought to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't think of any big stereotypes that jump out at me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would have to say from Axis Powers, Hetalia, America, who is always sitting in the corner eating cheeseburgers and giving emphatic orders.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to take the question in a different direction here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not my favorite Japanese media depiction of an American, but my favorite British depiction of an American was Bubbles from Absolutely Fabulous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure none of our listeners are going to get that reference, but that was my favorite depiction of an American.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only thing that's coming to mind, and it's not even her depicting an American, it's her depicting a Welsh... It's Dawn French doing her imitation of Catherine Zeta-Jones, but slipping into a fully California-American accent.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, oh, my California's showing!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to do it right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Catherine Zeta Douglas.
[SPEAKER_01]: I lost it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this something people can look up on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_01]: Catherine Zeta Douglas, Spartacus Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spartacus Jones?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just look up Don French or French and Saunders and Catherine Zeta Jones.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially the Roundabout one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think... Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a necessary evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know that's totally like I just picked none of the above in a way, which is sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the problem is that it's not just the gaming industry that I think has to deal with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movie industry, to a certain extent, definitely has to deal with this big time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sites like ain'titcoolnews.com or everybody's got a movie blog, it seems these days.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know,
[SPEAKER_05]: and bitchy people like Perez Hilton in some of these gossip blogs will oftentimes ruin a movie before it comes out with spoilers and things that it stinks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know most of us, even I'm too young to remember this, but when...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Empire Strikes Back originally came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Return of the Jedi originally came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was revealed that Darth Vader was Luke's father.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Empire Strikes Back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, leading into Return of the Jedi.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was such a huge fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh, what a shock.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would not be possible in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A huge reveal like that would have been spoiled on the internet a month before the movie was released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Snape killed Dumbledore!
[SPEAKER_01]: I did very well to hide myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, even though I figured out that something like that was going to happen from the freaking beginning of the damn book.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially when the last book came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hid myself in a hole and made sure to read everything that day before I let myself read anything on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and, you know, live performances, television, every artistic foray, which yes, gaming is one, we can have that discussion another day if you want, is, you know, is a part of, is subject to this scrutiny that is, you know, the blogosphere that we live in now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I think companies to overcome that kind of have to be smart in how they do things, but it's really hard to keep a secret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at what happened to Sony and having everything spoiled, except Final Fantasy 14 was one of the only secrets they had.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most of their big things were spoiled.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now you had this whole Sega, uh, Sony thing we talked about on the show last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a huge spoiler thing too.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's very hard to keep a secret anymore, but if the product is really, really good, it's going to transcend all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I totally agree with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: How many people who had their Harry Potter spoilers still went out and got the book?
[SPEAKER_05]: Going back to the original question, because we totally digressed from the question and probably missed the point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Has the gaming community helped or stunted the gaming industry?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the end, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a switch we can turn off.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would honestly say the answer is a little of column A and a little of column B. It's probably made things better as far as promoting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think games like Scribblenauts, Braid, some of these games, I don't think would have sold as well or been quite as talked about if it weren't for the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the concepts of some of these games wouldn't have even existed if not for the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Scribblenauts itself has so many internet jokes in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_05]: But has it hurt things?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Has it hurt sales of some games?
[SPEAKER_05]: But honestly, I don't even know if that's the blog so much as it is probably just piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Straight up piracy is easy to do, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that was a good question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Want to do one more from the Rob D?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Along the same lines, has online multiplayer helped or hurt gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Before, a good game could have glitches and they would be ignored or even revered.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, people will complain that it needs a patch because it will be abused if there's an online component.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's just a sign of the times.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I really think that it's just the evolution.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, you move in one direction, you're going to have problems that come because of it, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really think that you can't have one without the other.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't really see it as a hurt or help.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to plant myself firmly in the column of I believe multiplayer gaming has helped gaming altogether.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's created genres of gaming that really wouldn't exist otherwise.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it hurt arcades.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think multiplayer gaming and the online stuff, I think it hurt arcades and I think that's what finally put the nail in the coffin of arcades.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it hurt people's social life.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think it helped gaming in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the Xbox 360's biggest strength?
[SPEAKER_02]: Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is online.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what is a lot of people, you know, what made it so successful, you know, especially in the beginning over the PlayStation 3, you know, complain all you will about, you know, how Sony maybe botched the launch of the PlayStation 3 that they're trying to make, you know, amends for now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the online component has always been Xbox 360's greatest strength.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the one thing most of us are most critical about with the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: The lack of online?
[SPEAKER_05]: The lack of online and the lack of ability to patch games and the lack of, you know, we kind of see that as not catering to the hardcore audience.
[SPEAKER_01]: They said though from the get-go that it's not for the hardcore audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: But honestly, I've kind of made friends with online games, as strange as that sounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, I've met people on like LiveJournal that I'll go off and, you know, join my guild in Final Fantasy XI or World of Warcraft or what have you that I've become really good friends with.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, just along the same token, a lot of the people that I've made friends with out here, they were my online buddies in Alabama, you know, through playing Gemstone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: How's that for old school?
[SPEAKER_05]: That is very old school.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, you know, doing the silly little games on AOL.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: I met a lot of people who are now my in-person friends, but I met them online.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, Dan...
[SPEAKER_01]: your husband you met online my husband I met online so I think that while this may have hurt face-to-face social interaction I think that it has opened the doors for people who otherwise would not get out of the house you know
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sometimes kind of hard to meet other gay people because not everybody is out with it and a lot of people have to suppress it out there in society.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the internet's helped a lot of people connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't think that's necessarily limited to gay culture.
[SPEAKER_05]: That goes for a lot of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: fans of anything or lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, a lot of fringe groups too, you know, people who may think, oh, I'm the only one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm the only one.
[SPEAKER_01]: You find out there's other people like you, you know, you may, you know, it's, I think it's fantastic for especially not just as a social tool, but as, as socially informative tool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: because I'm able to meet other gay geeks like myself which is ironic because I actually don't go there a whole lot anymore but I went to a party they had once and I had a lot of fun and it was kind of cool because sometimes in gamer culture I feel like the underdog for being gay and you sign on Xbox Live you hear all that stuff and then as the gay guy I sometimes feel like being a nerd I'm on the bottom rung because I'm not a fashionista I don't go to every Madonna concert and all this stuff
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I rolled my eyes, because I see way too much of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't cry for me, Argentina.
[SPEAKER_05]: This happens in any social structure, not just the ones I've mentioned.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think the internet has allowed us to find people like us, and gaming is a part of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about the community we have here at Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: We've met a lot of awesome people just because they've listened to our show.
[SPEAKER_01]: To use an example directly through a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my friends that I played on the IRO back in the day on the International Ragnarok server.
[SPEAKER_01]: She lives in Canada so we haven't met face to face.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never been up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we're still friends on DeviantArt and through LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_01]: We still keep in touch.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm talking seven years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've made, even though these are people that I would never have come into contact with People of vast talent For example, I met Tiara online We were friends online before we had ever gotten to meet in person
[SPEAKER_01]: and now we hang out whenever we can go to each other's towns or go to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've made really lasting friendships through online networking and through games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, meh.
[SPEAKER_05]: What more question tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a good discussion.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one comes from DarkTetsuya, and the question is, how likely are you guys to be checking out La Mulana when it hits WiiWare when it's available?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did read the difficulty, at least of the controls, has been adjusted.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really wish there were demos, but that's a whole bigger issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have some extra Wii points from a gift card someone was kind enough to give me for my birthday, so I'll probably use it to pick up this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just right now, me playing much of anything is in small doses that I have to be able to take a lot of rest with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why isn't there like a Nintendo magazine that comes with demos?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they do this on the Xbox, they do this on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, those discs got made a little obsolete in this era of gaming because we all download our demos online.
[SPEAKER_05]: But remember, like on PlayStation 1, those demo discs used to be the shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a pile of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why doesn't Nintendo do something like that to make up for the lack of having an online thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't that be cool if they had a magazine that would have like five games you could play on a disc?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're too busy kissing Miyamoto's ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or kissing Soccer Mom's ass or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me just reload the Twitter real quick to see if we got any other last questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jeremy keeps trying to get out of the room and then she's like, Ah, the door!
[SPEAKER_01]: And then turning back around.
So.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be going to wrap it up in ribbons and bows You know what this means?
[SPEAKER_01]: to sort of tease a little bit an idea that I brought up to you on Sunday about a little one hour thing involving a room in my house that would make it entirely possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would.
[SPEAKER_05]: There could be plenty of good fun things in store for us in 2010.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thanks to everybody for the questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I somehow missed your questions, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll roll it over to another show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't forget, you can always send us an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank you guys so much for tuning into our show tonight, even though we weren't live or downloading it, even though it was a little different tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you guys have a great week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back to do our normal show one week from Sunday, which would be October.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to bring back our missing house guest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the ferret.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join the ranks of... Do you miss the ferret more than Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that what you're trying to say?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no, yes, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 11th, we'll be live again at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern on All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any final thoughts tonight, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't talked about food all day.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how you know it's in a typical episode of Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is, by the time you're hearing this, I will be on Space Mountain Ghost Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, let's go to San Francisco so we can wait for the tsunami.
[SPEAKER_05]: The tsunami is not hitting the West Coast, did you hear?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week, October 11th.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back live.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next week!
Thank you.