[SPEAKER_09]: Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight, August 21st, 2011, the PlayStation 3 price is cut, the Vita promises to deliver many popular social apps, and are Japanese retailers losing interest in the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live on this Sunday, August the 21st of 2011.
[SPEAKER_10]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games, gamer lifestyle, gaming culture, and all that fun stuff with my co-host, the one, the only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Philodo.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Philodo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speak English.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's kind of, it's Greek.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having spinach pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spinach pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like spanakopita, only big.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, it sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Greek.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's plenty.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I just know feta cheese.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's Greek, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the olives, they're really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also say hello to, I'm ignorant, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: What she meant to say is, Philodo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Philodo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Secret ingredient is phyllo dough!
[SPEAKER_10]: Just doing a speaker check, everybody out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make sure your levels are Loki appropriate tonight for him to scream in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_10]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, always present with us, the chat room, the fourth guest on the program, chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to join us on this Sunday night with us as we are taping episode number 425 of our show live.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't know about you guys, I've had a pretty busy day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was on another podcast this morning for a good, God, it probably went for about two, two and a half hours, but it was a good show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't it fun?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was hanging with my sassy British friends on the Girls Gone Wow podcast, which I know is funny because I'm not a girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still a good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the girls that are on the show are very fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: They took my suggestion and called you Sky and called him Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know that was your suggestion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway, yeah, I was doing that this morning.
[SPEAKER_10]: So a cheap plug for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: That works.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, before we get into Gaming Weeks, I want to talk about this because this is something I was kind of doing this weekend as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I haven't mentioned this on Twitter and I haven't really talked about this anywhere because I wanted to just kind of start off tonight's show talking about this, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be totally just blunt and honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I read that article on Joystick.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how many of you guys saw this, but Joystick ran an article a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're a very big gaming blog.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have their own show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's huge on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure many of you subscribe.
[SPEAKER_10]: As far as the more corporate blogs go, I guess you could say they're definitely one of the better ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's because of interesting things like this that they do that make them stand out and they ran an article Thursday or Friday about Xenoblade coming out in Europe and the article was basically how to play Xenoblade on a US Wii
[SPEAKER_10]: and it basically was here is what you need to download here is how you hack your console and here's where you buy your import copy of Xenoblade so you can play it on the Wii and I have to admit a lot of what was holding me back before to hacking my console was it seemed kind of complicated like I know Loki was always doing all that stuff but you know Loki and we've talked about this on the show before Loki breaks shit because he can't that's
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes I break shit when I don't want to break shit, but it happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just part of the process.
[SPEAKER_10]: so I mean it looks lengthy but it looks easy so I followed it step by step and I did it it was it was pretty easy and I gotta admit it was kind of neat seeing like all the you know because when you're doing some of this stuff you basically are booting your Wii like it's a PC and so it has kind of like that old school IBM PC font and you see all these programs that are running in that and so forth and
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Linux loaders.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even know what the hell's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just kind of followed all the instructions and there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now if I want to import Xenoblade, I can.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how I feel about that right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really, really do not like Xenoblade.
[SPEAKER_10]: This whole region.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like region locking.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like the fact that some games come out in one region and don't come out in the other.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love so much more what Sony's doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And maybe I think that was part of my big motivator was that I just wanted to make my Wii region free.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now I can check out some of this other cool shit about like what custom Mario Kart Wii and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play President Cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I could play President Cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't even think of that, but that's a damn good reason for me to have done what I did to my Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: If there's any game worth importing, it's that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I could even find a copy anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like to borrow President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought a copy of President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Played it once and it sits in the shelf somewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew there was a good reason I did this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I realize some folks out there that are very anti-hacking and all that are like, Rob, how could you?
[SPEAKER_10]: You've been the voice of reason on the show for so long.
[SPEAKER_10]: How could you do this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if you want to know how he could do it, the instructions were on Joystick.
[SPEAKER_10]: at the end of the day yes that's exactly right somebody wrote an article like how to do this for dummies and I was like alright I can do it and I did it and in some ways I realized I was taking a risk with my Wii console that you know I might break it or something like that
[SPEAKER_10]: You're such a naughty boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I didn't...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's interesting that I could use the USB loader to like load up my games onto one drive but I don't know I don't know if I'll really do that because I honestly think it's just easier to just get the damn disc and put it in the Wii if I'm actually gonna play any of those games let's face it many of which I don't anymore once in a blue blue moon I'll decide there's something on the Wii I want to play usually it's a virtual console game to be honest so there you go
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, what do you think of, now I gotta ask this question, what do you think of the fact that a big blog like Joystick did this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because clearly they did it to make a statement, like at least that's what I read out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did it to make a statement that Nintendo, by not releasing Xenoblade in the US, you leave us no other choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they've run an article similar to that before anyways, and I know they've done it before with the PSP, so, nah, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_10]: hmm what do you think DarkSakura what do you think of a website like that kind of you know a prestigious if we will gaming website they're kind of doing that they're gonna get a cease and desist from Nintendo and then take the article down but the damage has been done their protest has been made do you think that they made a statement or do you think that they look kind of you know and I'm not I'm not asking this to open any channel of disrespecting what they did but let's see look statemently to me you know yeah I think they did and well done
[SPEAKER_10]: So now here's the other interesting thing about this whole Xenoblade and the last story in this whole saga.
[SPEAKER_10]: My gut still tells me we've got PAX coming this weekend and there's going to be a lot of news that comes out of PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that usually you don't have a lot of big, big announcements coming out of PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like usually that's what E3 is for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gamescom usually ends up being a pretty similar show to PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, PAX has been getting bigger and bigger.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a sellout show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you do see companies making more and more announcements.
[SPEAKER_10]: and honestly in my mind, what better time to announce Xenoblade?
[SPEAKER_10]: I honestly think if Nintendo does not announce Xenoblade at PAX next week, they're not going to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think next week is really the last quote-unquote last chance I mean granted they can hold a press conference whenever they want and say whatever they want but as far as a celebration if you will of the fans next week is the chance for them to do that Nintendo is in Seattle they're in the backyard of Seattle it's not a problem for them to do packs and they do go I think every year
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not so sure if Nintendo's doing PAX that they're going to bring the Wii U. And the reason why is that the Wii U did not get a huge reception at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so they might have taken things back to the drawing board.
[SPEAKER_10]: They may not be ready to show that to the public.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Nintendo's going to E3, or excuse me, if Nintendo's going to PAX, they're going to be showing off the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll be their huge thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Their huge push will be the Mario game, the Mario Kart, and the 3DS price cut.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is going to be the majority of what they're pushing.
[SPEAKER_10]: but they do have a handful of titles coming out on the Wii this holiday season like what Rhythm Heaven there's another Kirby game right?
[SPEAKER_10]: it's on it's way so there's a few things that Nintendo kind of still has going on and what a perfect time for them to say oh yeah and over here on these kiosks we have hey American Xenoblade I really think the push is going to be more of the 3DS obviously because they just dropped the system down in price they've really kicked up the advertising for it I don't know if you've seen the ads about you know
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically highlighting the three big games from Star Fox, Mario, Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're definitely pushing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So going to the chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com, BlackWolf is in chat saying, Nintendo won't bring the Wii U because they only showed it at E3 to stop leaks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And see, I'm kind of inclined to agree is that maybe not totally the reason why.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think part of the reason why, I think if the Wii U had had a huge, oh my gosh, everybody's got to do this, and hold this whole huge reception at E3, I think they would have had a little bit of it at PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: but also keep in mind that the PAX booths are a lot smaller than the E3 booths and they don't always have as much space to show everything and if they were to bring the Wii U they would have those huge lines that go with it I just don't think now is the time for them to be pushing the Wii U next year's PAX maybe because we could be looking at the Wii U for next holiday but I just think this year's PAX is going to be all about the 3DS and maybe just maybe Xenoblade
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually entirely inclined to agree with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And SSJ100Matt is confirming for me that Nintendo is going to be at PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_10]: UnfoldedRaptor is in our chatroom saying, Sky, the last story, another big RPG for the Wii, is getting localized for Europe but not for America.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we'll see this whole situation again in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this is, the last story is still part of that, whatever that campaign, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But otherwise, the games actually, I mean, they're both RPGs, but that's kind of where the similarities end.
[SPEAKER_10]: The huge thing about the last story is it's Mistwalker, meaning, like, Nobe Uematsu did the music, the guy that did the Final Fantasy, the original, is behind this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, Mistwalker games are usually a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, well, I don't...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Gang fight, gang fight
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our little dog and pony podcast does not get quite the amount of viewers that Joystick does, so I'm not sure what kind of happens when you're that big, if you can get away with more things like that without getting blacklisted or what have you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I do seem to remember some time ago, Kotaku did something to piss Sony off.
[SPEAKER_10]: and they're another big blog and they got blacklisted for a little while but it was well when I say a little while it was literally like 48 hours or something something was quickly remedied there so you know a blog that big has a lot of pull I gotta say so I don't think Nintendo could just straight up blacklist them but you know there's there's things Nintendo could do if they want so
[SPEAKER_08]: They could stomp their little foot and pout.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black Wolf is being a party pooper saying the last story soundtrack actually was done by Yoshitaka Suzuki.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was not done by Nobuo Imatsu.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't even do the theme or anything?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's surprising to me because he's a part of Mistwalker Studios.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: uh we're gonna get into how was your gaming week here in just a minute but let me go to another kind of random question that popped up in chat uh from Danish hey guys Mr. Niche here I have a question for OLR from what information you know at this moment would you guys buy the 3DS now or wait for the PlayStation Vita if you could only buy one
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I already own a 3DS, but see, here's where I'm at, is that I kind of think the systems are spaced far enough apart where that if you plan well, you can kind of afford both.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you're very adamant, like, no, I only have X amount, and I understand there's students and people on fixed budgets that can only afford one or the other.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really hard right now for me to say, yeah, go for the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because for the Vita right now, we have a lot of announcements and we have a lot of ideas for games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now that the Vita is not launching until 2012, there's a part of me that wonders if it's not going to have a very similar situation to what the 3DS had.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meaning, yeah, it's going to launch in March, but there's not going to be any really good launch games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then everything you really want will be out at the holidays.
[SPEAKER_10]: so part of me says if you think you could have enough money this holiday and then again next holiday I think you're safe to get a 3DS right now and then get a Vita later otherwise it really depends on what games you want to play because if you want to play Uncharted
[SPEAKER_10]: 3DS doesn't have anything like that right now so clearly you need to get a Vita but if you want to play Mario the Vita doesn't have anything like that right now so you need to get a 3DS so I don't have an easy answer it really depends on what games do you want to play because that's the only thing that's setting the two systems apart right now if you think about it this way the two systems don't have any games in common it's not like the Xbox and the 360 herp derp the 360 and the Playstation 3 what do they have in common
[SPEAKER_10]: They might have some franchises that get one game here and one game here.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what games do the two both have?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lego Harry Potter, yours 5 through 7.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, excuse me!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you said none.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just pissed off a bunch of Harry Potter Lego fans.
[SPEAKER_10]: My bad on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will actually say that if it were me, I'm going to get 3DS because I haven't touched our PSP since I was playing Popola Cross.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I was playing Roku Loko.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing something back then, but it was about a year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's something else to consider.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you need that portable device to do other shit for you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Meaning, do you need an MP3 player as well?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you want something to surf the web with?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, the 3DS does have a web browser, but it's kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Terrible!
[SPEAKER_10]: Where the PSP really succeeded that the original DS or DS Lite, whatever you want to call it, kind of didn't do so well is it, you know, what's PlayStation's little tagline?
[SPEAKER_10]: It only does everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's kind of true when it comes to PSP versus DS, you know, going back.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what I imagine will continue to be the case in Vita versus 3DS is that the PS Vita is going to be able to do this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a story later on tonight about apps that you know from the iPhone are going to be making their way to the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't have an iPhone, so maybe you have a need for this kind of stuff, then the Vita looks more appealing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you don't need any of that crap, you don't need Facebook again because maybe you have an Android or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: and maybe you're fine with the 3DS so I know you want me to say one or the other but every gamer is different and it's really about at the end of the day what's the golden rule of gaming a system is only as good as the games that are on it and only you know what games you want to play so speaking of games you want to play let's talk about our gaming weeks and we usually like to start off the show talking about what video games we have been playing so DarkSakura start us off
[SPEAKER_08]: Games I have been and am playing right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got everything up except for the newest expansion.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I am playing the crap out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I have been playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I actually got really burned out last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I could not... I played for like five hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I was just sitting here going... I'm going to play my Paladin.
[SPEAKER_08]: It takes so long to level when you're in the 70s now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's faster than it was with my mage, because hi, everything there is undead, and hi, paladin, holy, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I've been playing a bunch of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've actually played Robot Unicorn Attack for a little bit today, and Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, what have you been up to?
[SPEAKER_10]: You're playing something right now during the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is this that you're checking out right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm playing Earth Defense Force Insect Norm again.
[SPEAKER_10]: The minute you paused it and it said, destroy the anthill, I'm like, oh, this must be Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I've been playing a lot of Earth Defense Force this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My boss is out of town.
[SPEAKER_02]: Normally, he wants to play Grand Theft Auto during our breaks and lunch and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But since he's gone and our other co-worker's gone, we've only had three people, and so we've been playing Earth Defense Force...
[SPEAKER_02]: All week long and it's been awesome I've leveled up my tactical guy Up to tier 7 Trying to level up to tier 8 now By farming this first level And there's a trick to it And it also involves the rubber band Kind of a cheat I guess So I will be doing that During the show You don't cheat at anything ever
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an exploit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not necessarily a cheat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am not hacking or anything, even though I could have done that, but I did not.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I am leveling up legitimately.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't feel like holding the trigger down for three hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's where the rubber band comes into play.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You do all the cheating you want in single player mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to cheat the hell out of it when you're by yourself, then go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all co-op.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no cheating.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only for my own benefit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other stuff I've been playing, I played VVVV and I finished the game, but I still have to get some of the shiny objects in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that game was really hard and frustratingly hard sometimes but I think that's the point of it and it was fun let's see what else did I play a little bit of Grand Theft Auto and
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's it, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just those three.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I played... I may have turned Tiny Tower on once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I probably should download the update for that, so I'll probably do that and then maybe build some more empty floors since I can't build anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: My gaming week, my Xbox is still out of commission.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you haven't heard the story yet, listen to last week's show at the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't really have any updates on that yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just sitting there collecting dust until that whole debacle's settled down because even though I can play things in single player mode, I don't want to get achievements and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've just moved on to PlayStation 3, which is what I've been playing mostly in my console gaming time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a lot of new stuff for me to talk about on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been revisiting some of the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Played Katamari randomly during the week and also was playing a game that I think I briefly talked about before, like last year on the show when it first came out, but it's Hardcore Uprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you don't know what this game is, it's basically Contra, but they didn't call it Contra.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Hardcore Uprising and what the art is all by Arc System Works and all this, although it's still a Konami game and
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's something that Extifer, of all people, got me into.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you guys listen to Horde House, you know Extifer.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he is really into this game right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when we all went over to his house about a week ago, he was playing it, and I was kind of watching him, and I was like, oh, this actually looks kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I don't remember feeling this awesome about the game after playing the demo.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and in the uprising mode you basically all your points turn out to be a currency and you use these points to upgrade your characters so that the mode can get a little easier and a little easier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like maybe you can make your life bar a little bit longer or you get yourself a few more lives or your power up will be a little bit stronger next time that you get that power up.
[SPEAKER_10]: so I like being able to progress that way because that way it doesn't feel like you keep banging your head against the wall because you keep dying at the same point you know you know that as long as you keep racking up points you'll be able to get your character more and more powered so you'll be able to get through all that stuff so um
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's the cool thing about Hardcore Uprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, if you want the hardcore stuff, though, there's Arcade Mode, where you don't have any of the power-ups, and you just gotta push through.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was excited that I could beat the first stage without continuing, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, that was... In the Contra game, that's huge.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it is huge.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, Zether's in the chatroom going, Get all the achievements.
[SPEAKER_10]: Try beating it on no-death mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck with that!
[SPEAKER_10]: Zether is also clarifying that it's more of a sequel to the game on the Genesis is where that comes from.
[SPEAKER_10]: Contra Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Contra Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the end of the day, it's Contra.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I feel.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have a spread gun, you have all the medals.
[SPEAKER_08]: Contra Hardcore was pretty dang hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Hardcore Uprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that was pretty much, other than that, some more PC games, more Civilization V because it's great, and of course World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, quickly some housekeeping before we get into the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to quickly say there is no show next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do believe another best of is being prepped for the live folks that listen at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: So at least there will be that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we will not be live next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be out of town and we're just going to take the week off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm helping somebody move.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a while since we had a week off.
[SPEAKER_10]: So darn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sometimes we take a day off.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're taking next week off.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a little bit of a bummer that we're missing next week because it is PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: but just the timing of everything not really going to work out so my hope is that maybe some of our listeners are going to PAX and they're just not going to be able to tune in because they're flying back or whatever so we'll do a big roundup and everything when we come back on Labor Day weekend we will be having a show so we'll be seeing you guys then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, in the meantime, follow us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're also on Facebook at facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, there's always our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: I noticed that we had a post where some of the things that we weren't sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember how last week we had the email that linked to a DeviantArt account and we weren't sure if we could post the pictures of the Capcom building and all the stuff that we were linked?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that emailer went and made a post in our forums and was like, oh, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here it all is.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you want to kind of like see that second half to last week's email, it's all there on the forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: So check that out at orange launch radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So start things off.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to talk a little bit about PlayStation and.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some interesting stuff came out this week from Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'm sure that's just to kind of pick up the pace for the holiday season because I don't think they've been top dog for the last few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they kind of have to, I guess, try a little harder.
[SPEAKER_02]: So also they're going to be rolling out some new bundles as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Infamous 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's one for Uncharted 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it'll work?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll help drive sales, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whether it pushes the whole 3D platform.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think 3D gaming is really what people want right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Does anyone in the room really want that?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a part of me, which I know is ironic because I own a 3DS, but I'm kind of like...
[SPEAKER_10]: 3DS is flashing the pan enough for me, I don't know how I feel about it in my living room
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it'll be better once it's more of a passive technology instead of having these active shutter glasses that cost $100 each.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it needs to be to the point where it's like, okay, here's some polarized glasses, like the crap that you get at the movie theater, where that would be maybe a few bucks a pair of glasses, and then it's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you can invite your friends over, you have...
[SPEAKER_10]: plenty of glasses that go around for them to do that kind of stuff I'm laughing to myself now because speaking of 3D totally forgot to mention played Ridge Racer 3DS this week because I bought it during the Amazon DS 3DS sale last week oops
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it's a really good show-off-the-system kind of game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, if you want to show off the 3D and show off... Some of it's a little gimmicky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the whole, like, oh, there's got to be confetti flying at your face in every race.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's kind of bootsy because the confetti does not go at, like, 30 frames a second.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks really bootsy to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And some of the collision is a little dippy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it just doesn't control... Like, if you...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: The technology is how far along.
[SPEAKER_10]: But otherwise, the 3D effects are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, I liked it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I didn't mean to turn your story into a Ridge Racer 3DS review, but I just forgot to mention that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another system that Ridge Racer is really awesome on, the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're late to the game and really want to get into the last generation...
[SPEAKER_02]: Soon to be last generation of handhelds from Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do so for 99 euro.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a new PSP model that's kind of a different look to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: More of like a sleek black.
[SPEAKER_10]: Weren't they all sleek black?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh wait, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they were shiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is more of like a matte.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alan has a silver one.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like a matte finish.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it will not have Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is without Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're thinking of playing multiplayer games, uh-uh, not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting that they cut out the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_10]: You going to surf the web?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is a pretty big component of the PSP that they just kind of chopped out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, you look at it and go, eh, but it's only 99 euros, which I imagine would mean $99 here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have they even announced it for America?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not coming to America.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that just because Sony does better in Europe?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this our punishment for rejecting the Go?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you're really looking for a cheap system, and this is the problem with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once again, they're releasing something that they think is cheap, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: for less.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, so why would you go and try to buy something brand new for slightly less and it's really kind of a crippled version of the system?
[SPEAKER_02]: Same thing was like with what the PSP Go was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you buy something, you know, more expensive that comes crippled?
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one wants that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, they might as well make it smaller and call it the PSP Micro because that's how it's going to sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one's going to want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why even bother releasing a new PSP anyways?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I think people are already done with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of at the end of its life cycle already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it's kind of their last hurrah for the holiday because the Vita didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put out a new 3000 bundle or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just had one that came out with Madden and Need for Speed in it or something like that in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do we have to... Why even bother releasing a new system?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why spend the time right now to redesign the system to make it slightly cheaper to put it out anyways?
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I can think of is that they're trying to cash in on...
[SPEAKER_02]: on these reduced price games that they have coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have some UMD dual packs that are coming out for $10 from a bunch of third-party companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, I mean, it's a good deal if you're looking for really cheap games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, yes, you can still download stuff off the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have a PC or a PlayStation 3, you can download it straight off there and put it on a memory stick or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, seriously, just buy a used system if you're really going to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no reason to buy this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, it's just a buy you system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, you could probably even find a new system for that price.
[SPEAKER_02]: If people are sitting on inventory for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we see how Loki feels about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do have to admit the idea of a new PSP is a little silly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Loki makes a damn good argument that if you can get a used one cheaper than this, then why go for this when you're missing Wi-Fi?
[SPEAKER_10]: Before he kind of pointed that out, I was thinking, all right, well, it's a way for them to get the system out under $100, so it looks really appealing to maybe younger folks that kind of want one, but the parents don't want to spend that much money on a toy.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: But, hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyhow, let's talk about the other handheld system, and that would be the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you all, I'm sure, are aware, the 3DS recently had a huge price cut going on to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that price cut included Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in Japan, the price of the device went from 25,000 yen down to 15,000 yen.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a huge price.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's almost larger than the one that it had here in the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's very big.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what was the effect of that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, a lot more 3DSs sold.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this week it was announced that, let's see, a couple different figures are out there about exactly how many units sold between August 8th and August 14th.
[SPEAKER_10]: But generally it's around 210,000 units sold.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind that the launch week of the system saw about, what, 350,000 units sold?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or no, 375,000 units sold.
[SPEAKER_10]: So by cutting the price, you got numbers that were almost back to launch week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the numbers this past week were larger than they were in week two.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it pushed the adoption mark past 1.5 million.
[SPEAKER_10]: So apparently the price cut did exactly what Nintendo needed it to do and it moved more systems, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just an overpriced system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And right now, I mean, they could have probably put it out the original price if they had a good lineup of games, but they didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they need to do something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Either put out some good games or drop the price.
[SPEAKER_02]: And right now they need to drop the price if they want to gain momentum going into the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's the other thing I want to know about, and that is what is the sales going to look like the next week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I'm sure you had a lot of people that ran out and bought one, especially in the U.S., because we had those stores that all cut the price early so that folks could get on that, and then they could be the early adopters as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm sure the sales figures in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: are going to look very similar when those numbers come out very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm curious, what's it going to look like in two weeks?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the long-term sales of this?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, through the holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really don't think any of this matters until the holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: The holiday is what's really going to make or break the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, honestly, it didn't really, from my perspective, it didn't really do much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, none of my customers were really buying more systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were just kind of like, great, now I can get rid of the system that's been sitting on my shelf for four months.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they probably just wanted to sell the shit they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's the situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: If a lot of the retailers out there were just sitting on these systems, then you may not see the spike that you see in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm sure it'll help, but I don't know if it's going to be that significant.
[SPEAKER_10]: Akuma JP is in our chat room right now at chat.orangeandre.com, and he is a listener of ours from Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he says, kind of in response to this, a lot of mothers complained because they bought it on the first day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you what you're going to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guarantee you'll see this by early next month.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to see Nintendo come out because the NPD numbers are going to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3DS is the top handheld system of August.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because the PSP isn't selling very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The DS isn't selling very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course the 3DS is going to be the top system now that they did a price drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's PR spin for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So look for that early next month.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what's the long-term effect of a statement like that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, I don't see soccer moms running out and buying a 3DS because, oh, well, it was the top-selling system in August, according to MPD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they're just hoping that that kind of momentum will carry on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it very well might.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because...
[SPEAKER_10]: you know the DS and the PSP are kind of being phased out when that Mario game hits all they have to do look this is all Nintendo has to do bundle that fucking Mario game with a 3DS that thing will sell like crazy for Christmas watch Dan's holding off until the flame one comes out because that's what he wants he wants the flare red he likes his 3DS like he likes his homosexuals flaming and yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: Red.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red's Dan's favorite color.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he wants Star Fox.
[SPEAKER_08]: So those are what's selling it for him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just... Like, if Nintendo wants to sell a shit ton of 3DSs, that's all they have to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, like, kids will be wanting that shit all Christmas long.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it'll be a huge thing that ends up under the Christmas tree this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might even end up being the must-have toy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, if this shit does Netflix and all this other stuff, like, Nintendo could make this the must-have toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gonna be the must-have toy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought...
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is coming from Activision.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought Skylanders was gonna be the must-have toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck is a Skylanders?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pain in my ass is what it is right now, and we'll get into that later on, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to say this without sounding like a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_10]: You all heard what I said about what I did with my Wii earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: So look, that shows you where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the 3DS will be the top selling system.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it will outsell the consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob's modified his Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I needed it to be more versatile.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, seriously, I think the 3DS will sell more than the living room consoles because I think most people that want to have an Xbox 360 already have one.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only maybe kind of possibly that could screw me on that prediction would be the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the whole price cut for the PlayStation 3, the fact that it plays Blu-rays, the fact that it's going to do 3D,
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't underestimate that shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do not underestimate the power of that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do not underestimate the power of Microsoft and if they feel that their sales are dipping because of the PlayStation 3 dropping in price they can still drop the price.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember you angry cynical sarcastic gamers soccer moms do not think like you.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are not rational.
[SPEAKER_08]: They cannot be.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should be put down immediately when spotted.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: They feel no mercy, no remorse, and they will not stop until you are dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's pretty much what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love when I read predictions on gaming sites from gaming fanboys going, well, this is going to be this way because gamers want this, da-da-da-da, without realizing, well, soccer moms spend more money than gamers do, probably, at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why else is the Wii the number one console for so many years?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because soccer moms buy, you know, Black Ops.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well actually they do because they don't read So I think the Vita getting out of Nintendo's way essentially whether that was intentional or not whereas I think I honestly think Sony's just trying to plan a better launch I think Sony was starting to realize they did not want to have a launch go like the 3DS's launch and if they didn't have the games to back it up they shouldn't launch their system I think that's why they've held it back a little bit
[SPEAKER_10]: At least in America and Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why they're still going ahead in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe there's going to be more games out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's totally cleared the way for 3DSs to just fly these holidays.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe I'll be wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's happened before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spread your wings and fly, 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spread your wings and fly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on to some other stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, better that it spreads that than something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Japanese retailers are not going to be doing much with the Xbox 360 anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just hit 1.5 million units sold, which is basically... That's in six years, by the way, which is basically what the 3DS did in six months, and that was considered selling badly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know why it's not doing well over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're racists.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last big Japanese exclusive came out, Idolmaster 2, is actually going to be coming out on PlayStation 3 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, it's the biggest retailer out there, Jio, is cutting back their stock, but said that they're still going to be available online.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, totally hacking my Xbox next so I can play Idolmaster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I would rather play Hatsune Miku, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, at any rate, the quotes going on saying is that it is our understanding that Amazon now handles a substantial portion of Japanese Xbox 360 software sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically, they say, you want it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Get it online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazon.co.jp.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We could special order one of those for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this really, really bad news for the 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_08]: The system, the games, aren't really geared towards Japanese players, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: My thought is that it's sort of like the reverse Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a good example, the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sega Saturn in Japan, fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was top seller, it really was well supported, great games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Over in the US, not so good, not so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many people do you know who still have an old Nintendo, not Nintendo, a Playstation sitting in their closet collecting dust but never ever played a Saturn?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then you sort of got the converse going on now with the Xbox 360 and with the Xbox that it just didn't catch on over there maybe it was marketing maybe it was that it wasn't a long time trusted brand over there perhaps whatever reason that it is but I think that it's the same situation it's not marketed the right way it's not pushing towards that audience
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I don't think it necessarily spells the end of the 360, certainly.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to keep pushing forward.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've done very well in the U.S., that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's the point, is that its performance here has been good enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, I mean, I'm sure the Dreamcast release in Japan was not based on American sales of the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can tell you that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it could possibly be that maybe the next Microsoft system to come out won't come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: that could be very interesting if that happens I honestly can't see that happening I think Microsoft has to try again you know what I see if it does happen that way we get a system over here that's not region locked or it's only available
[SPEAKER_10]: God, I wish a non-region lock system would happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of the games that come out on the 360 are not region locked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the Japanese games that come out are, for some reason, from the Japanese companies, but for the most part, a lot of your big first party games like EA, or third party games like from EA, Ubisoft, that kind of stuff, they are not region locked.
[SPEAKER_02]: you just have to look online either on release sites or on like PlayAsia has a good list of stuff that's not region locked and you can literally import that stuff back and forth there are a few Japanese games that do come out over there region free and you can bring them over here there are some of the cave shmups that were region free but it's rare, it's definitely more rare but you know
[SPEAKER_02]: I seriously think that if they were going to be smart about it and try to
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess avoid the same situation than when they bring out a US game they have a Japanese subtitle on it already or a Japanese menu that's just available through options I don't know how many Japanese games I have that have menus fully in English so it's not a big deal
[SPEAKER_02]: And even if the next system is region locked, most likely it's going to be on Blu-ray or some sort of proprietary format.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to guess probably Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if that's the case, we're the same region as Japan anyways, Blu-ray wise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Video, I mean... No, we're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we are.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we are not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's region A. They're both the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well, for Blu-ray, I'm sorry, I was thinking DVD.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not the same for DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes, not for DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Blu-ray, we are the same region.
[SPEAKER_08]: But regardless, the point that I was trying to make is that if they're going to be smart about this, they'll have all the games come on already.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't say fully localized, but they will have menus or, you know, even work with, you know, between the Japanese staff and American staff for two country developers.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: and then release a version that's got just everything in it already.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here's an example.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonic Adventure, when it came out in the US, had Japanese subtitles and Japanese voices in it and the English voices.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I ask this real quick?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Breakman's asking this in the chat room and this is a really good question that I'm not even sure I know the answer to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breakman in chat asks, OLR, seriously, why is region locking so important to these companies?
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_08]: And a part of it has to do with demographics.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's licensing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, licensing.
[SPEAKER_02]: License stuff for certain regions.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, obviously, some of them, they just kind of don't put it in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Branding, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Branding, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can see where, like, the NFL games, you know, NFL's very protective about their shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I'm sure those NFL games have to be region locked.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you say that for?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: All the machines that you saw over here were being imported from Japan and they really technically weren't supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were quote unquote illegal.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was kind of one of those things they didn't really enforce.
[SPEAKER_10]: Konami just kind of quietly turned their backs to it because, you know, obviously it was raising awareness for all the console versions.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they did actually have an official U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: machine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those songs were licensed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Mania
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a little back and forth with Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Madden has been region-free the last couple games.
[SPEAKER_02]: 10 and 11 were both region-free.
[SPEAKER_02]: NCAA football, though, in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: this year was not region-free.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was only NCSC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then, for example, some games that are coming out that have already leaked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: DSX, Human Revolution, Region 3, Colorado Warriors, The Cartel, that's also Region 3, Captain America was Region 3, Harry Potter was Region 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a Tour de France game that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not even in our region, but that's both region for PAL and NTSC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of funny there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a game that's never coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that I'd play it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: UFC Personal Trainer, Naughty Bear Gold Edition, Dynasty Warriors 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of them are coming out all region.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just don't really advertise it.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, though, a lot of times you'll see the Japanese only games like Red Faction Armageddon in Japan as only a Japanese region game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same with like Shaun White and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the versions that come out over here, I believe...
[SPEAKER_02]: are all region.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact... Go into our chat room real quick again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.orange.studio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Frisbee asks, but like, for example, if I buy a Japanese game from a website in Japan, would that affect licensing seeing as you buy it from that country?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think in what you're talking about, I think you kind of answered your own question because, you know, when you're buying a game from Japan, well, your money went to a Japanese company.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will tell you this most Japanese sites will not mail to the US like for example Amazon I've ordered you know I've ordered like a couple of books and a couple of CDs but other than that I haven't ever been able to order games from there they won't take your credit card information when I was ordering my because I had the money I was going to order my 2DX controller
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of these stores over here that sell the import stuff, the way they're doing it is that they have an alliance with a Japanese retailer who's feeding them all the goods.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's how they do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Toys and Joys is out of Hawaii, so they actually bring stuff back.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how they get it really quickly.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of companies are selling to these guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm assuming it's Japanese distributors for games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: as long as we're shipping to a country or a location within that country it doesn't really matter what you do with it we don't want to know what you do with it it's just if you're going to distribute it in another country you're not really supposed to do that but once again we're just selling it to that person what they do with it from there that's a whole other thing
[SPEAKER_02]: It is kind of stupid that they have region locked stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quite the conversation we've had stemming from the Xbox 360 chat in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got some more stories to cover here before we get to release dates and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation Vita, there's some more information that came out about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was rumored that the RAM was halved to drop the price of the system so that it would be able to compete with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, that is not true.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation Vita actually has more RAM than the PlayStation 3 in some cases.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also a few other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also have cross-game chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can also do... I guess it's part of their party system.
[SPEAKER_02]: The...
[SPEAKER_02]: System has 512 MB of RAM and 128 MB of video RAM compared to the PlayStation 3's 256 MB of system RAM and 256 MB of video RAM.
[SPEAKER_02]: While, of course, the RAM is smaller on the video side, the resolution isn't as great as the PlayStation 3, so it doesn't require as much RAM for textures and stuff as the PlayStation 3 does.
[SPEAKER_02]: but definitely with that kind of RAM in there we'll allow a lot more flexibility with different games and stuff because I know a lot of people have to optimize their game and do different things and cut stuff just to have it run in the limited RAM so that's kind of cool so we'll see some pretty good games coming on that system I'm guessing because of that we can hope
[SPEAKER_10]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess RAM's getting cheaper overall, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Talking about the Vita and some of the other things that were announced for the Vita this week at Gamescom, PlayStation Vita is going to be getting some more social integration.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, they're going to get some of the things that you usually hear about when you think about more of the iOS type of apps, or I guess you could say Android as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things like Foursquare, Skype...
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter, Facebook, all of that is going to be in the PlayStation Vita and I guess that's part of what you can use the whole 3G and all that for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember the AT&T 3G that everybody was really excited about?
[SPEAKER_10]: All four of those apps, they're going to be free downloads from the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doesn't quite say, you know, they didn't hint at if it's going to be at launch or if it's going to be a ways after that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I imagine none of these apps are that complicated.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure they'll be out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, what else is also interesting about them is I believe all of them, except maybe Skype, have open APIs, so they ought to be really easy to develop the apps.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody to get in there and do them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I can't imagine it will be much further after launch if it's not at launch.
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be, and some are theorizing that maybe they're just going to be right on the device when you get them.
[SPEAKER_10]: You won't even have to download them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll just be free and on the device waiting for you to use.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't that be nice?
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: All that integration is going to be there.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Skype specifically is interesting, of course, because Skype is now a Microsoft product.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't think that necessarily means that Skype is all things Microsoft and only all things Microsoft at this point anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that was probably something planned well before the purchase of Skype products.
[SPEAKER_10]: but what about the rest of this integration?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this a good thing for the Vita?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this a no one really gives a shit type of thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of where I'm at with it is I'm like well I guess some of the things are cool like if you don't have an iPhone or an Android or one of the other phone devices that runs all this stuff but I mean I can't really see using Twitter on my PS Vita because like how often do I use Twitter on my Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh never.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never.
[SPEAKER_10]: I used it once to say, hey, I'm writing a tweet for my 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think everybody did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I think though that you would use it a bit more on like a Vita than you would say a 360 because you're taking it with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least the Vita's on the go with you and it makes more sense for things like Foursquare and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: But again, I own an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't need it on a Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: but I understand not everybody's like me you might have a college kid who doesn't really want to pay the amount you have to pay a month to have an iPhone so they have like a cheaper phone that you know just gets the calling job done calling and texting and the basics and then you know we'll have the Vita to do all this fancier stuff like the check-ins and so forth Facebook
[SPEAKER_10]: status updates I'm thinking this also paves the way for you know I don't know this I don't know how I feel about this in a lot of games but it will pave the way for games to automatically post to your Facebook and your Twitter I just got to level 3 whoopee they already have that in a lot of stuff I know they do but not as much as I would think and especially like you don't see it in any 3DS games that I know of um
[SPEAKER_10]: And if they are, they're not first party.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a DS game I know that has that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, like one DS game, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't see it in a lot of the games right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whereas I think including this stuff on the PS Vita kind of opens the door for more of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do people want that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do people really want their Twitter to just be filled up with, yay, I unlocked a trophy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoopee.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I guess I have the trophy stuff post to my Facebook, which I kind of show that more as a way to kind of tell people what games I'm really into right now without having to put an update.
[SPEAKER_10]: But some of it's really cumbersome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would not want updates to go up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can have your thing announced to Facebook every time you download something.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Porn, porn, porn, porn Breakman in our chatroom says Can I get a Vita that just plays video games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Can it be cheaper then?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, please Breakman also says Fucking Facebook, can I pay extra to have that not installed?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word on Google Plus, or as we call it on Horde House, Google Positive.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word if Google Positive will be one of the apps that will be on the PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, one other quick thing I've got to say about the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, one other thing that they're saying, every PlayStation Vita game will also be downloadable.
[SPEAKER_02]: To what storage on the PlayStation Vita?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there is no storage on the PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Vita memory cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, why would I buy the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only can you buy the cartridge version of the game, for the same price you can download it off the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can buy a memory card to put it on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would I do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And no, I guarantee there's not going to be a discount for buying it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: There never is a fucking discount.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what if you're a PlayStation Plus subscriber?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe you'll get a discount.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what if, Loki, what if you have to have the game right now and I'm so fat that I can't fit in my car anymore?
[SPEAKER_10]: So I will not be able to drive to the store to get it, but I have to have the game right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also purchase a digital copy that you can't resell.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all used again, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will cost you more money because you have to buy a memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's win-win for Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at least I didn't have to buy the gas to get down to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the gas is that much of a problem for you, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, gas is not that expensive yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to cost you a gallon of gas to get down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guarantee that memory card, it's going to be more than a few bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably like $15.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, TigerClaw in our chat is saying memory cards are cheap nowadays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, regular memory cards are cheap nowadays, but this is Sony's proprietary memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like, you know, Microsoft has their, it's not even really proprietary, it's a proprietary case that we put a laptop hard drive in that we can charge a lot more money for, or our memory cards, or even, hell, they've gone to the point where they're like, hey, we got some USB memory cards that you can use that, you know, I know you can use any thumb drive out there that's, you know, really cheap, but ours are $50.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: for four gigs or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like the Nintendo Wii SD cards.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Wii will take any SD card, but if you want to get a Nintendo Wii SD card that has a little sticker that says Nintendo Wii on it, it costs like twice as much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can make a sticker that says Wii, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're just like SanDisk cards or something like that, but they're actually like another company that makes them, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, unless you're getting some sort of discount on it, like it's half the price.
[SPEAKER_02]: then I see no reason to do this which Sony may do those kinds of crazy sales online or and see I don't understand why they have well I understand why they have proprietary memory cards because they don't want people hacking the system but at the same time and I was kind of shocked because I had to buy my mom a camera a Sony camera and I'm like okay and he's like okay you can pick one of these new memory cards here and they're like you know SDHD cards I'm like wait a second uh don't I have to get a memory stick no they stopped using memory stick a while ago I'm like the
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God!
[SPEAKER_02]: Get with the program using a common format.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was kind of cool that they had that, but I don't understand why they don't take those anyways on top of their... Well, I understand, once again, it's piracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're worried about people pirating games.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo says I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, when Xenoblade came out in the UK, if you pre-ordered in a store, you'd get an exclusive classic controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was red.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you could get three A1 size posters signed by the developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they did not specify that if you did your pre-orders online, you would not be getting the posters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they said, Oops!
[SPEAKER_08]: If you previously placed an online pre-order to get these posters sent with your copy of the pre-order bundle, please get in contact with Game or GameStation using links.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they've got links on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically, if you're in the UK and you pre-ordered online and wanted your poster and were under the impression you'd be getting a poster, contact the retailer and tell them that Nintendo sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a fucking poster.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's not even personally signed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's digitally signed by the developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's basically photoshopped on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did not have their pens out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the RoboPen is what it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like Obama used to sign bills.
[SPEAKER_08]: DigiPen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what the DigiPen?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, there's a company, DigiPen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, I mean, I get it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: As much as I'm giving these people a hard time for being mad about their posters, I understand the fact that it is principle, and I understand the fact that Nintendo hasn't been making a lot of smart decisions lately, so why not, you know, kick a little more dirt at them?
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you pre-order it online in America, you're just not getting the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: but here's a lovely poster you can have as a parting gift alright, let's move on to travel the world and look at some release dates and what's coming out to a store near you quite soon
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: including now Super Mario Galaxy, Super Paper Mario, Super Mario Strikers Charged, and Punch-Out!!
[SPEAKER_02]: all for $19.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shin Megami Tensei Devil Survivor overclocked for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I thought that was coming out the week after next, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, sounds like an exciting week in the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move to Japan and see how exciting it is over there and their releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much the same story, except they don't even have Deus Ex.
[SPEAKER_10]: They get Dirt 3 this week in Japan on August the 25th.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure we're going to start to see those Xbox 360 releases get scaled back quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the PlayStation 3, though, they have Dirt 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess this is probably the big game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Monster Hunter Portable 3rd HD version coming out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't this this whole PSP game getting remade for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that is finally hitting the shelves this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a friend who's so psychotic about that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say that that's probably the big thing people are excited about this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: But some people might also be into the Koei games and Sengoku Musou 3 Empires.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: that's really it on the PlayStation 3 but I will mention on the Sony PSP there's Black Rock Shooter the game is out this week on the PSP there's lots of special editions one of them comes with this cute little figurine little anime character dressed in white there
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like a Vinylmation figure.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the game itself, I don't know, I'm just looking at the screenshots, I don't know, it's kind of like Sin and Punishment slash RPG-ish to me, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black Rock Shooter on the Sony PSP, as well as Mobile Suit Gundam, Shingire no Yabu, because it's just not a Japanese month without a new Gundam game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I believe that is pretty much it for releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to look at the 3DS real quick to see if there's anything of note there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, shall we go to Europe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep!
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 23rd, we have Call of Dirty Black Ops Resurrection on Xbox 360, and on the 24th, Hamilton's Great Adventure, Street Fighter 3 Third Strike, Tropico 4, and then on the 26th, which is Friday, there's Pac-Man and Galaga Dimensions, Rugby World Cup 2011, and Deus Ex Human Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get a couple more stories in before we get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about the new PSP that's coming to Europe that has Wi-Fi removed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Nintendo not to be outdone by Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're removing some other stuff in the brand new Wii that is coming out in the UK regions as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The value Wii for that region will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't really given a price yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be cheaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is designed to sit horizontally instead of vertically.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently the GameCube backwards compatibility, both accessories and games, has been removed.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a great feature.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do out sometime before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to include, I guess, a Wii Remote Plus, Nunchuck, Wii Party, and Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii Party, wow, that is a throwaway game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They must have had a bunch of extra copies of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, fun times.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's be real, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: How many people are still emulating GameCube games?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can think, and I know as the minute I said that, the chat room's going to light up with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can think of one that I play, and that's F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they really just need to give that a proper week, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's going to be the argument, and I'm sure a lot of people in chat are going to make this.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of games, they have the support for playing with a GameCube controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: for example, Smash Brothers or Mario Kart and that kind of stuff and a lot of people refer the GameCube controller or WaveBird or whatever to the Wii Remote steering and that kind of bullshit that they have so that's what a lot of people are probably pissed off about because they don't want to use the classic controller I'll give you that
[SPEAKER_02]: All they would have to do is create some sort of WaveBird thing that plugs you into either wirelessly or tethered to the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_02]: And boom, everyone's happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the audience that needs something like that is probably not the same audience that this console is geared at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, this is really about getting the Wiis into homes that don't already have them, which aren't a lot by now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is only coming out in Europe again.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least they say it's not coming out here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still say PAX next week could change a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'll go with it and say that it's only probably coming out in Europe right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: As of right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: but yeah I mean the GameCube compatibility thing probably isn't too surprising do you think that maybe you know since we talked earlier in the show about hacking and stuff that they've tried to take measures to combat all that
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's something interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're basically saying other bundles will also be forthcoming, and they also got word that Nintendo will focus on the new Wii bundles going forward, suggesting it won't coexist with the current model.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're going to be removing it out of all of the systems going forward.
[SPEAKER_10]: They already did and they didn't even make better graphics.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just put Wii...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, controls in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember new play control stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: That didn't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why you don't see them anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go a step further and say when the Wii U virtual console stuff hits, you're probably going to start seeing some of the GameCube stuff pop up on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then maybe that's why they're starting to try and phase GameCube accessibility out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Breakman has a really good point in chat room, and I kind of agree with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: The original GameCube is one of the sturdiest systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, those GameCubes are kind of hard to break.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know anybody that ever had a broken GameCube.
[SPEAKER_08]: The disc's not so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess a new Wii for the three people that don't have one yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meanwhile, who knows of a game called Steel Battalion?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell the listeners what Steel Battalion is, if they've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a huge war sim where you're a mecha, and it has this huge mongus controller, of which we have two now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, and when the controller came out it was like 300 bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was expensive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the controller was literally a dynamic, it was a console.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was panels and switches and the red button.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like what you would see inside an actual mech.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was crazy go nuts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Heavy Armor
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, you will be able to use Kinect and the standard Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: The controller will be used for movement, aiming, and firing, but the Kinect camera will use upper body gestures that you can use to start the engine, use a turret gun, use the scope.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can communicate verbally with the crew members if you want as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: They talk specifically in the release about
[SPEAKER_10]: High fives.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it sounds like they're bringing all these buttons and things that do stuff into a whole new realm, which sounds funny to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But honestly, the fun I think of the original was you had all the buttons and all the neat little stuff to push.
[SPEAKER_10]: My favorite was the eject button.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like to just push that button for fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was the fact that instead of moving your hand or doing something, you got to push the damn button.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't that the fun of it that you had the whole console there?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do like to push buttons.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to release a peripheral for the Kinect that's just a board with buttons on it that I can push.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bubble wrap the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't need buttons anymore because I have the Kinect, and that's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like my buttons.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the buttons.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to push the red one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I push it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week here on the program, DarkSakura dives into the gaming vault and says, Hey, back in my day, we pushed a lot of buttons, and you're going to be pushing my buttons if you don't try this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, what did you pick as the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_08]: The classic game of the week is Midnight Resistance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo, we can all thank Dan for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I was like, Dan, help me think of a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Midnight Resistance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it is a side-scrolling action shooting game that Data East put out in the arcade in 1989 and came out on the Mega Drive, also known as the Genesis, in 1990.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was put out by Ocean Software US.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is in the future where everything sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you're a member of a resistance movement dude who has to rescue his family from a mad scientist before he turns them into donkeys or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically it's Contra but not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's Contra but not.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can do two players simultaneous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nantra.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's what Loki said without talking to his mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, it had a rotatable joystick that's like the one used in Ikari Warriors, which is why this is a hard game to emulate unless you've got an arcade controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: At any rate, you also had your shoots and jumps and you would use your little dial to adjust your aim as you went along.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you could keep moving in directions but change your aim.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it had a power-up system that was like a heavy barrel, which was also a Data East game.
[SPEAKER_08]: where you would collect keys after defeating enemies and you'd get six keys at a time and then you could enter weapon storage and pick out different weapons and power-ups and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your main weapons that you could get were... You could replace your default rifle with backpack weapons that are launched so you'd actually push the joystick and press the shoot button to do it at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had different special guns.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had a supercharge upgrade that would increase your firepower.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a barrier that gives you invincibility temporarily and extra lives.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nine stages with different obstacles.
[SPEAKER_08]: And right before the final stages, you use your keys.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you have to battle the Crimson King.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the ending depends on how many of your family members you rescued.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it came out for home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like I said, it was published by Data East for the Mega Drive in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's very close to the arcade version, except, of course, the controllers, since it's just a Genesis pad, you couldn't have the rotatable thing, so you had four different button configurations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your default controllers will let you...
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a feeling that you were familiar with this game, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: How in the fuck you did this game on the Commodore 64, I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I look up a YouTube of that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I gotta see this on the C64.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's the ZX Spectrum, the Amstrad CPC, Commodore Amiga, and the Atari ST.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some development done by Special FX.
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, one thing, Rob, is that this is listed as one of the greatest games ever made for that system.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go back and play the previous one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the actual music?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, just to... Sure, sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me jump in here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you see, it's... I think it's pretty playful.
Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, for the Spectrum, by the way, it was completely redesigned and done really cartoony.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it had push-screen scrolling and very few colors, but it's considered to be one of the best games on the system.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Midnight Resistance.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Midnight Resistance for the, what system specifically?
[SPEAKER_10]: Arcade?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm talking about Arcade, but we'll also include the home releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so the Arcade slash Mega Drive slash C64 slash... Other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: A bunch of British systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've actually not heard of that game, but it looks kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here I thought I knew every game that was on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I thought you would be very interested, because Lotted is one of the best games for the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, every fucking game that was released in the 80s in the arcades came out on the Commodore 64 at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to give it a go.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a lot of games on Commodore 64, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to take a quick break, guys, but we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio after this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, we've got more information on VidRhythm, Harmonix's next project we're going to talk about in the next segment, as well as Diablo 3 and some of the rumors with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, your calls, your tweets, and much more when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about you guys, but I think that's pretty awesome
[SPEAKER_10]: Luminous 2 Luminous 3
[SPEAKER_10]: I really liked... Well, I had a Missy Elliott song and a Beck song.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say, my favorite, though, is still the first one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's fair.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's probably better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Both of them are probably better than the Xbox One, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just the controller on the Xbox Two is so... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's rough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Still surprised to this day they have never tried to really correct the Xbox 360 D-pad.
[SPEAKER_10]: In this country, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than selling it as a premium monochrome controller that, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't that only available in Europe?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it really?
[SPEAKER_02]: They still sell it today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more expensive than the regular controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's get into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some quick, quick news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're going to cover quite a bit here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo announced the launch of their largest title for the Wii, maybe even to date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword will be out in North America November 20th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can mark that down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that is holiday.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, it will require Motion Plus, which, you know, God, by now you probably have something that's Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I still don't have a Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that sad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you're going to play the game then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go buy Wii Party Motion or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a free crappy game with Thermo.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some portal turrets coming to Bastion on Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they've got some cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a quest exclusive for the Steam version of Bastion where the kid uses a gel canister marked with the Aperture Science logo that contains a vicious substance of unknown origin.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you use that friendly portal turrets will come into battle and they will shoot enemies for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby actually sent me a YouTube of this earlier in the night so I don't know if this is going to have narration in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me try to play this YouTube.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the narrator.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, there's the turrets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they talking?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's not in the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, they're talking.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scumbags don't take kindly to interlopers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now they're all over on this screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they're kind of patching different parts of the game together.
[SPEAKER_10]: The music's great in this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's part of the reason I'm pissed my Xbox got hacked.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to be playing this right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clip from Bastion plus Portal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boobz
[SPEAKER_10]: I was talking about 3D websites and how they need websites with boobs I remember talking about this and Bobby said he was going to go make the website even it was like 3dboobies.com or something I don't remember what we called it I swear this came up like last week on the show
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, apparently, the Half-Minute Hero designer, Kenny Chiro Takaki, he has set out to create a 3DS game based on, I guess, I don't know if it's an anime or whatever, but anyways, it's called Senran Kaguru, or Kagura, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's basically female ninjas with giant breasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the game will be on sale in Japan September 22nd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't plan on seeing that coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, they've got a trailer for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't really show too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just kind of this anime intro thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then...
[SPEAKER_02]: and lots of innuendo, like all of them sucking on stuff right now and large boobs and she's pulling out stuff from her boobs and yeah, lots of breasts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and panty shot.
[SPEAKER_10]: You say this like it's a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, this is really what people want a 3DS for, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's welcomed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on to some other news.
[SPEAKER_10]: This has to do with a game coming to PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a revival of an old arcade game, Elevator Action Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, apparently there's a new PlayStation Network version.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an HD update of the old game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you've ever played this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you have the original Elevator Deluxe, look up some of the clips on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it was on the NES.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was very popular back in the day, so I'm sure you guys probably will recognize this when you see some YouTubes of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: but the new version on PlayStation Network of course not just an HD you know upgrade and so forth but there's going to be new new weapons faster elevators multiplayer modes that are available offline including deathmatch and other competitive modes so that'll be kind of neat I guess ten dollars for that I don't know I always kind of thought elevator action was overrated I did not think it was that great of a game as far as like classic games go I think it's one of the uh
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm With The Chili Peppers
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll just do all the songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, Californication, Look Around, Monarchy of Roses, Other Side, Parallel Universe, Scar Tissue, and The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, the usual rock band pricing of $1.99 on the Xbox 360 or PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: August 30th is when it's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind, if the Red Hot Chili Pepper song you were hoping for wasn't in that list, there's already quite a few in the main game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you'd better check the master song lists.
[SPEAKER_10]: Matt Black
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those will be making their way to retailers over the coming weeks, and certainly if you're getting one of these for the holiday, you'll probably have one of those with the matte finish.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mega Man X2 actually has been given an ESRB rating for the Wii, so meaning that we should have it on the Virtual Console at some point, and it's E for everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know that's the one that has the Shoryuken in it, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: and for 3DS, Tekken 3D Prime Edition is actually going to come with apparently it's going to come with Blood Vengeance which is that movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be included on the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that sounds like it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you're actually going to be watching something and it's part of the PS3 bundle for the record which I really want to see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then, last but not least, LittleBigPlanet 2 Move Pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's what's going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has a brand new story for LittleBigPlanet 2 called The Rise of the Cakeling, five levels, seven minigames, two cutscenes, a new power-up for Sackboy called the Brain Crane, three move gadgets, the Moveinator, the Move Recorder, and the Paint Tool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Four interactive music tracks, eight music sequencer tracks, a new sound object containing 32 new sounds, 17 new music sequencer instruments, a new level background, six new costumes, 18 materials, 41 decorations, 31 objects, 66 stickers, 39 new LittleBigPlanet pins, 11 brand new PlayStation trophies, and a partridge in a pear tree.
[SPEAKER_08]: No price yet, but it will be out on September 14th.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still need to buy LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that sad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I keep waiting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I keep holding out for a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, you do the retail thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think there'll be one that has the move crap bundled in with it for a cheaper price?
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll do probably... Well, they did with the first one, a Game of the Year edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's what I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that's going to happen this year, though, because it's... Last one came out a year after the first one came out, and I believe... What's the little big planet, too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was January, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that last year?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was... I think it had been pushed to this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Early this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, I don't think that we're going to see that any cheaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it may price drop a little bit, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably when they have some more content packs for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to get back into some longer news and pretty soon the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: But first, I want to make sure I get at least one more plug in because we might be starting this segment when we get back.
[SPEAKER_10]: It depends if I can get this particular people on the show or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we
[SPEAKER_10]: We are, again, trying very hard to feature indie games on the show and are hoping to begin that around the Labor Day show, which will be, of course, the show when we get back.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are an indie developer yourself or you know someone who's an indie developer who needs help getting the word out on the game and you think the game is unique and special and needs a little help standing out in the Xbox Live marketplace, since Microsoft won't help you, we will.
[SPEAKER_10]: or even if it's an iOS game or a PC game or wherever it is drop me an email rob at orangelaunchradio.com that's me personally or you can always email the show if you'd rather mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and we will try to get to your game to feature it as an indie game on the show and even if we don't get a lot of bite on that we're probably just going to start the spotlights very soon so look forward to that
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura will be back with a second podcast hopefully very soon, something I'm joining her with.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, Labor Day-ish once all this stuff settles because there's a lot going on personal life for Jamie and Dan right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real life is intruding violently.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had to delay it a little bit, but it's still on the radar.
[SPEAKER_10]: So sorry we keep announcing.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've been announcing that for like six weeks now, but things happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we've got like show roles and everything and stuff ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We know what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're ready to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a matter of doing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into some longer news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of creepy and interesting at the same time, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop has been testing a console streaming service.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, they're hoping to have a beta in place by the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And right now, I mean, this shouldn't be a huge surprise because they bought a company called Spawn Labs, which they had their own game streaming box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically,
[SPEAKER_02]: this would stream console games so Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 games to smart devices and dedicated hardware and they're also tinkering with PC game streaming as well
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, that's kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess this will be a service for people that are GameStop Power-Up Rewards members, and that demos will be provided.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, the rest of the stuff, including pricing, is not known, and they're expected to have a full rollout by early next year, or I guess more details about early next year and a full rollout by middle of 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eh, I don't care because it's GameStop and I already told you my feelings on them a few weeks ago and if you missed that whole little rant, I am boycotting them because I think they're a shitty company.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I kind of don't care about this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, let me think of something nice I could say about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Competition is healthy and so these places like OnLive and so forth that are already offering something very similar, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: The competition is a healthy thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is GameStop you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the monkey that's in the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically the elephant in the room there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're the biggest... The monkey in the corner throwing poo at itself?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the biggest retailer for video games out there in the marketplace right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They dictate to publishers what they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what's going to be coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be disgusting.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, that right there, just add that to the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are new to OLR, and I know we have a lot of people that work at GameStops and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: My beef is not with the workers.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys have a thankless job, and I respect what you've got to do to pay the bills.
[SPEAKER_10]: My problem is with the management of the company.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you need...
[SPEAKER_10]: information about what that all entails, look at what Loki just said, because that will probably be reality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's, I mean, when it comes down to dictating, I mean, perfect example, there'll be games that come out that are street dated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Earth Defense Force, for example, you know, and Earth Defense Force was supposed to come out on Tuesday in July.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: D3, they fucked up, they accidentally printed a date on the box that didn't coincide with that date that was on the actual packaging and what they've been communicated to all the different stores.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, whereas a regular store would go, hey, wait a second, this date looks wrong, and they would contact D3 and D3 are like, oh yeah, that was a misprint, the street date is still the date we stated.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop said, hey, you printed a different date on here that happens to be earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to use that date.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you don't want us to put it out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just going to put it out anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even though that information wasn't communicated to all the other retailers out there, ah, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to put it out anyways because you put a date on here and we're adhering to the date that you put on this even though it is a misprint.
[SPEAKER_02]: that's the type of company GameStop is they will do whatever cutthroat thing they need to do to be on top so if you like all the streaming services like on live and stuff well I hope they survive
[SPEAKER_10]: Kaijudo in chat says why all the GameStop hate all they do is sell us games and they've been made buying games easier for people like me who don't like to shop online remember the 80s and how much Toys R Us and mom and pop shops would sell games an arm and a leg 90 plus dollars again I have to defer back to my earlier rant that would have been about three or four weeks ago because I really don't want to get into it again but there's plenty of other options plenty of other options so
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all I'm gonna say about that for now.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameStop is a company that has done some things to people I know that I don't like and I'm not going to support them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're perfectly justified, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, let's move on to happier news, shall we?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk about VidRhythm.
[SPEAKER_10]: VidRhythm is Harmonix's new video game franchise, music franchise.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a lot of people were saying, ooh, maybe this will be like when they heard the title.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we heard the title because of a trademark or application or one of those things before.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a lot of people were hoping, ooh, maybe it's like a new frequency or amplitude or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like VidRhythm, like videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it turns out that the game has been announced for...
[SPEAKER_10]: IOS.
[SPEAKER_10]: In a Gamasutra interview with Alex Rogopoulos, who's the Harmonix head honcho, he says that it's for the IOS and it's more of an app than a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quote, we think there are a lot of creative opportunities with smartphones that we haven't really been able to focus on yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're looking forward to doing more in that space.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it sounds like this may have something to do more so than just a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it has something to do with location.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it has something to do with pictures or videos that the phones can do now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, a statement like that could really go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I don't know if it's just CEO speak blowing smoke up my ass that they're doing something new when they're really not.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just their take on something.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then I go, but it's harmonics and harmonics.
[SPEAKER_10]: and they kind of, I mean, Rock Band and keep in mind, they made the original Guitar Hero with Red Octane.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, that really was kind of something new.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I know there's going to be the people that are like, but Guitar Freaks, Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: They took the risk of making that more mainstream for America that Konami refused to do time and time again.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why Harmonix succeeded here because they did what Konami refused to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Harmonix does what Konami don't do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But let's face it, we're long past that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That whole stuff is years old.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now it's about, what is vidrhythm?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Vidrhythm...
[SPEAKER_10]: I see in my mind that when he talks about we're trying to do things with smartphones that haven't been done, maybe it has something to do with location or picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why pictures keep coming to my mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: But maybe somehow it has to do with pictures on your phone getting incorporated into the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that alone sounds really cheesy.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess we'll see more when the demo is out or what happens with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, if it's iOS, then it'll be one of those things where they'll just be like, oh, it's coming out whenever Apple pushes it to the store, which could be like tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's move on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week, DarkSakura dives into the mailbag headfirst and pulls out some emails that she thinks, hey, I should read this on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: You wanna know what sucks?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that the window I had the mailbag open in was closed Sorry, hold on, let me reopen it You better open that shit real fast Alright, I guess I can plug Twitter again real quick at the end of the show, because we'll be doing your Twitter topics Twitter.com slash OLR We will be doing the Skype line later The 800 number is back tonight, thank you very much So, uh, wait for that
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I want to talk more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, and by the way, I'm not going to call you person.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey guys, thanks for the show, particularly to Rob for posting the podcast to the feed as quick as he's doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really makes a difference for those of us who are unable to listen live.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the top of the show, there was some angst about having mobile games that just aren't optimized for various...
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finally, with it being an open platform, there's a bunch of great apps for gamers who, like me, prefer a physical gamepad, even going so far as to use a Wiimote for our games.
[SPEAKER_08]: For free.
[SPEAKER_08]: A first-person shooter on my Zoom with the moat and nunchuck over Bluetooth is great for traveling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I haven't had an horchata in forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know a place that's open late that has them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But from thine eyes my knowledge I derive, which is a Shakespeare quote.
[SPEAKER_08]: He put it on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is from, I'm going to say Dr. Noir.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did I miss a question in there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought I heard a question about, we were talking about on the top of last week's show about the mobile games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or was it just a statement?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just a statement.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, my bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Android's better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad you think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last one, which is the only one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, OLR, SonicM88 here with another question for you wonderful folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
42.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm considering buying a few of my favorite games as downloadable games on Xbox via the Games on Demand service.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very lazy and can totally justify the purchase because my biggest problem currently is getting off my ass to change games.
[SPEAKER_08]: First world problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the problem though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember hearing stories a while back about a Tom Clancy game not being fully compatible with multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently the physical version was unable to play online multiplayer with the games on demand downloadable version.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the Xbox marketplace, all I know of the games say is that they don't support online multiplayer whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Try Wikipedia
[SPEAKER_10]: or actually, I'm going to say the official Xbox forums because when shit like that is broken, you will hear the angry gamers and complaints on the official Xbox forum.
[SPEAKER_10]: So all you have to do is read through one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: I vaguely remember what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say that was fixed, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they did do some type of patch.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think Microsoft is intentionally leaving that shit out, but let's face it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Games on Demand service is pretty lazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All they're doing is they're kind of doing what I talked about at the top of the show with the Wii hack.
[SPEAKER_10]: you can load the things you load the disk into an image and Microsoft's basically selling you that image
[SPEAKER_02]: It is literally the, when you take the disc and install it to your hard drive on your 360, it's literally that image that they're selling you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is fine because it's legit.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not piracy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's through their store.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's, you know, essentially they don't do the extensive quality checks that are done when a game is first released.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: they might do some minimal quality checks but you know very minimal as you can see by that little story there but those sort of instances should be few and far between to the best of my knowledge those games are supposed to be playable online they're supposed to be just like copies of the regular games it's not supposed to be anything crazy or something Microsoft's locking you out of but I will say this you know if you know it's your money spend it how you want if downloading the game so you don't have to get up and put a disc in is that important to you then fine do it but
[SPEAKER_10]: just don't be afraid to shop smart too and what I mean by that is don't assume that the price you see on Xbox downloadable is necessarily the cheapest what's more important to you getting up off the couch to change the disc or getting it cheapest you know because you might be able to find a used copy on eBay
[SPEAKER_10]: Really cheap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or possibly you could even find Amazon is having a sale or Best Buy is having a sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: Best Buy had a great Kinect sale a couple months ago where it was like buy one, get one free.
[SPEAKER_10]: So always be on the lookout for things like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: how come nobody told me about that but at the end of the day again it's your money spend it how you want and certainly I've downloaded my share of download games granted that's mostly the arcade stuff but I will say this when I had swine flu back in 09 I had swine flu I was out of work for 9 days I downloaded a game digitally because I was not allowed to leave my house for my doctor so I think in that case I might have a legitimate reason for having done that you know
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have left my house anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give it to as many people as possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares about co-workers?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just to make a quick mention.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's actually where the source of most illness is from the workplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, since I have not been working, Rob, I've only been sick, like really sick, once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quarantined here in the safety of my home.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since that was the end of the email bag, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need more emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a sad showing.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I get 10 emails next week, Rob has to get me an Orchata.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not going to do shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's because you're not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the week after, if we have 10 emails the week after, then I will get Rob an Orchata.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now we're talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Rob will get me an Orchata.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, 10 emails means horchata trading happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it'll just be Mexican drink night here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get a tamarindo.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go get some charritos.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will get horchata, and then we can have some, what's that, apple soda?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I'm thinking of, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yarritos makes the tamarind soda, and they have, I think the same company makes an apple soda, and they have like a lime soda.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we'll go to Target and get the Coke that's actually from Mexico, that has like the real sugar in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's kosher.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we'll drink lots of tequila.
[SPEAKER_10]: So 10 emails for Mexican drink night for a fiesta in studio here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: We gotta get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week on the show we get a little bit angsty and we have to share our angst with you all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to Northrend First world problems Loki FU to Activision for putting out a game called Skylanders Spyro's Adventure Skylanders is first off a really good game
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: $8!
[SPEAKER_02]: $8 for a toy that does nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is literally a figurine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is about 2 inches tall.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't move.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't do anything other than activate a character in a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Why kids would buy that or parents would buy that instead of, I don't know, a Mario game or, I don't know, any other toy out there on the market is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on top of all that, they want to sell this thing starting off at $70.
[SPEAKER_02]: $70 for a Wii game, PS3 game, 360 game because it comes with some bullshit toys that aren't really toys.
[SPEAKER_10]: What would you like to see sell more?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tickle Me Elmo or this thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything other than this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I predict right now that this is going to be as big of a failure as Tony Hawk Shred, Tony Hawk Ride, and sadly enough, DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: So meaning like a year and a half later, I'll be able to get them for $10?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really wish I could have gotten some of those Renegade or the bundles of all the stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's even better with that stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Flip it on fucking eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can make more than $10 off that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what you could do with that kind of stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you got the extra turntables and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: You could flip it to GameStop and make more than $10 off of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you really wanted to go that route.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, that's just money in the bag right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yes, it will not sell very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there's a lot of kids games coming out this holiday and with Mario and stuff on the 3DS and on the console systems and everything else and Call of Duty no one's going to give a shit about Spyro.
[SPEAKER_02]: A character that was popular 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Skylanders with Spyro, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: You done?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, finally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, uh, my FU of the week goes to Peanut Butter Pinkberry, because, you guys, it's so good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, they do one where they put strawberry jam on it and toasted breadcrumbs, and oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, it's so good.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's why I give it an FU, because, well, A, it's good, and B, it's not non-fat or low-fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every other flavor in Pinkberry's history has been, like, non-fat or low-fat, but this one...
[SPEAKER_07]: Extra fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Extra fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seven grams of fat a serving, which, you know, ice cream's worse, but still.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a little disappointing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Special occasions only.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, this is a real problem, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, there it is, FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: More news stories for you guys, and then the Skype line is about five stories away.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Ubisoft is apparently trying to pull a THQ and put out a tablet peripheral for, I guess, the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like it's supposed to be for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now they're kind of, it's a work in progress thing, Project InTouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have an internal marketing video that's been found leaked out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they have some sort of tablet that's going to be used to play games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically all the same stuff that you see right now with the U-Draw.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know the U-Draw is doing alright, but I don't know if there's really room on the market for multiple tablet peripherals.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's hard to convince people to buy... More plastic shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: ...a $100 skateboard for a game that, you know, it's really going to be the only game that's going to support it, or two games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So why is UDraw succeeded in where this one is trying to get some of that success?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, UDraw succeeded because they've got a lot of different games that have come out for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, they have...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's about five games right now that support it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's a lot more coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, there's going to be more UDraw stuff on other systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get it on the PlayStation 3 and 360 as well this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on top of that, besides the licensed stuff that THQ's done, like with SpongeBob and...
[SPEAKER_02]: They're Marvel stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got now licenses from other companies like Disney Princess stuff, and actually there's going to be a Mickey drawing program or something like that, a Disney animation program.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, that sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're getting other companies to support this kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Ubisoft, I'm sure if you played your cards right and talked to THQ, they would probably let you make a game for...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the UDraw tablet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Save yourself a whole bunch of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead, you're going to put out this other peripheral.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, why would they do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why would they do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would you concede to another company to make it a lot easier for yourself when you can just make something that will fail on your own?
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can just fucking steamroll with all your franchises.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, why would we bother publishing with the UDraw when we can make our own and take the market from UDraw?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... I don't think there's really going to be a market for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've tried to think outside the box with different stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, it was last E3, they had a bunch of games that weren't really games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had some sort of relaxation program or something like that, where you basically... It was basically the... What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The...
[SPEAKER_02]: That stupid Wii peripheral that they had that they never put out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the hell it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically the Vitality Sensor, but on the PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had that come out, and they had some laser tag game come out that wasn't really a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just something that ran on the PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically a laser tag toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had one other thing that was kind of along the lines of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're definitely trying some unique stuff over there at Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, we'll see if it works for him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think flooding the market with too much of the similar shit is going to end up being a bad thing, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, there's been rumors going around forever that Diablo 3, you know, big PC release coming out later this year, big rumor for the longest time that it'll probably end up on consoles as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's just fan the flames of that fire because during a Gamescom press conference this week, Josh Moschera, who's the lead designer behind Diablo 3, said that Blizzard is, quote, very, very serious about bringing the Diablo 3 experience to the console.
[SPEAKER_10]: The company is, quote, trying to build the best console team at Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_02]: now they're not saying what game they're working on but you can expect it's probably Diablo or it's the new MMO that would be ironic if that was the case because Diablo 3 doesn't have to be connected to the internet the whole time to play the game but the console version you probably wouldn't have to be
[SPEAKER_10]: um that's maybe or maybe not true uh we could that could be a sticking point for why it's not on the consoles right now I would think that whole real money trade auction house is what's holding things up especially when it comes to Xbox 360 I could not see that shit flying on the 360 without Microsoft getting a cut of that somehow although then again to have Diablo 3 on their console would be a pretty big score for them so it would have to be online only and if not um that thing would get hacked apart
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they're going to keep it separate from the PC one somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could do that without the real money auction house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we will see.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for now, that's all we know.
[SPEAKER_10]: More rumors to fuel those fires.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still getting Diablo 3 just because I was such a sucker for the first one.
[SPEAKER_10]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, sad face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never got into the other Diablo games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they'll be going back to Squirt, which actually makes sense because I'm going to use this as an example.
[SPEAKER_08]: The company that I used to work for when I was doing student loans, we were Educade.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Wachovia purchased the company, they've actually purchased First Union, which owned Educade and the money store and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we had to brand ourselves as Educate Wachovia, and then after a while we became Wachovia Student Services or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's the same thing, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that they've got Square and Enix in everybody's head, they're going to rebrand back to Square.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I also think of remember when there was G4 and then there was Tech TV and then there was G4 Tech TV and then it was like chomp and now it's just G4 again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's just part of rebranding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: With any acquisition, especially with a big company, something that's well known, you have to merge your branding so that people will start associating one with the other.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still sad to see the name Enix go away because now we'll never get another bus to move.
[SPEAKER_08]: We might, but it won't say Enix on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just bust out my other two bust moves.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Couple more stories for you guys, then we're gonna get to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: But not just yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki's got a story for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some interesting stuff on the PlayStation Network front.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're actually going to start offering some cheaper rentals for different movies and TV shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: $0.99 movie and TV rentals are coming, and right now they've got a really small list of what's going to be available.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess every Tuesday, a selection of movies and TV rentals will see a discount of $0.99 for the SD versions and $1.99 for HD.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe this week was Sicko, The Long Shots, Salvage, Tony, Shank, Bonded by Blood, JFK, Reckless Youth Part 1 and Part 2, Deadly Blessing, Carver, Devil in the Flesh, and Illuminating Angels and Demons.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was what was on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're going to be discounting stuff each week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of neat, I guess, to drive a little bit more sales in that category.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially maybe to compete a little bit with
[SPEAKER_10]: Redbox and yeah but the stuff they're offering is crap have you looked at what's on the list it's all a bunch of crap but hey you know what something's something cheaper is still better than nothing I still don't see how any of that stuff's really a better value than Netflix although I guess you know Netflix is kind of challenged for a lot of content and may continue to be challenged over the next year or what have you but I don't know
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I was looking, one of my friends uses that Vudu site and I kind of saw that for the first time over the weekend and I don't know, it seemed too expensive for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, dang, they want too much money for all these rentals of old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I guess everything seems expensive next to Netflix where you're paying the one fee for the whole month, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just me.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, one other story for you guys, and this has to do with Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course you love Portal 2, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura speaks for all the listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Portal 2, you know, we were supposed to be getting download content.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where the hell is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was supposed to be here in the summer, and it's still not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burn his house down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, it's going to be happening in September.
[SPEAKER_10]: September is when the download content will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they are saying it's free.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're like all huffy and puffy about the fact that the download content still is now, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good things come to those who wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have not said what the download content might include.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all that's being said about it is that Valve's Doug Lombardi apparently said, quote, it's still technically summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: which he does have a point, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fall doesn't really start until what?
[SPEAKER_10]: September 21st?
[SPEAKER_10]: So technically it is still summer in early September.
[SPEAKER_10]: So fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the dorkiest thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: You win on this technicality.
[SPEAKER_10]: You better have it out or we're sending more protesters out to protest in front of Valve because that's the thing people do these days.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.com slash OLR
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the show where every gamer has a voice and we welcome that through the phones or through our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or, of course, there's always the chat room if you're like, you know, I don't have a Twitter or I'm too lazy to call or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our Twitter brings all the calls to the yard.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can always do it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's like, damn right, my call quality is better than yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's see, trying to go to some of the tweets here from earlier in the week We got wished a happy third to a birthday Nice, by who?
[SPEAKER_10]: Twee Birthday or some account.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's probably a spam account.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to the phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been on Twitter a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a dollar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you're on Orange House Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Death Wishing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can see you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you can.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank God you have a shirt on.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm playing EVE Online.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's EVE?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've never played EVE Online before.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's EVE Online like?
[SPEAKER_01]: Space Cowboy with tons of space rocks and mining and just people being assholes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I can give you an example.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot harder than World of Warcraft and it's a lot better in my opinion because you can pretty much do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't have to follow your class guideline.
[SPEAKER_01]: The customization.
[SPEAKER_01]: They recently also just released an expansion where you can walk around in stations, which is also going to build into the game Dust 5.14, if you also heard of that, which I kind of want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk about that a little bit, because I did hear about that at E3, and it sounded really exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's this all about?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, think of, you know, the game Planetside, and did you ever play it?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dust is a first-person shooter that is going to be pretty much just like Planetside, but for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Only the PS3, which is weird, but it's going to tie in to EVE Online, where basically it will work as in the player-run corporations that are on EVE Online will be able to hire mercenaries from the PlayStation 3 to fight over planets in the EVE universe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which, basically, they will fight over minerals, blah blah blah, whatever the hell is on the planet.
[SPEAKER_01]: It could be a pile of shit, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, basically, corporations will buy us, the PlayStation 3 users...
[SPEAKER_01]: All their weaponry, all their tanks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So basically, if the PC users supply their mercenary corporation, they earn pretty much unlimited wealth.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's what Dust is.
[SPEAKER_01]: And EVE Online is really hard to explain.
[SPEAKER_01]: All I can say is it's hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: What makes it so rewarding to be playing the game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everything in this game is basically player-run.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have player-run banks that people make real spreadsheets and stuff where you put your in-game money, and it works exactly like a real bank, building interest, taking out loans and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then, as you would think, there's also people that scam that system.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think a couple months ago, there was a guy who made a bank
[SPEAKER_01]: made it for two years, got about $870 billion ISK, transferred all that money to another account, closed his account down, and all of the users were complaining that they lost money, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: The freaking corporation just told them, or the CCP, who runs the game, said, welcome to the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't trust people.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it doesn't hold your hand like World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did I say that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you did mention that a little bit, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's hard to explain, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, I want to say that I hate Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you hate Activision?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the guy who runs the company is such an asshole.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Kotick?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he ruins game series.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's ruined Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_01]: He ruined Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_10]: What fuckery is he responsible for this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: What fuckery set you off this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Besides jobs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's a bit of personal bitterness here to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just an angry person.
[SPEAKER_01]: An angry college kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just an angry listener.
[SPEAKER_10]: An angry gamer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I usually have more to talk about, but I'm actually a boring person this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm kind of on a recovery day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, let me read this tweet for a recovery day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was Burning Man this week or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What were you going to say?
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tiger Claw says EVE Online is by far the most hardcore hardest core game in its existence agree?
[SPEAKER_01]: I totally agree especially since my corporation got attacked like last week and we lost like 500 million so yikes which um yeah I can also say one thing a lot of the money in the game amounts to real money so like there's ships that cost they're called Titan Claw ships $10,000 real currency they're just throwing that out there $10,000 in real currency yeah
[SPEAKER_01]: Real currency.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because $360 million is $15 a currency, which you can use the currency that you make in-game to buy your in-game subscription.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've heard of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can buy these cards or something that you use, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, wasn't there a big story where they blew up a big carrier that was carrying a bunch of those cards and, like, all this game time was just lost?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I forgot what it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was some player who was really retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe you can put that stuff in your, like, a hanger and...
[SPEAKER_01]: He was retarded and kept it around and went with him for God knows why.
[SPEAKER_01]: So people heard about it, killed him, took game time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your fault.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Death Wishing, we're going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: But thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: And thanks for the webcam.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting to see our listeners there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're not hooking one up so you can see us, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not fat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mine rock time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see more well maybe that's something I don't want to wish maybe I don't want to see more of the listeners but yeah sure why not call us with your webcams it'll be fun we want to see the sexy ones alright now the 877 number is apparently broken but there is a back door you can use 916-226-9067 I want to point out that is not a toll free number so if you don't have like a cell phone that has free nationwide long distance that number will not work it looks like someone's using that number right now hi you're on Orange Lawns Radio who's this
[SPEAKER_10]: it's Shane Miklatov whatever hey what's up Miklatov again I want to clarify 877 I don't know it's like I'm having problems with the phone constantly last week and now this week 877 number will not work something's up with the toll-free forwarder you can use the back door a 916-226-9067 please only use that if you have free long distance which a lot of cell phone companies do but be very very careful all right Miklatov what's on your mind
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're just calling to say hey?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I meant to call in last week, but I have a little anecdote that leads into a kind of stance I'm taking, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so last week I was at work and we were doing a blood drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I go get blood, even though technically, legally, I'm not allowed to because laws are stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm sitting there giving blood, being all bored, and I bust out my phone and start playing some games on my phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm having a really good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes the time pass super quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm starting to think about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I play games on my phone when I'm giving blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: I play games on my phone when I'm waiting at the drive-thru to pick up food or order or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I play games at work when I am in the back
[SPEAKER_03]: looking for stuff or quote-unquote looking for stuff to put out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it hits me that I feel like the mobile phone games now are really what's portable gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like the definition.
[SPEAKER_03]: And things like the Vita, the PSP, the DS, too big, too bulky to really be portable systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I really begin to realize that I only use those portably if I'm on a plane.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, I'm playing my portable systems at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that Nintendo and Sony are going to find themselves in this same sort of mindset after a few years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, those things are just too big and bulky.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the iPhone and the Android phone, their games are just way more accessible for
[SPEAKER_03]: Your portable gaming nowadays
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, you all saw how well that worked out, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's why Nintendo... It was a CDI.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, CDI.
[SPEAKER_10]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was one of those 90s CD-based systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, okay, fine, the CDI.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clearly, that didn't work out well for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They got fucking burned on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they created it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just licensed the character out for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, still, though, it just goes to show you how they're very protective of their shit, and they don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, Nintendo's already kind of tested the waters with that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Japan, they have that Pokemon...
[SPEAKER_03]: Trading Card Rhythm Game on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Pokemon company has tested, but that's not Nintendo themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but that's Nintendo's brand.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Pokemon is, I mean, yeah, it's Pokemon company, but you're not going to see Pokemon go over to Vita or Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you do bring up an interesting point, though, is that the only place a lot of people tend to play their portable gaming systems is at home.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's kind of where I do a lot of my portable gaming, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I have my 3DS kind of by my bed, and maybe, like, when it's, you know, bedtime, quote-unquote, and I go into bed, and maybe I'll stay up for about 20 minutes and play the 3DS, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where I tend to do most of my portable gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and you know, at E3 this year, I had my PSP, which stayed in my hotel room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had my 3DS, which I used to get StreetPass Tags.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then play their little mini dungeon game because I did not have time, even when standing in line, or not time, but I was not really comfortable holding that thing in my hand playing some game that's in-depth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Had I had something like Tiny Tower, I would have been all over my phone at that point.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I probably would have needed to...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bring a charger or something with me
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you do the street pass for?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you do it to do that stupid fill in the puzzles?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or did you do it to do the stupid like
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do both when you street pass.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you meet a character and they go hello, it gives you their little URL.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was also street passing for Street Fighter 4 data and now I'll be street passing for Ridge Racer 3DS data.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want more ghosts to race against.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's a lot of really interesting things they can do with StreetPass I just don't think any of the games out right now really sell that stuff very well but I'm interested to see what future games can kind of think up with the StreetPassing that's very interesting to me but I'm not to say I'm totally disagreeing with you because I think part of the reason the 3DS isn't selling does have to do with the fact that mobile phones are doing it in some ways better definitely cheaper
[SPEAKER_10]: and I think the price of portable games needs to come down to stay competitive with iOS games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think charging $40 for a 3DS game isn't going to fly and I think they're going to be in for a rude awakening pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they can't get that price down to $20, kiss it goodbye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I look at my portable games I'm playing right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I pick up Zelda since it's launched maybe once every week and a half.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then I bust out my phone to play Groove Coaster or Tiny Tower or Juke Beat which I actually like a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Juke Beat's terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you download any of the download content stuff for Juke Beat?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, because they're all terrible sounding.
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's just to start.
[SPEAKER_03]: The three that they have you begin with are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that Contra song, and even the Frogger song's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Contra and Frogger songs are kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it is really too hard, but it's still...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm playing Tiny Tower right now while you're trying to talk.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm half paying attention to you, I'm half restocking all my stores.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because now Bobby had to go and make it a contest.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I said I was doing that and then I called in.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you go right back to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that and wow, I'm just like, oh, I'm flying somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I gotta check on my supplies, make sure everything's stocked up, and I just upgraded my elevator, so it's going faster, and I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it changed the game completely for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I still am.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because I don't foresee me going outside and busting out my Vita and playing Uncharted because that is not a game...
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, that you want portable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to sit down and experience this awesome game with best headphones and all sorts of being comfortable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to stand on a bus or in a subway playing Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more comment from chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to let you guys get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Kaijudo in the chatroom says, phones are not killing the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the lack of anything on the 3DS that's killing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I kind of tend to agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's really the 3DS' biggest problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I also think the price of the games is really an issue.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I think it's more of an issue than Nintendo wants to admit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I realize games are expensive to make, but there has to come a point where you go, we're not selling these games at $40.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have to cut the price to get these to sell.
[SPEAKER_10]: And maybe we'll sell three times as much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, go on.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really hope that this price cut and then realizing how bad the system is doing forces them to make an actual, real, honest-to-goodness 3D Pokemon game that's not some spin-off like the new one in Japan, because, I mean, that would get me to buy four more systems, even though I have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I plan on getting that red one, too, just to have a red one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just to have a flamey red one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I had a red and a blue SP when they came out, so I can do a red and a blue 3DS, I decided.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls, alright?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, give us a call at area code 916-226-9067 Again, not toll free, the toll free number is down right now Or call us on Skype, that's always free Orange Lounge Radio, all one word on Skype I'll get to the Twitter topics in just a moment here Let's see, I'm trying to get through some of these here Trying to get through the feedback for last week's show and so forth What is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to see if this is a story we've already covered
[SPEAKER_10]: No, this is something that EricRPG tweeted us, and this is about Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Could a new Fire Emblem game be on its way to the Nintendo 3DS?
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, an online gaming site called The Magic Box posted that a new Fire Emblem game will be announced by Nintendo fairly soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, it's called Fire Emblem Blue Sacred Sword and Red Demon Lance.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to be 100 years after Sealed Sword, and the story will center around the Princess of Kingdom Burn and the Prince of Kingdom Lycia.
[SPEAKER_10]: and each will have a different story in their perspective.
[SPEAKER_10]: There will also be a new casual mode for beginners and lunatic mode for advanced players.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word on where this information is coming from, but sounds good enough to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fire Emblem on 3DS seems like a logical next step, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds like an educated guess to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Spazernator PSN tweets us saying, OLR, could you please say hi to your newest listener, Shirley, in Arizona, please?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shirley!
[SPEAKER_10]: Shirley, we will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just did, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, and I'm sure that's a pun that Shirley is terribly sick of hearing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's go to the phones and get more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sludgeon Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, Zaku, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much, just trying to recover from Ramna's barbecue we held at his place yesterday.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's this all about?
[SPEAKER_10]: What was happening at the barbecue?
[SPEAKER_00]: Bacon-wrapped sausage, a lot of food, a lot of, like, raunchy card games.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were just, like, drawing and using Sharpies against other people while they were passed out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was exactly like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, God, I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll probably fill you in on the details.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_00]: So, they were mentioning Activision being the new devil.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think they're the new devil.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've been the devil for at least a good year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I mean, I know that's still debatable, but I mean, they're like, I don't know, it's like EA is starting to go back into the dark side, but then again, they've been doing pretty well ever since going away from it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It doesn't matter, staying in that point where you're making money, but you don't piss off the fanbase like Activision does by just shoveling out crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, I mean, you know, the way I see it right now is that Activision's trying to make amends by doing dedicated servers for Modern Warfare 3, but God knows what restrictions they will have.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, we don't know whether they're just going to be, like, rent-a-servers, or there's better, or it's like a full no-strings-attached ones, like, you know, like in Call of Duty 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's like, when Activision tries to throw out something like that, I don't even think it's them being genuine about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just them trying to capitalize, trying to sweep, trying to bury all their transgressions that they did in the past.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just trying to bury it, trying to kiss and make up.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that right there is just not really sincere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's a company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course they're not sincere.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't understand, but when they treated but if you remember how that whole Modern Warfare 2 on PC that whole thing went out that whole thing panned out where they got rid of the dedicated servers and you see a bunch of folks just like
[SPEAKER_00]: They basically said, to hell with Activision, it's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was one of them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was really hyped up for Modern Warfare 2 that year until that news broke, and I just lost interest, and I got back company 2 instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're talking about all those people that decided, hey, we're going to basically form a group that's going to boycott Modern Warfare 2, and then they were all playing Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just stuck to my guns.
[SPEAKER_00]: if you look at my Steam profile I don't have that game I have Call of Duty 4 I mean the last good one with dedicated servers it's like I basically have not I've never played Modern Warfare 2 not even in consoles SSJ100 Matt is in the chat room hold on because I have to get this out here because this is kind of funny is saying correction Bobby Kotick is the new devil Activision would be fine without him there you agree?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, I guess that's what I was trying to refer to.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, he is personifying the evil intentions of the devil.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, him and his company.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I mean, it's like, after seeing the 64-player multiplayer video for Battlefield 3 this week, I mean, like last week during Gamescom, it's like, I don't have any incentive to buy Modern Warfare 3 anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, sure, they may throw in dedicated servers, but you're going to get your money's worth in terms of production values and gameplay out of Battlefield 3, just by the looks of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going for a console version or PC version?
[SPEAKER_00]: Both.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean... What do you think of the origin stuff?
[SPEAKER_00]: Granted, the console's like, what, 24 players and obviously the PC's more, but it's still pretty good from both spectrums.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think of the origin?
[SPEAKER_00]: All that Modern Warfare 3 is just doing is rehashing perks.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: The whole basis is the more kills you get, the more balance you tip against the others.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, you know, UAV, just spamming UAV airstrikes and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about the fact that on PC you're forced to use Origin?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I'm kind of indifferent about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know I was holding out for them having to sell it on Steam, but at this point, I may give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because at the end of the day...
[SPEAKER_00]: it's it's like the same it's like what what Valve went through when they first released Half-Life 2 like when they first launched Steam they were basically they were completely dead set against it they just hated it they just hated its guts from the get-go and now it's pretty much one of the top digital districts the top digital distributors it's the thing to have on PC right now it's kind of the cool kids club
[SPEAKER_00]: I understand, but as I said, it's like, or EA's going to go through their own steam moment when launching.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's like, if EA can basically pass that test in terms of providing a decent alternative to steam, then more power to them.
[SPEAKER_00]: As long as they bring it on par with it, then it'll be an easier pill to swallow.
[SPEAKER_00]: It won't be like eating a shit sandwich.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I gotta let you go so we can get more calls, but I gotta say this, I wanna know when the next barbecue is happening, because I may need to come back out to New York for that, and I'm gonna draw all of your faces.
[SPEAKER_00]: Try next summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next summer?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, Adam, Ranma is only gonna hold, only holds them like once a year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe Labor Day, but I don't think Ranma, I demand one in my honor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma will throw one in my honor if I come visit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm pretty sure he will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get what I want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, take care, Zaku, thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the New York contingent we have a lot of fans in New York I don't know how it happened well I guess there's a lot of people in New York so it makes sense but still we have quite a few listeners there so I would I need to go back and say hello it's been far too long I need to go New York is so much fun oh my god you need to go see Mistress Tia because I love that bitch if people will send me a ticket I'll go I'm not even playing that's not how it works
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Jamie's broke.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold out for another one of those JetBlue sales, man.
[SPEAKER_10]: They go cheap sometimes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we got enough listeners out there that they could send us tickets.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see why they don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but then you owe them something.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Iowa?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a lengthy article from Gamasutra, and I didn't read this in advance, so gosh, I don't even know where to start here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are still seeing calls, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Launch Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it's ringing right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good, that'll give me time to skim this article.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally joined the contingent and picked up a 3D last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was this after the price drop, I'm assuming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, and how was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's actually a pretty neat little system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually digging it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not much in the way of games out yet, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, there's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there something you're looking forward to that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, no?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm pretty satisfied with the two that I've got right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you have right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: DOA Dimensions and, uh, Ridge Racer 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of 3D boobies and DOA, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've always liked the DOA franchise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm, a lot of guys do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask you this.
[SPEAKER_10]: What kind of made you decide to take the plunge and buy the three?
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that the Evil G had the, if you're one of the Power Rewards members or whatever the hell membership thing that they got, if you trade in a DS Lite, you can pick it up for 99 bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay, so you did the whole, like, the Evil G. I like that, by the way, the Evil G. I had a... True story, this is not going to make sense to anyone, but I just have to say this, because, you know, some teachers that you have in your past stay with you forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I had an awesome, awesome music teacher in junior high school, and his name was Mr. Gonzalez, but everybody called him Mr. G. Like, that was the name he went by for short.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he's a great... Oh, man, I wish I knew what he was up to these days.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if he's still teaching.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyhow, when you say Evil G...
[SPEAKER_10]: For whatever reason, that just triggers a response in my mind where I see his evil twin.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: But I like that as a name for GameStop, Evil G. So you bought into the Evil G's trade-in scheme, which is I can't fault you for a good deal, so it's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's what made you finally take the plunge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had thought about picking one up when they came out, but ooh, $250.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't you pick up one for about $100?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And considering that's what I paid for my DS Lite?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what did you think about, we had a call a little bit ago that was talking about, I don't really use my portable game systems portably.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you find that your gaming habits are similar, or do you think that you might actually get more use out of this on the go?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm interested in taking it to DragonCon and see what I can do with the street pass function.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll get a shit ton there, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't even imagine a pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: But other than that, my ass is sitting on the couch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see, so you're couch surfing and playing the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a lot of folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Bobby, I didn't steal your name for GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think I heard?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby's throwing a tantrum in chat right now, Brad.
[SPEAKER_10]: You need to go address this.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's just mad because his tiny bitizens are revolting because they don't want his tower to get bigger than mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they stink on ice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Brad, there's some new games coming out for the 3DS this holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's the new Mario game, the new Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any of this stuff look interesting?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I like Mario Kart, so that's definitely worth a look.
[SPEAKER_05]: May pick that up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely, I think it is going to be worth picking up So, well, I hope you have a lot of fun at DragonCon And I hope you are able to street pass with tons and tons of people And I hope you win lots of awards that I hear you're nominated for That apparently Bobby was not Hence some of the tantrum that's going on in there No, he was nominated, I don't just We weren't nominated either You were nominated Were we?
[SPEAKER_05]: You didn't make it as a finalist, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty sure you were nominated.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't see any emails on it this year, but oh, well.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I ain't mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, if you can get in on the deal for the 3DS, go ahead and check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another raving endorsement for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Brad, buddy, we're going to let you go so we can wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently these guys want to set up some type of collectible museum.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the guys that are behind the Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is all a tweet to a story on a Gamasutra that TigerClaw sent us via Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently they're the folks behind Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got a collection of 30,000 items that they want to put into a permanent official home where folks can research, document, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they need $30,000 to set up the base in Silicon Valley and
[SPEAKER_10]: and they got less than two weeks to go to do it and they don't even have half of the money that they need to do it so it's not looking too good and I guess a lot of the backers just don't have an idea where the money is going and you know I guess what they're going to get out of it so to speak so some of the collection shows off at trade shows and all that stuff so they want to do it but um
[SPEAKER_10]: It sounds like they may not hit it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be nice to have a video game museum of sorts.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Silicon Valley definitely is a much more logical place to put it than whatever the fuck Iowa.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I can see where they're having problems selling an idea like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: What they might want to do is maybe try to have it as an expansion to some type of museum that already exists that speaks to nerds' interests.
[SPEAKER_10]: One really cool place I went to last year was the Sci-Fi Museum in Seattle, which is attached to the Experience Music Project, which is a neat little museum.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe there's a place in that whole thing that they could fit a video game tribute into.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know San Jose has a technology museum that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe just come to my house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to do it for another show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But first, I need to make sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe so?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just dropping grenades on ants.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, so you're too busy fighting insects to do last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have some Last Minute Stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can talk about them if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, please, let's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a couple of music games coming out this fall, and we can talk a little bit about what tracks will be featured in said games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting with, of course, Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: They announced an initial song list, including some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it Sexy Chick by David Guetta and Akon?
[SPEAKER_02]: Daddy Yankee featuring Fergie with Impacto.
[SPEAKER_02]: Darude with Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Death Punk with Technologic, Bruno Mars with Grenade, Ozone with Dragoste Dente.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the Numa Numa song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember the guy sitting in his chair?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ayahi, my yaku...
[SPEAKER_02]: Donna Summers with Hot Stuff, Gnarls Barkley with Run, Lena with Satellite, Enrique Inglis with I Like It, Lady Gaga with Born This Way, Exile with I Wish For You, and Florida with David Guetta, Club Can't Handle Me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just Dance 3 Just Dance 3
[SPEAKER_02]: 2 Unlimited with No Limit, AHA with Take On Me, BananaRama with Venus.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have some new stuff in there, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see LMFAO and the Party Rock Anthem.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like a big song right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: A cover of Boogie Wonderland, looks like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Katy Perry with California Girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan will be so happy to hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: He loves Katy Perry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Mika.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see Mika's in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a pretty round set list.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're saying that may not be the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that for the Wii and the PS3 and 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: So it is going to be on all of them this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they even have Crazy Little Thing Called Love by Queen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Queen songs are good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Scissor Sisters, I Don't Feel Like Dancing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a fun song.
[SPEAKER_10]: That song for some reason makes me think of the Muppets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Must be that one performance they did at the Brit Awards, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that'll be a good one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess the music's very important to a dancing... I've never played Just Dance, but people seem to really like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very similar, kind of, a little bit like Dance Masters, but less... It gives you a little bit of an idea of what you're supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they have kind of... It's still kind of following on screen, but there's not that many cues to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a lot more than Dance Masters where Dance Masters doesn't give you any cues whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's going to be fun to watch these two games have a showdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No Dance Masters this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a shock.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Connectimals is coming to Windows 7 phone this fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSX looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were showing off some of the events that they can feature including 100,000 player events.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to be really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's going to start to close the book on another week here at Orange Lounge Radio, but we can't call it a show until we go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, DarkSakura, your final thought for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have good friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is Jamie has good friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is I got to cut back on expenses a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for downloading Orange Lounge Radio and tuning into us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you like what you hear, remember we don't ask for your money to do this program.
[SPEAKER_10]: We do it for free just because, you know, it's a way to kill a Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just tell a friend about the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Help us spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_10]: Leave us a nice five star review on iTunes or whatever website it is that you found this podcast on.
[SPEAKER_10]: You would not believe how much a little word spreading can go.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're not here next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: The show's got to last you for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: if you are tuning in live next week though there's a new OLR best of I actually don't have anything to do with those Dark Tetsuya has been spearheading those so that's all I don't even know what's going to be in it so I will tell you though that a lot of the stuff he at least the first one was all really old stuff so for those folks that are like what did OLR sound like nine years ago if you really want to subject yourself to it because it was a much different show then best of is a good way to do it it will not be on the podcast feed it will only be live you must must tune in live to hear it
[SPEAKER_10]: might be up for download on the website later if we're in a good mood.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it won't be on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a special thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great week, two weeks, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we'll see you back here Labor Day weekend with more of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!