[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight, August 14th, 2011, a patent possibly spills new details on the Wii U controller, games finally arrive on Google+, and Australia gets a new rating for graphic games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live on this lovely Sunday evening, August the 14th of 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and with me as always, say hello to the one, the only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Burpee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burpee?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little gassy?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been drinking root beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having a root beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, it's episode 424 tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: 424.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a palindrome episode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like dad and mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other words.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a palindrome, but maybe a prime number.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't worry, we'll end the same way as we began.
[SPEAKER_06]: Terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, inevitably when the show ends someday, it will end the same way it began.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just talking about tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, Loki will have to do the last episode in one of those cheap little $5 microphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that microphone we had on the first episode?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sounded like you were coming through a phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe it was a piece of foam wire attached to a paper cup.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was two Dixie cups and a string, actually, I think is what he was using.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, usually we start off the show with how was your gaming week, but I got to start this off tonight because this is some big drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, here's a word.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to hear about words.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to tell you about my drams.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ibophobia.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fear of palindromes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: A dog, a plan, a connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are so random.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, is the word itself a palindrome?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, what the hell are you just spouting off random words for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we playing Balderdash tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was I not aware?
[SPEAKER_02]: And so is Deleveled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deleveled is a palindrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I love the chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Always present.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fourth guest on our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat with us live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Alpha Cananogram starts us off tonight reminding us of another palindrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, also, boob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, ibophobia is an irrational fear of palindromes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look, I gotta tell about my dramas Okay, dramas And I just mentioned this to you guys before the show started But you haven't really heard all the details yet So, okay, here's what's going on So you know how everybody's all up in arms Like, oh my gosh, PlayStation 3 Our information all got stolen Sony's in deep shit And needs to give us all Years of credit protection And all this stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet we haven't really heard of any cases of people actually getting their information stolen On the PlayStation 3, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well I didn't have information on the PlayStation 3 stolen, but I had $125 charged on my Xbox Live account last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bleh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So while everything... And by the way, I'm not the first person to have that happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's happened to one of my friends who hasn't even really played Xbox in like a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's happened to another guy I know on Twitter who I know well from seeing it like E3 and he's a listener of the show and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to say I've solved one other case on Facebook as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not an isolated thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Folks are having their Xbox Live accounts hacked.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So I wanted to sign on and play it today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it last night for a little bit and I wanted to play it today before the show so I could give you more thoughts on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I tried to sign into my account on Xbox Live, it told me that the profile information was corrupt and needed to be resynced or it needed to be redownloaded from Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically the same pop-up you get if you ever have played on somebody else's Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you have to download your data to be able to play on that other person's Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that told me my information had been downloaded to another Xbox, except for the fact that I had just played Shadow Planet last night, and I hadn't played on any other Xboxes since then, I think I would know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only Xbox I really used to do that with was Alan's when I used to drive when he lived in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would go down there, transfer my info for the weekend, then come home, transfer it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hadn't done that in months, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that told me something was wrong, and instantly the first thing that came to my mind was, wait a minute, I saw Justin tweet about this like two days ago, his information got hacked, I'm gonna go check my bank account right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what made me think to look, sure enough, I look at my bank account, there's two charges on it, one for $79.99, one for $49.99, both from Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I go into my Xbox Live account and somebody had bought a gold pack, premium pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what game it was for because by the time I saw that I was already on the phone with Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: The good news was I was able to get right through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have to wait on hold for a half hour or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talked to a lady there who was fairly helpful but one thing that struck me as kind of odd that she told me was that, oh yeah, I got hit for $350 too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so a fifth person who works for Microsoft also got hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: and we're all mad at Sony, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I understand why we're mad at Sony, but something tells me we need to be a little irritated with Microsoft right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either somehow information got compromised or there's something out there siphoning our information and they are currently getting all of our passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: So my advice to you, you need to stop what you're doing right now and go change your password on Xbox.com because if you haven't, you're at risk for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So don't come crying to me when they take $125 from you because it's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to suck for them because I don't have $125.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a lot of folks that are saying, I'm going to a chatroom, chat.orangeandre.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sickman says, I prefer buying things with cash and this is why.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says, Sky, this is why I use the Xbox Live cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never put a credit card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's nice to do in retrospect, but let's face it, I didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft doesn't exactly make it easy either to do things that way, especially once they have your credit card from an Xbox Live account that I had set up for gold many years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've only had one card on the Xbox account, and it's been expired now for four years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to take it off, I think you have to call to get it removed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: They wouldn't be able to use it anyway because it's expired.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've never renewed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something's coming for Microsoft because I'm telling you this is happening more and more and it's not going to stop with just me and the people I've spoke about unless miraculously we've convinced the entire internet to change their passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to keep happening and I kind of think Microsoft needs to speak up a little bit about what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: If nothing else, they should be putting out some bulletins about security alerts because this is just more work for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to tell you this, by the way, as well, which is really important, is that the whole process for them to investigate is going to take 21 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not going to see that money back for 21 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, luckily, I'm gainfully employed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a savings account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can cover the loss of that money for 21 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't affect me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know we have a lot of college kids that listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, I don't even have $125 for them to steal.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just warning you, do something about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have thought about calling the bank but I thought at the end of the day ironically enough my card expires next month so I was kind of thinking like you know why go through all that hassle when I'm going to be getting a new card anyway and it's just kind of like if you start flagging all the Microsoft transactions as suspect then that's probably going to give me more headache in the future
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to go through anyway, and you're going to have to deal with overdraft charges on top of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, the good thing is most banks have a protection thing, and, you know, it's at least there's a way to have it investigated.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just the whole thing is frustrating.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just, you know, once again, knowing that someone has stolen my information is kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a crappy feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no other way to explain it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reason why I say once again, I had my Warcraft account hacked about...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, it kind of ruined WoW for me for a little while.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I came back to WoW, I rolled a new character.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't touched that character since that whole incident three some odd years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, learn from my mistake, I guess, although I don't think I made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, with Warcraft, I'm pretty internet savvy and I don't log into a lot of suspicious stuff, but my ex was not internet savvy and I did play WoW on his computer, so I think I know how I got compromised there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this, I'm having a really hard time figuring it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many other systems have you at all played on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Alan's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe one of Loki's systems years ago, but that would be it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, it would just be Alan's.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems to me that it's a breach from within Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or an old Xbox of mine that I would have given to Loki, but we wiped... No, because I had the old hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't have the information because I have the old hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have any hard drive zeros anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the systems I have, like I said, I don't have the hard drives.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it seems to me that it's something from internal...
[SPEAKER_06]: And once again, it wouldn't matter anyways, even if your profile's on there, unless I knew your password, it wouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean, in that case, all you would really need to know is the email address that you used for your account and the password, basically the live.com login details, and then you recover your profile that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bummer, but yeah, that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just kind of a heads up warning to folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, now I'm out that money, but luckily I have money in savings.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to transfer over to cover it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not too big of a deal for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thankfully, I have a savings, but I just don't want to see it happen to many more people because it's a shitty feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kind of want to know how it happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, somebody's trying to steal money from me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to kick their ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want to know right now, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's not just me, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are probably seeing it on your Facebooks too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, if you do a search on Google for hacked Xbox Live account and search for the past week, there's plenty of links for people saying, hey, my account's been hacked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby just sent me a private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to say who it was, but he knows somebody else that got hit for $100.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, good gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not isolating, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I'm bringing it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've all been panicking about Sony, Sony, Sony, Sony, but nothing ended up happening with that data.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not to say nothing ever will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't sit on your laurels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure everything's been changed and your passwords are up to date there, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm just saying, if you thought Microsoft was better, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen up, fanboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got $125 stolen from my Xbox account today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft is no better than Sony, I'm here to tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's what I wanted to just kick off tonight's show with, a lovely little warning that no company is immune from all of this data theft going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's money somewhere to steal, somebody is going to try to steal it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't matter what company it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: on that note let's talk about your gaming week and the types of video games you've been playing this week I won't be able to play my by the way I can't sign into my account for 21 days they've suspended my account during the investigation which will take three weeks they say I can play offline stuff and what have you but most of the stuff I play is Xbox Live Arcade and I don't want my achievements to get screwed up so I basically won't be playing Xbox for the next three weeks so if you see me on in the next three weeks you might want to drop me an email because it's not me I won't be playing for the next three weeks PlayStation 3 here I come woo
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: You should come over here and play Super Metroid Funny enough, I've been playing a Metroid very much like game this week, but I'll get to that in a minute DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, and stupid freaking Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking bitizens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ungrateful wretches.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just a few things on Steam here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, nothing major.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just sort of, meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Rebecca Black is level 70.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun, fun, fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, gang fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now who plays nothing but WoW?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very interesting how things have changed in a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a look at some of these comments that are coming in from chat room about the hacking going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xenacor in our chat room says, Remember, if Microsoft locks down your account, your games for Windows stuff will also be locked down, so check your Xbox Live now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't play Dawn of War 2 offline because it requires a login.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thankfully, I don't use Games for Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nor does anyone else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have used Game Room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about the extent of it on Games for Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Game Room games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You won't be able to download any more Game Room games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those releases that you're missing out on.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xenocore saying Dawn of War 2 is tied into that, and I'm sure there's other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we have a story on it tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All these companies want to tie you into their online service, so if you're a fan of one of these games, you kind of get screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to other comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackwolf clarifies he got hit while he was playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only must have missed it by a couple hours because I was on last night and then I noticed it this morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sickman in our chatroom says, the only mistake you made, Sky, was buying Microsoft products.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same mistake a lot of us have made.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm sorry, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to play Shadow Planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually probably the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little bit fanboyish, but, you know, obviously there's some haters out there on Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, PlayStation people can hate on Microsoft about network security.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, you can't say shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Sony fanboys can't point and laugh at what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't, but I'll...
[SPEAKER_04]: My point to telling this story was Microsoft fans can't point and laugh at Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are not allowed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm here to tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because money was actually stolen in this case, you are not allowed to point and laugh at what's going on with Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're not allowed to tell people that they can't, you know, this is what you get for supporting Sony or whatever bullshit I read on Twitter during that whole stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ziba in chat says, I don't have any info on my Xbox account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a silver account.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I said, my card is up in September, and I'm definitely having thoughts to keeping a card online now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I might have learned my lesson.
[SPEAKER_04]: IDK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if your card auto-renews, just be aware there's a whole lawsuit we'll get into probably later on about...
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll still try to charge it, and then when you put a new card on there, they'll charge it twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_04]: My card expires before Xbox Live does, so it won't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty good actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, I played it what I call the abridged version, which is I cheated the hell out of it and I finished the game completely.
[SPEAKER_06]: I literally have built as much of the Tiny Tower as I possibly can.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have all the shops.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of the different everything, all maxed out, all the achievements.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have as many citizens as you can possibly fit in the building.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I can do now is build a bunch of empty floors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're a cheater.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care because you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game made my brain melt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, that's the feeling I got from playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, oh, I'm so glad to be done with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think that they should be smart enough to know, hey, we're out of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we should, I don't know, restock it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then where's the game, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: What would the game be?
[SPEAKER_04]: You see, your problem with Tiny Tower is that it's not Tiny Tower Sniper.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's your problem with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: was a game dev story.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby says that Tiny Tower has a bug right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, if you have it open, you're only earning half the cash.
[SPEAKER_04]: The newest version botched something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm earning a lot of cash.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, I can't get any cash.
[SPEAKER_04]: You robbed the tiny bank and you took all their money.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more like he printed his own money with his tiny printing press.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I've gotten some FUs on Google and Twitter for mentioning Tiny Tower on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU for getting me into Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen that multiple times this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried playing Jukebeat on my iPod and it seems like a simple idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just tap the squares as they light up.
[SPEAKER_06]: For some reason, the difficulty is way too high.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming it's because I have an iPod and it's really small.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can tweak it so that the touch area is really big, so you can actually touch in the middle between two squares and it'll tap both of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even still, after doing that, I still keep failing a level 2 song.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sorry, if it's that hard, then it's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would I want to buy more songs for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm saying the game that the In The Groove people made is better than the game that Konami made.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe I'm saying that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reason why it's true is because I shouldn't be failing a level 2 song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is like if you're going to DDR, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Loki, you just suck at jukebeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I must.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm reading the comments from the internet right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just... I'm imagining these guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you just suck at jukebeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just...
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to try more.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing about Jukebeat that's irritating is that when that little thing comes up, you have less than a second to hit it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have no time to react.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're playing that first song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Literally, it's lighting up.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little passage in the Frogger song that goes... So you have to be able to hit it, hit it, hit it, hit it, hit it, hit it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like playing whack-a-mole at hyperspeed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's no real indication of what's going to be next other than it just moving really fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If maybe U-Beat is a little bit better in the arcades, I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if this is exactly what it is in the arcades, I'm not too excited about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of cool that they put something else out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Mac confirms in chat, Juby, which is its name over in Japan, on the iPad is a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I could see where on the iPad my fat finger isn't getting in the way so I can actually see all the things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can lay it on a table and probably play it easier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: All Universal is means it has both versions in one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can still have different versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Tiny Tower is Universal too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but still, then why is it played so terrible?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I didn't have this problem with ReRave.
[SPEAKER_04]: ReRave, it was easy enough for me to hit everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think re-rave just makes sense, and this game doesn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of where I'm at with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think re-rave was just more interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: The targets are a lot bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: They come up with more advanced notice.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually on the beat, and you can tell, like, oh, a red one means it's on the downbeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: A blue one means it's on the upbeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it just makes more sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like stuff that they used to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, fuck, there's notes everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like stuff that they used to do in DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: it's like Konami you forget that you released music games in the past and what you did to make you know make those see that's what I don't understand this is a company that understands accessibility with their DDR games a little too much accessibility if you ask me but yet for some reason a casual gaming platform as you would normally view it they made this game so fucking difficult that most people would be just like whatever and they're just gonna get they'll delete it because it's free
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that Contra song.
[SPEAKER_04]: That Contra song is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the rest of the songs are terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like Frogger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frogger needs to die.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to stop putting out new Frogger games.
[SPEAKER_06]: The 3DS Frogger, eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't understand the point for the 3DS Frogger, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least they're doing something slightly different with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frogger, not really a game I know for its music.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I don't believe there was any music in Frogger.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I got to read some comments from chat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're backing up on comments here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going back to the hacking stuff, Sickman wanted to clarify an earlier comment and says, Sky, you completely misunderstood me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I meant they make shitty hardware.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The hardware Xbox makes, I mean, considering the whole Red Rings of Death and all the other crap they've had to deal with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Microsoft does kind of make shitty hardware, but my problem wasn't a hardware issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other things I played this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: VVVVVV because I got the Humble Indie Bundle and yeah, it's very difficult and I'm kind of frustrated I'm at this one level in the game where you have to escort this guy across the screen and it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just annoying the controls because it's very floaty, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um.
[SPEAKER_06]: so but hey you get unlimited lives it's just sometimes it's annoying but I think I'm almost finished with the game I have like I think two more people to rescue and that's it
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but there might be a whole little twist coming up or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how Castlevania had the upside-down castle?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then other than that, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played more Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_06]: I downloaded the two weapons packs for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still haven't gotten a chance to actually try the weapons, but I've downloaded them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also more Grand Theft Auto, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I do have in Singingly Twisted Child Planet but still haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really wanting to play it because the reviews have been great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's all I've played alright I'll talk about my gaming week besides what I mentioned at the top of the show well I have mentioned I played insanely twisted Shadow Planet which I was enjoying it's basically Metroid with kind of like Limbo's graphics in a way I don't know how else to explain it I really like it I downloaded the demo and the minute I realized I'm like oh this is like fucking Metroid except it's a spaceship that you control so it's more of a you don't just move left and right and jump you fly anywhere you want
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: But it doesn't exactly hand you the what to do on a silver platter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very abstract in some ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it doesn't really take away from the experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was really enjoying the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm kind of pissed I'm not going to be able to play it for three more weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I was on a roll and I kind of wanted to beat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I only got about maybe a third of the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it said I was like 30% complete or 33% complete.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eh, won't be able to do that now for three weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thanks, hackers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you recover your profile to your system?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were unable to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, well, they said I could play offline, but I just, I don't know, I'm at a point where I just don't want to because I don't want my achievements to get screwed up and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it will get screwed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, if you recovered your profile to your system, you could play it and it wouldn't matter because it would sync back up when you're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you haven't, then yes, all those achievements would go bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, I didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I'm kind of stuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got some stuff on PlayStation 3 I want to play, but just irritating.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's always WoW, right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a lot of ratings to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can play some L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not touched L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire yet, and I have your copy on PS3, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally missing it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do need to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The silver lining in my crap story is there are PS3 games I need to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually got back my games that I've been loaning out to people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of them I completely forgot that I've been loaning out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my 3D Dot Game Heroes back in Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Portal 2 on every goddamn system now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to go back and finish co-op in Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's another thing I need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've got plenty to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And randomly, okay, so insane Twisted Shadow Planet.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like Metroid, you need to be downloading the demo right now after you change your Xbox Live password.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go check it out because, or the Castlevania, Metroidvania, any of those types of games, you will like this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got really pretty sharp graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like playing a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, I think you would really like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really need to make it a point to check it out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan, change your password!
[SPEAKER_04]: At least get the demo
[SPEAKER_04]: by the way I forgot so go ahead I randomly had a I want to play Civilization 5 and when you want to play Civilization 5 that turns into a 5 minute thought that goes on for like 4 hours because you can't just like stop playing Civilization 5 so I played an entire campaign over the weekend you were still playing when I went to bed I was playing as the Spanish and I played from start to finish
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, I was playing on dopey easy level because I'm really not good at civilization, but I beat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did a cultural victory and I got the no one expects the Spanish Inquisition achievement.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I'm playing another.
[SPEAKER_04]: What better way?
[SPEAKER_04]: I kicked it up a difficulty level and now I'm playing as...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my all-time favorite PC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's no secret that I adore Civ 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's one of the best in the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's certainly better than 2 or 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4 was pretty good too, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I love 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was playing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on the PlayStation 3, Extover had a random gaming night last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a couple of us went over there and played...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hardcore Uprising Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melee
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawls on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can never remember which one's which.
[SPEAKER_04]: We played the Wii one for a little while, and then we played one other game that I'm totally forgetting right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we played Katamari Forever on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, random, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I brought a stack of games over, and that's what we chose to play, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: that was my game night that's pretty much my gaming week lots I've been pretty busy and then of course wow wow wow lots of wow stuff but oh yeah I have the other show for that someone's gonna teach me how to tank for a fee I'm just kidding
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll pay you in Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackwolf in our chatroom says, I love playing Dopey on Dopey Easy level in Civ 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the way to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best way to play Civ 5, especially if you're not very good at the strategical types of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for how was our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope you guys had a good gaming week too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly, some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're still having shows over the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are going to do a show when I'm not here, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you're going to do it anyway?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not doing it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you were.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm babysitting.
[SPEAKER_04]: On a Sunday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sunday?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not a human baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the kitty babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: The kitty babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on the 29th and 31st, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still watching the kitty babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no show the 28th then?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, a show or yes, no show?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No show.
[SPEAKER_04]: No show on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can plan accordingly.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Visit us on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be taking some of your tweets at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and our Tumblr now, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orangelaunchradio.tumblr.com All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki just beat one of the hard parts of BBB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I fucking hate that stupid mission.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hated that, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's put this on pause for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you got to put it on pause because you got to start us off with some news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on in the gaming world tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's start talking about the Steam trading beta that they're going to have, which is kind of cool in case if you're buying some packs and you get a bunch of extra games or stuff gifted to you that you may already have and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, what this is going to allow you to do is trade different items for, I guess...
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't really say yet, but like, for example, you can trade, I don't know why you would do this, trade like games for hacks in Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, right now the service only supports trading of items, I guess, in Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're going to be supporting other things soon, I guess, Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think maybe they're talking a little bit more of just actually like in-game items right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But eventually you'll be able to trade for games and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they're going to be allowing you to trade for games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, if you think about it, I mean, that's pretty cool that they're heading in that direction anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you think about it, you can swap games with people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, essentially.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's still in its early, early stages, obviously, so of course it's kind of restricted to Valve products.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess it's not just Valve products you can trade, but I guess the stuff that you can trade for right now is really only Valve, at least with the microtransaction type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's still very vague to me, like how this all works, because I don't really have any extra copies of games to trade right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I'd known this when I bought Terraria.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't have given a copy to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have traded it away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Minecraft Aria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had four copies of that game and I literally gave a copy to somebody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, I think he'll like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't even know if he's played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I could have traded that for a hat.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of go, eh, I don't really need a hat in Team Fortress 2 because I don't really play that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then I go, huh, if 2K bought into this, I could buy the Korean Civilization expansion for Civ 5 and that I would enjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's amazing how this buy-sell-trade stuff works and how people like it and how it promotes the sales of new items.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee, I wish publishers would have thought of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we're going to get into the topic again, of course, of how they're trying to discourage buy-sell trade stuff with more of the online codes and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't understand that they're just... I think we have a game that's doing something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something different than an online pass.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they don't understand that they're only hurting themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, by discouraging buy-sell... First off...
[SPEAKER_06]: The argument that the developers don't get money for these games if people are buying used copies is a bunch of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, for one, the developers get money when the game is sold from the publisher, not bought in the store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect example, Catherine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So, say for example, your average gamer, they can't afford new games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so they're buying used games, they're selling their used games, trading them into a GameStop or wherever to get credit towards a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think, not everybody but I think there's going to be some people that are like oh I could buy the multi-pack for just a few dollars more and I guess I could maybe trade somebody that for a DLC and get like a deal there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's opening up this whole new flea market style thing for games it's really interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you purchasing something on Steam right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being nosy.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you buying?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oddworld Abe's Odyssey is $1.24.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: A whole dollar?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Oddworld.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Oddworld's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So looking at our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Infanel in our chat room says, buy games during the special deals at 75% off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trade later when the price goes back to normal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakman in chat says, what kind of in-game items does Portal 2 have?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing yet, but that's... Well, yeah, there are hats, but aren't they supposed to be getting some other stuff soon?
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, where the hell is that download content that we were promised back in June?
[SPEAKER_06]: IDK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that going to come out before or after Half-Life 2 Episode 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: After?
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's assuming it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you see people protesting outside of Valve for Half-Life 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know one of the guys that was doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was apparently an old guildie of mine from Valve.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they were just having fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad they're having fun because you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gabe isn't starving for sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's definitely not starving at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, so there's no reason to think that they're in a hurry to make Half-Life 2 Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got the sense that it was just something fun to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll do whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they'll work on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on, talking about other games and so forth, PC games specifically, Battlefield 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what's interesting is one of the ways a lot of people got hooked on Steam was that if you wanted to play certain Valve games, you kind of had to install Steam, and then everybody saw the deals that came with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course a bunch of other publishers got on board, and we just talked earlier, there was a chatroom comment about some games that require game for Windows to power them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: EA is soon going to be requiring Origin for Battlefield 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, if you want to play the PC version of Battlefield 3, you will have to register for EA's Origin service.
[SPEAKER_04]: This came from the DICE community manager, Daniel Matros.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was all confirmed via Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess somebody had put it out there if this was going to be a requirement, and it was confirmed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So retail, digital, doesn't matter where you buy it, you will have to sign up for Origin, which if I'm not mistaken, EA's whole online thing kind of all shifted to Origin anyway, so it doesn't totally surprise me, but I don't know, it's just like, I really don't want...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's because you want to try to sell exclusively on Origin.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really the deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you want to make Valve out to be the bad guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, because their complaint is that Valve wants to control the patching.
[SPEAKER_04]: And EA doesn't want that.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA wants to control the patching.
[SPEAKER_04]: To really make a long story short is ultimately what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't want to have to push all their patches through Valve and get approval from Valve.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want to be able to do it themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it blows down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but see, that doesn't make any sense until we know how hard the approval process is for patching.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they're like, here's the patch, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just an excuse is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom in the comments, Kaijudo says, I won't be playing Battlefield 3 on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether says, fuck Battlefield 3, I'll play Battlefield 2 instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going back a little bit further, talking about Half-Life and all that, Tigerclaw says, the Source engine throughout the years has been getting massive upgrades with every new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take Portal 2 for example, it runs on the Source engine and the graphics are better than before.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw also points out to the folks saying, fuck Battlefield 3 on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: A game like that was strictly made for PC in mind, then portaled to the consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, you know, this whole requirement for Origin and stuff, that's just right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, look at, like, Portal 2 and stuff, or even on the other, like, Valve products.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have to be connected to Steam nor to play those on your PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, hackers will fix the problem, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll come and save the day and that'll be the end of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of like Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their actions have shown that they're really trying to be on the pulse of what gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not what executives want for gamers, but what gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the sales have been really kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: This whole trading thing, although it's a little weird, I like that they're even fucking going there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I do not expect Origin or Games for Windows to be following this, what Valve's trying to do here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's kind of part of the reason I'm a little loyal to Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've shown, they've really tried to push what they're trying to do for privacy and security and to make sure all that stuff's locked down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their DRM is restrictive enough without being too restrictive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't want to come off sounding like a fanboy, but I feel like Steam's proven themselves where others have not.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's basically what it boils down to, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Prove to me you want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're starting to sound like what's her name in Portal 2, the secretary.
[SPEAKER_01]: Burn his house down.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, let's move on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Away from the PCs for a little bit, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some Wii stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_02]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_02]: and it has the microphone, speaker, and camera functions that are also included.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a neat little diagram of someone holding a Wiimote over it and using it as a, like playing golf with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So using it to sense where the Wiimote is in terms of the floor, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're also saying that it does have different IR modules and likely it's going to also include connectivity with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it also says it's going to be about as strong as the PS3 and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Magnetometer
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't want to do the Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's usually some type of navigation software for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they have an attachment for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an extra accessory.
[SPEAKER_02]: I meant this is going to be for the Vita, but it's already in the move.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's all just going to be integrated into their whole immersive environment type of thing I really want to know what Nintendo's online thing is going to be I almost think it's going to be something like a handheld Kinect
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll have this similar functionality, except it's going to use it in conjunction with the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think their online's going to be tur-arable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you say turd-arable?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you were going to say terraria, and I was like, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to Minecraft your way on Nintendo Switch?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was making it seem like I was going to say terrific.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, mid-word, I changed it to terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Turdrific.
[SPEAKER_06]: Therefore, being funny, adding humor to the word.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like turdrific.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to use turdrific from now on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Loki, yet another failure of your humor on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I considered excess myself, so... Failure, I do not see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like the 3DS, it is a very successful product.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not failing at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Horse turds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like turdrific.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll use that in a sentence three times today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: More gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: PS3's got another firmware.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hurrah!
3.7.
[SPEAKER_06]: It brings fun stuff as auto cloud saves and trophy syncing as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, in order to actually access any of these features, you have to be a PlayStation Plus member.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, some of the stuff that they were hinting at before when they were talking a little bit about PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they've done some rearranging of their TV and video services.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I'll be added to the cross-media bar now.
[SPEAKER_06]: and a new category will house online services like Hulu and Netflix.
[SPEAKER_06]: So kind of tweaking some arrangement around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving your stuff all around.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course the undocumented features are they're signing stuff with new codes now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or new keys, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to prevent all the hacking and cracking behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said trying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that is the key word, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure somebody found a way around it in 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they already have.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I downloaded the firmware and I didn't really notice anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I always expect maybe my games will suddenly be more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Patches don't ever really seem to have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Gamefly, you've probably heard of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a pretty popular Netflix-y type of service for games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this time, they're kind of going further in that direction of Netflix, where soon you'll be able to play the games on demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a PC thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's unlimited PC play service.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they took over direct-to-drive some time ago, and this seems to be the next step of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamefly says that they are talking to all publishers about participating several have been signed but we're not announcing at this time in the unlimited PC play portion for Gamefly subscribers we expect to have over 100 titles available for the beta launch but we'll be adding to the list constantly and should have hundreds at the time of our holiday launch so
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess also some folks are asking well then if they're going to have the PC thing only will there be a plan for Gamefly that is only PC kind of like how there's a Netflix streaming only plan Sean Spector the co-founder of Gamefly said in response to that we currently have no plans to offer a digital only subscription as we believe the real value to gamers and our members is our unique combination of console and digital PC game offerings so in other words no the plans aren't going to be any cheaper so
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of sounds like what GameTap used to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember GameTap?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're still around, but they suck now.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they first came out, it was an interesting concept.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, then they got sold and not so great anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess it's kind of neat that somebody's trying to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed this little demo screenshot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if this was just mocked up by somebody, but it has games like DC Universe and so forth in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because they bought Direct Drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and that was some of the games that were on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it'd be kind of cool if some of the games are playable infinitely, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have my hopes up that it'll be much more than a lot of the Flash games or really old games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of what GameTap had, which isn't necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, just because a game is old doesn't mean it's bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing I really liked about GameTap was that it had all the old-ass King's Quest games and all the old Zort games and all of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how about some news for the UK Nintendo 3DS price cut?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is basically just the overall game revealed recently that they have a trade-in deal where if you trade in a DSi XL, you can get a 3DS for 49.99 or with Zelda Ocarina of Time for 59.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's actually a pretty decent deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the regular price of that is $159.99 bundled with a Zelda Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, this is in British pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you trade in a DSi, you will get it for $89.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So looking at the vendors overall, this is what you're looking for for the different prices.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not all of them are going to price match, but here's what we have.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Tesco, it's 115 pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Morrison's, 120.
[SPEAKER_02]: Asda, 134.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sainsbury's, 140 pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Online, for Amazon it's $115, Shop 2 is $135, GameStop $135, GamePlay $135, and Play $140.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then High Street and online it says Toys R Us is $135, Curry's is $140, Argos is $150, Game is $150, while online it's $140, and HMV is $150 and includes a free game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's $140 online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to kind of piggyback on that a little bit, if you want to know what's going on here in the U.S., Target honestly started a system, which I thought was weird, because I didn't really think of Target as buying your old systems, but apparently Target, I guess it was just this past weekend, so you might have already missed it, so sorry about that, but I guess Target was accepting DS trade-ins as credit towards a 3DS, an XL was worth $100, a DSi was worth $75, so I guess...
[SPEAKER_04]: My target doesn't sell used games or any that I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there other targets out there that are in the used game market now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen it unless they have a deal with another used game vendor.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they sell them back to a vendor that sells those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep your eye out on places like Target and so forth here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: because there will probably be other details like that soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyhow, speaking of things to do at the game store, there's some release dates we gotta go over around the world, and we'll start off with the US release dates, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot this week, of course, because this month's... That's been the theme of the past month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been slow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least there are some actual things coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting off with No More Heroes Heroes Paradise on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually getting a budget price to it, which is kind of cool, because it was full price at one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: With move support as well, so you...
[SPEAKER_06]: Age of Empires Online on PC
[SPEAKER_06]: Puzzler World 2 for Nintendo DS Emily the Strange Strangerous on the Nintendo DS and yeah maybe this is the problem with the Wii right here
[SPEAKER_06]: Jerry Rice and Nidus, Dog Football for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the best part of the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dog Football.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only good part of the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only thing worth watching is the Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could give two shits about the regular football game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Kitty Cat Halftime?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Kitty Cat Halftime is what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dog Football on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an amazing release on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why you gotta be rough on the releases?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget to tip your waitress, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, wait, I did see one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw one, so I guess it is slowly coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, moving on to the Japanese releases and what's coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360, Dirt 3 comes out on the 25th on the Xbox 360, and that's pretty much the only release you have to look forward to over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PlayStation 3, on the 18th, there is Chojigan Game Neptune.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the heck is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from Idea Factory.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is the evil witch Magikon is back and GameGalio World falls into chaos.
[SPEAKER_04]: The shops ran out of business, the creators are starving, and most of the children are worshipping Magikon as a goddess.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a collaboration between Gust, Nippon Ichi, 5BP, KI Concept, Idea Factory, and Compile Heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: on the Wii, but on the PSP, Amnesia, I do not believe that is the same Amnesia that scares the shit out of people on the PC here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a scary-ass game on the PC called Amnesia that's in Steam and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the same game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Artsy Anime type of game that's available on the PSP and there's lots of kissing like look they're making out these two are gonna make out and he's probably dreaming about somebody making out with him like there's just lots of kissy kissy in this game so
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an adventure game on the PSP if you like kissy kissy stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Growlancer 4 Over Reloaded also comes out on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, there's really just not a lot to get excited about right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're already on the fourth one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow That's it for Japanese releases How about UK?
[SPEAKER_02]: A few On the 17th we have Cubix HD From Dust for PC From Ubisoft Toy Soldier Civil War And on the 19th we have Xenoblade Chronicles For Wii That's it Xenoblade Chronicles might be of interest to some people A few, maybe
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't be surprised if some of the Operation Rainfall people are like, okay, this week you have to buy a Wii system from the UK and buy Xenoblade just to show that we want it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, more news.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple more news stories for you guys in the classic game of the week coming up in just a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, a little more news about THQ.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked last week how they weren't too happy about...
[SPEAKER_06]: THQ is not going to actively pursue development of the MX vs ATV franchise
[SPEAKER_06]: and they were saying their latest game was kind of an experiment although it was a failed experiment and unfortunately releasing the title at a budget price didn't spur the extra sales they were hoping to make up on the back end with DLC and it was kind of not a good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to continue on with that franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they've let go of 200 people.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're shifting their development focus away from kids and licensed titles.
[SPEAKER_06]: which I gotta admit, other than the WWE games and the occasional Saints Row and stuff like that, they do a lot of fucking kids games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You probably won't see the shift away from it this holiday because they have a lot of fucking kids games coming out other than Saints Row and WWE.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of U-Draw stuff, lots of the Marvel Super Heroes Squad, Chibi Marvel stuff, and
[SPEAKER_06]: and Spongebob and all the Nicktoons stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's good that they're getting away from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, imagine that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All those little shuffleware games didn't do so well at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to, I guess I was joking about this earlier, but we do have a story about the whole Xenoblade and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is coming out, of course, in Europe very soon, as DarkSakura just said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reggie Fils-Aim made a comment to IGN this week about Xenoblade Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, we will be watching very closely what happens in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certainly if there are business opportunities and positive consumer uptake from some of those titles, that will be great data for us to consider as we look at what to do with these titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, if that's not a run-around-the-bush answer, if I've ever heard one, that's a, I'm not fucking telling you that the game is confirmed for here, I'm just gonna bullshit you with some of, that was the biggest pound of bullshit I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something smells.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Shermie's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, like, it's the nicest possible way he can say, please buy the game in Europe, but it doesn't mean we're gonna put it out here.
[SPEAKER_06]: That pile of bullshit was like 400 Keurig.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Operation Rainfall.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't stop Operation Rainfall.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to take no for an answer, not even for Reggie Fils-Aim, who didn't really say no, but he didn't really say yes either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Operation Rainfall is starting Phase 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kicking it up a notch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phase 2, we're stepping it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get these fucking games out here.
[SPEAKER_06]: So would this be considered Plan B?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, this is Plan B. So here's Plan B. It's going to coincide with the August 19th launch of Xenoblade Chronicles in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: To all residents in the regions of Europe and Oceania, says the organizers of Operation Rainfall, we encourage you to preorder and purchase it at your earliest convenience.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the Americas, we encourage you to promote awareness of these titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good sales abroad will be a strong indicator for the title making it to American shores.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, tell people in Europe to go buy the fucking game and buy it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't buy it used, buy it new so they get the sales, you know, try to sell a lot of copies of that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And send us a copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, yeah, hey, we'll take that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wanted, oh wait, we couldn't play it on anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a, do you have a, oh wait, you have a region free Wii, don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're going to be sending a rally of letters to Nintendo of America.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're supposed to mail them from August 13th to August 17th so that they all get there about the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: This kind of reminds me of when everybody sent the peanuts to CBS to try and save Jericho.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're just sending letters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to send something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to not just send a letter.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to send something with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of peanuts, what's something that they could send for Xenoblade?
[SPEAKER_04]: Switchblades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boxcutters.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good lord.
[SPEAKER_06]: They will look at you at the post office funny if you do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send them hand-drawn pictures of knives.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What could you send?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to turn that over to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would remind somebody of Xenoblade or I guess you could say The Last Story or Pandora's Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there like some other factor?
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a whole bunch of copies of Xenogears.
[SPEAKER_02]: from PlayStation the best?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about like letter X's?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like they should cut out the letter X from all their magazines and put them in an envelope so that when they open it up, just X's fly everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the X means Xenoblade.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about bees?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the bees would fly everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little more daring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to open the rest of those letters.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all buzzing over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought it was the one, but I'm pretty sure there's bees in all of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: This package is buzzing and it's angry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make it stop, Reggie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine, send them bees.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure bees wouldn't survive the trip, though, but you could try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put holes in the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we're sending in a box?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can fit a lot of bees in a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't send them bees!
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to just beat the shit out of a water right now, buy Nintendo stock and then complain as an investor.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you really want to kick Nintendo in the balls right now, become an investor of Nintendo stock and then say, as an investor, I feel that you need to bring Xenoblade out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And from what I hear, the stock prices keep dropping.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be cheap real soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now the chatroom has a great suggestion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send them porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because when you think X, it's XXX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send them porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send them... What is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat says, each one of these stings is how you make us feel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, because you know I'm thinking of that GIF that's out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: The animated GIF file of Oprah opening the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, Bees!
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on the Conan show.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw, find me that gif.
[SPEAKER_04]: Post it in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's even better.
[SPEAKER_06]: You send it like the Riddler.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how the Riddler would send you little boxes with question marks on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: But they have a box with a question mark on it in the Mario universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: It fits, and you fit that with the bees.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you can have the treasure chest from Zelda, so when they open it, it's all, do-do-do-do, bees!
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the note says, each of these stings is how you make us feel.
[SPEAKER_06]: or Bees in a Jar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like, you know, Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all... I'm really going with the bees here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the bees are a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, they keep sending bees!
[SPEAKER_05]: Throw them in the fountain and see if you get super bees.
[SPEAKER_06]: Super bees.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's more to this story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up about the bees already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: On August 19th, there's one more big thing that Operation Rainfall is going to be doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: As a show of an interest in RPGs,
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody on August 19th should purchase Final Fantasy on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: but if you already have it you should gift the money to somebody else or donate to Child's Play which I'm not going to make fun of that idea I think donating to Child's Play is always a good idea I'm not quite sure how that gets the point across that you want Xenoblade but okay whatever gets you to donate to a good charity that's fine as far as buying Final Fantasy on the virtual console I think your money might just be better spent giving the money to Child's Play in the name of bringing Xenoblade to the Wii
[SPEAKER_04]: How is buying Final Fantasy on Virtual Console and increasing Square Enix's coffers going to prove to Reggie that we want Xenoblade?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, can you help explain this to me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm not understanding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well... They have blades in both of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Square Enix made Xenogears...
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a terrible idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because once again, this is the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's lots of people on forums, lots of people on forums that are complaining that Xenoblade is not coming to the United States.
[SPEAKER_06]: But lots of people on forums also said, MadWorld is a fucking awesome game and I'm going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: People on forums, you know what your numbers are, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not 100,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not maybe even 10,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: And most people that post on forums that say they're going to buy it don't really buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They end up pirating it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're maybe a few thousand people that want this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sorry, a game that only sells a few thousand copies is a failure.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: it's just not gonna happen you know what just save your money save your time wait for E3 next year and maybe they'll announce it but in the meantime if you really do want to spend like I don't know how much it is for Final Fantasy 7 bucks you can buy a lot of bees for seven dollars I'm telling you I think it's a great idea and you know what hey okay fine if you don't want to send them live bees because that might be a terrorist attack or terror threat or something like that
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how they're all insensitive about that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But bees pollinate!
[SPEAKER_06]: You can send them like a chocolate-covered... They don't sell chocolate-covered bees, I'd imagine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe like... Pictures of bees?
[SPEAKER_06]: Send them Mario with his head cut off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spend that $10 or whatever that you would have spent on Final Fantasy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And donate it to charity and know that your money went to something good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or go buy lunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or go just rent a porno or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking chill the fuck out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you're getting your...
[SPEAKER_06]: All up in arms about like some... One damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, these are the best games on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: The best RPGs.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii is over, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii is done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty much done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's... You're just like trying to get this last good game out before the Wii is done.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's done, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going on to the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_06]: so just get over it better games are out there better games will be coming out there so they didn't bring a hardcore game to the Wii even though they said oh we're catering to everybody just get over it they don't care about you they don't care what you want otherwise you know Earthbound would be out you know Earthbound 3 or Mother 3 or whatever the fuck that is
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya points out, you know, Mario did have a bee power-up in Mario Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_06]: See?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo loves bees.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to end this conversation on a comment that's about as good as this whole effort.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't like bees because they fly around, it might be hard to catch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scorpions also work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm going to end on this comment from our chatroom at chat.org You can get candy covered scorpions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are safe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator says, Nintendo would boil the bees to make BT.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard BT makes for a good buzz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just going to let that joke settle for a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week here on Orange Lounge Radio, DarkSakura dives into the gaming vault and finds... Before we start, Breakman says, so Loki thinks trying to hurt the developers is a better idea than trying to bribe them.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not saying it to the developers, we're saying it to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not trying to hurt them.
[SPEAKER_06]: The developers are far away, safe from the bees.
[SPEAKER_04]: by the way, I believe DarkSakura posted that gif on Tumblr for those that are listening on the podcast I like having the Tumblr so when funny shit comes up on the show we can talk about it on Tumblr remove that thing that cross posts everything to Twitter though I don't think I ever set that up it's doing it see if you can find it classic game of the week yay
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura goes in the classic gaming vault, finds a game she thinks, hey, you kids ought to be playing it this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget the last story.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the only story you fucking need.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Warcraft 3, Reign of Chaos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Addict?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not really, because I don't like real-time strategy games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm trying to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to, so I thought I would bring it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, of course, the third in a row.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first one was Warcraft Orcs and Humans, and the second one was Tides of Darkness, and this one's Reign of Chaos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: The music one that I put up there is actually from the expansion, The Frozen Throne.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh, yeah, it did come out, um, and it had, um, it actually was released on July 3rd, 2002.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's the second sequel to, um, you know, as I said, Warcraft, Orcs, and Humans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, it had an expansion pack called the Frozen Drone that came out on July 1st, 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have four playable races this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Orcs and Humans, um, and you also have Night Elves and Undead.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, uh, it's sort of laid out like StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have other races in the expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get the Draenei and the Naga, who are really elves.
[SPEAKER_02]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, you've got multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play against the computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can even later on mod your levels and do customized levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: The proper storylines basically is if you've done the orc campaign on Warcraft and the human campaigns on Warcraft 2, so that would be Tides of Darkness and Beyond the Dark Portal, then those lead into Warcraft 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it sold 4.5 million units, well shipped I should say, and it sold over a million within a month and it is one of the game beer ones listed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically it's a, you know, like I said, real time strategy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have the stuff called the Black Mask that covers places that you haven't explored but when you explore it goes away.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you move too far away, then you get the fog of war, which makes you can't see what troops are doing and what building construction is going on, but you can still see the terrain.
[SPEAKER_02]: I call that saving space for, you know, rendering, but that's another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have to get your different resources.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need gold, lumber, and food.
[SPEAKER_02]: and um you have to have those to make buildings and then food determines the number of units you can control at any given time so basically the more troops you can feed the more you can have out and play you also have creeps which are controlled by the computer and they guard different areas like gold mines and buildings um you can kill them for gold experience and special items and you have a day night cycle that was also introduced for this game um
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Limitations as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, with this one, you also get something called Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, when you have an enemy unit killed, your hero will gain experience points and can level up as far as 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they also get new spells, kind of gets like an RPG element to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they can boost their units that way, and they'll get ultimate skills!
[SPEAKER_02]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, you've got your different campaign modes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got five campaigns, including the prologue, that introduces the different races.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two orc campaigns, one human, one undead, and one night elf.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have different chapters, which are kind of like your missions.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you do not have briefings, as you did in the earlier games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just sort of comes out in a series of quests.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the story unfolds through cinematics and cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you get your different objectives as you progress through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like how World of Warcraft is doing now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems to me it's exactly a good transition.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go against your friends and other people on Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had different gateways.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had your Azeroth, which was the eastern U.S., Lorydron, which was the west United States, Northrend for Europe, and Kalimdor for Asia.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: You could actually play anonymously with other people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called matchmaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you could have different battles against random people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there were also scores and standings that were marked on the ladder.
[SPEAKER_02]: So as far as the game goes, I'm not going to tell too much of the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I prefer to paraphrase it as Arthas is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: About sums it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arthas decides he's going to get all big and bad and burn a bunch of people to death and then get some sword and give his soul up for his sword and then become the Lich King's bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then he does a whole bunch of awful shit like, you know, killing his dad and killing a bunch of other people and turning Sylvanas into, you know, a banshee and...
[SPEAKER_02]: All kinds of other crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, it's basically Arthas is a bitch, the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: but you also find a few people that went to MIA in earlier games what happened to them and of course for anyone who's playing World of Warcraft now pretty much all these characters that were in this game play into you can find them in World of Warcraft or they've been dead and are affecting the game but it's all built on what went on in this game
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, it has great sound.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could actually, if you got the limited edition, it came with a soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, there are different types of, uh, you know, music for the different, uh, races.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the one that I just, we were just hearing was the Night Elf theme, which is pretty good music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's at the end though, so I'm going to switch to the Undead music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, and like I said, you could also, there was a world editor that you could change different events and change different things.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could download each other's maps, and there were also third-party developers that had different tools that came out, like different spreadsheets and customizing skins, all kinds of different cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically the game, there was this epic bundle that came with the soundtrack, instruction manual, the Art of Warcraft book, and lithographic prints.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you could also get the battle chest, which had Reign of Chaos with the Frozen Throne in box.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the guides from Brady Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was also an exclusive gift set that had a cinematic DVD and a bunch of other crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was also, for anyone who played Warcraft the board game, it actually was based heavily off of Warcraft 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It got a 93.09% at GameRankings.com and basically it's just considered one of the greatest game, I'd say modern games of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is folks, your classic game of the week, Warcraft 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arthas is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Arthas is a bitch and as SalaciousPop says in chat, Arthas is a bitch and Illidan needs to stop listening to Linkin Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's going to do it for Part A here of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got plenty more to come of the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to move into Part B, talk a little bit about Google+, more Nintendo news, and, of course, Mailbag, FUs, tweets, and calls, all when we come back with more of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live, of course, on this Sunday evening, August the 14th of 2011, with the 424th episode of our show, taping live at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You missed a fun Part A that was full of Bs, but we are going to continue on with Part B of our show right now, and we're going to start off with some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game is hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: What game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you're still playing VVVVV over there, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I had to dodge the lies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, so this is interesting, uh, Kojima, of course, during his podcast, they had done, um, a Snatcher Universe radio drama, which was, I guess, entitled Suda51's, uh, Sedature, um, and it's now being offered as a free download, and if you want something a little bit more physical, you can get a CD that'll be sold later on, um, I guess to pay the voice actors, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: and I guess the voice drum also featured a lot of the people that did voices in Metal Gear so that's kind of cool and so yeah check that out and if you're looking for more information on that I believe you can just check out his actual podcast it's www.kjp.kanami.jp and I think it's the Hideo blog on there
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Motorstorm Apocalypse is getting a brand new update and they're adding make a mode support, which I guess allows you to customize, you know, the vehicles, um, and some of the other options that are in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, you can tweak everything, including you can just, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, you can disable brakes, you can disable gravity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, sweet, a racing game with no brakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'd have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also added PlayStation Move support for, I guess, if you wanted to do the old Wii steering type thing on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I'd recommend that, but, you know, that option's there at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's out there now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just connect to the internet and pop in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then Child of Eden unfortunately has been delayed a week but I think it's kind of cool because they're getting 3D support now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you'll be able to check out the game September 27th.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's PlayStation 3 though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 3 version, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course it will feature move controls as well which I...
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest, I think that's going to be way better than what the Kinect was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would be kind of curious to check it out on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: But 3D, man, I can only imagine that game is going to be just amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's going to be kind of a trip in 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I know anyone with a 3D TV and a PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't think of anyone off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3D televisions haven't exactly cracked into the mainstream.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have one in my work.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a Sony TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've really contemplated getting one of those monitors, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's about that big.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metal Gear Solid Peace Walker
[SPEAKER_04]: It will have a download code, however, for the first Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't believe it's up-resed or anything like that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just pretty much the original PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the overseas version, which would include the one that's going to come out in America, it will not have the download for the first Metal Gear Solid, but it will have the HD version of Peace Walker.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know why the difference is, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also of note, Metal Gear Solid 3 HD is going to be the subsistence version of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has the user control camera and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It also has emulated MSX versions of Metal Gear 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty awesome because that was all the subsistence versions of Metal Gear Solid 3 had that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that means that we'll see them here in America because those games were never translated to English because the MSX was never out in America.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know how that's all going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really hope we can play those games in their original MSX format.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, by the way, there's a huge difference between Metal Gear 2 and Snakes Revenge, by the way, if you didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Snakes Revenge was completely done in America, and Kojima was not involved with that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there was an official Metal Gear 2, I'm not talking solid, Metal Gear 2 on the MSX oh so many years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: We never saw it here.
[SPEAKER_01]: There are fan translations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, well, I don't think they'd use a fan translation, but I would, man, I really hope the MSX version show up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Metal Gear Solid 2 HD release would also be based on Subsistence.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess he really meant to say the Substance version of the game because there wasn't a Subsistence, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what's Subsistence?
[SPEAKER_04]: Subsistence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, those games will be in HD and we'll have all the trophy support and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: A game that you might have forgot about, but it's still coming, you know, eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic 4, Episode 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there was Sonic 4, Episode 1, and it kind of came out, and the whole internet was all, no one care.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people thought that Sonic 4 was pretty much dead, now that, you know, Sonic Generations is kind of going and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: But nope, Sega West CEO Mike Hayes said that new info regarding the second chapter should be out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: No date, just soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just basically saying, hey, the game hasn't fallen off the radar.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will come out, you know, eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: He did mention that episode one did get a million downloads across all the platforms, so it didn't do that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: A game that should have done a hell of a lot better than it did was Rock Band 3 and a company is taking a second chance on the game because, you know, I guess MTV Games isn't really around anymore so you can't really get new Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Mad Catz is going to be basically re-releasing Rock Band 3 this holiday with their peripherals.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a really weird type of thing to see a company come in and pick up a game for a re-release like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but they did the official peripherals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Controller Version and Drum Kit Version
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for fans of SingStar, there is a new version to be coming out calling SingStar Back to the 80s and it'll be out sometime before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has 30 massive hits.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I gotta ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it gonna have the song Back to the 80s?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like by Aqua?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That wasn't an 80s song.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it'd be cool though.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's gonna have Whitesnake and Devo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be for sale on the SingStore.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe Meatloaf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for the members Thanks for the members
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And moving forward, we have for North America on September 9th, the Flame Red 3DS will be out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's flaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I like... There was a DS in that exact same color, wasn't there?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the name in Japan, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Flare Red.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, it's a 3DS and it's red and black.
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, guys, before we get back to some more long-form news, I do want to give one more shout-out for the indie game Spotlight that we're going to be doing on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't had a whole lot of bites on that, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we must not have a lot of developers listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, if you or a friend are developing an independently produced game, either for iOS, PC...
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Arcade or you know pretty much anything we'll take a look at it and maybe invite you on the show to talk about it and hopefully get you noticed because right now one of the biggest bitches we're hearing about that is it's really hard to get noticed on Xbox Live Arcade because A. Microsoft doesn't really highlight a lot of the indie stuff and B. a lot of it is crap there's a lot of crap out there but there are a few good things and if you believe you have a diamond in the rough we want to call it out here on this program
[SPEAKER_04]: so coming soon to the program and if we don't get a lot of developers to bite on that we'll just kind of start spotlighting stuff we like and that's where we'll go with it because we're committed to helping indie games get more acknowledgement because after all we're an indie podcast and we know it can be tough
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I want to give a plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of any podcast to another show that we do here at OLR Network, it is Horde House.
[SPEAKER_04]: The best little Horde House in Azeroth.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.hordehouse.com If you like World of Warcraft, there's all sorts of fun stuff about WoW on that program.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week especially was a really fun show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We taped on an off day this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a guy from Britain on the show and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess crashed the show about halfway through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess she's not Rice Princess anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm supposed to call her Irene.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll always be Rice Princess to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: She crashed the show about halfway through, and we were talking about PvP for a little while, so it was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is she having withdrawals?
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't sound like it, but it was still nice to have her perspective, even though she's pretty comfortable in her decision to quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think, you know what's funny is that most people that were on the show this week are on a bit of hiatus, but all of them were like, yeah, I'll come back eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even Picaruno, who is our guest over from overseas, is like,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Girls Gone Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they are lovely people and they thank you for the biscuits Awesome Yes, it's .net, girlsgonewild.net So check them out, I was on episode 25 and Rob will be on episode 26 Hooray Alright, lots of Warcraft stuff We also had a little bit of Doctor Who discussion We do more than Warcraft, I promise Oh really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah Fun It came up a little bit Fun Alright, the new show has nothing to do with Warcraft It is very much not about Warcraft, I'll say that much
[SPEAKER_02]: If Dan's involved, it's not about Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get back into some more long-form news, and Loki's going to start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't I take a break here from this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: You and that VVVVV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I'm getting pretty far.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Google Plus has started doing some games, and this is not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: We kind of knew this was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, their rollout is a little bit like what we thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have a separate game section so you can play your games and all the updates for those games are on one section.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't clutter up your feed or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So of course, they're going to start off with Angry Birds, Dragon Age Legends, Sudoku, stuff of that sort.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be starting to roll out some more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, in the great Google tradition, not everybody had it right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got mine the day after this was announced, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I play Bejeweled Blitz on Google Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I forgot to say that at the top of the show, but I play Bejeweled Blitz on Google Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I gotta say, I love that the game stuff is just on a separate frickin' page.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it sounds like that they're trying to be a little bit more of kind of a destination for these developers because they're offering, you know, the commissions that they're taking from these games are a lot less than, say, Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, VentureBee is reporting that Google is only taking a 5% commission on its games, whereas Facebook takes 30.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, that might be a little bit more beneficial for some of these developers out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think it's going to get harder to be noticed on Google Games because they don't clutter your feed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I honestly think part of the reason why Farmville was so successful was that it did spam the shit out of everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people who didn't know better, i.e.
[SPEAKER_04]: soccer moms, started playing it because they saw, oh, Ethel's playing this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should play it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I think that's a lot of how those games became so successful.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's going to be interesting to see if the Google Games model is successful because, honestly...
[SPEAKER_04]: How is going to a different page to see your game content any better than, I don't know, MSN Zone is a Microsoft site where you can play games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I bet a lot of people don't really play there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to a different page, how different is that going to a different website to play your games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say this to Google's credit, it's clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I feel like when I go to Zone MSN, it's very cluttered.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's ads everywhere, blah, blah, blah, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a cluttered website full of clutter.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Google Games, I thought, is pretty slick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the things people either love or they hate about Google Plus is that it's very plain.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not a lot of flair to it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very plain looking site.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't really have ads at all right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how long that's going to last.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a very clean site and the games site kind of carries that on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did notice that Bejeweled Blitz was kind of skinned for Google Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it looks like it was very specific towards that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I didn't play anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only one I played, but I'm down with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to check out more Google Games if they get some more stuff I want to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know, Civ World could come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, go into our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blakeman is talking about Dragon Age and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be illegal to use games like Dragon Age in the same sentence as Angry Birds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Believe it or not, Dragon Age Legends is one of the launch games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never played that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that like Knights of the Clicky or what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's more of like a simplified version, kind of like a Diablo-esque type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might actually be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether says, Bejeweled Blitz is good, but it only gives you one minute to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's kind of the point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the little bite-sized version of Bejeweled there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is another Nintendo story.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting patent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: GameSpot found the filing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The MSO, I guess, would be an environment where your actions and choices affect the world that they and everyone else live in.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, for example, an economic system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe a case where a player finds building materials and they make a house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then all the other players are going to see the house, just not the owner.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm imagining they're not going to see the material either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there's an idea too where players would gossip to an AI non-player character who spreads it to other characters in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course that instantly made my brain go, oh, it's Animal Crossing, which I'm sure a lot of people are thinking at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and not to say this is the first game that's been kind of single player, but yet had sort of the multiplayer tie like Demon's Souls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby was talking about this on his show right before that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, I don't see why Nintendo  I guess I should properly plug his show.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's always before us here at All Games Radio, but he's on at 5 Pacific.
[SPEAKER_04]: BobbyBlackWolf at BobbyBlackWolf.com was talking about this subject tonight a little more in depth on his show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said, I can think of two right off the top of my head that already do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he said Demon's Souls, and the other one was
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking forgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a PC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to come to me as soon as somebody yells it out in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't remember what the other one was, but there's another game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Random game on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was exactly like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he was saying, he was trying to say Diablo 3 was kind of part of this too, where Diablo 3 has a single player mode, but yet it's going to have this auction house that's more massive.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's interesting that Nintendo would be getting a patent on this when it's kind of already been done.
[SPEAKER_04]: And can they really do that, IDK?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, especially if the patent was in 2010.
[SPEAKER_06]: Demon's Souls came out in 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fable Spore
[SPEAKER_04]: But yes, Spore was very much, remember, you would make your little monster and then it kind of went off into the Spore universe and the universe was made up of other creatures that other people had made.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you never play the game with these people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that the players made the environment.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that game was out in 08, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to a lesser extent, you could even say that the Wii with people's Miis because you share the Miis and they pop up in games sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else do I want to say about this patent?
[SPEAKER_04]: More, the filing talks about how the game has to be suitable for play on something called the Wii 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was filed, of course, in 2010, so maybe at one point the Wii U was going to be the Wii 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the 3DS was the Wii 3D at one point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows, but don't read too far into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure this does not mean Wii 3D confirmed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that Nintendo explores a lot of options about what they're going to do and files patents to cover their butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just interesting that Nintendo would go for something like this when, yeah, I think we have examples of other games that already kind of have done this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it would be a little bit crappy if Nintendo gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, only if Nintendo decides to go after these other developers.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, if I were the company that made Demon's Souls from software, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be all like, F you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have...
[SPEAKER_04]: This game was out a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: But just because they do that, though, can they still patent it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like if I come up with something but I don't patent it, then they do?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole patent system in this country is fucked up anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, I'm going to defer to Bobby's show because he puts it better than I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just talking about how...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's ridiculous that you can patent all these software concepts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to see the headache it's causing, just look at all this bullshit with LoadSys.
[SPEAKER_04]: LoadSys is specifically a patent troll company.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no office.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing to LoadSys besides some troll.
[SPEAKER_04]: Literally a troll sitting under the bridge begging for money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or demanding money, in this case, with their stock of patents.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's kind of screwed up you know something needs to be done patenting hardware that's a little different I get that but a lot of this software patent and the other example I know that Bobby always brings up again just to totally bite his show is the one click thing from Amazon it's ridiculous that Amazon has a patent on one click that whole one click to buy one click to purchase nobody else can do that Amazon has the patent on it that's ridiculous
[SPEAKER_04]: In my opinion, you're patenting something that's kind of like a key functionality of the internet, a link.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm patenting the Q key.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I patent device to create queue by pressing button.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, it's interesting to see what comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it's just a patent.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't mean New Animal Crossing confirmed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, those Animal Crossing games do sell.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Animal Crossing confirmed, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: They do sell pretty well, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Another system, another Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're going to see another Animal Crossing regardless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we are assuming it's Animal Crossing, but to not assume it's Animal Crossing would be to then assume that Nintendo is doing something different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to take the safer bet and say it's Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo, different.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just put different in the same packaging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blakeman in our chatroom says, you can be a professional troll.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why was I not informed and where do I get an application?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but Troll's more qualified than you have already applied.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those doing the interviews were thoroughly insulted, therefore they were hired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag's up now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week here on Orange Lounge Radio, DarkSakura likes to open up the mail, dive in headfirst, and pull out some emails to read for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the music's playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So therefore you must.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangelaundreater.com if you want to email us sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm also going to again say that if you send multiple emails, I'm only going to read one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So do not take offense.
[SPEAKER_04]: That being said, the first... And if you send one email that's like 500 pages, she might trim it down too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or just not read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or just put it on the forum or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been talking about Capcom a lot lately, and it reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back in 08 when I visited Japan, I made it a point to hunt down the Capcom building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Though I couldn't read the website, I used Google to loosely translate the addresses on it until I found a likely one and had a cab take me to the building.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guard there was pretty surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband and I were looking around for maybe a store or something, but it was just a building with a big old Capcom logo on the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guard asked us if we need help, and we told him we were tourists and wanted to see the Capcom building and if it had a gift shop or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well this card goes inside and brings back the public relations manager for Capcom Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: We thought it was so cool she kept apologizing that we'd gone out of our way to see the building and there wasn't a store or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: We told her it was still great and we love Okami.
[SPEAKER_02]: She gave us folders about investing in Capcom and her business card so I thought I'd send it along to you here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just something cool you might like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure if she still works there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a link to the pic on my DeviantArt page.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry about the watermark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes that gets fixed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear DeviantArt randomly turns it on sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's from Holly D. Oh my god, I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a pamphlet on investing in Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, again.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the picture of the building.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to come look at this over here over your shoulder.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we can't Tumblr these because these are private pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on DeviantArt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chihotamoto
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on the other page?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a second page there?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's an image.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's her signature.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's still kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me see if there's anything else, though, included in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, just the... I love that whole, here's some information if you want to invest in the company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, you know, again, if you want to really get your point across, you should invest in a company.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should invest in Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought a hoe
[SPEAKER_02]: We bought it on the corner outside your building.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you call me, Earl?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Personages, After returning from my Vegas trip, during which I had a truly fun time, I gave myself an extra day to run errands and unwind just a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the things I did was I called up my local Walmart, called up the Walmart that is also on the same road but slightly farther away from me, and found myself a $170 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also got a game because a gaming system without a game is just an expensive paperweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: much like my Sega Game Gear is now I've got Guardian Heroes on Game Gear and you probably don't anyway I'm not emailing you to gloat or be a braggart about my purchase I'm being a braggart but I just wanted to ask a question of you are any of you three aware of any pornographic websites that can be viewed on the Nintendo 3DS
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me Google that for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura is going to search right now for... Nintendo 3DS boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you just Google 3D porn?
[SPEAKER_04]: 3D website porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3DS porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is actually a pack you can get that someone made that's a bunch of 3D pictures that you can upload to your device.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not pornographic, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Like sexy swimsuits and things like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like lingerie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's some idol.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then I'll leave it to the chat room to try and fill us in on some 3D porno.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, you know what though?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's people out there, they have 3D cameras.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure people have taken 3D pornographic videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that, look, here's, look, let me just break it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to break it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every 3DS has a 3D camera in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pictures of boobs and penises were taken within seconds of the 3DS launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: So those pictures are out there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a matter of having a place to share those pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email from Chiggers
[SPEAKER_02]: Has anyone tried the demo for the indie game No Luca No on Xbox?
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole demo is you sweating Luca the cat away from your cereal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if the whole game is like that, but I giggled like a schoolgirl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tee hee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give DarkSakura tacos because she deserves it.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen you guys on Drenden in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're ArtVal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only able to check in like once a week because I'm really busy with raiding now all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are actually doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will check in on the Drenden Guild very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do at least once a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tuesday, let's have a Drenden-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to check the personal calendar, but maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drenden-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, as far as the whole Luca the Cat or whatever that game was called, no, I've never played that game, but I'm going to as soon as I... Oh, I fucking can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will in 21 days when the investigation is complete.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually looking up NoLucaNo, and there's a video on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says worst Xbox Live game ever on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm going to have to just send you the link to this, Rob, so that you can pull it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, BlackWolf is on it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: He makes websites, so I'm assuming that BlackWolf is currently in the process of making 3DS boobs right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll just wait on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi Rob, Jamie, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say keep up the amazing work and dedication to your fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by the way, Jamie, I wanted to inform you about a website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please use... The website is Abandonia.com A-B-A-N-D-O-N-I-A.com
[SPEAKER_02]: The website hosts abandonware and such, although I would verify its legality because I honestly didn't pay much attention to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was looking for a copy of SimTower for my PC and found it on this floating site, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I know it's technically ultra lame to plug a podcast that is unrelated to said current podcast on said podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I would appreciate it if you would plug my podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: BEEP!
[SPEAKER_02]: Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Square Tech Podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first episode hasn't been posted yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can view the site associated with my show at Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Where we talk about Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, you guys rock my socks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, it's squarepowered.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so kind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revised.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some tips on reducing the pain and cost of an account hack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this is from Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: So after what happened to Rob this weekend, I thought it might be nice to try and put together PSA on account fraud since I had to deal with so much of it at the porn place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind... Sorry, I'm watching a video of NoLucaNo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't play it because it's got douchebags talking over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All you do, all it is, you just push the stick to shoo the cat away.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not your cereal, it's my cereal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so dopey, I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, serious topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Hacking, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're comfortable confirming that the fraud is isolated to one account because the card used was on file and not actually revealed to anyone, try to have the firm handle it first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some places refuse to do repeat business with a customer who has filed a chargeback against them without contacting them, which might matter if you want to keep a relationship with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Many will panic and immediately have their bank kill and reissue everything, potentially overkill and an added nightmare of work if it is not truly needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly not everyone can do this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep recurring digital services all on the same credit card.
[SPEAKER_02]: And most importantly, a card that has its balance against credit, not a debit card that has its balance against cash.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you decide that a firm sucks ass and you're over it, it's much easier for a bank to issue chargebacks against stolen credit versus real electronically transferred cash.
[SPEAKER_02]: So banks have little to no buyer protection when it comes to online fraud made against money.
[SPEAKER_02]: also be prepared to wait you can always escalate to a manager but generally telling people you need this money within 24 hours to pay rent or even if it is true will not accomplish much after making the rep feel like crap other than making the rep feel like crap that Rob has to wait 21 days after doing all of his due diligence to get a refund is not uncommon I can vouch for that too
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't give away my money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are all some good tips and I know he kind of used to work in a sales type of environment and probably had to deal right with all that stuff on the front line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I worked for a mortgage company too, I can tell you that it is incredibly easy for anyone who has a little bit of your personal information to call in and impersonate you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to tell you what I used to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every so often involved in mortgage situations when we would have people call in for payoffs on their mortgage.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see, is there a prepayment penalty, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would have the new loan officers call in and impersonate the customers because they had all of their personal information right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if I at any point ever suspected it then I would put them on hold call the customer and say I think someone's impersonating you I'm going to three-way you usually screwed you know a person out of a mortgage but we would have spouses call we'd have exes call in
[SPEAKER_02]: and because they were privy to all that information.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another thing that will help is that with any of your facilities that you can work with on a phone, if they have a password set up verbally, set it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really don't like to talk about my day job on the show because I try to keep my work life and my night life separate but I will say that for many years I worked in a health insurance call center environment and I will tell you there's many strict laws about what type of information can be given because you're talking about people's health information there's strict federal laws about what can and can't be said in a conversation and honestly part of me is kind of like I think
[SPEAKER_04]: We need strict laws like that for everything, no matter what the industry is.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of companies take good care, but clearly my information is at risk in some places.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was such a snot as a customer service rep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, I also took escalated calls because I got promoted to a training rep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would actually start quoting the Federal Privacy Act.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had it saved as a PDF with parts highlighted and say, well, you can tell me that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, actually, according to the Federal Privacy Act, and would read them line for line, like, I want to talk to your manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my manager can't break the law either.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then just hang up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, all good tips.
[SPEAKER_04]: All good tips.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things I probably should have listened to before this happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also want to say that the Federal Privacy Act came out in 1979, so look it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, 1974.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Luca.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every time it's no, and I guess you get points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every time you shoo him away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, does the game get harder as you go through?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, just eat my breakfast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the cat meowed and ate breakfast.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the record, by the way, the Federal Privacy Act of 1974.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, got pwned.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no one told me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just looked it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know what this big flashing elephant is.
[SPEAKER_06]: In what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, VVVV?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an elephant with a tear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you made it cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, speaking of making people cry, once in a while we like to rant on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called the FUs of the Week, and we're going to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: to the unemployment office here in California for switching people over to debit cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the only reason I'm saying F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: about this, actually, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: is really the Bank of America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because California Unemployment decided to go through Bank of America to issue debit cards, which, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no problem with a debit card.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so far it was actually fairly easy to set it up to do a direct deposit when my money comes in into my checking account so that's fine I just have to do my fill out my stupid form but I set it up for my first deposit to do that it's like no we're gonna set it up for every deposit afterwards it doesn't work on your first one so that means I have to go to the bank and have them do a manual transfer so Bank of America can suck my non-existent call Loki do you have any FUs of the week
[SPEAKER_06]: Um... I don't know if you get a KFC for only having 7 out of the 10 hot wings I won.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get shorted 3 hot wings?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they said that, well, for some reason we only have 7.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll give you chicken tenders instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, eh, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, um... These are serious first world problems, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Serious first world problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, they substituted three of my hot wings for chicken tenders.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to the fucker that stole 125 bucks from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, you fucking fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, burn his house down.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, don't burn my house down.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I meant the fucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably... It's got to be some mass operation overseas somewhere that's doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet anything it's some other country where they've got a shop of people that are hacking all these Xbox Live accounts somehow that probably... The information was probably breached and Microsoft just doesn't know it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably got stolen the same time as Sony's, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to make stuff up, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: All I know is that I have money stolen and I'm pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at least the lady that worked at Xbox.com was nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: She was nice enough to tell me that, hey, she's had money stolen from her, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft keeps doing this and yet we all get mad at Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just irritating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not mad at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just mad at... I'm partially mad at myself for letting it happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kind of mad at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Poor Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we move on to more news?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're apparently going to be doing some new... I'm assuming it's just a port of Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Valve is putting out Counter-Strike Global Offensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming to Xbox Live Arcade, PlayStation Network, and Steam early next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course it's going to have new maps, characters, and weapons.
[SPEAKER_06]: And some renovated classic maps as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: and new modes, matchmaking options, leaderboards, all the usual stuff that they have in shooters nowadays.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool that they're actually putting out a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone loves Valve games and I'm sure this one will be supported just as well as all the other stuff that they put out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe they'll have hats someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay hats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other cool stuff, of course, they're going to have a new decoy grenade, which is kind of cool, and some other new animations and models and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be a new heavy machine gun, a new range of shotguns, specifically for close-up combat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Molotov, uh, cocktail grenades, and, um, I guess, uh, some stuff for cutting off certain areas of the map.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, uh, basically a decoy grenade, which it'll do is it'll send out a burst of gunfire from wherever it's thrown.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to make someone think that you're in one place that you're not, then you can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they also have some other stuff that they're tweaking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gunfire for different weapons and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they're going to have, I guess, different things where they're going to give everybody Kevlar, the round starter, making people have to defuse bombs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it sounds like they're trying to tweak up the gameplay and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited for a new Counter-Strike game?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I own the old one on Xbox, even though I am terrible at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I maybe played online once, and I was so terrible, I got screamed at, and I just... You know, I've never really played the original, but I know it's definitely popular, so, I mean... I don't know, this should do well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's one of the first major military first-person shooter games that they had out there, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it'll do well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So can I read a text message I just got from Extifer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My co-host over on Horde House.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I just thought you should know that, insert person's name redacted here, Xbox account and money got hacked a few weeks ago, just in case you're talking about it on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, that's person number five I know that's been hacked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was six.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever, it's a fucking lot of people that this is happening to, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing's going on Microsoft, but Sony needs to provide free debix.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to have Dan check ours now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you guys, change your fucking passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is about Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not news about Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there is, of course, Kingdom Hearts 3D or Dream Drop Distance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is coming out, I guess, soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be getting a hands-on if you're going to the Tokyo Game Show in the fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, what's also interesting in the Kingdom Hearts universe is in the latest issue of the Japanese magazine Dengeki PlayStation,
[SPEAKER_04]: Tetsuya Nomura actually said that it's becoming difficult to get new players into the series with each new iteration well the plot's kind of complicated I'm not too surprised at that but what's also interesting about it as a celebration of the franchise's 10th anniversary he hopes to release an HD technical test of the series what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that mean like a tech demo like Final Fantasy 7?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it mean remakes of the first game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're talking about trying to get people into it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: But perhaps there's more information at Tokyo Game Show next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, don't tease me like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's terrible that they're teasing us so terribly with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, DarkSakura, do you think Kingdom Hearts is a tough series for people to get into?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't think it's like... I mean, it is a weird plot, but it did always kind of fascinate me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts was sort of for kids, but not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably older kids, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a young kid would never understand that plot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Why is Mickey wearing black and has a sword?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really convoluted.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that's why people really love Kingdom Hearts is that it is a little bit the darker side of Disney, which, you know, Epic Mickey sort of tried to do, but eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You made a grammatical error.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did I do now?
[SPEAKER_02]: You use an apostrophe for it Oh my gosh It's a radio show, nobody sees that I do Well, how about I just use that to go ahead and get into my news then?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure Okay Australia is getting an R18 plus rating Finally!
[SPEAKER_02]: Get with it, Australia They actually have it added to their new rating system so that they can have mature games
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead of just banning them outright, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe Mortal Kombat will finally come out in Australia legitimately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some of the other games that have been banned there recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, if you look at it from a financial point of view, putting the ratings out there and allowing these games to come out instead of banning them is revenue.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be an explosion of violent and graphic games in Australia really soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and kangaroos will run all over you and punch you in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll have a bunch of unrated editions come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it wasn't in the show role, but did you hear about the fuckery?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm sure you heard about the fuckery that was going on in Britain this week with all the rioting and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's terrible, but the real fuckery I'm talking about is how people wanted to blame all that on Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, of course, you gotta blame it on something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't just blame it on fuckers being fuckers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, on top of that... I mean, there's trashy people everywhere, but I just, you know, you didn't think it would happen there in jolly old England.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see the thing I put on my Tumblr about the old man's barbershop?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was an elderly gentleman whose shop got ransacked, and he had owned it with his wife, and his wife passed away.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they, like, completely tore up his barbershop.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'd had it for something like, I want to say, 40 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: How sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that he'd have to go out of business, but there's actually an online group going around raising money to rebuild his store.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I can find it, I'll link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I thought that was a nice touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: RDGSinge in the chat is throwing back to something last week, but wants to ask DarkSakura a question, and I guess now's a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any updates on the tester?
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I've been upgraded to contestant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that means I have to do a stupid video.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now I kind of, I mean, there's part of me that doesn't want to because I don't want to be away from Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when he was gone for five days and it made me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only going to be a few days.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think it's like Survivor where you can't call people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they let you talk to your family and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they do, but I mean, I don't like L.A.
[SPEAKER_02]: either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd just be like, we're done taping, bye, I'm going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd just hang out with Marissa all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd be with other nerds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, of course, they're purposely going to cast people, they're going to drive you bonkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, if you don't kill them, you might get a job and a couple thousand dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, I got my account upgrade a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you are an official contestant of Tester Season 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: This bothers me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why I'm so bothered by this.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Loki, we got a couple more news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Folks, I need to put this out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 800 number is not working tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can only Skype us tonight at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is temporary.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll hopefully be fixed by next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just a heads up, you can only Skype us tonight at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the 877 number again, not working tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please don't use it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, a couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now normally you don't hear of some wild successes on Xbox Live Indie games, but there is one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this should come as no surprise, seeing as it's kind of a clone of another game.
[SPEAKER_06]: FortressCraft, the kind of Minecraft knockoff, has sold 350,000 copies and brought in over a million dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, uh, they said, of course, no, it's not really like Minecraft, it's more of like Dwarf Fortress, but it's Minecraft, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it looks like goddamn Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, um, it is the, probably the best-selling, I would imagine the best-selling game on Xbox Live Indie Games, it's making a million dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently there is an 84% trial to purchase conversion rate, which is pretty impressive if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_06]: 400,823 copies sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a bunch of different statistics.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's funny in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: 96,197,520 Microsoft points spent on the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of the purchases being in the US, followed by Great Britain and Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's good news for Minecraft when it comes out over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like people want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one more story for you guys, then we're going to open up the Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this has to do with the game Rage that's going to be coming out fairly soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, this is a new FPS franchise that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tim Wiltis, who is the ID Software Creative Director, of course, ID Software is putting out this game, he says that the access to the game's underground...
[SPEAKER_04]: will be restricted to those who get their copy new at retail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me, new at retail.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's saying, you've played Rage five times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever found any sewer hatches?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you bought the game new, that would be open for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he says, you still have to download it, but you don't have to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those hatches are all over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most people never find them, but as soon as you do, you're like, oh, and then you start to look for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's our first time buyer incentive.
[SPEAKER_04]: so instead of doing an online pass or whatever a lot of companies are doing I guess there's these new little zone for lack of a better word that you can explore but only if you are a new game owner otherwise you may never notice it's there I guess because it's all in the sewer and what I understand none of the main storyline happens in the sewer I guess this is all like side quests so it's basically additional content that's only available when you buy it new
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, it's not additional content because if it's already on the disc and you're just unlocking access to it, then it's not additional.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if it's some download content, then that's a little different.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I have a feeling this is crap that's already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just allowing you access to it, which is kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well we're going to go ahead and open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go ahead and give us a call on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, we're going to check the Twitter and go to some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to the Twitter right now, twitter.com of course slash OLR if you want to send us some tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, let's go on to some tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting off with Flocko Jones, who I guess must be listening live tonight because he's tweeting us and saying, LulzSec announced in mid-June that they released Xbox Live account information and Microsoft did nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox Live, Facebook, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and it does say that the story is appended with an update that says Microsoft released a statement that Xbox Live was not compromised to the best of Microsoft's knowledge and the login's passwords were released at random with people encouraged to try the information on services like Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I do remember that happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do remember when they released like a big list of login and passwords and all that stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Flaco Jones in the tweet says to us, maybe if Microsoft took Xbox Live down for a month when they most likely knew account info had been compromised, no money would have been stolen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of like I guess Sony did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to another tweet here from Nico Nico Chan tweets us saying, I heard from a friend that DarkSakura likes Parapara.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was wondering what Parapara dancers she watched on YouTube, if she does.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just watch whatever I find.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just kind of a YouTuber.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more the songs for you, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's certain dances that I like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the one for Velfar.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a number of them that I like.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'll find different groups and see different people doing them.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that don't know what Parapara is, how can you best describe it to people?
[SPEAKER_01]: Cheerleading and line dancing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheerleading and line dancing combined.
[SPEAKER_04]: How would you classify the music?
[SPEAKER_01]: Synth-y.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me play you an example of a song from Para Para Paradise, just in case you've never heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So imagine doing like... Play Valpar if you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have that one ready, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is like cheer dancing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie is actually waving her hands here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is one that I used to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Rob, that's not possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to find Like a Virgin because it has the funniest intro ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I've got to find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you miss the Parapara machine that was here locally?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you said something about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And someone's supposed to lend me Dance Masters so I can do Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do now thanks to Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, where is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I got one other directory I gotta check.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is awesome live radio, but hold on, I gotta check one more folder here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hurry up, we got Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to have the entirety of DDR Freak's radios rotation here on the computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm pretty sure they had it in their rotation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hilarious opening.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the band, of course, is called Virgin L. So here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether in chat says, when I dance to Eurobeat, I pretend to drive a car really fast down a mountain pass, shifting the gears of my hands and the steering wheel movements.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not Initial D. I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is Initial D. Initial D. Most of these performers, by the way, the bands are out of Italy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, Skype line is open, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to Tigerclaw sends us a couple tweets here.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them has to do with Nintendo looking at trademark applications for Wii U in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is not just, I think, what DarkSakura was talking about earlier, but some other related things, such as...
[SPEAKER_04]: point cards, advertising and publicity services for providing information let's see, telecommunication via electronic bulletin boards providing images via communication with handheld game devices clothing for domestic pets bags and the like and so forth oh god, you know what game that is clothing, waistbands, belts for clothing card games notebooks consumer video game machines fitted with a camera function meaning I guess the camera's already built in
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm Interesting IDK Alright, also TigerClaw tweets us another tweet Sony wants to know what Playstation Vita peripherals you want What do you want to see on the Vita?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess some of the responses that are showing up on this poll so far It's on the Japanese PlayStation Vita community site A UMD drive A cradle with HDMI out A compact full keyboard A grip adapter with a secondary battery built in UMD drive is by far the most popular response so far How about a USB connector?
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be already there, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Loki's confirming that it's already there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, Orange Laundry on Skype if you want to give us a call tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should have one of those paypoint things where you put your card up to the sensor and it charges you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, I don't have to enter anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just buy all of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya says, we should totally start bees for Xenoblade.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a hashtag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it'll catch on like President Cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think it should be done, you should start that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will endorse bees for Xenoblade.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones and take the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: TheWordNate again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up, Nate?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, dude, I was calling about the indie thing, the indie gaming.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm an indie game developer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are an indie game developer yourself.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What games are you developing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't laugh at me now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm making a farming game right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: A farming game?
[SPEAKER_00]: But hold on.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not like Farmville.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's more like Monopoly mixed with Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, people like Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Monopoly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monopoly is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I read the most weird news story ever this week that was talking about how in Monopoly, you actually don't want to own Boardwalk.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to own Illinois Avenue.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I saw the article too, but I didn't read it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just saw it and said, these people don't know what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the game's not out yet then.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have anything to plug just yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you want to give away all the secrets, but how do you combine the worlds of Monopoly and Harvest Moon?
[SPEAKER_00]: well in the game you really um okay you're trying to start a farming monopoly so um you start off as a small farmer and then later down the road you just you just uh you just get opportunities to take over other people's farms and um
[SPEAKER_00]: Get new property.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get to get the government to help you out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a lot of crazy, like... We get to take over people's farms with guns?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you get to put them out of business.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're producing government-supported crops.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're encouraging people to grow government cheese.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's good, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, but you know your game's probably going to get, like, targeted by the organic growers of America or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, especially the Slow Food International.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Tea Party.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the Tea Party's all down for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't care about organic food.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to say that crops are organic in the game, even though they aren't.
[SPEAKER_02]: if you have organic ones then you need to have them cost more
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it didn't get bad quicker than it tastes worse.
[SPEAKER_00]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, let me ask you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where did you get the idea to develop a game like this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what inspired you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, people got to remember, you don't write an indie game in one night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess you can, but that's, you know, most of them definitely are not done in one night.
[SPEAKER_04]: They take a long time to develop.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you really have to be committed to your idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: So where did you get the idea that I want to do a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Farming game that's not Farmville.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll say, I want to do a farming game that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where did you kind of get that idea?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it was just random thoughts during the day, and I kind of got down to it because it started off with just three people farming on a farm.
[SPEAKER_00]: and then I thought they should make money and they should have enemies and they should kill wolves and stuff too.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was thinking about keep a spend on the enemy concept and they should have a huge mission to be the best farmers in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh cool, so your game does have violence in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm on board.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get to hit wolves, not people.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't steal people's farms.
[SPEAKER_00]: You just make them sell out to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: By selling your crops for less money than them on purpose.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, like the Walmart model.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what are you developing for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you developing for Facebook or iOS or what?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's going to be for the big three.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's not LeBron James.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be for Mac, Windows, and Linux.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, okay, so you're going for not the big three consoles, but the big three computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I'm down Mac, PC, Linux.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you will be in the next Humble Indie Bundle.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope so, but I need to keep developing, especially the graphics, because...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't have much backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just have like skies and trees in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's a website we can keep tabs on your progress?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have like a blog or something or at least a Twitter where we can keep tabs on your progress?
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to type it on the chat so you can like see it.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: That works.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Tailware.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tailware.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll look for that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so on the side, it's utter crap on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it'll get better as the game gets further along.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a really bad demo up already, but that's like a really, really old and bad demo up.
[SPEAKER_00]: It feels so fresh.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll give you the link.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, when you get your game finished and you're ready to get it out there, you've got to come back on the show and tell us more about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't you give away all your ideas yet because you're still developing it, but you've got to come back on the show, maybe with one of your co-developers, and talk a little more about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, most definitely, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Smurf it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: La la la la la la.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio on Skype if you want to call us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, tonight the 800 number does not work.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we didn't forget to pay the bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some other issues going on so we will be back with that next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio on Skype if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to more tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Osfer tweeted us saying, Hi guys, guess who's in Disney World?
[SPEAKER_05]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: S2100 Matt tweets us saying July 2011 was apparently the worst month for the video game industry in almost five years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I read this story too and it has a lot of people going, oh shit, the video game industry is in trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm like, well, what games came out in July 2011?
[SPEAKER_04]: Catherine.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Catherine is your biggest release like all month, like I'm sorry, no disrespect to Catherine, but it's not exactly a AAA title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or disrespect to Earth Defense Force Inside Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I said, it's no surprise that it was a weak month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I demand an explanation for these shenanigans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus the 3DS really doesn't have a lot going for it right now, nor does the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're kind of in between a lot of consoles right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted the 360 and PS3 are still kind of at their prime, but those systems don't have fucking anything until the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except Catherine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to MNZiba tweets us saying, I downloaded Jukebeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Contra song on Extreme is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you supposed to beat that?
[SPEAKER_04]: You literally have to memorize it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have to memorize where all those little fuckers show up and know exactly where to tap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you tried a song on Expert yet, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just out of curiosity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't even tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it's pretty hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether tweets us saying, Loki could learn from reason number one on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Five crucial lessons learned by watching kids play video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess, Loki, you could learn from number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's recap.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a cracked article.
[SPEAKER_04]: All they do are like top 10 lists, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like every time I get linked to some top 10 lists, it's all fucking cracked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like they've made a website out of top lists.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not top lists, but top lists.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Five crucial lessons learned by watching kids play video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number five, they don't tolerate losing, so modern games just let them win.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't tolerate losing, so modern games just hand it to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number four, they have no tolerance for grinding.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like in an old school Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three, if they want to read, they'll buy a fucking book.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be referencing how I always like to skip to quest text in WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two, they press Y to skip as fast as they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: And number one, Loki, you could learn from this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't like it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Break it!
[SPEAKER_06]: versus people like me that just want to play a really fun game with some weapons that necessarily weren't in the stock version of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, last tweet tonight from Fydelt61 on Twitter Tweets us, Final Fantasy things, fucking want And it's a tweet to a clock here And maybe I'll have to get DarkSakura to reblog this on the Tumblr So you guys can see this too It is a clock that is made up of Final Fantasy logos So like Final Fantasy 12 is at the top And then 1, 2, 3, get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's all the different Final Fantasy logos in a clock Send me that and I'll put it on our thing
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I will send you that link right now so you can reblog that so listeners can see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, that came to us from 5delt61 on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to send us stuff to cross post, you can send us stuff on Twitter as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess not having the 800 number tonight just killed us on calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to go ahead and close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, it has been kind of a slower week and there's not a lot of new games that people are excited to talk about and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to close on up the Skype line and cover any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: See if Loki has any last minute stories he wants to talk about real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just one that I think is kind of funny and ironic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Facebook has decided that they're changing their game service.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually going to be updating things a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they said that game growth has slowed and because of that they're starting to tweak things around so they're going to have some sort of looks like a games tab or something like that and different sorting options.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And
[SPEAKER_04]: I love how they announced a lot of this the same day that Google Games came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They reopened Ferility, I guess, is what they were promising.
[SPEAKER_06]: It basically looks like they're ripping off a bunch of ideas that Google Plus had.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, these have been in development for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've been in development for 6 to 12 months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: that's it alright well that brings us to the close of another week here at Orange Lounge Radio we will be back next week we will be off in two weeks but we'll be here next week we've been asked about a marathon show this year on Labor Day weekend I kinda don't think that's gonna happen this year just because there's a lot going on around that time however we're gonna look at targeting another three day weekend in the future so don't be too disappointed
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to do not just a marathon show, but we want to do a marathon that has a little more oomph this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what better time to do it than kicking off the 10th year of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll be looking at that in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oui.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so anyhow, let's go around and get everybody's final thought Loki, we'll start with you, do you have any final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I'm hopefully going to be able to play some more games this week I had plans on doing that this weekend, but that kind of fell through My final thought tonight is I'm looking forward to having some Pinkberry, yay DarkSakura, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read exactly what's on macro memory now.
[SPEAKER_02]: 50 Cent got shot and still whines about it on stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Teddy Roosevelt got shot mid-speech and didn't leave the stage until he was finished.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50 Cent got shot on stage?
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he got shot.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just whines about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, if somebody shot me, I'd whine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Teddy Roosevelt got shot and finished his damn speech.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still, if I got shot, I'd be whining about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's for another week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should never be shot, actually, on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back here next week to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope to see you here live Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until then, we'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell a friend about the show if you enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spread the word at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have advertising dollars, so therefore we don't stick the show full of ads.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask, word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.