[SPEAKER_16]: Tonight, August 7th, 2011, the Vita gets bumped to 2012, the Humble Indie Bundle adds even more games, and can you soon make a living playing Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, the one, the only, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a culinary fucking goddess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: What makes you a culinary fucking goddess?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I'm sharing one of my favorite recipes with you guys today.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what would that recipe be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Monkey's brains?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: While, you know, famous in Cantonese cuisine is rarely seen in the United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or in Washington, D.C., I should say.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, they are blue potatoes baked instead of fried, but baked with garlic, marjoram, oregano, Himalayan salt, pepper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Himalayan salt?
[SPEAKER_04]: I asked for Mongolian salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lots of garlic and plenty of Italian cheeses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, garlic salt always makes things better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I will, I will, but I've got to set up the show first.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello as well to less of a culinary goddess, but still pretty awesome, Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has there been any culinary works in your life?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you used to deep fry everything in good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I haven't really done any deep frying in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, let's start talking about games with you guys in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com If you've never joined us for a live show, you should sometime Sunday nights, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at AllGamesRadio, www.allgames.com And, yep, we have our chatters there Let's see, TigerClaw says Rob, did you just say monkeys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you must have seen the new Planet of the Apes Nope, didn't see the new Planet of the Apes I heard it was number one in the box office, so it did way better than everyone thought it would
[SPEAKER_12]: And they threw lots of number two.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to hate those movies actually growing up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I think my dad or my brother or somebody really liked those movies and I always thought they were terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the Charlton Heston.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really don't like Charlton Heston.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it has nothing to do with the politics side or the gun, my cold dead hands on stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, I just, God, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like something about him in movies just irritates me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there's a lot of people that would disagree and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes we disagree on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also, I saw Bobby posted on Twitter, there's a Bad Dudes reference in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a bad enough dude to take on, or to save the president or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that line from the original Bad Dudes game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's pretty funny though.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I actually didn't play any Groove Coaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mostly because I've been forever alone.
[SPEAKER_12]: My husband's gone.
[SPEAKER_12]: He'll be back next week though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been neglecting your consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually was going to go in and play the Saturn, and I was like, I gotta do what to hook it up?
[SPEAKER_12]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually an email that I was reading in the emails, we'll have to get to later on, that kind of asks you about playing the old games in the vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Curious to hear about that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll get to that in part B. Alright, well Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played lots of Groove Coaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost seems like it should be like a Q Games game, but here it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: More Grand Theft Auto and more Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, a lot of Earth Defense Force this week, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leveling up my tactical guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finished going through... Well, I had already gone through all the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Normal Mode Level Up
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and now, of course, Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have to join the cult that is Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you on Game Center?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't use that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I use that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you have to add me on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have you on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are the only person that's on my Game Center.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't see your tower yet because you didn't start playing until today.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, my game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I picked up the Humble Indie Bundle, which I know is going to come up in the show later, so I'll talk more about the bundle itself when it comes up in the news later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one of the games in the Humble Indie Bundle has been taking up a lot of my time, and that's because I think it's terrific.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a terrific game.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's one of those games it's been brought up on the show before and I distinctly remember somebody had called in at the end of the year last year to say that this was their favorite game of the year and I was like oh I'll have to check that out at some point you know and amongst all the other games I try to fit into today I just never got around to it until now but now that I play this game it's just like taking up all my time that I'm not playing like WoW or an MMO or something and that's VVVVVV
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_13]: The game is fucking cracked.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is like Super Metroid meets the Commodore 64 meets an incredibly simple premise of you press button, flip gravity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this game could have been on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's obviously kind of like the style they're going for.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the music adds like...
[SPEAKER_04]: So much to it because the music is amazing in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all chiptune type stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like the Scott Pilgrim soundtrack, Super Meat Boy, that type of stuff, you'll love the soundtrack to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And obviously it takes a lot of influences from more recent gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if you like Super Meat Boy, this type of game is right up your alley because it's about dying over and over and over again on a level until you get it just right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then there's that whole exploration and open world thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Like one dungeon or whatever you want to call it that I was in had tripwires.
[SPEAKER_04]: And whenever you hit the tripwire, the gravity automatically flipped.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you really had to kind of maneuver your character to hit tripwires, sometimes sequentially, to get through the room without landing on spikes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another area I was in was all about warping from one side of the room to the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the only way to escape a room would be from one predetermined exit.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it all just kind of makes a mood.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think if the game had just done new graphics, it would have been horribly overlooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think sometimes that whole little retro catch kind of adds a lot to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not just, by the way, the open world Metroid-y part of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also time trial levels that you can play and...
[SPEAKER_04]: you can play made up worlds like there's like a little level packs in it and so forth so yeah amazing deal because right now you could get this game for a dollar if you wanted to I think you're kind of cheap if you do but I understand some people are broke and in school and what have you it's honestly if you miss the Humble Indie Bundle altogether it's worth the $10 on Steam I think so especially if you like like if you like Super Meat Boy and those type of games retro fan this game is right up your alley
[SPEAKER_12]: I bought it when it was two bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh nice, during the Steam sales?
[SPEAKER_12]: Way back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've had it for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, that was taking up a lot of my time this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played some of the other stuff in the bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played COGS for a little bit, which is kind of like a puzzle game that's all about, like you know the sliding puzzles, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know when you have
[SPEAKER_04]: The picture ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like you have to move, instead of making a picture, it's like the dual puzzle of line up the wheels right so that way it powers the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of got that whole like steampunk-ish vibe, but not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very puzzle-y interface and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are kind of the big ones I've checked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, most of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Warcraft, Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_04]: Randomly played Wipeout this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, just wanted to play F-Zero and didn't feel like cooking up the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm like, oh, let's play Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about the next best thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: After I mention real quick, you should always be following us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are places to follow us online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, there's always our website at OrangeLoungeRadio.com where the forums are as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please always help out the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Five-star reviews on iTunes are much, much, much appreciated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we don't make anything off the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't even ask you to pay what you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just free.
[SPEAKER_13]: Question for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of?
[SPEAKER_04]: The dish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what you made?
[SPEAKER_13]: Am I a culinary goddess or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've been talking most times, so I haven't been able to really eat it, but it's really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, everybody?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to inflate your ego too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have to go on Hell's Kitchen or something and get your ego kicked out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, because I would punch What's-His-Face.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd be like, you're much nicer to the people on MasterChef.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gordon Ramsay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator PC in chat says, if there was a sequel to VVVVVV, would it be called VVVVVV2?
[SPEAKER_04]: VVVV was 70s or WWWW?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it would be WWWW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would probably be a letter repeated.
[SPEAKER_04]: The soundtrack is called PPPPPPP.
[SPEAKER_04]: PPPPPPP.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all the songs on the soundtrack start with P, so it's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft in the chatroom says, VVVVVV is like Portal, but in 8-bit goodness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackwolf said he just paid $25 for the Humble Indie Bundle, split between the devs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakman says, sliding tile puzzles?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ugh, I think I'd rather glue my forehead to a donkey's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: An ass's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, it's, it's neater than it sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think this, it really depends what types of games you're into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you like action-y type of games, you're probably not going to get so much out of COGS.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's some people that just, to kill time, like to sit there and play a little puzzler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, some of you probably play Plants vs. Zombies, Bejeweled, those are puzzlers.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of right up that same alley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, chat.orangelaunchradio.com if you want to join us live on this Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, apparently, the PlayStation Vita will not be coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least, not over here in the United States or North America or in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said it'll be coming out in early 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, I'm assuming, Sony being a Japanese company, the Japanese will get theirs holiday, 2011.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, right now, no real reason given other than, you know, I don't know that they're delaying it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a good idea because if it means either more units being produced so that they don't have shortages or, you know, to have better games coming out at launch, I mean, both of those things would definitely help them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: and of course they were asked whether they'd be lowering their price because Nintendo did it on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: They lowered their price to compete with the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: They basically said we packed so much into the device and made it very affordable.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no need to lower the price just because somebody else happens to be in the video game business and decided that they were going to lower their price.
[SPEAKER_05]: And honestly, there is a lot of components in the Vita, but if that shit isn't going to sell at launch, they will lower the price.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just the way things are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else that got delayed to early 2012 as well, that'd be Twisted Metal, which was supposed to be coming out in October, and now it's early 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: They basically said, you know, late game is only late until it ships.
[SPEAKER_05]: A bad game is bad until the end of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great quote.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we ship Twisted Metal tomorrow, going off the response from folks who have played it, I assure you it would never be a bad game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, they're spending the extra time polishing the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that game's been in development for quite some time now, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's go back to the Vita being delayed.
[SPEAKER_04]: What does it boil down to, the cost for delay?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's parts?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's strategical?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you kind of knew about this before the rest of the internet did, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing really, they didn't say.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said it's 2012. 2012.
[SPEAKER_04]: Part of me wondered if maybe they saw what the 3DS was doing wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was that the 3DS launched without really having any good games at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Debatable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand Street Fighter 4 has its fans, but let's face it, that was a port of a game that had already been out for a couple years, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And if that's your strongest release title, something's up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe they were looking at that going, well, what do we have coming out at launch on the Vita?
[SPEAKER_04]: If these developers aren't really ready to put out all-star games, maybe now's not the time to put out the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that was where my mind went.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, well, maybe the Uncharted people weren't ready to put out the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if that's your biggest game and that's going to get delayed, let's just delay the whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's call the whole thing off Apparently So Alright, well Going to chat.orangeloungeradio.com Black Lab is in chat tonight saying I can tell Rob started talking mid-chew Hey, I gotta eat sometime When I got something to say, I'm gonna say it Let's see Breakman in chat says I got a PSP at full price, if only I'd waited
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's a newsflash.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could wait to get a Vita, too, but it's probably going to take a long time for the price to drop on that, especially if it comes out in the first part of next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: There could be a small price drop at the end of next year going into holiday 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's not for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd be interested in the Vita if they had Saints Row on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Might just be a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either one of those is very interchangeable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any of those three, I would definitely be down for a Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as of right now, I've seen how much I play my 3DS, which is not at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just don't need another system cluttering up.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bank account Alright, well let's talk about the other handheld The 3DS Oh, before we get to 3DS actually Let me ask one more question Does this change your opinion at all about the Vita?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I asked this to chat too Does it change your opinion thus far of the Vita?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it change the fact whether you want one or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, I'll start.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it doesn't really change my opinion of the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I actually kind of say, you know what, if you're not ready, then that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take your time until you've got a really solid launch lineup.
[SPEAKER_04]: And B, the fact that the holidays are going to be killer anyway, I'm kind of glad to not have to spend $250 right now on a Vita as well because you know I'll have to have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So actually, I'm not so bothered by this.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about you guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of just warm about the Vita to begin with, and nothing really stood out so far with the Vita that says, I gotta have that system.
[SPEAKER_05]: So until I see something like that, then I don't really have to have that system.
[SPEAKER_12]: It depends on finances.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, the Vita looks nice, hooray, but I hardly touch my PSP, so why would I want to touch the new one?
[SPEAKER_12]: I really didn't play the PSP that much except for Popolo Cross and Loco Roco.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's gonna have to be those must-have games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's really gonna be more of a matter of games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, even Dissidia wasn't really enough to make me really want to play my PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I got on board with PSP early because the very first time I played Luminous, I was like, oh my god, this is the best music puzzle game ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had a PSP the day they came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: And, but, I mean, I've played stuff that I've liked, but it's never been really enough to keep me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I've taken it on trips and watched movies on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now I have a netbook, so I watch movies on that instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the chatters and see what they have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Defective Candy in our chatroom says, Kudos to them for taking the time and trying to launch something solid instead of rushing it like Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: SonicM88 says, Vita doesn't interest me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never liked Sony's games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kitsune says, it may not carry all your favorite games yet, but it definitely has a lot more than 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm psyched about the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: DungeonBuster says, doesn't really change my opinion either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the same opinion that Loki does.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't play handhelds all that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miklatov says, having played it at E3 this year, it doesn't change my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just makes me sad I have to wait longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Need sound shapes, since it's like the Vita's luminous to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator says, I'd be interested in the Vita if it'll print money, make me a sandwich, and order me several slutty strippers every night.
[SPEAKER_04]: you might be a little bit disappointed I don't think these slutty strippers will be in right away that could be in the 2.0 firmware though so stay tuned Breakman says it's a smart move for Sony to move the Vita to next year they don't want to compare its sales to the sales of the 3DS which I think will be one of the biggest Christmas gifts interesting theory maybe they did it to not compete with the 3DS maybe they want to hand this Christmas to Nintendo maybe they're a little afraid of the competition
[SPEAKER_04]: is that is does that sound too fanboy motivated or or what
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it really just is a matter of putting out a polished product because especially with the mistakes that Nintendo's made with bringing the system out and not having the right games for it, that's really hurt their sales.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I think that they're really just trying to avoid that trap.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've seen how it's bit Nintendo in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, let's move over and talk Nintendo then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to move on and talk about the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the 3DS, there's some more comments from Nintendo CEO Satoru Iwata.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you all know who Iwata is.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's the man at Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's talking about the 3DS and talking about kind of the GameCube and how the two relates.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said in an interview that the GameCube suffered because Nintendo did not take opportunities when they were available.
[SPEAKER_04]: The general feeling within the company's management is that the console had a chance to succeed, but that the chance was not taken advantage of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Iwata has said that the company learned its lesson, and that's why they did a price cut so soon after launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting that they've kind of brought up the comparisons to the GameCube there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also wanted to mention this with the 3DS price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some rumors going around that Walmart is going to drop the price early.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to go to Walmart on August 9th, that's the rumor anyway, they are supposedly dropping the suggested retail price down a little early to the $170.
[SPEAKER_04]: What this means is that you might be able to get your cake and eat it too, meaning...
[SPEAKER_04]: if you can buy one of these things in that window between the early price drop and the price drop for everybody else quickly get it on the Nintendo eShop then you will be an early adopter so not only did you get the cheap 3DS but you got the $80 worth of games too so that's one way of working the system
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I guess call your local Walmart or check.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo may put the smack down on that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I don't know if you know from the retail angle, but could Nintendo stop this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if Walmart wants to cut the price three days early, can Nintendo stop that or no?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a couple factors that they have in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: One, whether there is map pricing on it or not, which is the minimum advertised price.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if they have map pricing in place on it, it may prevent them from advertising it lower than a certain amount.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, if they're being price protected on it, any of those...
[SPEAKER_05]: Any of those units that they sold prior to it dropping in price, they don't get any of the money from when it dropped in price.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they would be eating the cost on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I wouldn't see Walmart as a company doing this, but I know that, and none of the people I know or work with in the industry do this, but I know there's people out there to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can manipulate your price protection by fudging the numbers, if you will, and saying, oh, I didn't really sell as many units as I did, and then you get the price protection, and then you sold those units, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of ways to work the system, but Walmart's probably too big to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't think they would be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that they would be getting any sort of special exception either, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, I think there's a very small group that this would even really apply to because you're talking about people who won a 3DS, who didn't already buy one, who are really just waiting to seize an opportunity, like it's like couponing or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got the extreme couponer crowd of video gamers out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't buy meat until Wednesday because then it's on sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the crowd that this type of thing calls to because that means you have to have $170 burning a hole in your pocket right now saying I'm dropping it on a 3DS because I need to be an early adopter and I know I want a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: so I don't know if that is really a whole lot of people but if it's you start calling places like on or even you know get out in the car and go to some different places on the 9th what Tuesday and I totally lost track of time yes that's Tuesday and go check out you know who might have dropped the price early because you never know and you have until what Thursday night to connect that thing online
[SPEAKER_04]: Rage!
[SPEAKER_04]: Podcast Rage!
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, it's pitchforks and torches.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, that's kind of where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, hey, wait, I have Zelda Color Game Boy that I got for free, so clearly I had it during E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, I bought this, like, was it almost day one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it day one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember when I bought that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you had the Japanese 3DSs, like, heck of early.
[SPEAKER_05]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, though, I had it almost, like, day one, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Twinbee, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: But Twinby!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems interesting that out of all the 3D remakes they could do, we're in Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to admit, it's not really the first title you think of.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think Twinbee, though, if you look how the levels are laid out, I think Twinbee does make sense from a graphic sense.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because you've got your clouds with all the bells hidden in them.
[SPEAKER_12]: You've got your bottom layer with... So you can actually move your...
[SPEAKER_12]: Same way to Xevious, basically.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, basically the same thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I think it would work for the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it would be cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going back a little bit, since we're a little bit delayed between when we say something and when the live listeners hear it, because of the encoding and everything, Kaijudo in chat says, No, you'll know you're an early adopter because your eShop list will have a section for it like the PlayStation Network store did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: But how do we know the non-early adopters don't see that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we haven't gotten that far yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: could just be a place that's in the store it's like a heads up or something, who knows Zether in chat says, I hope Twinbee isn't Japan only for the 3DS, it's a good game I would imagine if there's money to be made, why not come out here but of course I don't know, the whole region this is Nintendo we're talking about and the same could be said of the last story, Xenoblade I don't know Zether in chat says, the thing is, Stinger was actually the second Twinbee NES game
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows what they might do with this 3D remake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably won't buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, me neither.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, if I was going to go buy Twinbee, I'd hook up my PC Engine and play my HuCard and play a good version of Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the old NES 3D remake.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not saying the NES version is crap, but I could play a good version.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got multiples.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, what I would do is probably just play Proteus instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: More news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, they've just expanded the bundle with Steel Storm.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, the average price is just a little... Well, at the time, it was a little under $5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, it's just a little over $5.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess Linux purchasers are paying a little bit more at $11.62 is the average there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually get the Humble Indie Bundle 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's another six games thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crenn, Physics Deluxe, And Yet It Moves, VVVVV, and then the set two was Braid, Cortex Command, Machinium, I can't pronounce that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't I pronounce that shit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Machinarium.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_05]: My mouth just didn't want to form the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, bleh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your mouth was mushed for Machinarium.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Osmos and Revenge of the Titans.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know it's a weird week at OLR when I'm the one correcting people on pronunciation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what is up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something is in these fries that DarkSakura made us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mouth-numbing awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like suddenly it's that level in Yoshi's Island where you touch fuzzy and you get dizzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all of a sudden it's like Loki's trying to read Machinarium and he's like, Machinarium!
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Made from the tears of Himalayans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to the humble indie bundle, which may or may not be available in Himalaya.
[SPEAKER_05]: How long are they selling this for anyways?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's only for about another week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a limited time, I know that, because I totally missed it last year because, I don't know, I was drunk or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just totally missed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I meant to get it, and I never did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this year, you betcha I got it, especially because I'd heard such great things about VVVV and I wanted to try it for myself, and I'm really glad I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm telling you guys, for as many games as you get with this, if you put in six bucks, you've got to get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So even if you're like starving student, whatever, at least pay a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go without a soda today and pay a dollar for just the Humble Indie Bundle 3 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the money, you know, goes to a good cause.
[SPEAKER_04]: It goes to wherever you want it to go to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can split it between the different companies and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, don't kick yourself later when you miss out on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't be a cheapskate either.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can afford more than a dollar, then give them ten or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give them as much as you would pay for an Xbox Live Arcade game or what have you at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I think the games are really worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'd like to see a humble indie bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Part four!
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Only day and a half, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Better hurry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Day and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have all the money go to charity if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the cool thing about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You better hurry up on that, especially those of you listening to the podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's after Monday night, you might already be screwed, but you really gotta check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on to something less humble, and wouldn't you know it, it's another story about Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom is testing the waters in Japan on something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a demo of a game called Nazu Waka Yakata.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an interesting title.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't use buttons on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It relies on sound and the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like this little trailer that I'm playing in studio for the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can kind of look at it here, get the sense of what this game's all about.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess you...
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if this is kind of like Seaman or something where you talk and interact with the on-screen characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of the sense I get.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a ghost.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has no feet and he's a ghost.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mika!
[SPEAKER_04]: Mika!
[SPEAKER_04]: now granted that's a cheap demo and one could argue that well you're still getting to play at least part of the game but uh doesn't something strike you as really really wrong about the concept of a paid demo especially from a company that's thrived on you know great word of mouth from free demos throughout the years like I don't know Dead Rising like a lot of people decided they wanted that game based off the demo Lost Planet same type of thing right so why now a change in the strategy
[SPEAKER_04]: was this maybe a part of the whole they were going to charge for the Mega Man Legends 3 prototype which was essentially a paid demo
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what is going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think of paid demos?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it a rip?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is it worth it?
[SPEAKER_12]: It depends on how much of the game you're getting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because if it is, like, a really in-depth demo, then, yeah, I can see $254.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, keep in mind, we used to get the PlayStation... People used to just basically buy the PlayStation magazine thing for the demo discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an interesting comparison.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the same was done with the Xbox magazine.
[SPEAKER_12]: The same was done with Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's not the first time they've done this kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, look at...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead Rising Case Zero Dead Rising Case Zero
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of looked at it as DLC that didn't require the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's why I kind of let it slide.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something extra that wasn't actually in the game that had its own achievements, it had its own ranking, it was its own kind of standalone thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: What if for people who've bought the demo for the game, they get something cool when the actual game comes out?
[SPEAKER_12]: What if that's associated with it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we don't have that detail.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a similar comment we have in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: ChalacesPop in our chatroom says, If it was a pre-order bonus disc that came with a cash deposit where I could use that money down against the retail version of the game and I don't buy it, my loss, then I'd be okay with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to buy a demo and then buy the retail version for full price?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd just wait for reviews and go straight to the retail.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they're going to have to work out some sort of perk with that or it's going to fail.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have to give people incentive, especially for such a bizarre looking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What an interesting way that digital distribution could go, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine if, and I guess to some extent one could argue you kind of have this already with some things, but what if you could play the first stage of a game by paying two bucks?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then if you like it, you buy the entire game for an extra thirty-eight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Xbox Arcade Game Room Game Room Game Room
[SPEAKER_04]: I think more about Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they did this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they chopped up Fable 2 into like six chapters and they put it out as episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they kind of did something like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, it was a while after the whole thing had already been released.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just wanted to sell as many freaking copies of that game any way they could.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slice it, dice it, circumcise it, whatever you got to do to sell the game bit by bit, little by little.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Milk that franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dungeon Buster says, Wolf3D gave you the first few levels for free, and then if you wanted the whole game, then you paid.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't pay up front.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same with Doom.
[SPEAKER_04]: One could argue that you might have paid for Wolfenstein 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I did pay for shareware.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had to buy the shareware discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you used to have to buy the discs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would go buy the floppies at the store that already had it on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that was fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing, though, about shareware, for the most part...
[SPEAKER_05]: shareware you could enjoy the game as a whole with just the shareware like you would get one campaign of it I guess but you could get the additional campaigns if you had the full like Wolfenstein you play through the whole first campaign but there's four campaigns total with the full version this is a demo this is not you know part of the game this is the demo this is Capcom figuring out ways to be dicks
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, whether it's locking saves or weird DRM, it's their way of, you know, how can we make more money and fuck people over?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's what we do best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, but this is not the same Capcom from a year ago that started Mega Man Legends in the first place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is Bobby Kotick running Capcom for some reason?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he like this all of a sudden?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he like, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fred Savage where he wears a bunch of different skin suits Did Activision buy Capcom?
[SPEAKER_04]: We just didn't hear Is that what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: So Alright Anyhow, I guess at the end of the day if you don't like it, don't buy it That's how they'll get the message It's a weird Japanese game that will probably never make it over here so that is easy enough And I'm saying it to the Japanese listeners all three of you Kitsune, IkumaJP, and I think there's one other
[SPEAKER_04]: All three of you, make a stand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three out of three OLR listeners in Japan reject this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, how about some news about Harmonix?
[SPEAKER_12]: We haven't really heard from them in a while, have we?
[SPEAKER_04]: I heart Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's new with Harmonix?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever happened to that... Sorry, I know this isn't what you're reporting on, but whatever happened to that freaking game they were supposed to announce at E3 that kind of disappeared?
[SPEAKER_12]: What you mean, VidRhythm?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, VidRhythm.
[SPEAKER_12]: They didn't say much about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No real details yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyway, they're happy.
[SPEAKER_12]: They like not being a part of Viacom or any other, you know, com there is.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, Tracy Rosenthal Newsome, who is the VP of production, said it's been a terrific opportunity.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I quote, We are very well supported, but really the most important thing is that there's a huge amount of creative energy that has bubbled up during our independence.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've been in development of Dance Central 2, and they're putting small games together, making prototypes, and innovating, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: They are still working on VidRhythm, which there's not too many details, but it's just been described as fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're not giving a timeline, but we'll be hearing about it soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, VidRhythm is made up of vid and rhythm.
[SPEAKER_04]: And fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: But right now, the focus is on Rock Band DLC.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's saying that Rock Band 3 still has tons of life left in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So...
[SPEAKER_12]: We can be expecting, of course, Dance Central 2 on Connect in fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any thoughts on possible Rock Band 4 next year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you think, no, it's still too soon to bring?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's too soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think, really?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was randomly thinking about that the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously all those games took this year off, except for Dance Central, but the plastic instrument games are taking the year off.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that Guitar Hero is not dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they've said Rock Band's not dead, but they're all taking a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wonder if it's a break until next year or maybe it's going to be a break long enough for the next wave of consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think right now it's just they're really trying to avoid that oversaturation.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've got a good product now.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're still selling something without having to develop anything new right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So as long as it's selling and as long as people keep buying the download packs, then there's no reason for them to make a new one yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan Central 2 is probably going to sell really well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll probably stay a huge Kinect seller through the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think everybody knows it.
[SPEAKER_04]: First one was a quality Kinect.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's travel around the world and look at some release dates and see what you can get a whole lot sooner than the holidays as in next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's coming out next week in America?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not much of anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hasn't that been the reaction for the past four weeks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing has freaking come out of here but Catherine.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was actually stuff last week, or this week I should say.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the next week there really is hardly anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what we got, and I'll run it down real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, can I say this real quick though?
[SPEAKER_04]: It did make the show tonight, but there was a big press release about how Catherine is Atlas' biggest launch seller ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already sold like 200,000 copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta admit, there is this cynical part of me that's kind of like, you sold that much because there's nothing else to buy right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is nothing else.
[SPEAKER_05]: it also helps that you put a woman with large breasts on your yeah that helps too that does help too yeah and all the trailers have been you know her sleeping with a dude it just shows America wants porno games think about it yeah they do um
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here's what we got coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: All DS titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Touch and Play Collection on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a bunch of casual games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hurrah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an adventure game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Puzzler World 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once again, another collection of casual puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing else to report on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it because kids are getting ready to go back to school?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's just a dead week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: A week after there's some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's travel to Japan and look at the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if it's a similar story over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll tell you this, on the Xbox 360 this week, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing coming out on the 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going over to the PlayStation 3, WWE All-Stars is released this week from THQ, so I guess you have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the Nintendo systems, seeing if there's anything coming out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I have the PSP up first on my list.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Monhooniki, Poka Poka, Ailu Muraji, and then Uta No, Prince Sama Repeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, those are the two games coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uta means song or theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: That first one, the Monhooniki, is a farm fish and hunt monsters RPG on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the second one there is, it looks like it's from Broccoli.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh oh, let me look at it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought Broccoli went into business.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, they're still there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it looks like it might be like a... It's a dating sim for girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pretty boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, pretty boy dating sim.
[SPEAKER_12]: Theme of the prints, repeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it could be like a redo.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's called repeat, it could be like a re-release or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Special Edition Whatever, I don't think anyone here is going to be importing that Kitsune, Ikuma, JP, any interest in that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking no and that's that's that's it you go to the Wii there's nothing 3DS Super Pokemon Scramble I guess that's kind of a big deal it is a Pokemon game coming out it's not like an official like Pokemon black or white type of Pokemon game but it is a Pokemon related universe game that's probably the biggest release this week unless you want to get like a new pouch for your 3DS with Street Fighter characters on it
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go!
[SPEAKER_04]: Your very busy release date schedule in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Europe?
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a few things.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, today, well I guess already, Dragon Quest Monsters Joker 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: On the 10th we have Fruit Ninja Connect and Hysteria Project 2 for PSP and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on the 11th we have Edge, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God we do have some people in Japan who actually listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Katsune actually is jumping in saying, Uto no Prince-sama is actually an anime in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it is an actual anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, I'm actually trying to... Opening theme.
Yeah, I want to play that.
Shoujo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just watching that trailer gave me a period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: No ice cream for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: More gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very wonderful image.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a uterus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's make a baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Click it, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a card RPG strategy game or whatever And it kind of looks a little medieval-ish And so Bethesda's saying, hey, that infringes on our own trademark, the Elder Scrolls I don't know if I'd buy that
[SPEAKER_04]: Monopoly on Scrolls
[SPEAKER_05]: Cables, electronics, anything
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, these people are what we call assholes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or their lawyers are assholes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, you know, when it's a generic, it would be different if it was like the Elder Cards or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, you got something there, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, if a word scrolls, which no one owns the trademark to the word scrolls, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have the Elder Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it was like the Elder Card Scrolls
[SPEAKER_05]: The Elder Parchments Armageddon That might be a case We're going to file a lawsuit against you so you little indie developer bear do what we want
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do big companies have to be bullies like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a double-edged sword.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically they have to protect their intellectual properties but at the same time they kind of overstep their boundaries and try to go after people that really aren't trying to infringe on their intellectual properties and that's what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because the people that make the games aren't necessarily the suits and the lawyers that are actually going after these people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's
[SPEAKER_05]: and separate entities altogether.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clearly this will get settled out of court.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means they're probably going to end up being forced to change the name and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they kind of stick to their guns and don't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call it Mind Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about some Connect news related on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently a rating has been spotted for Connect Fun Labs Airband.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that is the next Fun Lab that's going to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you guys know that that whole like be in a talk show thing came out for Fun Labs?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have yet to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess Sparkler's out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was Avatar Connect.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it's called, Avatar Connect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that came out, and then the sparkler thing that they were showing at E3 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played either one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care about either one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, at some point, you should take your Kinect out of the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll work a lot better.
[SPEAKER_12]: As soon as someone lends me his Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: He said you were going to lend it to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have Kinect Adventures to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go rafting.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I don't want to go rafting.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do Avatar Connect.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can host your own Oprah show as your avatar.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do Connect... Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Connect Sparkler.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like having fire in your hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't like fire?
[SPEAKER_12]: I want a para para.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like if fire was lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: And really, you know, how can you make fire lame?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yet...
[SPEAKER_05]: Connect Fun Labs manages to make fire lame
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I really hope it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I could relive that scene from Big over and over again, and I will be the life of my own party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: In about another year, wouldn't something like that entertain Josh for like 15 minutes at least?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even a babysitter?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: Connectimals would entertain him, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Connect Fun Labs, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like, hey, look, haha, look at all these indie guys who are doing all these hacks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We want a piece of that action, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come to Connect, because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's whimsical.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, all this shit's gonna be is fucking Wii music, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all this bullshit.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, even saying the word Wii music just flashes me back to the E3 press conference where Miyamoto comes out playing a fucking fake saxophone thing and how lame that was.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like, ah, it burns!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like you're suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm suing Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: PTSD from their damn conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX LIVE ARCADE GAME A MONTH
[SPEAKER_04]: We're targeting a frequency of about one a month for Xbox Live Arcade portfolio that will have Kinect integration.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will be really powerful and differentiate the platform.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, coming out very soon, Fruit Ninja Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll kick things off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fruit Ninja Kinect, eh, that's stupid, silly fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: But some of the other stuff that they had, you know, like the new Burnout game, just makes me want to cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout, a great franchise, great racing game, and we have this top-down thing where I gotta hop up and down to make my car explode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't Micro Machines, this is fucking Burnout.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I wanted to play Micro Machines, the top-down racing game, from like the 90s, I'd play Micro Machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Might be before the 90s.
[SPEAKER_09]: Freaking John Machida.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on, I guess, to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just running through the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hard to fill a three-hour show when there's not too much going on outside of kids going back to school and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially look at what's coming out this week in games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why not go back and revisit a classic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week here on the show, DarkSakura takes a step into the vault and finds a classic video game that she thinks, hey, you ungrateful brats, study this.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what game did you pick?
[SPEAKER_12]: I picked a really fucked up game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Game series, I should say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Black Matrix.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's actually Black Slash Matrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that like Keanu Reeves?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's actually a tactical RPG series.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's sort of like... It kind of does like a mimicking of Christian religious themes, but it's kind of different.
[SPEAKER_12]: It has heaven, hell, earth, and all the people that live there.
[SPEAKER_12]: and the first one came out in 1998 for the Sega Saturn and it was just so weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: First of all, you play as a different character who belongs to a dominatrix of some sort and then you fight sort of like you've got your move, your attack, your item that's all a turn-based strategy game type of game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't really quite get into it, but it had a very interesting story, I should put it that way.
[SPEAKER_12]: You also had counters, you could defend, you could dodge attacks, you also had a waiting attack, you also had magic commands, you also had different spell effectiveness that changed from turn to turn that was controlled by biorhythms.
[SPEAKER_12]: you had instead of magic points you had blood points and you can distribute your blood points to all the usable characters to use for their spell casting and you get more by attacking defeated enemies so you basically kill them and steal their blood
[SPEAKER_12]: and then you can actually put blood points into weapons to unleash a special attack called its latent ability or you could make it more effective you could add different types of damage that the weapon would deal and then after each battle you get a letter grade rank depending on how well you did and so you get bonus items, money and experience depending on how well you did in battle which I thought was a really cool system
[SPEAKER_12]: So basically, the main character of the first one is named Abel, who is an amnesiac, and he is the main protagonist of Black Matrix.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's basically an angel, and he's locked up in the prison for the crime of love.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, uh, he can change, uh, black wings into white wings and all kinds of different stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then you get your different, um, masters, your dominatrixes.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, you have Demina, Purika, Michette, Cureshus, and Prob.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, who I always used to just call Plague, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: You also could get a male master named Zero who was available after a code.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you had all kinds of different ones.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then Black Matrix 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, let me go back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I should actually talk about Black Matrix AD Advanced and then Black Matrix Cross are in the same series.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're the same game pretty much.
[SPEAKER_12]: They just add different elements to the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I forgot to mention those.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we got, okay, Black Matrix 2 came out for the PlayStation 2 on March 28, 2002, and it's set in the Hell Realm.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's, again, more of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have, instead though, you have your main character, who was like the strongest devil in Hell, and then he got amnesia.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so, you know, it has, the story actually revolves around that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Black Matrix Zero
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You really cannot get them in English unless someone has managed to do some kind of patch.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're really fucked up games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, they have great music.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do have to say that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, that one right there?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's Zero Zero, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is First Battle.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's got great music.
[SPEAKER_12]: One thing I did like about these games is it has fantastic music.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's just the themes are really, really dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakman in chat wants to know who made this game, Cheech or Chong?
[SPEAKER_12]: That wasn't funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: It actually came out by Flight Plan.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was published by Interchannel.
[SPEAKER_12]: In case anyone actually was curious for a real reason.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of the titles actually did get considered for a North American release.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, because of the religious themes in it, I would actually have to say pretty sacrilegious themes in it, it got the boot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think we were supposed to get... Could they have just changed the art or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't there other ways they can kind of get around it?
[SPEAKER_12]: They can release anime with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: They should be able to release a video game with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Black Matrix just had a pretty interesting story.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, but the first one was really, in my opinion, the best because, you know, you have to work for your dominatrix mistress.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you choose your mistress, by the way, at the beginning of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week, Black Matrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Black Slash Matrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And good luck finding that one to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a friend who's got the Saturn version.
[SPEAKER_04]: But think about it, you'll learn Japanese while you play because it's not in English at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: So good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, but a good trip down memory lane nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_04]: One that I'm sure most people listening probably have never heard of.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for the first half of our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still have plenty to go here tonight on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some rapid fire news when we get back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to talk about what happened on Blizzard's call this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some really interesting updates on Diablo 3 as well as World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another lawsuit involving Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're never going to believe this story about Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually has nothing to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about all that when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live on this Sunday evening, August the 7th, if I look at my calendar right, of 2011, where we're taping the 423rd episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm starting to lose count, oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, we're going to get back into some rapid fire news tonight and do some quick stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so let's see, starting things off, let's talk a little bit about Borderlands 2, which I'm very excited that got announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be coming out sometime after March 2012, it's gonna be the next fiscal year for Take-Two, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a little bit of a tease in the new Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the details have kind of leaked out about it so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the new playable characters is going to be Salvador, the dwarf.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is what they call a Gunzerker, basically a guy that's able to dual-wield weapons, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, they're saying that there's going to be better AI as well as...
[SPEAKER_05]: The old characters from the first game are going to be NPC characters in this new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait to check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first game was just amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, DC Universe Online is doing pretty well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, they're going to be merging some servers into mega servers, and this is going to be happening on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't strike me as news you hear when a game's doing well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well is a subjective term.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, apparently, uh, they're previously hailed as super servers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, mega servers will give the players the ability to switch, uh, between PvP and PvE styles of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, I guess the last... Before it was maybe... Oh, hey, apparently we're playing listless tonight, except we're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think maybe before they were... You had to switch actual servers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had to have a player on each server in order to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now the servers are set to be merged into four mega servers.
[SPEAKER_05]: One PC, one PS3 server for the US with twin servers in the European regions.
[SPEAKER_05]: So wow, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess if you're playing in the US, you'll be playing with everybody in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: All five other people that are playing DC Universe right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: DC Universe players are going to write angry emails to the show I'm only being half serious I don't know many people at all that are playing it but obviously some people are I don't know anyone that plays EverQuest either but that game is still going although the way things are right now with all the server merges some players will be forced to change their names after the merge since two characters cannot exist with the same name on the same server
[SPEAKER_04]: So now you'll have to be XXXSeparoth69XXX Yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: And then finally, the first PS3 jailbreak raid in South Africa has one man arrested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't even know they were still going after people there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently they raided this guy in Parktown and confiscated $14,000 worth of computers, PS3s, hard drives, jailbreak software, USB kits, and fake PS2 games and original PS3 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: and they said one man was taken into custody at the Special Commercial Crimes Court but made bail.
[SPEAKER_04]: What exactly is the crime that these folks are committing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jailbreaking the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, jailbreaking the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: which really shouldn't be a crime in the first place well I mean I guess it's a different country but I thought like when it came at least to this country they found in a court of law that you can jailbreak your phone well your phone yeah because that's added to like a list of devices that it's okay and legal to do that with however the Playstation 3 is not one of those devices
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, they were hoping, you know, the whole Geohots thing, that it would actually go to trial, and he would be found, you know, innocent, which case would set a precedent that, you know, it's okay to jailbreak that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, him being a pussy also backed out of everything, and, you know, they settled that, of course, so he can get his job at Sony or whatever, and so there's no precedent set there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think he works at Sony actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he works at Facebook, but who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's still pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're not mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no reason for me to jailbreak my PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't play enough games on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let me do some quick stories here.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them has to do with that 3D TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember this announcement at E3 from Sony?
[SPEAKER_04]: Turned a lot of heads.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were going to be selling a 3D TV that came with the TV, obviously, it was like a monitor, glasses, an HDMI cable, and a copy of Resistance 3, and it was all going to be $499, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not really going to come with Resistance 3 anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's changed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they've decided now it's going to be Motorstorm Apocalypse instead of Resistance 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps they want folks to buy the game separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they don't want to be giving it away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perhaps that Motorstorm Apocalypse didn't sell as well as they'd planned and they are sitting on a ton of them and they need to get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: You also get a free copy of E.T.
[SPEAKER_04]: for the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just throwing that in there for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how Sony got a hold of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they moved their corporate offices to New Mexico.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: In Motorstorm Apocalypse, it's sad that it didn't sell as well as they had hoped.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, I think people were hoping to get Resistance 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, I'm not sure if it made our show roll, but if you pre-order through GameStop, you still do get Resistance 3 and Motorstorm Apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that would require pre-ordering through GameStop And I hate them so much, I'm not going to do that Why would you pre-order a TV through GameStop?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't do that, do not be tempted by this Amazon will match it, somebody will match it Just wait Anyhow, let's see Apparently there was a statement made to GameSpot That, not GameStop, but GameSpot I want to start a website called GamePots Because apparently there's this
[SPEAKER_04]: Every way, which way you can rearrange that word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Motorstorm Apocalypse, it will have the full screen but split screen functionality.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that whole, you know, 3D but one person will see one screen and one will see the other?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've played that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be in Motorstorm Apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played with MLB 11, the show, which I really didn't want to play MLB See, they had a demonstration during our little Game of Summit thing I wanted to play Motorstorm But no, the two guys working the booth decided Hey, we're a fan of baseball, we're going to play baseball It's about us, not the consumer So I played that, and it works I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: Lollipop Chainsaw
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also a partnership now with Katakawa Games that Warner Brothers will have moving forwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: So more cheerleaders fighting more zombies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: They said, quote, when we first saw and got our hands on the game, we fell in love with it That quote from Square Enix London Studios General Manager Lee Singleton It's a great big bucket of fun I think it's a good idea that they picked it up I don't know why Activision got rid of it
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you might be wondering, Square Enix and True Crime?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the heck?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that mean Cloud is coming to the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget, Square Enix now includes Eidos.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this would not be out of the realm of possibility for, you know, that group that brought, what, Deuce X and, you know, some of those other games that now fall under the Square Enix banner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just Dance 3 is getting a Just Create mode that lets players record their own choreography and challenge online and offline players to fit it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's just practice right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a trailer out for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm ambivalent, of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then we have very sad news.
[SPEAKER_12]: This makes me sniffle because...
[SPEAKER_12]: The CEO and founder of Game Arts, Takeshi Miyagi, actually died on July 29th.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I've reviewed a number of games that have come out of Game Arts, including Grandia, Sylphid, Lunar, and very sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: He will be succeeded by Ryu Okoriyama, who is a CEO of Gaia Holdings.
[SPEAKER_12]: And last little bit for Rapid Fire is there are pre-order skins available for the new Batman Arkham City game that are going to be related to wherever you happen to pre-order them from and there will be download content.
[SPEAKER_12]: It hasn't said yet though if these are going to be available to everybody maybe through a purchase or whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the different ones that they have is that you can have the 1970s Batman skin which
[SPEAKER_12]: is through shop2.net and Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shop2.net, by the way, is a UK retailer.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can get the Batman Beyond skin through gamestop.co.uk or mightyape.co.nz.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's New Zealand or UK.
[SPEAKER_12]: you also get the Dark Knight Return skin which will be if you buy it at any store if you buy the collector's edition at any store there's the animated series version that is if you get it from Mighty Apes that's again New Zealand there's Earth 1 Batman which is again through Mighty Ape and then there is the Robin Batman which is available through Best Buy or Gamesmania.be which is Holland or JB Hi-Fi for Australia I want the Adam West Batman
[SPEAKER_12]: It's there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where do I get that?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll link the picture to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but where do I get that in America?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pre-ordering that from.
[SPEAKER_12]: That one is Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like I said, the 1970s Batman.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have burning hatred for Toys R Us, so that'll work.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually more like the comic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can go be a Toys R Us kid.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's more like the 1970s comic version, but that was the same as the Adam West one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's Adam West, Batman and Me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the one I want to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except, you know, he doesn't have the drawn-on eyebrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: That or animated series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the animated series one, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, that Michael Keaton one's kind of awesome, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one way on the right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that Michael Keaton, Batman?
[SPEAKER_12]: The one on the far right is actually, I do believe, the Robin Batman.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's on the far left, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's Batman Beyond.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_12]: So in order on this one, let me see if I get it right.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have from left to right, you have the Batman Beyond one, you have the Dark Knight Returns, you have Earth 1, 1970s animated series, and Robin's Batman.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just keep in mind, Dick Grayson took over as Batman for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know who they have, or know who one of the characters is going to be that they haven't announced yet, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nightwing, actually, is going to be one of the characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is shaping up to be more and more awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, then let me see something real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I just want to say quickly in our chat room, Breakman in the chat room at chat.orangelandradio.com says, Can I get George Clooney nipple Batman?
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I was incorrect.
[SPEAKER_12]: Robin gets the Red Robin skin.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was incorrect.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not the picture of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red Robin as in the mascot for Wonderful Burger Chain?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's almost as cool as Fighting is the Perfect King.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I could support George Clooney Nipple Batman being in the game because that means that Mr. Freeze might show up and it might be really bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Allow me to break the ice Cold Freeze Cold Freeze Cold Frozen Ice Cold Chill Chilling Winter Ice Winter Ice Chill Cold Ice Cool Freeze Chill Freeze Winter Ice Cold Cool Ice Frost Winter Ice Freezing Ice Cool Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Freeze Let's
[SPEAKER_04]: Kick some ice!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, some quick plugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out one of our other shows we produce, The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth, www.hordehouse.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all things World of Warcraft, which, funny enough, we're actually getting into a couple Blizzard stories coming up here, but there are things that go beyond just WoW and possibly affecting some other games, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a little bit of a crossover tonight going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We're hoping to talk to some indie developers and spotlight more indie games here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, we've talked a lot about the Humble Indie Bundle tonight, which is a great place to start, but we want to try and talk to some of the developers themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you or anyone you know is developing an indie game, either for the PC, a homebrew thing, maybe for the iOS or Xbox Live independent games, I know it's very hard to stand out on Xbox Live, that's for sure, so come get some exposure on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't charge for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I made that clear last week, but it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do it because we like your game, not because we're getting any money off it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So email us.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can email the show at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com or you can get in contact with us on Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can email me directly if you want, rob at orangeloungeradio.com because I'll be producing the new segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mentioned Blizzard a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some big stuff that came out of Blizzard on an earnings call this week, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Where Blizzard goes, the industry may in fact follow, correct?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so they announced a few things about Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, Diablo 3 is going to feature player-to-player real money auction houses for virtual items.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you're going to be able to play this game, find items or whatever, and then sell them for real money, or I think in-game currency as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you'll be given the option either.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Blizzard will take fixed fees.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't say what it is, but they'll be nominal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of the sale price, both when the auction goes up for sale and when it's sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when an item is sold, players will be able to keep their money in a Battle.net account for spending on Blizzard products and services or cashed out entirely with another percentage-based fee, although not yet announced third-party payment provider.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, if that's not good enough, Diablo 3 is going to require a permanent online connection.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not going to be able to play the single player portion of the game unless you are connected to Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things that they felt was really important was that if you did play offline, you start a character, you get them all the way to level 20 or 30 or 40 or what have you, and then at some point you might decide to venture onto Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you had to start a character from scratch, because there's no way for us to guarantee no cheats were involved, if we let you play on the client and then take the character online.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, their whole thing is, if you're connected to Battle.net, there must be no way that you can cheat at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it certainly would be a lot harder, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, exploits will be found in the game one way or another, but this is tricky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, I have to watch Blizzard very closely because I spend a lot of time playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will buy Diablo 3 because I loved Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: In some ways, the reason why I like World of Warcraft so much is that it almost plays more like Diablo than it does the RTS Warcraft games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is all news that definitely impacts, relevant to my interests as they say.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think a large part of what they're doing with the online connectivity and the fact that they say you can't cheat or whatever is that they do have huge problems in Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: with folks cloning items and buying characters that are made in China and so forth by shady ways, getting the characters all leveled up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheating, duping is a huge thing, and hacking and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game has been hacked to shit, and it makes a lot of people not want to play online because the experience is just screwed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think about if that becomes a problem, it's going to screw up their entire game because, yeah, okay, we're assuming that
[SPEAKER_05]: They're making the assumption that if it's connected to the Battle.net all the time, that's going to eliminate cheating.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to eliminate cheating, but it's going to cut it way, way, way back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're going to have a problem, though, with people if they're duplicating items and they're selling them for real money.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not going to be able to duplicate items because they're always connected, and the system's going to look out for that shit and ban them instantly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The real problem is people that buy this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if you buy gold for these games or you bought one of these characters, you're part of the reason this is happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've probably had your credit card stolen too because a lot of those companies like to do both.
[SPEAKER_04]: They sell you the info and then sell your credit card information to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Makes you happy I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the whole real money auction house thing is just the weirdest thing I've ever heard in my life.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the same time, if people weren't buying this shit somewhere else, they wouldn't have to do something like this, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're just trying to get a slice of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the weird thing about it for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, A, I'm never gonna use it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will not use the real money auction house because I don't really want to support it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And A, I don't want to buy this stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: and B, Blizzard's going to charge a listing fee if you sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Part of me wonders if Blizzard isn't going to profit off false dreams.
[SPEAKER_04]: That they're going to profit off people trying to list all these items for sale that will never sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of people that are saying, yeah, I'll sell items on there and make money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't hear anyone say, I'll buy the items off there and make money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's some other things that you need to consider too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I can guarantee it's not an in-game currency.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that means you're going to have to have your credit card in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: that let's say hypothetically somebody could sell enough items that they make a significant amount of money on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think anybody's going to make more than maybe $20 on this stuff, but let's say somebody does make a fair amount of money off some of these items.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't they have to claim taxes on that at some point?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't forms have to be filed by Blizzard or I guess whoever their third party is that they're going to get involved on some of that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Can you be taxed on not real items?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where the whole internet gambling thing comes into play is that
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no... I mean, Blizzard controls the drop rate of these items that they're then going to turn around and charge you to sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something about that seems really devious to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, there's not a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Check and balance to that Like Blizzard is gonna control It's insider trading Yeah, that's what it is, it's insider trading Like, that's legal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I think it's only legal because it hasn't really been done yet But I think this is gonna catch somebody's eye This is gonna catch the eye of a Leland Yee or somebody out there That's wanting, you know, the same way online gambling did It just doesn't add up to me
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, Rob, this is the same company that got a ton of suckers to pay $20 for a dumb mount.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never bought the dumb mount, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I ever bought were the charity pets.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were charity, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know some people who did buy those mounts, and they quite enjoy them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They spend a lot of money on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: and at the same time, I'm not going to tell a person what they should and shouldn't spend their money on to make them happy, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And if a fake little star pony that flies makes you happy, then go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't pay for tower bucks and tiny tower either, but I still play the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DungeonBuster says, I'm surprised that they didn't opt to let players into making a separate profile for off and online play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me too, but maybe they were worried about things like blurring the lines or whatever and leave it open to abuse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slaces Pop in chat says, that issue has come up before with Second Life where people were making tangible income for digital goods on their skins, house, digital assets design that they put the time into making and then selling on PayPal.
[SPEAKER_04]: The IRS had no idea what to do with it, but you can look up news articles about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a big deal when Second Life was still relevant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm really interested to see where this goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's my thing, and this is with the whole IRS stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they're going to tax you on in-game currency that you make, then I should be able to pay those taxes with in-game currency.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's always been the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to associate a value to this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say, for example, I sell some items in Diablo 3 and earn...
[SPEAKER_05]: 20,000 Blizzard Space Bucks or whatever they're gonna be under there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then somehow that translates to $15,000 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if I never cash that stuff out, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's digital.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not really worth that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, but if they're going to charge me that, then why should I have to pay in real money?
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's not real money, then I'm earning, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, keep in mind there are the two completely separate auction houses.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's going to be the auction house that runs completely off in-game currency.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll use that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I use it in WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why you're mad, because you can't cheat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm not mad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just think that it's a bold statement to say that you can't cheat.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is no can't, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: It will happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they'll be like, we ban you!
[SPEAKER_04]: You banned me from Diablo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Do people still do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really want to play Diablo 3 with strangers either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be playing co-op with friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe OLR people would count as friends if you wanted to play Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd go on a co-op mission together.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Blizzard... Diablo isn't really something I'd want to try and play on the go anyway, or somewhere that I can't have an internet connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have internet connections on planes now, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not an internet connection to run that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I get... I am being a little bit of a hypocrite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I admit that, because I'm okay with what Blizzard's doing here, but yet I'm not okay with Ubisoft doing it with Driver.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: from what I understand the single player of Driver doesn't have any online elements the single player version of this game now does have a real money auction house involved where people could be making money off of it and I guess they've got to protect the environment and heaven forbid somebody does cheat and now this turns into like real money that's when it's going to be a legal problem Blizzard better hope that having everybody connected 24-7 really does keep out the cheaters and they better really be watching that shit like a hawk
[SPEAKER_04]: because if somebody's able to exploit that real money system, it's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to news that came out about the next WoW expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DarkSakura, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been playing this for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rumor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I laugh every time I think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The name, apparently, that has been registered for the next expansion verified by MMO Trampion with trademarks and so forth is Mists of Pandaria.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Mop expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pandarias, of course, are named for the Pandaren.
[SPEAKER_04]: Living, breathing, walking, talking panda bears that made their way into WoW culture as part of an April Fool's joke and never left.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can't get the Pandaren Monk.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one of the charity pets that actually they sold there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The trademark was apparently registered July 28th, and it could be that this is going to be out in time for BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the expansion itself, but more news on it will come out at BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that the rumors say Pandarins will be a playable race, that you'll get to go to level 90, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: A monk hero class.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you know, panda bears are all monks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we had some discussion on this in guild chat not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, I believe that Miklatov was amongst the people because that's who I heard about it from.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we were talking about other possibilities that it could be like the ruins of the Pandaren Empire.
[SPEAKER_12]: That perhaps there's only a few left and you learn to become a monk from one of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we just got new races.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it could just be that you're exploring their culture like they're... Who are the freaking Walrus people again?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Kaluak.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I like the Walrus people.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: They remind me of Wilford Brimley.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, they all look like Wilford Brimley.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, um, I mean, it could be that, you know, you just get to visit the Pandarens and you learn from them so you get a monk class and maybe, like you were saying, level 90.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or, you know, we get more goody items.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, I mean, I would personally like to, you know, have another reason to do five more levels worth of quests.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite theory about this, though, is that this is just a Facebook or an iOS game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a spin-off game.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I hope that's the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be much more understandable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay with the whole archaeology idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I call that the archaeology concept, that you're trying to figure out why the Pandarens got, you know, all murdered.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't want to see everybody playing a walking, talking panda bear because that's getting a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really don't think that we're going to get them as a race.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, I mean, it's like every even-numbered expansion now has, I mean, there's only been four versions, has had a new race added.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was a new area.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Each one's had a new area open, so I think that this one's just going to be a new area and a new... Because, alright, let me look at it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just real quick, Mikulatov's correcting me in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Walrus people are the Tuskar.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Tuskar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the Kalawak is the faction.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad!
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, we got the first one introducing the world and everything, blah, blah, blah, boring, because it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then you get the Burning Crusades.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get two new races, one for each side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Demons, demons, and more demons.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get space goats.
[SPEAKER_12]: And pretty blood elves.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're fighting demons and fire.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was the Burning Legion?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you had to learn to fly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Burning Legion sounds like something you have to take antibiotics for.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a salve.
[SPEAKER_12]: And okay, the next one you get basically a new character class and a new area.
[SPEAKER_12]: So then when we get Cataclysm, it was against new races and a new area.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the whole world gets fucked up and the game gets made fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it would logically stand to reason that if they're establishing a pattern, then you'll be getting a new area and a new class.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it could possibly be... Okay, what was the level cap for...
[SPEAKER_12]: Wrath of the Lich King?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Burning Crusade.
70.
[SPEAKER_12]: 70.
[SPEAKER_12]: You start off with a 55 character coming from a level 70 cap.
[SPEAKER_12]: So given that the current cap right now is 85, I would think that maybe monks start off as a level 70 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you know what else Wrath of the Lich King had?
[SPEAKER_04]: It had lots and lots and tons and tons of ice.
[SPEAKER_00]: Allow me to break the ice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cold freeze.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arthur's that bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to draw that, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: It was some... Well, of course, somebody in our guild said it was all those cookies.
[SPEAKER_12]: That Arthas likes cookies.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I was going to draw a picture of Arthas lounged out like Jabba the Hutt eating cookies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saying, let's kick some ice.
[SPEAKER_12]: I should do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Pandaria, yay or nay?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm all for something new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard's going to do what they're going to do and I can't really control it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Firelands has been kind of burn depressing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, they can send us to, you know, they can send us to play with... To the land of P. We can go to Keyboard Cat who lives in the land of P, P, P, P, P. I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, as long as it doesn't have that horribly steep curve into raiding and doing all that stuff that Cataclysm did, as long as it's more accessible, I think as long as it just plays more like Wrath of the Lich King, to be honest, I think it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well...
[SPEAKER_12]: Now that I'm raiding, I really like it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that more people, it should definitely, there should be, maybe they'll incorporate easier raids.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, beginning raids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miklatov in chat says I don't get all the hate for this being a possible expansion I think it's neat that they are thinking of doing something completely not related to anything currently in the lore of the game makes it the most exciting part to me like I'm with you Miklatov take exactly what you say and I'm with you but then you have to remember we're talking about panda bears that started as an April Fool's joke being that new part of the lore like that's why I'm like do not want
[SPEAKER_04]: I like panda bears.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't like them that much or I need them in my warcraft, you know?
[SPEAKER_12]: And maybe the pandarins are actually a magical illusion of panda bears and they really look like, not like space goats.
[SPEAKER_12]: For the record, Space Goats are the best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to the email bag, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Every week you email us, and we might read them here on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: If DarkSakura's feeling saucy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or burpy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, I didn't have the mic up.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to read some emails for you right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: You better be nice to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gave you ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: You did give me ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was delicious.
[SPEAKER_12]: I found Samoa's ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was really fucking good, y'all.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the first email here.
[SPEAKER_12]: While looking at the disused televisions in the basement, I was inspired to ask again, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Does the Vault have a collection of older television sets as well?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure someone has to make adapters to hook up Atari 2600 or Odyssey to HDMI, but do you prefer the original sets?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: The only way I can really play the Odyssey is to get up to the original sets, but all of our other systems will work with the modern TVs.
[SPEAKER_12]: They make different adapters.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't have to use the little prongs to make it work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, can't you get an RF adapter at Radio Shack that will change it to RC?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you can get an adapter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just the one problem is that I think actually since the Odyssey was from, I want to say like 81 or something like that, there's no way to make it work with a newer TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I think you might expose yourself to some shitty lag if you use the converters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really do this in my house, so I couldn't tell you, but I think you do open yourself up to lag issues.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: That they were Xbox 360 demo units.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got monitors from them.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's what we have hooked up with a couple of switch boxes.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we have about eight systems hooked up in the other room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Eight or nine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hooked up to these TVs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, really, to be honest, we have two games on the Odyssey that I really have an interest in playing.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we don't really bother hooking it up.
[SPEAKER_12]: And again, like I said, we don't have anything to hook it up to.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the other ones, no problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: We can hook them up to just about anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although I really do think that...
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I don't think that we've tried the Atari on an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that last time we played one of our Ataris, we actually did have a CRT.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not like it's that hard to go find a CRT monitor anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I can go to the thrift store.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh look, a TV.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rabbit ears.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, I apologize for any confusion about last week's email regarding the voices of multiplayer games My use of the term character was somewhat misleading I meant specifically the volumes of online players speaking through their player characters not those of the NPCs Thanks again, Robert M
[SPEAKER_12]: I think we did address that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we were leaning towards the NPC answer, but I thought I had brought up something that the characters did sound further away, but I can't remember off the top of my head what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind, a lot of MMOs, you don't really do voice chat through the MMO itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: And those are actually kind of hard to find, the games where that happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, like, yes, you have voice chat in WoW, but nobody uses it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, nobody uses it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't even know it was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not in the public chat channels anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ooh, we have one from Silk.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, I started to play this game and even if it is an older game, I really love the story.
[SPEAKER_12]: The options where you can choose how to respond and that it actually has an effect on the story of the game is something that I really enjoy.
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes me want to replay the game and try different things just to see how the story changes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Perhaps I'm also just happy to see some proper blood-sucking vampires instead of the woo me and my curse and stare at you while you're sleeping glittery twats that seem to be ruling the media now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_12]: For the record, the email's titled non-sparkly vampires.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you ever start playing a game thinking it would be okay, but nothing mind-blowing, but the more you played it, the more you loved it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Guardian Legend?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because when you start playing that game, it's like, oh, I'm shooting shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whoa, there's an RPG!
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you ever started a game thinking that it would be okay but nothing mind-blowing, but the more you played it, the more you loved it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mr. Final Fantasy XIII No, but those games I kind of already had the bar set high.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really trying to think of something kind of outside the norm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me think on that for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think of any others actually when I got back into WoW yeah I gotta say World of Warcraft actually kind of jumps out at me when I first played WoW I didn't think it was really all that and I didn't think I was going to get that into it but you know when all my friends were playing and it became a lot more of a chat room with fire spells and swords so to speak I think that was actually a game for me when I started questing
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess you could say VVVVV that I played this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think I was going to like it as much as I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I knew I was going to like Portal 2, but I didn't know that I'd like it as much as I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, yeah, I mean, I'm sure there's a bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm still loving this show and I'm still waiting for my biscuits, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're with the tea and crumpets.
[SPEAKER_12]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're an MMO player, you'll love the attached image, I hope.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, let's have a look.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Nine Circles of MMO Hell.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm actually going to save this and post it on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLawnsRadio.tumblr.com Image.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll do MMO Hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do it after the mailbag segment.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just saving the image because I'm going to close the email.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, bite my behind, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_12]: Newsflash!
[SPEAKER_12]: The Tester Season 3 is casting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Info below.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll be watching, not auditioning.
[SPEAKER_12]: Robaba.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, I heard about this on Twitter this week and I sent it over to LokiOLR and I was like, Loki, weren't you saying something about you'd like to try a new career?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I will link it in the chat room and if any of you make it on there, plug the crap out of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I want to say...
[SPEAKER_04]: They were saying that the prize for the winner this season isn't like a testing thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like actually a role in production.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're kind of up in the ante on prize this year a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, Jamie's trying out.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God, you should.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sign up now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look into it and see if the prize is something you'd actually want.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, because if they can get me in any level of art production, that says my career right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe the prize is like actual on the production team this time.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it better not be peon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I actually have some skills to offer.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... It's kind of crazy, but I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you get on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually watched The Tester.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might I go so far as to say I enjoyed the last season of The Tester.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they could do a little more with it, but... You might also want to watch the show to see... Oh, they give you an option for them not to share your shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have an idea what to expect just saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh man, I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope DarkSakura gets on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that means she won't be on OLR for a few weeks while they're taping the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Party at Jamie's house.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yeah, but I'll be famous and you won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you'll get booted off first.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_12]: It doesn't like my password.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have any more emails or is it the last one?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: As Loki predicted, GameStop has decided not to honor the price guarantee thing, which does not surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, I'm not even sure I'll be able to get the 80 back from where I purchased it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bought it at Best Buy, and they didn't know about the price drop or didn't say anything about not honoring their policy when I bought it, but I have this feeling that it won't work.
[SPEAKER_12]: Either way, in my mind, it's totally worth it just for the GBA titles alone.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really miss the Game Boy as a platform.
[SPEAKER_12]: I never really got into the DS like I did with the Game Boy and ended up selling the one I had three years ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I've been out of the DS world for three years.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's where you come in.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd like to keep my DS for more than just retro GBA titles I bought it for, so I would like to hear some of your favorite DS games that might suit my interests.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you recommend as games that appeal to everyone and what specific titles would interest someone like me?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not a fan of RPGs anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hang up.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Since I don't have the time to play them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm more into shooters, arcade games, and platformers.
[SPEAKER_12]: I plan on getting Geometry Wars Galaxies, a Castlevania title.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which one is best?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, what was that one?
[SPEAKER_12]: Order of Ecclesia was really good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, Retro Game Challenge, WarioWare Touch, Trauma Center 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: I picked up Ocarina of Time, obviously, and Plants vs. Zombies download version so far.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Mario Kart DS is my favorite DS game from when I owned one before.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, I like, I got Puyo Pop, I mean Puyo Puyo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got Osutatakai Oendan, um, or you could get Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually really prefer the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, what else is in my thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah, um, what was that Professor Hatsworth game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Professor Layton?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it was Hatsworth.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like a combination puzzle game and investigation game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I kind of know what you're talking about, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: That game was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: What else, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: He named a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, gosh, you got a whole full plate there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Retro Game Challenge was one of the ones that came to my mind, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really good games on DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need more time to think.
[SPEAKER_12]: I should just go grab my DS case and see what's in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I can't see my DS collection right in front of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people are really into the Pokemon games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I play a lot of Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_12]: Since he's talking about Trauma Center, Cooking Mama's like that with food.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And don't worry, Mama will fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked the Kirby game where you draw the lines.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: and Kirby's... Epic Yarn.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, that was the Wii game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a different Kirby game where you would draw all the lines and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're making me think.
[SPEAKER_12]: What am I, a talk show host?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the old school, like even the Mario 64 port is actually really good too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Elite Beat Agents says Dungeon Buster and Chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I said that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I said Oendan, but I said you can get it as Elite Beat Agents, although I prefer Oendan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, there's Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's RPG though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked it though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakman Civilization Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really liked that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I liked it on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know how well I should get my DS custom look.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then again, I've got like a box of games.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'll lend you one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe I'll sell you some of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I might not be listening live because of work early in the morning I'm on the east coast so if the chat has any good recommendations too I would love to hear those in the podcast which we just did oh he said he's not into RPGs but the Final Fantasy 4 remake is so fucking good like you might want to think about going back to RPGs for that keep up the great work with the podcast it's still my favorite out there by a long shot thanks guys SonicM88 oh and by the way I am playing Final Fantasy 3 and it's pretty good on the game see there you go
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_12]: My profile's made.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I love what Zether says here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meteos is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meteos was an amazing DS game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Electroplankton was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a great DS game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, is that it for emails?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And by the way, I've got a profile now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: I ain't got a picture, but I'll link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should put a picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to start filling it out with why you need to be on the tester.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will, but I'm linking it already.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: you have to talk about how much you love Sony and how you've been a gaming girl all your life I bet you'll get on I bet you will
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got some more news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we got the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We gotta do those.
[SPEAKER_05]: As much fun as I would like to join the tester, I would hate to have to move to LA to be a game tester.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you do know you have to move to Santa Monica to be a game, to do the production, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: She doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll be closer to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be closer to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, the problem is though, it's a judging panel that decides whether... Or is it challenges?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never watched the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's weird challenges that sometimes have nothing to do with games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's like we challenge you to like, you know... It's not like... See, because when I first heard about the tester, I was thinking it's that...
[SPEAKER_05]: I own more than 40 different video game systems and have decades of experience I'm also a graphic designer with a focus on video games and an experience in 3D design and Maya I could use a job!
[SPEAKER_12]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_12]: You should give a shout out to the podcast too Just for when you uh Just for, you know When I am on I'll do it in my video Oh my god, I gotta do a video I better be super cute Better get your hair did I need to get my hair did, my nails did
[SPEAKER_04]: They're still naming DS games in the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether says Contra 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakman in chat says, Loki couldn't do the tester because Loki doesn't take orders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki gives orders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mwahaha.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you looking at there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you doing a Tiny Tower cheat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that what's happening?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you cheat and you have 6 million gold in Tiny Tower, you damn cheater?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the crap?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am a cheater.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are a damn dirty cheater.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a jailbroken device.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do whatever the fuck I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's completely legal.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a lying, cheating sack of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you're not going to be a fucking game tester.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can't play by the rules.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could be an awesome tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, there was a thing that I saw.
[SPEAKER_12]: My picture, and it's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a... I mean, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played so much Grand Theft Auto, I could easily be a tester for their goddamn multiplayer stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know the ins and outs of all of their Grand Theft Auto games, including the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know shit that they probably don't even know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then, again, I don't want to compete on a show where I have to compare images to see what's different.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I wanted to do that, I'd buy a DS. ...
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Breakman says when you apply for the job, DarkSakura, just tell them you know the Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be hired on right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: After all, he is a trending topic in Sacramento this evening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, my FU of the week goes to me not having a copy of Black Matrix.
[SPEAKER_12]: I found it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_12]: No one will buy it for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Boo hoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to Loki for cheating on Tiny Tower and I hope his tower, because it's so cheaply made, I hope that the material that his Tiny Tower was made out of just collapses on itself and the whole building just implodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have the blood of his bitizens on his hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, and you'll have the blood of all those bitizens on your hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, I give an FU to tacos for being so delicious and making me fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess my F you would go to the tester because if I were to win the tester I'd end up working at Sony and I'd look at the sheet of things that they want me to test I'm sorry, I'm supposed to test to see if this game doesn't suck I don't know, I got nothing I'm not really mad at anything
[SPEAKER_05]: It was surprisingly easy to do with the jailbroken device.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might add.
[SPEAKER_05]: Download a file, copy it over, done.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it didn't even erase my progress.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just added six million money.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so I see that DarkSakura has a profile.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how do I vote for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's a big clock in the corner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Voting begins in 16 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I can't actually vote for you yet, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I've added a second picture of what my hair looks like curly You know, it just occurred to me Derek H, I think on Dead Pixel Live last year had the casting dude for the tester on his show You need to talk to Derek and get dude's email address and just be like, yo, cast me That's what you need to do You need to just bypass this whole system right here
[SPEAKER_04]: Go directly to show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do not pass go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should all be on the test.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're not all going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going on that goddamn show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, it'd be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I go on the show, it is to be a judge because I would enjoy nothing more than the judge, the two of you sitting up there getting ready for elimination.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that guy doesn't know shit about testing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: He wasn't even a trending topic in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Loki, you're a goddamn cheater at all your video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explain why you should be on the tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I know where to find the information that you're looking for.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know to find all the exploits and backdoors for your games and how to get around this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't fix this shit, other people are going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, your Kinect is still in a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why should you be the tester?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my Kinect's in the box.
[SPEAKER_05]: My move is fucking on the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is why I need to be a fucking tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we have a goddamn Gran Turismo setup built in our house where we can play in a fucking race car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your name DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't sound like DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, because we have a $400 rig setup to play Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that we've built seats to play the setup out of the seats from a Honda Prelude.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have every Sony system ever made.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, here...
[SPEAKER_04]: This is fine radio and all, but there's a part of me that is legit worried you're actually going to get on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have legitimate concerns.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I get a job out of this, fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this could also end up very bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could end up being the bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen you go without eating for some time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not going to be pretty if you have to do something Yes, Rob knows what low blood sugar Jamie is like And you might have to do something that you don't like on this program And I am very worried I should sign up too, it would be hilarious Like what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Play Imagine Babies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, one last season they had some fucking challenge where they were out there doing army stuff Okay, I know, I know what will piss you off Working together as a team with people who are idiots That is going to piss you off beyond belief See, you're already fretting
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I will tell you this, because I worked with idiots at my job and I hid it very well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know how to be a team fucking player.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you teach Loki a thing or two?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am my own team.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, because his team is the voices in his head.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can take a picture of the vault.
[SPEAKER_12]: and show it to them.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is why you need to have me because I've played all this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legitimate concern that you actually may make a case for yourself to be on this show and you will actually be on this program.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look at this face.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look at this adorable face.
[SPEAKER_12]: I try not to.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gave you ice cream.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look at me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am for real serious.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to be on the tester.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do realize this is for a minimum wage job in Santa Monica, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: But know that Annie's up this season.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a production job this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means that I would be... A production job?
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's that mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll put it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Production is like... For a graphic designer, production would be like color editing, color correction, adjusting textures, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a bunch of spindles of discs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a bunch of cases.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need you to produce the finished product.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not how it works.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyone that's in production is in the actual building part of the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: You may be crunching numbers or doing some data entry.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would be something that's the equivalent of the job that I was just fucking doing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except I actually have skills to bring to the table.
[SPEAKER_12]: They could put me to work in art production.
[SPEAKER_12]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I would be good at it because that's what I'm trying to do with my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If I sign up for the tester, I'm going to do it in my costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you people trying out for the tester?
[SPEAKER_04]: You used to make fun of this show two years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you understand?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I need a job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you understand?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the funniest part about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What better way to get back at something that you hate than to be part of it and then be a complete asshole on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob, for real though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to win.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: And see, I want a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Frisbee.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to be the very best that no one ever was.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want a job.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, any of you people listening to the show, I'm talented.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hire me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because honestly though, because I was thinking about it, I would, if the job equivalency is what I'm thinking of, I would be making about what I made at my old job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will you be able to tighten up the graphics on level three?
[SPEAKER_12]: I could try.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to just show DarkSakura this real quick here.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I just want to show you this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, look at all those douchebags.
[SPEAKER_03]: You really are going to have to team play with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: You do know that, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, see, as Rob, as the one of superior intellect, I would actually manipulate them into failure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pick one of the contestants.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congratulations, 8-Bit Mickey.
[SPEAKER_03]: These 12 gamers will be living together in PlayStation Paradise.
I am one with the video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to hurt him so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have to murder these people.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had to do a dancing competition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to do a dancing competition, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_12]: I got rhythm.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll do all para para.
[SPEAKER_04]: She didn't even miss a beat in saying that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got rhythm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, have you seen... Now, this is hilarious because Joystick decided that they made casting videos for each one of the people on their staff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have some really funny ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, seriously, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll do Parapara.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you get the job.
[SPEAKER_04]: I legit hope you get the job.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll bring the video camera and show off my bemani.
[SPEAKER_12]: and all this other quality PlayStation shit I have.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, quality PlayStation products that I've spent my good hard-earned money on and my first generation PlayStation 3 so I can say, look, Linux!
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, look at PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether is linking me to a YouTube saying this was a tester contestant.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait to see this here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watch out, they're coming through the window Watch out, they're coming through the window
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that Rebecca Black?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, yes, it's Rebecca Black, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: All grown up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to say, if you go on the show, that's going to be you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we get a hey there coming through the window?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bite my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not a team player.
[SPEAKER_04]: You lied when you said you were a team player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki, let's move on with some actual gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maroon 5 has decided to join in the lawsuits against Activision over Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this case, it's Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is suing because Activision improbably uses likeness in Band Hero and...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great because he said he did the motion capture to have his avatar used in the Band Hero song, She Will Be Loved, but didn't give Activision permission to use his likeness with other songs, which it totally did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deja vu from like a year ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Levine alleges Activision asked other artists for expanded use of their avatars and paid them more for the process.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, it's last year all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, you know, the same thing happened with, you know, No Doubt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think they just want a piece of the money as well?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's really what it's got to do with, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because boo fucking hoo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're in a game singing other people's songs in their voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an avatar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: No one made you like... No one drugged you up and made you sing those songs on stage for like a live concert or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a digital...
[SPEAKER_05]: Character, not really you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they don't steal your soul and put it into the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, unless you may think that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not really you.
[SPEAKER_04]: My art is my soul.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when I sing a Miley Cyrus song in these games, that's raping my art.
[SPEAKER_05]: well here's the problem I didn't want to hear anything about Miley Cyrus and rape you put your songs into Band Hero Band Hero which is the poppy version of Guitar Hero you should have really put your stuff in the Guitar Hero not Band Hero or Rock Band alright I don't know what to make of this next story let's see what you guys think of it let's see
[SPEAKER_04]: Pete Hines from Bethesda Softworks figured that February 18th would be the perfect day to conceive a child, as the baby would be due on November 11th, which would be the ship date for the Elder Scrolls V Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another couple, though, that has conceived a little bit earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atari Lin, I guess, is the child, decided to come out of...
[SPEAKER_04]: The mom's womb as mom and dad sat down for the half-hour demo of the Bethesda Skyrim demo at QuakeCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: The father talked to Game Informer that I guess the sight of the Frost Dragon on the screen sent mom into labor.
[SPEAKER_04]: The couple hung around rather than dashing for the hospital because they thought it might be false labor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she loves Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_04]: They named the baby apparently Atari Lynn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dorks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they are one letter away from Atari Lynx.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they went into labor.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they didn't go to hospital right away.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the baby drowned at the thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they didn't want to miss the demo, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a once in a lifetime opportunity to see Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Kotaku, who first broke this story, so to speak, was actually contacted by the mother.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that she's actually still in labor and reading the comments, but I guess they are still naming the baby Atari.
[SPEAKER_04]: The name Atari comes from the name Ataru, which means to hit a target.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, yeah, that's what they named the baby after, is to hit a target.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ataru hit a target.
[SPEAKER_05]: This baby's gonna be a bullet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gonna hit a target.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not naming it after a game system that these geeks obviously named their kid after.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also do say, we assume by the time she's in high school, most of the children her age are not gonna know what an Atari is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That...
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, you know, it's just like, can you imagine when the kid wants to know someday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, tell me the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is so retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they're not going to know what an Atari is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because children don't learn history?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is, you know, the 13 colonies?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know because I wasn't alive then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, name five movie stars from the 1940s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: See?
[SPEAKER_04]: You couldn't do it, so maybe they can't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's the thought behind it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Fay Wray?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's... She's in the 30s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit!
[SPEAKER_04]: Ernest Borgnine?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's old enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: So, here's the interesting comment, though, from Skyrim director Todd Howard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's speaking to PSM3, one of the magazines there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do think industry-wide we would benefit from more games out at $19 or $29.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would try more games because I'm not going to try a game for $60.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tough decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then they went on to say that, yes, the $60 price point is still what Skyrim is going to be at.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there should be more games at $19 and $29, but Skyrim is still $60, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to say it, okay, all joking aside, the irony aside, he kind of does have a point, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: If games overall were kind of cheaper, it wouldn't feel like such a loss to try a game at $19 or $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the fact of the matter is most games aren't worth $60.
[SPEAKER_04]: 300 hours out of a game, I mean, that's unheard of in most cases.
[SPEAKER_05]: If only there were a way to try games before you bought them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could call it...
[SPEAKER_05]: or Rentine or Demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: If only such things existed in modern society, but us being so barbaric have not had the foresight to create such wonderful implementations of trials.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should tell the studios that spend millions of dollars in production to, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to put your game out for two bucks because no one's really going to buy it unless it's two bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I know you're working on your application, but do you have time for another story for us?
[SPEAKER_12]: I sure do well you know they just had the EVO tournament well they're going to have to relearn all their characters all over again at least for Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition a patch is coming out that will rebalance the game so right now it's really imbalanced so they're hoping to fix it it's going to be version 2012 and they did announce that at EVO Yoshinori Ono actually said that they've been location testing the version in Japan
[SPEAKER_12]: So there.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't have to buy it again.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just have to download the patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's good that it's just a patch this time and yet not another way to milk more money out of the same damn game as they've been doing for the past three years.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a couple more stories for you guys and we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio and we'll get to your Twitter topics as well at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, a couple last stories for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully, that wasn't the case, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Namco Bandai came out and said, actually, there is a way to reset your game saves on our game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what you do is basically upon startup, players can input the command abxylr and it will wipe the save data from the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, how they should have done it on all the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resident Evil Capcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: So there was a secret code the whole time just hiding out there behind the couch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, unfortunately that's not the case with Capcoms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that might be one of those things that they kind of announced it now just to kind of like cover their ass?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's exactly what they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because everyone's like, whew, okay, maybe I will buy the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's interesting though that there was kind of like, I'm imagining that feature probably existed for the purposes of like testing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you might want to listen up because this could be your future career.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: This could be something that was there for the testers to use that they did, you know, because sometimes that's where a lot of these codes come from is like the play testing of the game, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a lot of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the Contra code.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, all that stuff came from like play testing.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: So sometimes those codes kind of get out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, just maybe, could one actually exist in the Capcom game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe there's an A, B, X, Y, L, R type of thing that maybe will save the day for Capcom too?
[SPEAKER_12]: Could possibly be.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably don't hold your breath though, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, or else you'd need a dev system or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm noticing this comment from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: RDG Singe says, so are they backpedaling?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you consider this backpedaling, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, no, because I don't really think they, I mean, okay, maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because they did say, well, the whole purpose was to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What they should have said, yeah, well, you know, we originally wanted it to be that this is kind of an arcade experience and that's why you don't have this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if, you know, you really do want to erase your save, then here's how you go about and do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would have been the proper response.
[SPEAKER_04]: But instead they sent out something cryptic that looked like trying to crack a code from that horrible Nicolas Cage movie or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's drunk at Namco right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the end, all that matters is the end response.
[SPEAKER_05]: And their game has a code.
[SPEAKER_05]: Capcom's doesn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: So guess which one will be most likely purchased?
[SPEAKER_05]: True enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was on the fence about this game, and now I'm back in the maybe I will buy it column.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one other story for you guys, and I know some of you are looking forward to this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a game I play a lot of, but I know a lot of you play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, Modern Warfare 3 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember we were talking earlier in the show about Activision Blizzard had a conference call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, something they confirmed about Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's going to make some of you guys very happy, some of you holdouts.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be available on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out that cutting edge graphics and technology on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Modern Warfare 3 is going to be available on the Wii this holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently on November 8th, right when all the other versions of the game come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's being made by Treyarch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spider-Man Web of Shadows
[SPEAKER_04]: Modern Warfare 3 Modern Wii Faire
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that name for it, it makes it sound cute Modern Wefair
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But while we wait for some calls, let's do some Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to start from this one from TigerClaw305 because it's news that we forgot to mention and I think it's kind of important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metroid turned 25 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the old NES games are turning 25, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario turned 25, I think Zelda's 25 pretty soon Metroid as well, or Zelda did turn 25, that was part of what they did at E3 Metroid just turned 25 this past week Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: In related news, you're old Because I'm sure many of you have played Metroid in the past And that's now a 25 year old game DarkSakura, how does that make you feel that Metroid is a 25 year old game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Perky.
[SPEAKER_13]: Perky and full of ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to other tweets while we wait for some calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, the Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or as your name on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, right as I say that, we get some calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the one and only Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, one and only Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a, not a question, but something I want to discuss from a podcast a couple of weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we can rewind back just a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I wanted to talk about it last week, but it would have been too much for me to cover, so I have to spread it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if you remember, a couple of weeks ago, you posted on your profile an article about sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I was thinking about that, and it's like how the person said that you could say Mario Kart is also a sports game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do remember this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't it the whole article about don't be so harsh on sports games because sometimes they're kind of leading the way for other series of games?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was thinking, well, I guess in my opinion, you can't say that Mario Kart is a sports game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like saying WWE is actual legitimate wrestling.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to some it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, isn't Mario Kart something you might see on the Ocho?
[SPEAKER_04]: ESPN 8?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever actually looked at ESPN 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of that shit isn't sports either.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of the sports games, you have to have a bit of a learning curve.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to study the manual so you know what you're doing, what all the buttons do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas with games like...
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Kart, any of the Mario titles, you just pick up the game and start playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have to learn any strategies or tactics or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a pick up and play.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, I mean, but I do understand that it can be considered a sports title, but on the same token, it's not because it's, it's just a fun game to pick up and play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, a lot of sports games you can kind of pick up and play too, like, you know, especially the old school ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what's the goal of basketball?
[SPEAKER_04]: Throw ball in net?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, that was a sports game, but on the same token, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: All you had to do was push in the command for your play, hit the button, and that was it, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was amazing and awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you just called in to bitch about how Mario Kart Wii is not a sport.
[SPEAKER_02]: More or less, but I understand where the person's coming from, but I guess from the way I look at it, it's not really a sports title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though it can be considered that, but I'm just saying that's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, it's not a sports title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a family fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what you call it, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying whereas most of the sports games that EA puts out you have to learn the insides and outs of it to play it really well whereas there are other games that are sports games but you don't need to learn the insides and outs you just need to know what the buttons do and just start playing and that's it alright, fair enough anything else on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you should try out for the tester too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying out for the tester.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could be Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fucking fabulous, bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: A gay guy won last season.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to win two seasons in a row.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it could happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may start a revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could win it and just walk up and win it two snaps up in a B-Monte formation.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time for a girl to win.
[SPEAKER_02]: But won't you vote for me?
[SPEAKER_04]: You made her cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not a team player!
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, hold it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back it up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just so you know, I always have the back of Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, and Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Always.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no matter what, I will always vote for Jamie because Jamie's the number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Simple as that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always got Ook-Chan's back no matter what.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we've ranked the OLR hosts from most desirable to least desirable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am the cutest.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm the cutest.
[SPEAKER_02]: She put up with me for a weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that alone deserves a trophy.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I've got the best rack of anyone in this room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no, maybe Loki's is better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rama, I'm the cutest.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're more like the fabulous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fabulous.
[SPEAKER_04]: And cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done with Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Werenate.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the name?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Werenate.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I was calling because I wanted to comment on your Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you're going to be pre-ordering on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_15]: Most likely.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sucker, why is that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that all you got?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, because, you know, I'm a diehard Nintendo fan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Long live Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_15]: And also, I mean, like, I played Modern Warfare 1 on the Wii, and it was pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had online play.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why are you saying it won't have online play?
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta do the waggle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll have online play, but it's not gonna be as robust as, you know, with the voice chat and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd say something like Xbox Live or PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll just be...
[SPEAKER_04]: which might actually, to be fair, might be for the best because you don't want to play those games on Xbox Live because people are just rude.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, if you shoot someone or blow their head off in real life, do you want to have voice chat with them or do you just want to get the job done?
[SPEAKER_04]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The caller has a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I do want to have voice chat with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like the fact very much that you just blew off my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you should prompt apologize for that, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, you know, so I'm a Wii user, but I can't wait for the Wii U, you know, I think you all should be glorifying the Wii U, because it's going to be a pretty epic
[SPEAKER_04]: Not until we see the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: What we saw at E3 wasn't enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it, and I am not convinced yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, yes, they talked about some of these third-party games, but they talked about games that are already coming out this holiday that might not even really end up in their same form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they talked about the Assassin's Creed game is not the same game that's coming out this holiday for the other systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a separate game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm not sold one way or the other on Wii U. I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Outro Outro Outro
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you not see the tech demos?
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had like tech in on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be changing to more hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suddenly sound like you're underwater, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dalek voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he's got the Dalek voice going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The demos, it's interesting, but let me ask you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't the Vita and the PlayStation 3 essentially do the same thing?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm, oops, almost muted it, but the Vita is not even better than the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's got, well, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of relative.
[SPEAKER_04]: It depends on what games it gets.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about the processors, put them side by side, but I imagine that, sorry, Loki's showing off his cheating in his game.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's cheating, getting five million tower bucks from cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot cheaper than buying them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: As a developer, I hope that I can see some better games besides that roller skating game and roller goo on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the one with the guys in the Speedos trying to get through the walls.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a real fun game, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad you can say something critical about Nintendo, because I was getting a little worried that you were a little bit too much fanboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yes, I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their online as a whole really needs to improve, so I hope they do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say the 3DS has done some things right online, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't have one yet, but you can send me one if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might have a contest around the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I've got to let you go so we can get more calls, but thanks for the input.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: is taking another call here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yo, guys, it's Xenocore from the OKC.
[SPEAKER_14]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up, Xenocore from OKC?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just been playing a bit of Earth Defense Force 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, a game that's near and dear to Loki's heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not bad, but I'm not even sure if the game has an ending yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been playing it online so I can have some backup, and every time it gets to the last miss and it just resets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, is this a problem?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the very last mission, I mean, it depends on what difficulty you're playing on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ending's not very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't really end.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I never figured the ending would be that long.
[SPEAKER_14]: This whole game, it's the gameplay itself.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I do at least want to know what the hell happened because it's just like all your characters vanish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you just have to play it on a harder difficulty because each time you beat the game on a harder difficulty, the ending's longer and longer.
[SPEAKER_14]: it would have been nice if they gave you some sort of a hint like play this on the harder difficulty to find out what happens or something like that well I think they also have DLC coming so you know it's hard to say what exactly they'll be having and I've been playing the hell out of 4k kill team as well you're cutting in and out a little bit there but that's alright you've been playing the hell out of what?
[SPEAKER_04]: hammer 40,000 kill team oh didn't you mention this game on an earlier episode of the show I think you did
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I finally grabbed a hold of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not bad for 10 bucks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Definitely worth the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might have to look into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Trying to save some money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any new stories you want to talk about tonight that we talked about on the show?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I did want to comment on the whole thing about Diablo 3 going online only.
[SPEAKER_14]: and what company aspects of that are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're still cutting in and out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going on with the connection, but I'll let you get your thought out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can understand you enough.
[SPEAKER_14]: Blizzard knows that everything is possible with code.
[SPEAKER_14]: All they need is time.
[SPEAKER_14]: They do have to do something for copy protection, but honestly...
[SPEAKER_14]: If they think this is going to stop anything, then they really need to get their coding team and reevaluate who's working for them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because whoever told them that this is going to defeat online hacking is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it happens at World of Warcraft right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they ban players from World of Warcraft left and right too, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but that won't keep them from getting back in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about StarCraft 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are the issues that that game's having?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they having issues too?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they have their own variety of issues.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not so much because there's no real persistence in the game other than you think.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you'll see people do lag hacks and stuff to interfere with the other player's game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remove the fog of wars.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can see what your player's doing without having you nearby.
[SPEAKER_14]: More gameplay hacks more than anything else.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's even more critical to the play of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it does more damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very curious to see just, you know, how legally this all plays out, especially when the first exploit does come down the hill and then suddenly it's impacting the real money trading house.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got to be thinking of something.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got to be something in place they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, they're swearing up and down that they've looked at it from a legal perspective, but just because it's totally legal right now, too, doesn't mean it will always be legal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the other thing I kind of worry about with them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Especially when they have... The main thing between Second Life and this...
[SPEAKER_14]: Second line, people are making the assets themselves.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game isn't supplying them with assets.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you supply them with the assets, technically Blizzard still owns them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Second line, you have rights to whatever you create.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be very, very strange what happens, but we'll see what happens once the politicians pull their heads out their asses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard is going to be printing money with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Xenocore, I've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Skype's acting up, so take care, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, later, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to hear his thoughts on that, and I know he's cutting in and out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably a little annoying, but I was able to understand most of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go back to Twitter because I got to get through some more of these Twitter topics here and then I'll see if any more calls are coming in at that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: More Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR as I load them up here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually don't have a whole lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment says, I meant to email you, but can you warn people that deep vein thrombosis is serious?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get up and walk around about every two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, when they say take a break during a long gaming session, they're not kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really should get up and take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even when we raid in WoW, we take a quote-unquote bio break every couple hours for a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a chance for folks to get up, get water, stay hydrated, get a snack, go to the restroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just good practice.
[SPEAKER_05]: That guy sat down, I think, for 12 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we talking about the guy overseas that died or whatever?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what was that all about?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a 12-hour gaming session.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on to more tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple from Tigerclaw back to back here.
[SPEAKER_04]: North Korea's Kim Jong-il is running MMO gold farming racket is the tweet that's sent here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a news story from Game Informer delivered to us from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: The New York Times is reporting that North Korea is using a team of hackers to infiltrate popular South Korean MMORPGs and farm in-game points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Specially trained North Korean hackers working in concert with South Korean and Chinese operatives have been infiltrating popular MMOs like Lineage, accumulating in-game points, selling them on the internet black market.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, the Times say that they've earned over $6 million for their efforts, over half of which has been delivered to North Korean agents in the capital of Pyongyang.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so please don't support this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's just, I mean, look, people are going to do whatever they have to do to make money, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when you support it, like you're supporting devious tactics, like hacking, like credit card information getting stolen and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all going to ruin your gameplay experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Ragnarok Violet Ragnarok Violet
[SPEAKER_04]: it does not say oh no it looks like it is in US you can read the description on the app store and I click on it and it takes me to the US app store for Ragnarok Violet I didn't even get that sentence out of my mouth and DarkSakura I heard the click on the iPhone shut up it's free but there oh there's in-game items like you can get pet eggs and all this crap it's like a free thing
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to go, Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just lost DarkSakura to Ragnarok all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but the one problem is that if it works with my IRO account and I'm not playing IRO anymore, then I might be kind of SOL.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya in our chat reminds us about a birthday that happened, saying yesterday there was a birthday that harkens back to our music game roots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Taku Sakiakyabra, I probably mispronounced that name really horribly, turned another year older.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you guys all know Taku, or T-A-Q, not taco, but Taku, turned a year older.
[SPEAKER_04]: How old does that make him?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: A year older.
[SPEAKER_04]: A year older.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here you go, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy some Birthdayholic.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Birthdayholic for Taku.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to Black Lab.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember him?
[SPEAKER_04]: He used to come to the show years and years ago, like in the first hundred episodes or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's listening tonight and sends us tweets and has some Twitter questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one, will there be a drunk show soon?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gave up drinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question two, does Jamie still have that copy of Owen Don that I gave her?
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy face.
[SPEAKER_13]: How to get a Nintendo fangirl to try playing non-Zelda games
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if she's not playing non-Zelda games, then she's not much of a fangirl, is she?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you convince other girls to play games that aren't Zelda?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pass over your DS and say, here, give this a go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they say, no, I'm too busy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Busy doing what?
[SPEAKER_04]: My hair.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, well, that's important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Baking a pie.
[SPEAKER_12]: As long as they share the pie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing my application for the tester.
[SPEAKER_12]: I already did that there's always time for games
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm updating my echo phone find something where there's something there's like a Barbie mode where you can do dress up or customization because women like that shit no you want to know what's funny is that like I seriously think that wrestling games those WWF games or whatever WWE games are like dress up dolls for dudes
[SPEAKER_12]: cause seriously you can change your outfit I've seen Dan spend hours making wrestlers it's freaking hilarious alright oh and also you know changing the bikinis out on you know Dead or Alive Volleyball
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's going to do it for the Twitter tonight and the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for your tweets and your calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't get through tonight, send us an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com or send us a tweet for next week at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, I'm going to go over to Loki and see if there's any last-minute stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think there is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we got it all.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was really slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was kind of a slow news week, hence why it's kind of a shorter show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they can't always be action-packed weeks, especially as we get closer and closer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once we get after Labor Day...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just going to be go, go, go, go, go until the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that means we're coming to the close of another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to thank all you guys for listening this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for supporting our show as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you liked what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, please tell somebody else about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Word of mouth is all we have.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't even ask for money.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are the humble indie podcast bundle of all games programming.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't even ask for your money.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask is spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leave us a nice review on iTunes or whatever podcasting site you use to find this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It goes a long way to help promote the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thank you guys again for continuing to support the show week after week, showing up on Sunday nights, those of you that can, and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes it all worthwhile to be here again.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for Dark Sakura to make an audition tape that you all can vote on soon for this show that I can't believe she's actually going to go on.
[SPEAKER_12]: We should stack all of my Sony stuff behind me and go, look at this shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: You owe me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cheating cheater of Tiny Tower, the hacker who has five million Tower bucks that he did not purchase.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's basically infinite because it's not going down.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I have 13 floors already.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hire me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my final thought tonight is tacos.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks again for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back to do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_16]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_16]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!