[SPEAKER_17]: Toto, I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, for Monty Talk and then some.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
[SPEAKER_27]: You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I will spank your child.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my big opening.
[SPEAKER_08]: A sphincter says what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm super, thanks for asking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you little bitch trove from hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: What am I doing here?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dodge this.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is a tasty burger.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look, you stupid bastard, you've got no arms left.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look, there's a flesh wound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Searching for a boy in high school is as useless as searching for meaning in a polyshorum.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
[SPEAKER_26]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got a sniff.
[SPEAKER_26]: Skye.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
[SPEAKER_26]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_26]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live, and this is episode number 48 for June the 8th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're tuned in to the Beemani Scene's most bitchy radio station of all things Beemani.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miss Summers, if you're nasty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, I'm watching Transformers.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: In that corner, say hello to our TechMassa Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lied, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is episode number 47, not 48.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lost count.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody makes mistakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also with us tonight, say hello to nobody.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's empty.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a ghost town here in Orange Lounge Radio headquarters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody loves Orange Lounge Radio anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They showed, like, the crappiest Transformers, though, when they showed the commercials.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're getting phone calls as if we could, like, take calls on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting more carrots.
[SPEAKER_02]: How rude.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am being a good girl today.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you being a good girl?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm eating carrots.
[SPEAKER_02]: As opposed to?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eating candy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll be talking to us, ourselves, since there's no guests here, we'll just be talking to ourselves a little later.
[SPEAKER_02]: And first, we're going to take a quick break, though, featuring some five key songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: And this first song is called Waterflame, and it's by Kay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, a buddy of mine, Navi, who's been on the show before, he picked up the Kay album not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, lots of fun stuff coming up tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to do listless tonight because we haven't done it in forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: In the city where neon lights shine, that person left a shadow and disappeared.
[SPEAKER_13]: Suddenly, he said goodbye and said he loved me.
[SPEAKER_13]: At that time, I realized that memories are in dreams.
[SPEAKER_13]: They wake up when they're forgotten.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
[SPEAKER_13]: I do it, I do it
[SPEAKER_27]: It's more contagious than SARS.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you just listened to a whole bunch of 5 key songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't you enjoy that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Athletics with Disco Dog from 7th Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before that, Love to Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Athletics did Please Don't Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Athletics also did War Game, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before that, the Japanese version of Love to Me, as it's easily called, from Third Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's debatable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before that, GTS featuring Melody Sexton from Fourth Mix, Brand New World, and starting that off, K from Seventh Mix with Water Flames.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't get my single propeller open.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds like that Margaret Cho joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Water's flame.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, it's pretty mellow here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't really have a whole lot going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot going on in the land of Orange Lounge Radio this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, there were a lot of changes that happened at the station on June 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully they've been invisible to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been some positive changes and there's been some negative changes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is all due to Live365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Positive changes, we've been given a lot more web space.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we're gonna add a whole bunch of new songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Jamie brought me a whole bunch of new stuff to add into the normal playlist.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get to hear it all tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've got some good news and bad news.
[SPEAKER_28]: The good news is, I saved lots of money by calling Geico.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_28]: You're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, we're going to have a whole bunch of new stuff in rotation of Monty Music and more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad news is, and this is the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know it's gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I drank all my Propel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the interesting part.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're capping how many live listeners we can have at once.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's capped right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're going to cap our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's capped right now when we're live at a number which we've only hit during one show ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't want to say on air, but it's that many times this many.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we've only ever hit that number once.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what's going to happen is if we ever hit that number again, what's going to happen when you try to connect to the station where we're live, it's going to go, we're sorry, but this station is too popular and you have to be a preferred member.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're sorry, but you have SARS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you get that message, we're going to be aware of it that we've hit our cap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what we'll do for the next week, we'll increase our cap.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just don't want to have to pay any more money unless we have to, but we don't want our listeners to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're cheap bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we take donations.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can send us via PayPal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here's the next question is that they go, well, if you don't like all of my 365 rules, why don't you go through Shoutcast?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Shoutcast is the suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not necessarily that Shoutcast sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, for talk radio, it's actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, this is the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the sucky part.
[SPEAKER_02]: We play music.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the music part, you get into that whole licensing thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you could get into like, oh, well, you know, you're doing Konami a favor here, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think Konami cares.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Konami cares the station exists either, but let's just not take chances, especially because we bring you a lot of dance media stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing being is that if we ran a ShotKast server, all the bandwidth would have to come off our personal line here at the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but I'm too busy downloading porn to run a radio station off the computers here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm too busy downloading Transformers.
[SPEAKER_02]: We hope you have a summer to remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now let's have an update on our... I'm reading your apartment thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, our apartment is so lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to read the apartment thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Make a splash this summer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whether your idea of fun is heading out to the ballpark, lounging by the pool, or watching a spectacular sunset, we hope you have a summer to remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_02]: They also have a list down there where you can sign up to watch rattlesnakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just going to watch them rattle?
[SPEAKER_02]: What would they do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you eat them?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, yeah, we've got... Sign up in the fitness room for tennis, singles, doubles, Friday night, round robin, walking, running, biking, swimming, weightlifting, slash yoga, canoeing, slash kayaking, slash hang gliding, cards, slash computer games, rattlesnake watching.
[SPEAKER_28]: Seriously, have we left anything out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, hang gliding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can pretend like I'm in Pilotwings.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I really, really suck in Pilotwings.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, but, yeah, they don't have, like, rifle shooting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skeet shooting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does anybody remember that movie, Don't Tell Mom the Babysitter's Dead?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: The dishes are done, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're done, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that movie was the shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why I'm thinking about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just feel like when she shot the guy in the pants with the water gun, it looked like he pissed himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'm thinking of that movie today because I saw Christina Applegate in the commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so now we had our update with what's going on live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get our update with the host.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm happily getting some overtime now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything Mamani related?
[SPEAKER_05]: I suck at 2DX now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you suck at 2DX?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm like a month out of serious practice.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I hurt my foot on DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that using the pad that I have?
[SPEAKER_05]: That was playing at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was my butt foot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since then, like, my left foot's been swollen and it hasn't fit in my shoe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you been playing with my new dance pad?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I use the term my new dance pad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, over 30 days.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's legal.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a whole lot of other drama going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'd have that on VHS anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Some joke that was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, let me tell them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretend it was funny.
[SPEAKER_29]: Can you pretend it was funny for me?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the most hilarious thing I've ever experienced, ever!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge practical jokes and bloopers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this is what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki made a brand new remix, and we're going to premiere it for you guys probably during the next break, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sound good to me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll introduce that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess I have to tell you what it is in order to...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened is that Loki left, he went somewhere, he went to go over to his girlfriend's or something, and he left IRC in Orange Lounge up, and I kind of was just like looking, because sometimes I do that, you know, I'll see, oh, is there anybody talking in Orange Lounge right now, should I set myself back from away and join in the chat or whatever, and I saw that Loki had said, hey, I finished this new mix, da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Brad and Irene were over here, you know, Rice, Princess, and LankyStyle were over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, like Brad, being a big Loki fanboy, was like, oh, I gotta hear that remix.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, okay, well now that Loki and I live together, let me just get on the network and access Loki's computer and find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know where he keeps all his remixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went in there and played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, and that's when I found out, okay, it's Rob Zombie, it's Gravity.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm getting to a point here, trust me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: When Loki finally gets home, he walks through the door and I get him, I'm like, oh my god, Burmani style, they're having a new remix contest, and I heard the most awesome entry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, somebody mixed Gravity with Rom Zombie, and it's called the Twin Burnination Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki was not of the amused, but I was.
[SPEAKER_28]: The joke fell on his face before I stepped in the door.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was just like, guess what, I heard this new remix, right away I knew what was going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hoping that Loki would be too silly to realize that, you know, oh, he might have gone on my computer and did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But see, Loki knows I'm a big old snoop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, no, I wouldn't look at anything else, just his remixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wouldn't share anything else on his computer, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I'm porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do have your porn shared, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, no, it's not shared, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Poor Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're so mean to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heteroporn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heteroporn.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't be interested in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: True or false.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is dick in heteroporn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some heteroporn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And where did the, what was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ellie McFeel.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Adam McFeel?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess and Lanky Style are getting through a friend at Rocky Horror.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been getting all these pornos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ally McFeel, Horror of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know Q. You know Q. Q, the guy that looks like Striker's son from X2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the DVD exchange hands after the pate thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see X2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember Striker's son?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Q.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure No?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Dark Sakura Burnination Mix
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, this is bad.
Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here is punishment.
This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is fucked up!
Oh, this is bad.
This is fucked up.
Here is justice.
Here is punishment.
Here.
This is fucked up.
Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops, hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oops, that was fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, Loki vs. Tack featuring Rob Zombie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gravity!
[SPEAKER_02]: The DarkSakura Burnination Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's say hello to our new guest that just arrived during that little song.
[SPEAKER_02]: New?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a noob.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're new tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's new!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, LankyStyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's up, guy?
[SPEAKER_02]: See, the reason why we played that is I was telling the story about Oracle's practical jokes and bloopers about how I joked with Loki last night and said it wasn't funny at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was funny to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: The night before, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was funny because you were so horrible at lying to him.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no way.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as you walked in, you said, Wow, I heard this awesome reading, but if you could see the look on his face, like, Oh, I know what he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He found the MP3 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's exactly what he said ten minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good minds think, or great minds think alike, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello also to the Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, how are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Crush tonight?
Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: For you and Jamie especially.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she's tailor-made this one for me and Jamie apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This should be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a kick in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: This should be very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have that to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Jamie, did you have anything else you wanted to say about your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of cut you off with my whole blooper story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a bad man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Show?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a cookie, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then my week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: My week was my last week of indulgence before I'm a good girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're going to be on diet?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a diet, it's a lifestyle modification.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a lifestyle modification, amen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am cutting down to one, because I found out that working where I do, I cannot give up soda completely.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need caffeine and I need sugar.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm cutting to one soda a day and it's balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I drink balls at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're going to drink soda, why not drink the worst one for you?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'll drink one with the worst caffeine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Jolt would be worse than balls, probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: Much worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am exchanging all of my cookies and fun sweet stuff for carrots and broccoli.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm going to not eat chocolate that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to have carob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew, carob makes you poo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything makes me poo, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: With my really crappy digestion, I will eat what I can get.
[SPEAKER_03]: This show makes me poo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It obviously makes Rob poo because you're in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I ran to turn on the AC.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because... No, not applesauce.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's because Brad and Irene entered the room and it just got too hot in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's getting hot in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's something rotten here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You better hold your nose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, by the way, I haven't whored out the chat room yet tonight, so I probably should.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're listening and you want to join in the fun in our chat room, because there's a whole clusterfuck of people there tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, fuster cluck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to www.callybomani.com, click on Orange Lounge, and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't forget about our LiveJournal community, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.livejournal.com slash users slash Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, post there, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we need people to post.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, you need to assign people a topic for this week to post about in Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like an essay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be an essay project.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best Bomani song to fuck to.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we want to know, in the Orange Lounge Live Journal community, the best Bomani song to fuck to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diamond Jealousy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Holick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the worst porn ever two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was something that, um, that, uh, Jabberwocky had.
[SPEAKER_26]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: We were watching our movie night, and, like, I had to leave before the anime actually started.
[SPEAKER_26]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was some, like, really rotten, horrible, like, camcorder porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this woman had a wart.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was straight, like, trailer trash hooker or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we, like, they showed this, like, shot of, of her area.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a big ol' wart.
I was like, eww.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did it have a name?
[SPEAKER_03]: The wart?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the wart.
[SPEAKER_03]: The wart had a name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bubba.
[SPEAKER_02]: FYI, our ever-faithful Black Lab, our correspondent for the People's Republic of Kansas, Ben, and I'll hope you enter here.
[SPEAKER_02]: TM.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: He is posting that in the community right now so that it will not be forgotten.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, while we were talking about porn and Bomani, I thought this would be a good chance for me to ask Loki about his week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about my week?
[SPEAKER_20]: It was pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_20]: My girlfriend had her 21st birthday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happy birthday!
[SPEAKER_20]: She was 21 on Wednesday, so she's happy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, she could have been happier because also for her birthday she got strep throat, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: She's still sick, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I guess you guys didn't go dancing or some club or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, like we never do that anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go drinking, go to a porn strip club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, that's 18.
[SPEAKER_19]: She can't drink anyways because of her disease.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's no good.
[SPEAKER_28]: But no, we just hung out and stuff and that's all.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yeah, I'm sure the thing Rob is wanting me to talk about.
[SPEAKER_23]: Tell us, Loki, tell us.
[SPEAKER_20]: I believe last week we mentioned that I was going to be getting a certain video coming in over eBay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Coming in.
[SPEAKER_20]: And this video that I have received, and it's funny because we only missed it by one day, too.
[SPEAKER_28]: This video is called Dance Dance Fuck.
[SPEAKER_28]: D.D.F.
[SPEAKER_28]: Eat me raw.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was supposed to be...
[SPEAKER_20]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's DDF 6 Mix, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there a 1.5?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that the Chicks with Dicks episode?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea, but we're going to hear a little bit here of DDF.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you guys want to see?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't worry, it's children's safe because it's mosaics, like all Japanese porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rated R porn.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like porn that would be on VH1 if they ever had porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like Showgirls with the drawn-on bikinis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here it is, the intro screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the sound should be going through.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going through the little intros right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like DNA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's from Deep 5 Studios, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is that Deep's?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance, dance, fuck!
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the star, Wakabayashi Habayashi or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's the biggest pair of camel lips I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there they go.
[SPEAKER_02]: To describe the scene for you guys, it's just some chick in a nightclub wearing a bunch of silver.
[SPEAKER_02]: And rubbing herself.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's rubbing and feeling herself.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then she's just kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: And this has nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not dancing on a DDR pad or anything, it's just... Oh, head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Occasionally on the screen it will flash, DD, DD, Dance Dance Fox 6 Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think back in the early 90s, except it's like, the grind in Japan, on MTV.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I think, yeah, Jamie says with fucking, but I think if it was the grind in Japan, there would probably be fucking anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right on there, on TV.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's give it a head here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's definitely really any good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the cool thing about Dance Dance Fuck 6, Nick,
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely nothing to do with DDR at all, except for the fact that sometimes on the screen it'll flash the title, Dance Dance Fuck, and they're in a nightclub and they're dressed like nightclubs.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're dressed like Kara chicks without the boots.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm gonna go sit over here now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that sucks now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want my socks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Camera 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, there's milky angles or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it just says Camera 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's dancing.
[SPEAKER_05]: This music isn't any good, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Loki, what would you say about putting this in a sim?
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, I should do that for a random video.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I still enter Tournament 4?
[SPEAKER_28]: You have 4?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, but I'll get to Tournament 4 later, because we've got news on that too, but... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where can I get the soundtrack for this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's one song, so... It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh, we got another song.
[SPEAKER_03]: This could be Tak.
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_13]: This sounds like I've got the rage on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: And again, it's the same girl in the silver dress who's got like... She's like the slut of the nightclub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn, I wish Tourney Mix 4 wasn't closed, because I would so envy this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, she has her slutty friends with her.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'd have this in the background, just a video, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's always Tourney Mix 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: coming soon to screen near you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, dance, dance, fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's getting tongue now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not... Ew, that's not even slightly erotic.
[SPEAKER_02]: At all.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looks like something out of a sci... Oh, my God!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a history... I mean, an animal planet or something, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Discovery Channel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like something out of a bad science fiction movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like something from Anti-Anime.
[SPEAKER_28]: That guy does not know how to make out at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: He's like, what am I doing here?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's riding me.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we can turn off the bad porn now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was really awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's ten minutes of my life I'm never getting back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance, fuck, six mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So is that all you want to say about your week?
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't do too much of them and make the remix.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else did I do?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't do really much of anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Slap.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's tired.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Still trying to get the phones working.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Find it eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Suddenly Susan's been off the air for a couple years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, I don't watch TV, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he looks dorky now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, he's still, you know, cute, but with his haircut he looks really dorky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not when he was young and hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Breakfast Club's cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: He looks dorky in a not cool way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not like Elijah Wood, you know, he's dorky in a cool way, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: LankyStyle, since you ruthlessly took the mic away from Jamie, you want to tell us about your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: My week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm just the same old me, you know, unemployed, playing Rhinerox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, let me think if anything special happened besides the, you know, thing you found out about today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want me to tell you about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Today, I mean, I got an email June 2nd, but it went to my garbage folder, my, my, my
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuckin' junk mail folder for hotmail because they suck and they can't decipher I usually get the enlarge your penis emails like right to my inbox But all the other stuff that's not junk mail goes to my junk folder So I didn't check it until today, which is what, the 8th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I got accepted to be a Final Fantasy XI beta tester And they're sending me my shit, and that's gonna be pretty cool On Windows Yay Yeah, yay, it's cool So if anybody, we can talk about, you know
[SPEAKER_02]: How the game looks to people, if people listening want to hear, you know, might be interested in getting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'd be curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, but I don't know when it's going to get here, so I'll let everybody know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know Jamie, and did you and your fianc both apply?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie played for the PS2 beta, and I played for the Windows beta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_29]: I can play that while I'm playing Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_29]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_29]: Does anybody else we know sign up to beta test?
[SPEAKER_29]: I've never seen Ragnarok.
Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Irene's saying that she's never going to see me again because I've got Riding Rock and Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they have a launch date for Final Fantasy XI on computer yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: There might be, I just haven't been looking into it because I'm just like, hey, I'm a beta tester, so I get to play it before everybody else.
[SPEAKER_13]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not everybody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anywho, I don't know anybody else who is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I think it's just me, Jamie, and Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck to you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should apply.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's probably too late now, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in the emails it's something about July is when the public beta starts.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like less than a month of closed beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, you could at least play the public beta in July.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're too popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm excited about Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of wish it was on GameCube because I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just love my GameCube and I want everything to be on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm already there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, do you talk about GameCube?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: My computer, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just can't play games on my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, even when I seem to have a top-of-the-line system, games suck to play on my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can help you out there, but... I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, by the way, I'm bringing over Slow Caliber 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had it for, like, a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw the demo at Fry's this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: The demo doesn't do the game justice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have GameCube, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess... Yeah, we'll link.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I'll talk about my week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Navi and I decided to go to Fry's on Monday because I wanted to make a random purchase, so I decided I wanted to buy a GameCube game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it came down to two games, like we were looking, and we were either going to get Mario Party 4 or Cubivore.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I decided to get Mario Party 4 because I like to be popular, and when I get Mario Party 4, people will come over more and want to play, so I bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that worked for Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Cubivore, actually what happened is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Navi was so obsessed with Cubivore and the idea of it, he went and freaking bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's actually pretty cool, because you get to eat things.
[SPEAKER_02]: You ruthlessly tear the tails off of little cube snakes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like a mix between Faceball 2000, except everything's cubes and 3D, and EVO, that old SNES game, where you kind of evolve, you eat things, you get experience points, then you can evolve.
[SPEAKER_03]: But everything's still cubes, so it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I especially love the screen where you have to go mate, because you have to mate to have offspring to get more limbs, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's kind of complicated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's funny, because it says, like, you attracted five females.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it says, would you like to mate?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes or no?
[SPEAKER_02]: The mating scene in Cube of War is, like, the best thing I've seen in any video game in the past year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you like to mate?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes or no?
[SPEAKER_03]: If a guy's playing the game, who's going to answer no?
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are some pretty hot cube chicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, whoa.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then at the end he says, I mated with five females.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I had three kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or three of the females had kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like an episode of Jerry Springer.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Cube Springer, Jerry Springer.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Rice Princess, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was as good as always.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I started a diet on Monday, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's your diet going?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been going pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I lost like five pounds.
[SPEAKER_13]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I need to go on a lifestyle change.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's not a real diet, so to speak, it's a lifestyle change.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boring old me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so anybody else have anything they want to say here during the first little bit of show?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually been going on a while now, but anybody else have something they want to add to the conversation going on right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone wants to be like me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, sure, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I think we're going to take a quick break, and we're going to start this break off with a song.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't hear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I wanted to play one more song real fast, and we'll get into some Guitar Freaks stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But since this is graduation week for a lot of people, and they're graduating high school and college, I thought I'd play graduation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that cute?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go drill out my ears with an electric drill now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll sound better.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is dedicated to the class of 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, since we're all ranty, I suppose we should do the FUs of the week next.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why don't you go ahead and send those to me over a private message in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you aren't in our chat room, get your ass over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.callybomondi.com, click on Orange Lounge, click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, congratulations, and then a couple Guitar Freak songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, this is to you, Class of 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't invest our job market.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Watch them disappear without love Where would you be now without love?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Illinois is such a seven-centi-feet That I keep on pushin' mama, you know they're runnin' late
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio is proud to present a celebrity interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you introduce yourself for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's great to have you on the show today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, how are you today?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm great, thanks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you have a question?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yes, actually I wanted to know... Can I please have your first name only and your birth date, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, well, no, I actually just wanted to know what you thought of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what do you think of Loki, one of the three hosts of Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is he incarcerated?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, actually, no, he's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what do you think of the ever-ranty DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, dear, how are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see you two must know each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what do you think of Sky?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did he used to play football when he was in high school?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, no, he didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what do you think of Intern Zero?
[SPEAKER_12]: I want you to really remember...
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm seeing some forgetting, possibly.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm seeing a new baby in the next three months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, thanks for being on Orange Lounge Radio today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, I don't mean to sidetrack your question here, but who are all of these nosy people?
[SPEAKER_12]: Outside influences I'm seeing around you by the moon card.
[SPEAKER_27]: Get away from me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio, helping to free your mind and spirit.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're listening to episode number 47, not 48.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: We hope you enjoy our cheesy little promos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, Jamie threatened in her live journal today to make some new ones this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you said you wanted to make new promos.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's right, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, go for it, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dudette.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, her?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to make a couple more celebrity interviews, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to call some people and get more celebrity interviews.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was fun, interviewing Miss Cleo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to try to get some wrestlers.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's... Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Brad does a really good impression.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am very sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Miss Elizabeth is dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's Miss Elizabeth?
[SPEAKER_05]: She was Macho Man's wife, like, in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't follow wrestling.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're doing wrestling drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shall we get to the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want the new song?
[SPEAKER_02]: You want the new one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is now FU of the week time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is this FU of the week thing all about, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where we get pissed off and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first one goes toward the stupid bitch that was in front of me driving.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was obviously drunk, and she would... True to the law says you have to stop a full car like behind the person in front of you at a stoplight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But who follows that anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she was stopping, and then she was like driving all twitchy, so I just had to speed around her.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then her question in the seat next to her was obviously on E. She kept putting her hands in the air and then trying to hug the girl in the front seat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, uh, fuck having SARS.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole beginning of this week I was so sick of my allergies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thanks to, uh, free gifts from Allegra and Claritin D, I was all better.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't have a voice, but I work in friggin' customer service, so what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then...
[SPEAKER_05]: Another one goes to not having, you know, money and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my breaks, which grind.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, I think that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not really all that angsty that much anymore because my life is sort of happy right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, that's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Break my ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I can get you, Rani.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that, that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And another one goes to Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And another one goes toward, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: All of these communities I'm a member of, just about, in my live journal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm, like, taking them, I'm taking them all off, because people just post really stupid stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm leaving up the DDR and Baymani communities, but, like, you know, it's just been, like, some stupid drama going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this other guy, okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, everyone knows about, you know, I go through my fans, you know, crazes and my little phases, and right now it's Transformers for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm on this roleplay board.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's this guy being... You're on the microphone cord.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy's just being all godmode-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate godmode RPG players.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially when you're not doing anything with a set combat-based rule, and he's like, oh, I just had me appear there, and you're blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, okay, and where in your profile is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then he was like, well, you've been here a month ago, you would've known blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he got smacked down by one of the admins on the board, so that made me feel all happy and justified and I couldn't help rubbing his nose in it, so... Did he have an ogre-slaying knife?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got an ogre-slaying knife as a plus nine against ogres!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not even there, you're getting drunk!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was just being stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really, really... And another thing, people who have their live journals...
[SPEAKER_05]: and cannot use paragraphs or complete sentences.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're doing it on purpose, and if that's the case, stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some of these people are really, you know, nice people.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's going out over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great people that I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you to death.
[SPEAKER_05]: But please, use grammatically correct sentence structure when you post in your live journal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also for people who put humongous posts,
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's such a feature called LJ Cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a really easy code to remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can even go onto the FAQ page and cut and paste.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_05]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could name names, but I won't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll just tell them to their face later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry for messing with the phone.
[SPEAKER_28]: I forgot to connect this to the soundboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we want to hear your conversation that you're going to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to, because I fixed something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was seeing if it worked.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was calling my voicemail to see if it would leave a message, because if it left a message, that meant the phones were working.
[SPEAKER_21]: So Matt's first fuck you goes to Brad.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm not that mad this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: First, slight...
[SPEAKER_28]: First F.U.
[SPEAKER_28]: of the Week, not really an F.U.
[SPEAKER_28]: of the Week, kind of like I'm laughing at you because you're stupid, type of thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm gonna laugh at the stupid bitch that I mentioned last week, cause, hi, you're licensed, you have to take a picture, you have to take the stupid veil off, you stupid bastard.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go home, go back to your country, you freaking Al-Qaeda.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, enough.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, um, enough of that, and, um, let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_28]: Um...
[SPEAKER_28]: FU's stupid phone program not working because I can hear the phone, but I can't talk.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, it's kinda cool and all, but I like to talk, and that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, what else?
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, I don't know, FU for not having that many good, you know, files coming out lately, friggin' sim files.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, also the fact that Terrible Mr. Grinshaw was out today.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh yeah, Terrible Mr. Grinshaw came out today, yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, all these phone programs that are for making phone calls on your PC that claim to be free, but they're not.
[SPEAKER_20]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Why even say they're free if you're not going to make them free if you have to pay money to use the phone for free?
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know, I'm not that smart and all, but paying money to use a phone for free is just paying to use the phone.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's like saying, well, you're paying the 35 cents to use the payphone as a right to use the phone for free.
[SPEAKER_28]: Makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I really didn't have anything because I've been kind of like busy with other stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, yeah, I just really haven't been paying attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, my FU of the week goes to exes that screw your friend in the shower.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Short symbol to the point.
[SPEAKER_24]: Brad, anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry about that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: No hard feelings there.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just didn't fall into the penis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not drag it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: His hand landed there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twenty times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Up and down.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm glad Loki brought that up about the crazy lady who won't take her veil off, because I wanted to expound on that.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a word, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if people know, but in this country, especially in California, just anywhere in the country, in America, driving, having a driver's license, is a privilege, not a right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have the right to have a driver's license, it's something you have to strive to get, you know, you have to go do it, and it's just a privilege, so, if you're not, you know, you can't fucking sue, I don't know if they are suing, but I would be surprised if they're trying to sue the country for not letting her have her fucking license picture taken, or having her license, but you can't do that, because it's not your right, we're not infringing on your rights as an American, or as a legal alien, or as an alien, because it's not your right to have a license!
[SPEAKER_03]: Fucking follow the rules!
[SPEAKER_03]: Retard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and another thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All these people who are crossing the border from Mexico and stuff, who are getting killed because they're breaking the law.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not racist, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a law that says you can't try to, you know, you have to come in an illegal way.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do it illegally, you're a criminal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you are a criminal by doing it illegally and you get hurt doing it, you can't sue our country, which has been happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're a freaking criminal in the first place for breaking an American law.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's actually a true...
[SPEAKER_03]: Some sort of international law or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm, urgh, anger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what did you just say, Matt?
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, MTV Music Awards are on.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, anyways, um, no.
[SPEAKER_28]: My FB of the Week, actually, I forgot, is for stupid movie sequels.
[SPEAKER_28]: For God's sake, stop making stupid... I'm kidding!
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop it, Brad gets his ink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for instance, Legally Blonde 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't want to watch Legally Blonde 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to see a sequel of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're talking about making it Back to the Future 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: They ended it fine, and now they're making it Back to the Future 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only will the two directors not be back for it, but Christopher Lloyd and Michael J. Fox will not be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it might be animated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, does he go back in time when he didn't have Parkinson's disease or whatever?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm supposed to go back to 1985, but my hand is shaking so much that I went to 485.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, the hijinks that ensue.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's wacky fun for the family.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said hijinks, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, he wouldn't be so good at that gun game anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ah, yeah, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't a superhero movie with Christopher Reeve and Michael J. Fox be great?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be the Avengers of Handyman and the Tiny Avenger.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess, do you have anything you'd like to F you today?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you see, I'm kind of pissed off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you see, I'm kind of... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really have anything that I'm pissed off about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I do a love you of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you can do a love you of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we have love yous of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: I give my love you to Rob because he bought me that Dog of Glee notebook and it was so cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was so great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's the movie awards or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're parading the Matrix here at the movie awards.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a love you to Brad because he's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you too.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is really weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have Wanda Sykes as the oracle, that's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Matt turned on this TV, it's the MTV Awards, Matrix thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Justin Timberlake is some sort of like... I wanted to see this, for the movie awards this year, they did a parody of the Matrix Reloaded, and I really wanted to see this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry that I've broken the FUs, I'm sure people can go ahead and, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's continue on with the FUs.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the MTV Movie Awards, call a sham.
[SPEAKER_02]: Justin Timberlake's dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, he's doing the Matrix stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, uh, let's go to the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you done with your, uh, love use, Irene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the chatroom FUs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Puppy would like to say, or Black Lab, I should say, would like to say, fuck the ants that invaded my bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck every single Kazaa WinMX user in my dorm for hogging all the bandwidth, even at 3 AM, and making my games play like shit online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck my ex-roommate for leaving a pile of garbage outside the window of the suite's living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I have to clean it up because this lazy ass won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck finals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you for not setting the webcam up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, fuck you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mulheimer would like to say fuck the Matrix for ending out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't feel like waiting until November because it was so good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck the Six Flags near me because they had to get rid of their four extremes because some bitch complained about the word bitch in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, nobody even heard that at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, we're kind of sidetracked by watching Sean William Scott playing Agent Smith.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to come back to that later and make a little topic out of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, anyway, hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck exams this week, and I don't normally say this because there is a reasoning for exams.
[SPEAKER_02]: But everyone is running around like chickens without dicks trying to remember everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's really annoying, so fuck them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sharkskrl!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sharkskrl would like to say F you to everything!
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything!
[SPEAKER_02]: I want everything's balls to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not my balls, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanna keep mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Tetsuya would like to say, I have no FUs actually, just the happy news about the female that has contacted me over the past week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, you can go sit in Irene's corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you were listening to me, you'd know, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninst would like to say, just one this week, but it seems to be constant.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU'd my dial-up connection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry bud, wish there was more we could do for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: John Fields would like to say F you to IBM for making a floppy disk type called XDF that Windows can't read.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to having to move into a condo because of a divorce.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the pains of cleaning out a house.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly, huge F you to Dell because my 19-inch CRT died.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not only that, but so did my DVD plus RW drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It won't burn DVD-R anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sure, RW works fine, but R is much cheaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you, Dell.
[SPEAKER_02]: You better fix this stuff for free because of my warranty when I call you tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, oh, after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he meant to type or else.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dude, you're getting a broken Dell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, you're getting a dump.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to summer school, says Nico Adachi.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would suck if you have to go to summer school.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: AkumaGM would like to say F you to my infernal MP3 player that decided to go on the blink.
[SPEAKER_02]: You used to work so well until you started to skip for no reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you set MP3 player?
[SPEAKER_02]: I stab at thee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why get an MP3 player anyway?
[SPEAKER_03]: I should get a CD player that can read MP3 on the CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I don't read mines.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would just like to share.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving right along, we have the 23rd Magus' FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to graduation rehearsal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Four hours stuck in the football field in the hot sun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because 200 fucking seniors can't walk and step, it's Johnson, so they have to pimp strut.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sub-sunburnination.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a new word.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to me for being such a damn glutton and ordering the biggest sundae they have at Leather Bees in celebration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Burps.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to summer visitation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to go to Kentucky, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks for lawyers, damned if they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Angel would like to say, F you to the egotistical bitch co-worker for making me work for her tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh wait, more money for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, still, F you to her for being an egotistical seniority-slinging bitch that she is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Tyrant would like to say, I have not gotten your F yous of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send them to me over a private message.
[SPEAKER_13]: So... Well, sorry...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway, I'm doing the show by myself right now, apparently, because the others have more important things to watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... Oh, Rob, I'm listening.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm adding to the show, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Rob, I think we should go to a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still waiting for one more FU to come in.
[SPEAKER_13]: A world of pain all over your candy ass!
[SPEAKER_13]: Here it goes!
[SPEAKER_13]: Vis-a-vis!
[SPEAKER_13]: Concordantly!
[SPEAKER_25]: Justin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to say an F you to MTV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because they suck anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Matt turned it on in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so... I guess I'll get to that one missing F you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, I guess I ought to go to break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't feel like doing a show myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll be back after this potpourri of Bomani music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's Bright Light starring Noco Flo A kung fu fighter in a disco He's out to take his chance, he knows the hundreds in the house Only go for romance He's got a white suit on, five past one and the night has just begun Cause when he lays it on with style, a lady's man with a nice smile And right before his eyes, sees a pretty young thing looking real fly He wants to make the score, so he takes a hand and leads her to the dance floor He's giving her line after line, she tells him that he looks real fine
[SPEAKER_00]: Like what he's come for, buy it
Thanks for watching!
I feel, I feel You are the only one that can feel this way I feel, I feel
[SPEAKER_27]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Brad's splashing me liquor.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wants me to start drinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I already got pretty toasty last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I need to get drunk again.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to go outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Brad, bring me one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: One will loosen me up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: One or two or ten.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually with Rob, one leads to two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, can I take one home with me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't carry an open container in the car.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you can take one home with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to drink something before I'm driving.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm responsible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't drink and do radio, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not underage.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're underage, you must have your parents' permission to drink.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although people at restaurants seem to think that I'm like 18.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't look 18.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever been carded in an R-rated movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shit would piss me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did you... You look like... Oh!
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: I have good news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is more centered toward Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when we went to see The Matrix?
[SPEAKER_05]: And remember that crap with the thing and the credits?
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I got six bucks from the movie theater and a $2 off coupon.
[SPEAKER_05]: How'd you get six bucks?
[SPEAKER_05]: I gave them my ticket and told them what happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll get money.
[SPEAKER_05]: They turned on the lights and ended the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they turned it back on, but didn't really turn the lights off.
[SPEAKER_21]: You mean like before the trailer came on?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like during the credits or the end?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when Mar and John was in town, we went to see X-Men 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I was just thinking, you know, so I have that ticket, and I personally wonder if they would, you know, give me like a movie pass or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went and told them about it, and they gave me money off of another movie ticket, and then they gave me money.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, she should totally take your ticket there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like we never saw the movie because they never tore our tickets.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we just walked right by them because we got there, like, I guess there was this, what happened was we were thinking, I was thinking of getting a Fandango ticket the night before, you know, buying them online.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I was like, you know what, maybe they'll be, I don't know, I don't want to wait in line, you know, a huge line if a bunch of people bought Fandango tickets or whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because then you have to wait on a Fandango ticket line or whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I just went there early, and there had to be two other showings happening before that weren't posed the night before.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we got these two showings that nobody had tickets for, because everybody bought Fandango tickets.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so we went in there, and there was no, what do you call them, the person who, the chauffeur, taking the tickets.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we just walked in there, we could've, like, I don't know, probably gone and seen another movie, or, Usher, that's what he calls him.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gottman's chauffeur.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, thanks James, or Jeeves, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I don't know, we probably could have sold the tickets, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, Loki gets a present.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't use it for like a new movie, but any movie that's already out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a 2, or a 1 car.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hardly go to movies anymore, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving right along, did we want to get into Cage Match or does anybody else have something they want to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you not have a song still?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because your song's first, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, no, I don't have anything yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you had the vinyl you wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: I did?
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you do that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're up first, bud, so get that vinyl out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know they have it in Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do they have in Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Pooh hat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found the stop sign hat today, someone was selling one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You walk around with a stop sign on your head, and then there's a mask that makes you gothy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like the pretend murder, it's a giant knife in your head.
[SPEAKER_21]: You walk around with a knife in your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's one that's an apple with an arrow in your head, so you can be arrowed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I want Imperium.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fell in for 625,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I want Empyrean so I can start a guild and call it I Kick Your Ass Guild.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or like Battle Royale, which is my party's name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we ready for Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_13]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Cage Match, for the fourth week, Loki's pick from the Matrix Reloaded soundtrack, Mona Lisa Overdrive, won... They all know how it goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: ...once again...
[SPEAKER_02]: So here it is, one last time, a little piece of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mona Lisa Overdrive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because guess what, kids?
[SPEAKER_02]: When this song is in rotation four weeks, it is retired.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're like TRL up in this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, here's a little clip of Mona Lisa Overdrive, and it's retirement.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now, the winning song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna skip her out, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's it, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, alright, that was Mona Lisa Overdrive and it's out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, all three of us have brand new picks this week because Mona Lisa Overdrive may no longer participate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you need a little more time, Loki, because I have some late FUs I can read.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki needs a little more time, so I'm going to read some late FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you're good?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I need to do these anyway, so I'm going to read some late FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, late FUs, shame on you for being late.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have way too much fun with those sound clips.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Late FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: From Nintz.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to my connection because I didn't get to hear my first FU.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I take my socks off a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Tyron would like to say, F you to my ISP, I have to go through a proxy server to access the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: ISPs are dumb that block sites.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to not having broadband.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually sad now that I'm leaving high school, so F you to heading out to real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been great hanging out with all you great people, but now we're going to go our separate ways.
[SPEAKER_14]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the people at the LAN party yesterday who just wanted to play the fastest map possible on StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop using noobs maps and try to beat me because you don't know how to play a strategy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And F you to them at Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just using the AWP shows you have no skill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girls, please, I'm begging you, will you please stop ignoring me when I talk to you, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't talk to me when I'm doing FBs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me a jewel case.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want a jewel case?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or a sleeve or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a big one or a little one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where one is over here, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, back to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that sound effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: This week in the Orange Launch Cage match, now that Mona Lisa Overdrive has been retired, Loki's up first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, tell us about your pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: This should be great.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is from our girlfriend, because she loves Donna Summers.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it's the song... I would say that Donna Summers is like... Well, obviously, she'd be like the erotic, but... You know, like the 70s and 70s age...
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyway, this song is Love to Love You Baby.
[SPEAKER_20]: I believe it's been featured in a few movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's also one of my stronger picks because, you know, I gotta give the other people some chance, you know, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_20]: Love to Love You Baby.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here it is, Love to Love You Baby.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love to love you, baby I love to love you, baby I love to love you, baby I love to love you, baby I love to love you, baby When you're laying so close to me There's no place around that you're believing in me Yeah
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Wacka Wacka Baby Baby
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, it's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the first pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Donna Summer would love to love you, baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, let's go around and get the room's thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, it's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what did you think of that one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked Donna Summer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, she did, you know, a good version of MacArthur Park, which was later parodied into Jurassic Park.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she did Bad Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: She did that, girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Second mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, her version wasn't in the second mix, but she did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that song, you can't disco to it, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only, and it's too slow to get like a good, you know, you know... It is bump to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sex music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you not notice the moaning in the background?
[SPEAKER_05]: But that would not be any good for sex either.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too slow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Studio 54 music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Studio 54 music, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, the only thing that would make that good for like, like even, what were you saying it was good for, anal?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the person was constipated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: On a station, on a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_05]: Three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because it gets a little bit of good because Donna Summer has a very nice voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, she does.
[SPEAKER_05]: But her moaning needs to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, lanky style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_03]: My rating for it, probably, as like a song, I give it, you know, for what it does in its genre, I think it's pretty good, it's 8.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for being on our station, I give it a 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should not be on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, who that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: The song sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was way boring, too.
[SPEAKER_20]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_20]: What's he doing in my chair?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like all breaking.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_20]: I give it an 8 because it's the best damn sex music that's on this record.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you have to understand it's sex making out music.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not meant to be dancing.
[SPEAKER_20]: You don't dance while you're supposed to be having sex.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is like when I watch TV instead of having sex.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, that's different, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: That had more of an upbeat to it, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: And they knew that they were there at the Dance Dance Fuck.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, this is like Studio 54.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have two words for that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dumbass, it's not a word, it's a sound clip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd rather listen to the Dance Dance Fuck music than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what my next week's cage match pick is going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: The moaning was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But otherwise, I'm glad that I no longer have the crappiest cage match pick in Orange Lounge history.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for that, I won't give you a one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you a two.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't even try to find bad.
[SPEAKER_20]: You want me to find bad.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of my picks, let's get to my pick for this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a little trancy song.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is an artist that was suggested to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You, nothing but you The reason for living I lay my life on you
You, nothing but you, you're calling to me, I lay my hand on you
[SPEAKER_13]: Nothing but you, the reason for living, I lay my love on you You, nothing but you, the calling to be in, I lay my hand on you
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: You, nothing but you The calling to be in I lay my hand on you You
[SPEAKER_02]: My pick for the case match this week, that was Nomi with you, and I don't think anyone in here was listening, but let's see anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, you thought it was boring?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was going to put me to sleep.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty, so it gets like a 7, but it made me sleepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made you sleepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyone else want to comment on Nomi, you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, 3, it was kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play some good stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd stick my tongue out at you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Brad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we talking about playing good stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge means crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: Crap radio, crap music.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for listening, everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was mediocre.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd say 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: Give me the mic.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: It started off good for like 5 seconds.
[SPEAKER_20]: Damn, my poster's all fucked up!
[SPEAKER_20]: Nah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, so then... Yeah, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was like... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was just going to say, you're lucky that I played the Donna Summer song because Rob was suggesting that I play Party All The Time by Eddie Murphy.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I'd be glad.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have plenty of other really shitty records that I could have played.
[SPEAKER_02]: My song was fabulous, as it always is, and it'll be the sleeper hit of Orange Lounge 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: It gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, would you be kind enough to intro your pick for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fantastic Plastic Machine with Take Me to the Disco.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what else did they do?
[SPEAKER_05]: They did Beautiful Days and Beatmania CDX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Buy their album.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it at half.com for $6.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is the name again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Take Me to the Disco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's Disco After Something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Disco at the End of the World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disco at the End of the World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they do a song called Take Me to the Disco.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We forgive you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Disco at the End of the World by Fantastic Plastic Machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, a fantastic classic machine with disco at the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's hear what folks thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll have to bring you a copy of the original Take Me to the Disco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because it's like, you'll hear what parts they took to make that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a weird remix of the song, which for me, I think it's just kind of neat to play Ragnarok to that music.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I give it an 8 myself, just because it's one of my neat little things I listen to when I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alrighty, Lanky Stout?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, hard to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe it's a little too repetitive for me, so I'd have to probably give it like a 6.
[SPEAKER_21]: And also, you know, Beautiful Days is so much better than that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess I've been jaded by that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bryce Princess?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was way better than the crap that you played the last two songs, so I give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found myself bopping my head to it a little bit, kind of like a Night at the Roxbury type thing, so that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agreed to get it maybe a little bit repetitive, but not too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I could put up with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could put up for maybe three minutes of it, just not four.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was still pretty cool, so I give it a... I give it an eight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, let's run through the three songs you can vote for one more time, and then you can send your votes in over private message to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can vote for Donna Summer with, uh, what the hell was that called?
[SPEAKER_02]: Love to Love Ya, Baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play a little clip for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just drop it in the middle and hit start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's Donna Summer with Love to Love Ya, Baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you can vote for Nomi with You.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you can vote for Fantastic Plastic Machine with Disco at the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so there they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send in your votes now.
[SPEAKER_02]: The voting is open now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So send those votes to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Write in candidates for a song that was not played as one of those three will be thrown out and you cannot vote again and we will taunt you and make fun of you openly on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we'll find you and start drawing on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will wiggle our private parts in your general direction.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mother was a hamster and your father smelled of elderberries.
[SPEAKER_02]: And don't threaten to not vote for anything because we've already gotten one vote so we have a winner either way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if it comes down to one vote then I guess it'll be a one vote win.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine by me.
[SPEAKER_02]: because we're evil dictators and we always get our way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either evil dictators or just evil dicks, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, by the way, you need to get rid of the Furby, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Furby?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my Furby.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to put the Furby in the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Furby's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, give me.
Hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the parrot's coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the coyote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's the coyote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's like the desert dog.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a parrot coyote.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to stop drinking now because I have to run to the store after the show's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I've only had half a bottle, but I need to stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to let my system process it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, let's do listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do listless?
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to find paper and pens, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's do a quick break while we find paper and pens.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just break with a bunch of music, so I feel like we've got to talk about something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll find paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to talk about something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have anything interesting you'd like to share, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have something I do want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I haven't been to Scandia yet since they've done this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently, and I never knew this about 2DX machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wish Brad was here to hear it, but he's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing about 2DX machines, I guess, is that they have like an S video output and a VGA output.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for the longest time at Scandia in Sacramento, where Orange Lounge is headquartered in Sacramento...
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been using S-Video and it's been kind of blurry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's been playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been very playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, a little bit blurry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't get quite that crystal clearness that you get when you play it at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: But now they've switched over to VGA and I guess a lot of people really like the differences.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I haven't seen the differences myself, but what do you guys think of it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the difference between S-Video and VGA?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's nice to be able to see everything, like all the options you picked and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, like 717 and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a bit bright for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'm just
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought maybe it was darker before, but it was just a little bit brighter for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But otherwise, you know, it's kind of the same for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I don't really notice that kind of stuff, you know, too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes a difference when you're playing at higher speed.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see your keys a lot clearly.
[SPEAKER_05]: The color needs a little bit... It's not like as bad as, say, like AI's machine was before, you know, with the discoloration.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just slightly off.
[SPEAKER_05]: The contrast needs to be adjusted, but since the...
[SPEAKER_05]: The menus are all in Japanese, it might be a little bit hard to read.
[SPEAKER_03]: They changed over... Am I the only person who notices that it looks better?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I just... I'm sorry, I just came out of the bathroom, so I missed something, but it looks like everybody I've seen so far has said that it looks like crap, like it's been, like, really discolored and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I think before it was discolored.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now it looks clear, I can play almost anything on high speed 3 with, like, no problem, except, of course, like, Sakura and Max 300 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it looks way better.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know, I may have some weird... Even on high speed it looks great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Lab during the last break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we already heard Lab.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Lab's good, so play it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although the Act from 9th is pretty much just Lab.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's got like a, kind of a, well not a similar video...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like an anime girl, like, running.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a CG anime-ish girl.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I've already had to throw out two votes for Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any reason why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, yes, they both voted for Rob's voice the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: My listeners are such retards.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, was that my outside voice talking?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we have some listeners who are some real retards.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love you, but you lose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rules are rules.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love you like our retarded children.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we have to love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The state says we have to.
[SPEAKER_03]: We keep you in the attic.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're the special ones we keep in the attic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the basement.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we take them out of the basement when it rains.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, if they get sick, then we have to start taking them to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, but they're saying something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that CDs are cool because you can see the spindle through them.
[SPEAKER_05]: All distorted-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ah, retarded kids are already broke, so, I mean, we'll... You don't really have to take them anywhere.
[SPEAKER_20]: You can't really tell the difference, you know?
[SPEAKER_20]: Especially if you have, like, any blows to the head or anything, you know, and you think that they might give you damage and you're like, and you forgot, and you're like, oh, that's right, that was like that before you got hit in the head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the chatroom's getting defensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when did you guys start taking things we say seriously?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't take things seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at the cow!
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, bark!
[SPEAKER_02]: Bark, bark!
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Bark, bark, cow!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's the upstairs, uh... I think it's the upstairs neighbors.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our neighbors are pissed at us because we're making retarded jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't like those cage mat pics either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, they've been, like, totally banging on the, like, ceiling.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know, like...
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know what they're doing upstairs, but... It's an older lady and her daughter.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's her daughter.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, it's an older lady and her daughter.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think it's their daughter.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, like, I hear banging on the walls all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't it the one with the cat?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the alien's.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I'm saying is they can go suck it because it's before 10 and, you know, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mike, please, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we were talking about, that was the one with the spheres, they take the energy out of their body.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I haven't seen that movie in forever and I couldn't remember what that movie was, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, this is a different movie with the mother and her son.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they were like fucking... And the cats could see... The cats could see that they were really alien or demon or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the cats killed them at the end of the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, DarkTetsuya had a good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: He said that the upstairs folks might be playing World Class Track Meet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember on the Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they're playing Dance Aerobics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woot woot, DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he gets an honorary zing for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was like a half zing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a z. He gets a coyote.
[SPEAKER_02]: He gets a non-retard.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's our official non-retarded listener of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the special listener of the day now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy ferret to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm here to chew bubblegum and that's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm all out of bubblegum.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I will never forget in Nintendo Power when they had that segment on like the kids who were having the slumber party and playing the Power Pad game or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had like the red team and the yellow team and they were playing... Remember it was like this highlight on the Power Pad and kids having fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I wasn't a dork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, surely somebody remembers that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Surely.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember you telling me about submitting to be in some video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You submitted... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a dork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're such a dork.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish we could get a power pad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember Howard and Esther.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have a power pad, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to bring that shit over and we should have a world-class track in the Orange Lounge one day.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll bring over the power glove.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I remember Howard and Esther.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I'll try to find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an archive that has almost every Howard and Esther comic online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember seeing that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: You pointed it to me before, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Long-ass time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long-ass time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I remember the Mega Man ones.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like that Howard Nestor one, but I want to find somebody who has scans of all the Zelda comics that were in the Nintendo Power, because those were cool, and the Metroid ones, and the Star Fox ones, because they were all cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I have an archive that has the Zelda ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still need to download episodes of the Zelda cartoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, excuse me, princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before my computer died, I had the one where he was invisible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where he stands up in the middle of Ganon's chamber and goes, Zelda loves me, Zelda loves me!
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they all get shot at.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, quiet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, we're gossiping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, stop gossiping, dammit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about you, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: This?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can, I suppose, if I have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to be loud.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're going to take a break, and when we come back, we're going to have Liss Liss.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know they had a monkeypox virus.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was reading about that on AOL.
[SPEAKER_05]: They showed a picture of a prairie dog on there, and the prairie dog looked like it was the prairie dog of Satan.
[SPEAKER_28]: You are monkeypox.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gonna be the new... It was making this face, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like... Sars?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like... I have a prairie dog of Satan.
[SPEAKER_20]: Move on over to Sars because for the second quarter of 2003, yes, monkeypox will be the official virus of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it replacing SARS?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's monkeypox dense.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now... So now, Rob, do you have monkeypox?
[SPEAKER_05]: Monkeypox!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well then...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess on that note, why don't we head off Hey look, it's Paul and Terry Alright, on that note, we're going to head off to break and when we come back we will announce this week's cage match winner so this is your last chance to submit a vote unless you've already been disqualified and when we come back, more show and list lists so we're going to take a chance to prepare our list lists for tonight so we'll be back and on that note
and the rest.
[SPEAKER_13]: Creeper Creeper
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live, and I bet you're all dying to know who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here it is, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight's cage match winner is... Drumroll, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fabulous, here it is!
[SPEAKER_13]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Fantastic Classic Machine with Disco at the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Makes me want to shake my booty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shake your booty.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ha, no more Matrix!
[SPEAKER_20]: Ha, I didn't enter the Matrix into the frickin' contest.
[SPEAKER_20]: And ha, my song would have been gone this week anyways.
[SPEAKER_20]: So there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have had a sniff.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what we decided to do this segment, Brad went out to go run an errand, so we're going to hold off on list lists until the next segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: But guess what we have tonight, everybody?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you ready, Irene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you're going to have to be the timer since there's nobody else here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you ready for this, too?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to be a timer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you time 30 seconds?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to cue up the music here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm having a little problem finding the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to put all the theme songs in a separate folder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because my drive, if you haven't already figured it out, is very dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: You silly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to get dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to get a little... Oh my God, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of you has to leave, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're not starting right now, but we have to have the theme songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, it's time for Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's everybody's favorite segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows the most on Orange Crush?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rob vs. Jamie today on Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should I leave or should Jamie leave?
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go ahead and leave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoever wants to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll leave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, you can't tell me tonight's Orange Car.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I just have to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to wait until you come back, you silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one doesn't go all the way back there.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about to me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to me, and then I'll pass this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll wait until you're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, is he ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, are you ready, Matt?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or just let me know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: The name of this one is called Destiny and it's questions about Politary.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew it would be so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, tell me when you're ready, Matt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, where was she born and how old is she?
[SPEAKER_05]: Italy, 25.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what is her mother's occupation?
[SPEAKER_05]: Opera singer.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the name of her acid jazz band?
[SPEAKER_05]: Politary, blows me hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is her alter ego's name?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not Politary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where did she live until she was 16?
[SPEAKER_05]: Italy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I say how many you got right and wrong yet, or do I wait?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Time's up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You only got one right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's not bad, considering most of the time people usually don't get a lot of them right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's Rob's turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should I leave?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to Rob's room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll go to Beth's room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fear the room of Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just don't go potty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear anything of that at all, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
You're going to love this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, how did Jamie do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ireland, and 27th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what is her mother's occupation?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, she was born in Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is her mother's occupation?
[SPEAKER_02]: A chef.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the name of her acid jazz band?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is her alter ego's name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Donna Summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, where did she live until she was 16?
[SPEAKER_02]: Australia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, is that it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Since your first answer was incorrect, that one doesn't count, the first question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a two-part question, which means it counts for one point, so you get a half point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we have to get Jamie in here, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Jamie can come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you got a half a point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, I got a half point overall?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like games where Jamie beats me.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're the only one who doesn't like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're like, Jamie, it's time to come out now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, is she up?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I think she's, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, should I just read the answer?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, the first question, how old is she and where was she born?
[SPEAKER_05]: She's 27 years old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she was born in Australia, but you said... Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said Ireland or something first.
[SPEAKER_06]: I changed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wham.
[SPEAKER_06]: It hit me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: My clit hurts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the one... Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make it one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're still tied.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wham.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the one she got right?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, did you hear that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I threw a fit because I said Ireland at first for the first question, then I'm like, no way, Australia.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I made her give it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I was... I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, he got one point anyway, and you got one point, so you guys are tied anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: He would have gotten a half point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I guessed 27.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guessed 27.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, anyway, yeah, so she's 27 years old, and she's born in Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Her mother is an opera singer, a famous opera singer at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, and the acid jazz band she's a part of is called Cracker Jam, because she's white, I guess, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Her alter ego... Naoki, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Close, but no, it's Sonya.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's her alter ego's name.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she lived... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: She lived in France until she was 16.
[SPEAKER_05]: No wonder she's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and other interesting facts.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's married.
[SPEAKER_06]: But she tells everyone she saw it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and she lives in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That concludes another segment of Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I have to get back to the computer so I can...
[SPEAKER_02]: Officially close out this segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, that's like shitty radio, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the end of Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_02]: Politary really sucked on Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_02]: One point for Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Australia was the answer, not that country with red hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said Italy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said Italy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I technically got one right because I said not Politary for her alter ego.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you can get Australia, then I get not Politary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you get, you know what's your prize?
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to listen to Politary music all night long.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what you can do?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pick a key, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: And stay in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: YouSuck.com So did we learn something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat room, did we learn something from tonight's Orange Crush segment?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's actually kind of neat because now we know who to hold for ransom if we ever want to have Paul Cherry never sing again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the Orange Crush segment, Irene.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you do your research for that?
[SPEAKER_05]: So that we know where to look.
[SPEAKER_02]: On a mic, on a mic, on a mic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quiet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so, so quiet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got my Bjork tickets today, and I have to sell them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm going to go to Cyber Beat Nation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's she playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to go to Bjork?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you afford to pay me kickback some for the tickets?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm probably going to have to get the cost.
[SPEAKER_02]: A hundred bucks for two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm probably going to put them on eBay if none of my friends take them just because I need to make my money back so I have money to spend in LA.
[SPEAKER_05]: When's the concert?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is August 8th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where?
[SPEAKER_02]: At Pier 3032 in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't go to that anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic Gaming Expo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to be at the Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you already register for that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I should.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're just going to show up at the door and go, Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll talk to Xander about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll talk to Xander about it because I can't go to Fonamay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's just because, you know, what's the point of going if I can't cosplay?
[SPEAKER_02]: What else was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cyber Beat Nation 2, there's this little teaser.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been teasing it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a little teaser trailer that's out, and it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They hint at that there's going to be perfect attack singles and doubles this time around.
[SPEAKER_02]: That should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Freestyle, if I read this teaser correctly, they're saying any Bomani song you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which makes me think they're going to do Freestyle on a sim.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just a guess, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the only way you could do it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they're too dumb to find actual sim files that are synced up correctly, and then you have people going, Watch as you get an email in a couple of weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, you're going to get an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, help.
[SPEAKER_02]: But actually, what if people were responsible for making their own sim files and bringing them in?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I would have meant.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll happen.
[SPEAKER_20]: That'll be awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're giving away another arcade machine, you can bet people will go to the distance to make it happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it could be successful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, at Shaft we ended up using a sim.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I'm cool and I'm the only one that can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only one anywhere that can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one will be able to do it, except for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me, me, me, me, me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really now?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, segue into the sim section of... Okay, stuff that's going on.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, first off, um, you've got a couple sites, um, you know, going through redesigns.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have Maniacs and stuff being the site, and it looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_20]: You've got Tourney Mix 4, which is ending their submissions in four days.
[SPEAKER_20]: So if you've registered already, which you must have if you're joining up, have your file done in four days.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because I need to get my file done in four days because it's not yet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Also, there's rumored to be about 400 entries.
[SPEAKER_20]: They've got about 10 judges, so it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're going to be doing them.
[SPEAKER_20]: I believe releasing a group of files every week, and then voting on those, and then a new set will come up, and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_20]: Other than that, we've got... Let's see, a few fun sim files came out, like the terrible Mr. Grimshaw.
[SPEAKER_20]: Go check that one out, from Monty Sims.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_20]: Really, um, oh, one more interesting bit of information.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not really sim related, but it was on a sim site that I found it.
[SPEAKER_20]: DDRUK, there's this guy who goes by the name Havoc on there, and he, like I, just like me, he has copies of their arcade discs.
[SPEAKER_19]: But since, you know, you've got the UK arcade disc, he's got a Dancing Stage Euro Mix 2 disc.
[SPEAKER_20]: And what's funny is he found some songs on the disc that weren't in the actual game itself.
[SPEAKER_20]: And one of those songs would be from NSYNC, Bye Bye Bye.
[SPEAKER_20]: And this is an official Konami song that was supposed to be in Euromix 2, but never made it in, or it's an unlock that, you know, obviously, because the Euromix 2 site was never finished, so, you know, maybe they just never got around to releasing unlock codes for it, but he says that's not the only song that's hidden in there, too, so there's actually more than one song, so...
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, we're going to find out in a few weeks here that there's going to be more and more songs.
[SPEAKER_20]: And rumor that these songs, you know, for some reason didn't appear in Euromix 2, they might be in Euromix 3, or in fact, the licensing might have been cut on them.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's hard to say, but that is an official song that was supposed to be in Euromix 2, Bye Bye Bye.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, yeah.
Bye Bye Bye
[SPEAKER_05]: And they suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I have to listen to people play The Light FM.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I thought I got away from it when I lost my job.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, people play it around me all the time now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what, though?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I get them back by playing, um, I'm Gonna Make This CD Tonight Take to Work.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of Hair Rock.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poison, Motley Crue, Cuds and Roses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Walk this way!
[SPEAKER_05]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Tesla.
[SPEAKER_05]: Walk this way!
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they have to put up with my trance.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everyone leaves the office when I'm working my overtime, so I turn up my trance CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a cool... We can't hear you, Irene.
[SPEAKER_06]: I play Orange Lounge all day, every day, because they let me listen to it and they don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny, because, you know, when you play, like, Highs Off You or, you know, any other song that says, like, fuck or shit, you know, like, somebody will be a faxing next to me and they'll say that and...
[SPEAKER_02]: He can't even understand it in Highest Off You.
[SPEAKER_02]: He can't understand the FU in that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually a good segue, because I wanted to go back.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys weren't paying attention because you were watching the Matrix thing, but Muheimer had a pretty interesting FU of the week, so I want to read this again.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said... Welcome back!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I wanted to go back to Muheimer's Fuck You of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, this was a part of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, Fuck the six flags near me, because they had to get rid of their four extremes...
[SPEAKER_02]: because some bitch complained about the word bitch in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoever took that out, you're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bitches are everywhere, you can't get away from them, so just deal with it, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Just like retarded kids and faggots.
[SPEAKER_19]: The official term, or the technical term for them, are window lickers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd just like to say to that woman... Wait, it's somewhere in here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you do every time that song played on the radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you call the station and complain and tell them to go off air?
[SPEAKER_20]: Once again, it's stupid parents trying to get other people to parent their kids for them.
[SPEAKER_20]: If your kids are listening, oh my god, they heard the word bitch.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, oh my god, turn on the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what people's fascination is with curse words anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the fact that you tell them you can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't like the word bitch, become Amish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Children would not be as apt to curse if you acted like it was no big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you don't let your kids watch TV because they say bitch on it all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone should read the first story in The Illustrated Man, which I'm reading right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It talks about parenting and what happens when you don't parent your kids yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's really bad, so yeah, you should read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have a question as to what song in DDR has bitch in it... Yes, Little Bitch.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-2, Little Bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is everybody...
[SPEAKER_02]: Blow Your Whistle, it says in the background, not an extreme, bitch, no that song is gone, but this is going to be interesting because the rumor is, and this is merely rumor at this point, but supposedly in that trailer for Max 2 USA, somebody caught a glimpse of the DJ Alligator Project video for Blow My Whistle, bitch, which is going to be interesting to see how the USA treats that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, here's the thing, though, is he actually officially has, it wasn't, you know, the fact that it was censored, there's two different songs.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're the same damn song, but it's Blowin' Whistle Bitch and Blowin' Whistle Baby, or The Whistle Song.
[SPEAKER_20]: See, so that's actually, you know, the official title is, you know, The Whistle Song.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, you know, that's over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I call them both?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucks!
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, here's the thing anyways, I mean, I'm sure they're gonna censor it, because if we have, like, you know, was it Gentle Stress, the AMD
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting yelled at because I played the 1-2 Little Bitch by Bus Stop and not the specials, which is the one that's actually in Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, get over it, my bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, if you want to be technical, Little Bitch was in the first DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, and that's why it was brought back for Xtreme, because remember they brought back a bunch of old school DDR songs like Butterfly?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, some guy wanted me to play Butterfly the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you tell him?
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, um, I played that a lot when the game was new!
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing DDR with someone I've never met before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss being able to do that, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Back in the days when, like, no one knew who the other one was.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'd all randomly play DDR together.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we just sort of eventually told each other our names.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can stop that right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, let's do Listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we going to do Listless now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so we have to take a quick break, and then we're going to come back and do Listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play the Desro songs from Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're going to play some Desro songs from Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's going to be not a too long of a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have Cobalt from Poppin' Music 9, and we have...
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Pier from Poppin' Music 8 And then I'm gonna play I'm gonna play something from DDR Solo Mix just for good measure No, I'm gonna play Wonderland from 3rd Mix And when we come back Listless And what is tonight's listless topic?
[SPEAKER_02]: Best Bimani songs to fuck by Yes, just like our live journal Best Bimani songs to fuck to We'll be back
DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
and many more.
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: All my brothers and sisters, all in all over 10 billion listeners, let me hear what you want to hear, the hypest and ripest sound of the year.
and the rest of the crew.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, this is Melby of RTF.
[SPEAKER_13]: For an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Melby can join us on all the fun together.
Hey, if you're a broke-ass like I am,
[SPEAKER_24]: Why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_24]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, you tell him, Mel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our buddy, Mel B. Okay, so, back to the show and back to the listless topic at hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, what is the listless topic at hand?
[SPEAKER_05]: Best demonic songs to fuck to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or to hand to.
[SPEAKER_05]: To fuck to.
[SPEAKER_02]: To fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is UNF, the UNF-erific topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So are we ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to be okay, Irene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you said you weren't ready yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You said you weren't ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who wants to start?
[SPEAKER_13]: I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: You will?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Jamie, number... Oh, we haven't done list list in a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I should explain what list list is all about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you want me to let... We all pick our top threes, and then we all vote one off, and then you vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the chat room has the final say, so you can vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is a scientific proven process.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the top three of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: No disputing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, Jamie, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it, we're the experts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, my number three is Gravity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gravity?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a Loki remix?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's a little bit too angry.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like the S&M, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say Gravity because if you think about it, it's like rhythmically good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brad said Gravity, the anal burnination mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go next.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number three pick, and this would be for like if you're having some fast, dirty, rotten sex, Max 300.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was going to say probably we've got to go with Hot Limit because it's a longer song.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, you know, people like things that are longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to make a comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't.
[SPEAKER_26]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_02]: As the room slowly gets it.
[SPEAKER_02]: La, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Irene, your turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I picked a serious one, Ecstasy, because, I mean, come on now, like I need to explain stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Brad, your turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brad, Mr. Lanky Style.
[SPEAKER_29]: Wait, did Matt go already?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody but you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna have to say In the Heat of the Night is my number three.
[SPEAKER_29]: In the Heat of the Night!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: My number two?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, your number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's from Solo, Let the Beat Hit Em.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let the Beat Hit Em!
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, no, take that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the version from Solo, the version from Max 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, uh, Let the Beat Hit Em R&B style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like if you want, you know, the slow groove.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number two pick, and this is one that came to me during the break, but honestly, think about it, this song would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: This song would be awesome to have sex to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jam Jam Reggae.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck are you smoking, man?
[SPEAKER_02]: Instant Softie for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's not going to do anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't spell reggae.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's validity behind it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A.E.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm too white.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too white to spell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just thinking, on the main goal, jam, jam, bring it over.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get away from me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Irene.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: Matt.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, just because it's got the, you know, background to go with it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sexy Planet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You took my fucking pick, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so Sexy Planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Irene, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since you took it, I have to go with Love Machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love Machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just a love machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have another one, but I... All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mr. Brad, your number two pick, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: DXY, baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: DXY.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got the perfect flow.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's got the climax in there, and then the call, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_02]: The flow, the climax, and the cigarette, it's all there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually does have the slow build-up, the, the, yay, you know, this is fun, and then the dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's if you're into asphyxiation.
[SPEAKER_07]: So.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what, everybody, this just in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zero's having an orange lounge party at his house in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Party, party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, read.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, Zero, just, uh, thought I'd remind you a little bit.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_20]: Continue.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, you thought two weeks was Fanime or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or what, I don't know what, uh... Exactly what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, sorta is.
[SPEAKER_20]: In two weekends it'll be Fanime, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, let's keep going with the list list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back to list list, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one pick would be, of course...
[SPEAKER_02]: Now this is obvious, I'm sorry, I am going with the obvious, because it's true, do it all night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fine, well then fine, let's hear your number one obvious picks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, mine is going to be Wild Rush, because it starts off slow and it gets faster as it goes along.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the Wild Rush remix is pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is no one going to say one of the other obvious songs?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's down to you and Brad, so you better figure out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I give an honorable mention?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, say what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: After we're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, my number one's Afranova.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't ask, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Afranova.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess everybody was being nice to me, so they can give me the real obvious one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, my number one choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trumbo, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flash.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Insertion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Insertion, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now we're going to the honorable mentions.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one said the whistle song.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one said After the Game of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: After the Game of Love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because those suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Temple of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: No Greco-Bulman style.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so here is the list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you never been mellow?
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's some of the bullshit lists I had before we go on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dead End, Healing Vision Angelic Mix, Hypnotic Crisis, Paranoia Dirty Mix, in case you're paranoid, you're jealous, and Crash, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, one of the other ones I was going to say was Paranoia Clean.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially the pounding one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or I was going to say Hellscaper.
[SPEAKER_28]: or maybe Crimson.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pat Center.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some suggestions from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some suggestions from the chat room as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gimme, gimme, gimme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think V is good.
[SPEAKER_02]: V. Oh, Nick, please not so quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than Erotic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boom Boom Dollar, W Dub, So Many Men, It's Raining Men, Test My Best, Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard the full version of So Many Men.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like she's an utter slut.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, I would have picked this song had it been, you know, in the actual game and not just part of the megamix, the Paranoia Evolution.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's kind of like a trip-hop version of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, and of course, shame on all of us for forgetting this one, Be In My Paradise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be In My Paradise, Rob, makes me break out in hives.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really nasty.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's, uh... Or this is like, like, um, right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, guess what?
[SPEAKER_29]: Come on, baby, do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was looking in an old issue of People Magazine, because I leave those at my work sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a review for Atomic Kitten in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I saw an Atomic Kitten video at Faces one night.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you were there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so now... But they said that they suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little advice, if any of you guys want to, you know, get the ladies in the mood, any Thomas Howard song or... Jeff Coot, any Jeff Coot song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, ladies will love you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ladies love Thomas Howard, trust me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Even though he's gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tack.
[SPEAKER_02]: All tack.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get to the elimination part, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the list so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gravity, Max 300, Hot Limit, Ecstasy, In the Heat of the Night, Let the Beat Hit Em R&B, Jam Jam Reggae, Sexy Planet, Love Machine, DXY, Sync, Do It All Night, Wild Rush, Afronova, and Insertion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, what's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jam Jam Ragu.
[SPEAKER_02]: You stink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jam Jam Ray is the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: You stink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine, I'm going to take off... I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to take off... I'm just kind of drawn to the... well... I don't know why... All these songs are pretty good, but I just... I don't see gravity so much, so I'm going to take off gravity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think of stoic, not gravity, so I think it goes back to that whole stoic versus gravity thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, no, because Matt's next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Matt.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't care, but, um... Jack does not make good sex music.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sink, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are so full of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Outphase, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, Irene.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna take off Hot Limit, because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dude, take Tylenol.
[SPEAKER_21]: Raging Ritalin.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um... Man, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't... I should've said Love Me Do, that would've been a good one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um... Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'll say... Shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, I'm gonna have to go with... Let the beat hit him RB5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great, vote all nine off, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did all yours get voted off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry, I didn't notice that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess Jamie's are all gone, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you folks can vote on it right now in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Max 300.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I spelled it wrong, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the heat of the night, actually, why didn't it come up in my spell check then?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the heat of the night, Sexy Planet, Love Machine, DXY, Do It All Night, Wild Rush, Afranova, and Insertion.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you can send those votes to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Sky, and I'm in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can send your pics to me over private message, because you love me.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, a quick break featuring, um, some more Guitar Freak songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about, I'm just going to pick random ones from this little CD that Jamie gave me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Monkey Magic, that's always a fun one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, I like monkey.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, Sweet Feline, or did we, no, we already did that one, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I did that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to pick another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Star of Muse?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that will be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then that's all the time you've got to send in your votes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll be back to wrap up the big, fat, hairy, scary show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_20]: Real quickly, because I know I forgot to mention it, but it is big news in case if no one's been reading.
[SPEAKER_20]: It sort of ties in with the stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_20]: The edit code for the DDR Extreme machine has been found, and now we can make DDR Extreme edits and have started to do so.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, yay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rejoice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello everybody!
[SPEAKER_28]: So what's going on?
[SPEAKER_28]: I wasn't paying attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I think we have to do the, um, the winner or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposed to be announcing the winner for something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but Rob's occupied.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, why is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, seriously, when we went on air, did or did not, the house line rang and my cell phone went off right when we went on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then why not turn them off?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember who it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, when I used to come for my visitations to Undersedation, I would turn off my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: My cell phone wouldn't even work in there, and it hasn't been... That should have been my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my God, my cell phone has not been working in the house even recently, so I'm surprised it even went off at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who was it that called?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess... whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, the list list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: The top three songs to...
[SPEAKER_02]: HaveSexor2, GetDirtyAndNaughty2 Third place!
[SPEAKER_02]: Drumroll please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was number three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Second place.
[SPEAKER_02]: The winner is... DXY!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, second is DXY.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in first place, ByALandslide.
[SPEAKER_02]: Insertion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope you guys enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And an honorary vote for Sky's Voice the Game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_20]: And now with some show news.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think we'll be able to do phones next week.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I figured out a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_20]: So.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you're interested in being able to do this next week, we're going to be using a program probably called PhoneFree.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I will post a link in the chat room where you can find this program.
[SPEAKER_20]: And just basically sign up.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's totally free.
[SPEAKER_20]: And what you're going to want to do is I'll also give you guys an ID number, which will be our phone number.
[SPEAKER_20]: And so during the show, we'll have this hopefully available live.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I should be able to answer, well...
[SPEAKER_20]: PC phone calls, you know, it's not really using your actual phone line, phone line, it's just like, you know, almost like voice chatting over like Yahoo Instant Messenger or something like that, so maybe we're going to try that.
[SPEAKER_20]: But anyways, I'll post links, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll probably test it out during a fuck-off show sometime in the next week, like before the weekend, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you planning on doing any fuck-off shows this week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you were thinking about, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of preempted the rewind Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The way I think about it, the fuck-offs get more listeners than the rewinds anyway, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I think, you know, for me it's easier just to come home and do it on Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm sort of angsty anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to move the rewind?
[SPEAKER_02]: We can always move the rewind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care about when we do the rewind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we can talk... Let's go to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat room, go on the live journal community.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I was going to say, there you go, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puppy, start a thread on the live journal community.
[SPEAKER_05]: and everyone let us know if you would leave the Rewind on Monday or just keep the Thursday one the way it is or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can always move the Monday Rewind to Tuesday as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could just do both of them on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a possibility too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Run them back to back to back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Wednesday or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Saturday afternoon or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we cannot do it on Saturday afternoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that when Understation Live is up?
[SPEAKER_05]: We want to encourage people to listen to Understation Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I didn't realize they were on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they moved to Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought they were still doing it on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll check.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you're right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't want to interfere with Understation Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll check and make sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they moved to Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other show news, Arcadian reminded me of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arcadian42, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to point this out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But everybody, look at the person next to you and give them a big pat on the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see some pats on the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, pat people on the back because...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ladies and gentlemen, this week, Orange Lounge Radio crossed 2,500 total listening hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the highest we've ever been.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're high.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's because of a lot of hard work from a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some events that happened this month certainly helped.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we were a Bomani-style side of the week for a while, which really helped the website hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our B3 coverage helped a lot, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the shows have been doing really well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the fuck-off shows and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: So everybody's done a great job.
[SPEAKER_05]: and also I am going to start doing well I'm going to be going to school so I don't know I may have to change the night that I do this but I am going to be doing at least one regular fuck off a week one regular fuck off a week?
[SPEAKER_05]: and I think that this week I might do video game trivia I have to find my CDs or re-download stuff but maybe not this week but next week for sure I'll get all the stuff ready to do music trivia cool very cool
[SPEAKER_02]: and, uh, yeah, it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll do a fuck-off show at some point this week, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tend to do them, like, uh, whenever I'm just, like, here, Friday or Saturday, late night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to figure out how to get them to run while I'm doing Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to figure out how to get them to do while I'm doing Auro.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am seriously thinking about getting a Ragnarok account.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh!
[SPEAKER_02]: This week, finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play on, play on, play on Chaos.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna, I'm... To make everybody happy, I'm obviously gonna have to have one character on both.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: But, this is the thing, then I can have two different classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, one of them can be, like, my learning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, see, I figure when I do my next job class, I'm gonna do it on, um... If I do a merchant, I'm gonna do it on Chaos, so I can buy stuff cheap for my character.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if I do, um, any other job class, I'm gonna do it on, um, on the Loki server.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might do a Sakurai one, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: I started a Sakurai one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, there's three character slots for each server, independent to each server, so you can start three classes on each server.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um...
[SPEAKER_21]: And Loki's got technically less people on it at most times because Chaos was the original server, so there's more or a lot of people who were there since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, if you want less lag, really there's not much lag on Chaos either.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, because they only have like around 5,000 at the most.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know, I didn't even think up 5,000, so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so it, yeah, I mean, it doesn't really matter what server you start on, it's just whichever one has more of your friends on it, go to that one, I guess.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's just
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably won't even end up signing up because, like, you know, I maybe have to get back into PSO.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine automatically, I remember when you talked about last week that yours auto-canceled, I went and looked at mine and mine auto-canceled too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'd like to give a thank you to Sega for being a respectable company enough to do something like that, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless they just made it free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which would be cool as well, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I doubt that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else I wanted to say, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did get a lot of listening hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, our rating, our actual rating for the station, has fallen quite a bit in the past week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a feeling we're being zero-bombed by another station.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just suspecting it, and I'm probably creating conspiracy theories it's going to be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I noticed that the rating for another Bomani station...
[SPEAKER_02]: has gone up significantly while ours has gone down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm wondering if something's going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's really unprofessional and very dubious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm probably suspecting things I shouldn't be and going places I don't need to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't listen to another station who did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Posers.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, I listen to another station, but I have an obligation, you know, not just an obligation to... Well, I hate for their, that other station's thing that, you know, happened to them, because you know what comes around, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to say right now, it's not under Station Live, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Freak Radio and Orange Ones Radio kind of have a silent agreement on where we're not going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to give a very big thank you to the powers that be with DDR Freak Radio for being very considerate of us, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we need to be partners.
[SPEAKER_05]: All of us, Bimani Stations, we need to be partners in this and not snipe each other.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just Petty, but all of us are working to promote the games and the music.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope nobody came in in the middle of this and is thinking that, like, a specific station that we know of has been doing this, because we really don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob said, again, like, that he doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's not interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just interesting that one goes down and one goes up.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and in all honesty, I've looked at a lot of Life 365 stations, and Orange Lounge is, like, really the only entertaining one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: I personally like to listen to talk.
[SPEAKER_21]: If I want to listen to music, I'll just find pictures of the music files somewhere online.
[SPEAKER_21]: But if I want to listen to talk, it's like, Orison is the most interesting talk one.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's definitely more entertaining than any other ones out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, Under Sundation is like a completely different subject, and that's really cool too, but as far as Bomani is concerned.
[SPEAKER_05]: I consider them to be our parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: What you can do, now don't vote other stations as zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't need to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to check other stations out, we're not total Nazi radio people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go vote for them however you want to vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for us, vote a five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, vote five.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is no choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you have your little live 365 window up.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other numbers that pretend and don't work, so hit five.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have your live 365 window up right now, just change that little vote in the bottom to a five, and we would love that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll come to your house and have sex with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we'll send the monkeys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Rob can't see this, because Live365 doesn't supply this kind of technology for him to see the IPs of the people voting.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I can, because I have something that snipes in the middle and finds it, and so I can see who's voting bad, you know, and I will fucking blow up your computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: So don't vote anything low.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll send our leak team a grad after you.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was just kidding, I can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a loser.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a fucking script kiddie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that being said, our little help us be the high-rated station as opposed to going down the crapper where we've been going recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are we going to wrap it up in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ribbons and bows?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to wrap it up in pretty pink paper.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leather and pantyhose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thought time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start with our guests.
[SPEAKER_02]: LankyStyle, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye Bye Bye by NSYNC and DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: RicePrincess, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, and bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll get these phones to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kills me.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't know anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is give me money.
[SPEAKER_05]: and play Ragnarok on the Chaos Server.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just play Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so, uh, I'm trying to queue up the outro still, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does anybody have an additional final thought?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: My socks are cool, because they have blue stars on them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my cat's butt stinks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yay, I love your fortune cookie message.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and the, uh, final word of the show goes to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: The final word of the night is... Crack whore.
[SPEAKER_25]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: We expect you a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_25]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_16]: I inherited my father's eyes and my mother's eating disorder.
[SPEAKER_16]: My mother and I have the same eating disorder.
[SPEAKER_18]: She said to me, when I was pregnant with you, I eat only cherry and I think that you are just one big cherry.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are just one big gay kitty!
[SPEAKER_16]: I was on the cover of The Star once and it was for this thing called the Chow Like Cho Diet.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was so fucking racist because they just made this diet up.
[SPEAKER_16]: They didn't consult me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, it was like this total diet that they made up that they said that I went on and all these fake quotes from me.
[SPEAKER_17]: When I was young, I was raised on rice and fish.
[SPEAKER_17]: So when I get heavy, I go back to that natural Asian way of eating.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can almost hear the mandolin in the background.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I was a little girl and I grow up on the rice paddy
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have any food, because this was before Sally's daughter.
[SPEAKER_01]: So... We are so hungry all the time, and we have no money, and I want to go to the market to buy a chicken head, but I have no money, so I have to sell my finger.
[SPEAKER_13]: But... I... I...
[SPEAKER_01]: was very hungry but I still have tendency to put on weight which is why I really hope that I catch malaria because that is very good way to lose weight quickly, malaria and dysentery.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for listening and we'll see you next week.
The Afterbirth of Orange Lounge Radio.
Here we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so what's up kids?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything, uh, extra?
[SPEAKER_02]: Die, monster!
[SPEAKER_29]: You don't belong in this world!
[SPEAKER_29]: You take them souls and make them your slaves!
[SPEAKER_29]: Are you gonna, are you gonna do that as support on Cookie One Week?
[SPEAKER_03]: The same could be said of all religions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you guys just gonna act it out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I know is the die, monster part.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the Grim Reaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Grim Reaper had the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, there was supposed to be an ending where Maria turned evil.
[SPEAKER_13]: It does just sound
[SPEAKER_05]: The sound file's on the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's like, like, who would have thought such a little girl had so much power?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, but she's like the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, I like the Grim Reaper part.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, hello, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love his voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, do the intro.
[SPEAKER_02]: The dark brief shaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do the intro to Castlevania, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it, Brad, do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I'm gonna fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Come on, do it, do it, do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I need to get my, like, wine glass and my Dracula teeth.
[SPEAKER_21]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't look at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody look around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not looking at you.
Don't look at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Die, monster.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't belong in this world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody else has to do the Dracula part.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know the Dracula part, so you just have to do your Dracula voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was not by my hand that I was once again given flesh.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was brought here by humans who used to wish to pay me tribute.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tribute?
[SPEAKER_21]: You steal men's souls and make them your slaves.
[SPEAKER_21]: Perhaps the same could be said of all religions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your words are as empty as your soul.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mankind ill needs a savior such as you.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is a man?
[SPEAKER_03]: For a little wine glass.
[SPEAKER_03]: A miserable little pile of secrets.
[SPEAKER_03]: But enough talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, it was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_21]: That is the best dialogue out of any video game ever in the history of mankind.
[SPEAKER_02]: The acting is perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care what you think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, can you make a remix using those lines?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why you wanted me to do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I knew, I should have known that's why you wanted me to do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Brad's voiced the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got, I can give you the whole thing in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_21]: Die, monster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Die, monster.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should actually copy off my Japanese one, too, and play it for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: I might do something like that, but unfortunately, my name starts with an M. What?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: In other words, I'm not a person that also has four letters in their name, begins with a T, ends with a N, and makes stupid remixes.
[SPEAKER_19]: So there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, then I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you know what that is backwards?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Newt.
[SPEAKER_02]: well now I'm gonna make a remix called the beauty of silence silence mix and it's just gonna go the beauty of silence and then like a minute of silence and I'm gonna say see it's beautiful and then like sex noises in the back and kittens getting choked just kidding
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, do you want to give a plug to going to vote for Shermie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I put Shermie's picture up on RateMyKitten.com, but it's not up there yet, and I actually don't know where her site is for her picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she's just on there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a picture of Shermie on Mel's lap, being sleepy and cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so does anybody else have anything they want to say for the wrap-up here?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm fucking hungry, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a bunch of snack foods up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want snack foods.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a meal.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I just want a meal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm tired of eating all these sneaky snacks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, poor thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poor thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can eat my dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, that's too many calories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I promise you it's sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's full of fat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And high in fiber.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, did somebody fart or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, yes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki has something he'd like to share with you all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, we just had, like, a bunch of radio silence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mumble, mumble, mumble.
[SPEAKER_02]: That air is such great radio here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, are you trying to do the poodle hat thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to play a poodle hat track?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Loki wants to play a poodle hat track for you all.
[SPEAKER_12]: A hat rack?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's quiet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is shitty radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You talk!
[SPEAKER_02]: I do too much talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: People complain that I talk too much, so I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rod, you talk too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: See what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: People, visit our live journal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody visit our forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody vote us a five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to us all day long.
[SPEAKER_23]: and watch all the TV you ever wanted until your brain turned to mush.
[SPEAKER_23]: Would you go for it or just let it slip?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yo!
[SPEAKER_23]: The remote is ready, eyes wide, palms are sweaty.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Flintstones on the TV already, Wilma and Betty.
[SPEAKER_15]: No virgin, the channel's serving and I'm HD ready.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I flip, garbage is all I'm getting.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Simon Cowell who folks wanna disavow.
[SPEAKER_15]: He opens his mouth, always says something.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Fowl, they're dyin' wow, wanna be the cryin' now, see both the mouths, it's time to throw in the towel, show based on reality, oh, the humanity, oh, of these families, show the profanity, oh, the insanity, oh, the fat crappin' behold, of depravity, no, they live happily, yo, plus the allergy show, and celebrity mo, oh, the van and the coal, she's scarin' me, look monocavity, oh, it's a station break, better go out to the
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm watching TV, they told me, they told me, but I'm still good at every show, my game will be Street Fan TV, Landon, HBO, The Travel Channel, Discovery, and Lifetime, I'm watching TV, they told me, they told me, I'm gonna watch Street Fan TV, Landon, HBO,
[SPEAKER_15]: My blood is aching, as I watch NASCAR racing, that show about undertaking, Larry King, till 24 to, line order, the weather channel's boring, like 50 minutes of ancient reporters, next up on True Hollywood Story, the rise and decline of pro-actors in quarries,
[SPEAKER_15]: Choke for next call, they've already been naming CSI Braves, he's touched by an uncle, but sounds pretty layman So does everybody tolerate Raymond?
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't believe Richard Simmons ain't in it I'll move right on the way, simple rules for late My teenage daughter, then I bet I'll watch The Bachelorette Followed by Welcome Back, Potter, and The Muppet Show Where they go, but I'm not in it Use your mind, watchin' TV They told me, they told me, but I still do
[SPEAKER_15]: and every show.
[SPEAKER_15]: My game will be Speed Fan TV Land and HBO.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll just be channeling day and day and lifetimes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't wanna lose your mind watching TV.
[SPEAKER_15]: They told me, they told me, but that's the lowest I could go.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm looking at Speed Fan TV Land and HBO.
[SPEAKER_15]: My game will be channeling for a TV lifetime.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never miss no replay for
[SPEAKER_15]: I would've raced, but I only watched Will and Grace one time one day Wish I hadn't put Steve on our three-time game I watched Macy an hour, after that felt like I needed a long shower
[SPEAKER_15]: Naked Ambition, next week on Fox, watch Lions beat Christians, life to tie up the programming planners, make them watch all of that junk till their heads explode just like standards, reach cover driving and fool the survivors, let their dreams live in discussing the oeuvre of Mr. Rock Snyder and the still again in SpongeBob Plus, with MacGyver and Jay Leno, I've got Madonna haters, Luke Perry, and a special all-pig Latin episode,
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm Drew Carey, wanna turn on E.T.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cause I'm a gossip freak, and I gotta know who they know It's Marianne this week, a 30 second spot, looking back to R.U.
[SPEAKER_15]: Potts I was planning on recording the Sopranos, who I forgot I love shows with or without a plot, I'll stare at some of the legs and numb my eyes Bloodshot, because I only have got one brain to rot I'm gonna spend my life watching television a lot You're not a music, if I'm watching TV They told me, they told me, but I'm still doing every show
[SPEAKER_15]: Good Dear Lord, this is like the longest afterbirth ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay though, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else want to be said about Weird Al or anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_13]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, before we murder your eardrums further, I think it's time to put the proverbial bullet in the brain of this evening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fire it up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you be correcting my English.
[SPEAKER_02]: I are speak good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so we're going to kick it to some music now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to play a fun non-stop for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one of my favorite non-stops.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Super Classics' best non-stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a bunch of like 80 songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least like 80 songs that were big like in Japan and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you get some cool stuff like Together Forever, Telephone Operator, and then it's mixed with like Heaven is a Place on Earth and Flashdance and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is a fun mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a feelin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a feelin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then some more non-stops on into the evening.
[SPEAKER_02]: So enjoy you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you as always for supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We really appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big kisses and is that it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going home now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.