[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight, February 7th, 2010, a new Sonic the Hedgehog game is announced.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could you soon get premium Warcraft features on your iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: And what first-person shooter is coming to Facebook?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm here with you every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to the lady shouting fail, fail over there in the corner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our very own fail blog here in house, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fail!
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I win.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like cookies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, so tonight he is Cookie Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm sure he'll talk about tech here and there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, you've been kind of over there hammering on YouTube, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on over there on YouTube, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they just uploaded my new video and disabled all the audio because they're awesome like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you use copyright music?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, copyright.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there's tons of videos out there that have copyright music in them.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll find someplace else to upload it because YouTube sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Daddy playin' the game!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played a crap ton of Star Trek online.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I realized when I decided to go on the quest to find Deep Space Nine that my little character had been just running around the promenade for about an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just running around.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Running around.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except for some solitaire.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been playing actual solitaire on the computer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, do they even include solitaire on the computer anymore?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's included.
[SPEAKER_09]: That and Spider Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really looked.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few others, Hearts and Freestyle and all that crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played more Borderlands and...
[SPEAKER_11]: That's still entertaining me.
[SPEAKER_11]: More Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_11]: Finally made it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm in the top 100 players now for true skill rankings.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm in like the mid 90s now for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And working my way up just the cumulative ranked deathmatch stats.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I think I'm
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it varies depending on how much I play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I'm around 230 something right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I purchased Bioshock 2, so I played a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that one's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very similar, obviously, to the first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Bioshock 2 wasn't out until Tuesday, but you have the hookup, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not out until Tuesday, but it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, definitely worth checking out, especially if you like the first game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It seems like there's going to be a lot of similarities between this game and the last one, but so far I'm digging it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do they have multiplayer in this one?
[SPEAKER_12]: They do, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be the big kicker right there, because that was one kind of glaring omission in the first one, and what a lot of people were clamoring for.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's probably the whole sale of the game right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if I'll even play the multiplayer, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just doesn't seem like anything I'd be interested in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever I play those multiplayer shooting games, I get raped in the face, and that's not a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, not necessarily that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just seems like tacked on or something, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of the same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing more Bayonetta and World of Warcraft and some of those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only new game I really checked out this week was one of the new Xbox Live Arcade games that they have called Chime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody on Twitter had posted, hey, if you like Luminous, you should play Chime.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, I could definitely see where somebody is making the comparisons between Chime and Luminous.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're both puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're both heavily involved with music.
[SPEAKER_04]: They both have a beat line that sweeps across the screen and they have very similar looking screens, might I say, that affects the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But where the games get very different is that, you know, you could say Luminous is somewhat of a Tetris inspired game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chime is like, I'm going to get really old school here and I bet half the listeners don't even know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chime is like Dedalion Opus on the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyone ever played Dedalion Opus?
[SPEAKER_08]: A while back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's one of these games here, since you probably haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically like you have all these shapes that you're trying to put in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're all square based, but they might be in an L shape or a jagged shape.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't think just Tetris pieces, because sometimes they're like five or six blocks in a row.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you try to fit them into this square or some other type of geometric shape.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think maybe like tangrams.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all based around Tetris style shapes, if that makes any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You try to kind of fit them in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Chime is about trying to make 3x3 squares as fast as you can out of these odd shapes, which it's a little harder than it sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Ray Iannami in our chatroom, chat.orangelunchradio.com, Tetrominos, I think it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what you're talking about there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same kind of idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, here's the thing is that as you build these blocks, your multiplier goes up the faster you build them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And oddly enough, yeah, it enhances the music as you build.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are songs by Moby, one of the guys from Orbital.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phillip Glass has a song in there which I thought was totally random so there's some actually some big name talent in the game probably only about five songs in the game but it's only a five dollar game and I don't know maybe there will be expansions later but anyhow the beat sweeper will kind of sweep out your crap if you leave it behind too long like if you've let these isolated pieces that didn't get formed into blocks the beat sweeper will filter them out after it gets hit maybe like five times and then they all flush out and you lose your multiplier multiplier
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's good for cleaning up the board, but it's bad for your score.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's the gist of Chime.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually kind of a neat little puzzler.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was kind of cool, and the music was very trancy, zony, but I thought it was decent for a game like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And best of all, it's only $5, even though it's only five songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now here's the thing, is that the game is supposed to go for charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really advertise heavily in the game that 60% of the purchase price...
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to these various children's charities and you can go online and look.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I thought was a little weird though is that they actually as part of the sales pitch of the game say, buy this game and feel good about supporting charities.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and you get 50 gamer score just for buying the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's an achievement that is called something like, and I'm paraphrasing here, feel good about yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50 gamer score.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can feel good about yourself and the purchase you've made of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it just gives you basically 50 gamer score for I guess going to the title screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was a little weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, yeah, I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're essentially buying gamerscore, if you think about it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not that I necessarily have a problem with that, with the charity angle, but the fact that it's kind of marketed like that is a little, I don't want to say off-putting, but that's the best word I can think of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say, though, that it's more like just a little way of saying thank you for your donation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that badge should be worth zero gamerscore if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'm okay with there being like a little badge of pride like, yay, have your warm fuzzies for buying our charity game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't think it should be worth any gamerscore and I don't think they should be advertising like, hey, if you buy this game, we'll give you 50 gamerscore just for getting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, that just kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: It just seems like it opens the floodgates to all this kind of like devious behavior.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I understand it's for charity and maybe like Microsoft kind of let him get away with that for all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not trying to like knock the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just, when I kind of looked at that, I kind of made one of those raised eyebrow faces of that ain't right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That ain't right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I think for just like a good little chill out game, five bucks is not asking too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, despite my little issue with the 50 gamer score for free, it is a feel good thing that you can do like, hey, I bought this game and the money's going to charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty much my gaming week, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_04]: So those are pretty much the games I was playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about you guys in chat?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some guys in chat kind of talking about the charity thing I was just talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Kevin DDR in chat says, Only thing that irritated me was the different choice of pieces on different songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that something that fundamental to the gameplay strategy would stay consistent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kevin DDR also said, I assumed achievements generally got the amount of points based on the relative difficulty of the achievement.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, unfortunately, some developers don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good point, because that 50 gamerscore achievement is like the biggest one in that game, because they only have 200 to work with.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the rest of the achievements are, some of them are fairly difficult, at least from the little bit I played.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments from chat.orangeloungeradio.com Some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we always like to plug our Twitter and our Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.twitter.com slash OLR if you want to follow us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do a segment of the show called Twitter Topics up a little later where you guys can get your questions and your story suggestions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Done right here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we like to pitch ourselves as the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we want you guys to be heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook is also another way you can follow us at facebook.com slash orange lounge radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can join our little Facebook club there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we like to post little updates with what's going on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to thank the community at AllGames.com www.AllGames.com It's All Games Radio and it's the place where we do tape our show live every Sunday night and as I always say on the show if you don't like what you hear from us maybe one of the other shows on the network is more your cup of tea because as mentioned before, I think Jamie mentioned everybody she knows is playing Mass Effect 2 but we're all sitting here going, well we just really haven't been playing that because I've been too busy playing Bayonetta and Raiding and DarkSakura's been too busy playing Star Trek Online and
[SPEAKER_04]: Shooting Klingons But I'm sure there's lots of other shows where they're talking about Mass Effect 2 non-stop So if that's more your cup of tea, hey, cool But if you do like our show, one last little plug Please visit iTunes, search for Orange Launch Radio And leave us a nice little review iTunes, by the way, recently changed the podcast page format To kind of match the rest of the CDs and things in the marketplace So if you go visit Orange Launch Radio You can see the most popular shows in our feed and so forth Although...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a little early to really be tracking those type of statistics but I thought it was neat you can see the little cover arts of the shows that it suggests like people who listen to Orange Lounge Radio also like and it shows all the little cover art you know who the number one show is that suggested people who also listen to Orange Lounge Radio also like you know what the number one show is in the list any guesses do tell Bobby Blackwolf our good pal Bobby is the number one suggestion of course he is because you know we're on right back to back on all games radio I'm sure we're number one on his list too
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, also getting information from our chatroom, www.orangelantradio.com, click on chat or you can go to chat.orangelantradio.com TigerClaw says, hey this just in, Dante's Inferno ad just played during the fourth quarter, because they're watching the Super Bowl right now With the tagline, Hell Awaits, which if I remember right, wasn't there some controversy that they weren't going to air that promo?
[SPEAKER_11]: They just made them edit it so it wasn't saying go to hell
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, that's right, it was gonna say go to hell, now it's hell awaits Who cares, it doesn't matter A little weird I did play the demo for that game, it was neat It was kind of God of War-ish, but fun Yeah So, not that, I mean, being God of War is not a bad thing Alright, let's get into some gaming news Lots of gaming news this week, surprisingly enough We're really starting to kind of kick into the year And all the game news, and Loki's starting us off with some big news, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, this is, I don't know if it's completely big news.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, kind of, we could have figured this out pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_11]: Project Needlemouse, you know, the project that they were working on that was a 2D Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a surprise, except it's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is kind of unique about it is it's going to be available only as an episodic game, and it's available on all the different download services.
[SPEAKER_11]: We wear PlayStation Network, Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess the first episode will be available this summer, and hopefully it's good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just not that excited about it, that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it because maybe there hasn't been like a really, really like OMG, squee in my pants, exciting Sonic game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, because they always say, oh, we're gonna do what people wanted us to do, and then they fuck it up somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments in our chat seem to agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ray Ayanami says, can Sega not fuck up Sonic 4?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I know you're a big Sonic fan girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was your reaction to the trailer?
[SPEAKER_08]: Squee.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna take a cookie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you better eat that last cookie before I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's, no, no, no, I don't need any more cookies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here, I have to admit, even though the trailer didn't show much, I mean, it just kind of showed the whole idea of, hey, we're making a new Sonic game in the original Genesis game canon, which we haven't touched in, what, 15 years, I think?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, maybe longer than that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it is the updated model.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: right and what I thought was interesting is that you know the little glimpse of gameplay you see was a very Sonic 3 corkscrew looking thing that just looked very souped up in 3D like it's interesting Mega Man 9 has sort of opened the floodgates to this kind of stuff in a way I don't know do you think this was inspired by the success of Mega Man 9 or do you think Sega's just finally getting the hint people just want the old shit with new a new coat of paint or what
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I've noticed, and this is almost with any type of genre, be it art, music, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of times you get this going towards the bigger, the better, the whole, you know, brand new, shiny, 3D, whatever, digital.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there comes a phase in everything that you go back to the old way of doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, you want the classic look, you want the classic play.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, else we wouldn't have, you know, Sonic 4, we wouldn't have the new Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, shoot, even art's done the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like right after the Victorian age, you know, we, well, kind of around the same time, there were people that were going back to the old handmade way of doing things.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think it's just culture.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: History repeats itself kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitstun says, Well, Sega did a great job with OutRun 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if we're thinking of the same game here, but there was an OutRun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was OutRun 2, but there was an OutRun game on Xbox Live and PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, OutRun 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like for a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan played the crap out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't like OMG best game ever, but for a little arcade racing game that kind of invoked the old style of OutRun, I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I did buy the full version and played it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It had Magical Sound Shower and that's the important thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sure did.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Magical Sound Shower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some other comments in chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee says, I think this is Sega's final try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that if this doesn't live up to the hype that Sonic's done?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a done franchise?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bury it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Sonic isn't going to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't think Sonic would die either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something to think about, even if Sonic 4 tanks, which I highly doubt it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're doing the right thing in invoking the past here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if, for whatever crazy ass reason, Sonic 4 tanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's not forget, Mario and Sonic at the Winter Olympics and the Summer Olympics and all that stuff was huge on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Sonic as a character I think still has a lot of kind of clout, if you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that
[SPEAKER_04]: Oddly enough, if Sonic 4 were to tank, which again, I don't think it will Sonic would mainly exist in Nintendo franchises Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just the way things are going
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to suck for them because now, since they're not putting out a full retail version, I'm assuming it's going to be cheaper.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if people really hate the game, they're not out as much money.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is good for the consumer, bad for Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think maybe they're just doing this so that by the time they put out Episode 1, Episode 2, Episode 3, they make about as much money as they would have if they just put the game out on DVD, Blu-ray?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much, but that's assuming if everybody buys all the parts to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, chat.orangehauntsradio.com if you want to comment on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there anything else for this story, Loki, you wanted to add?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, yeah, I was also going to say that, um, one other platform that it's supposed to be coming out on is the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's kind of typical with anything nowadays.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, I'm going to assume that this is on the iPhone is going to control like shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just my guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a little weird that it's coming to the iPhone because, you know, I'm not a big fan of all these games getting adapted to the iPhone because the touch thing is a little weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments, more comments from our chat room, chat.orangelounge.com Tiger Claw says, the fact that the game is episodic probably means you will have your epic boss battle against Doc Robotnik.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't that a given?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like at the end of every stage you always have to have your, you know, Doc Robotnik battle at the end?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's every stage, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, TigerClaw says, actually, he's correcting that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will not have your epic boss battle against Doc Robotnik.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe that, like, you have, like, mini-bosses.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how that would work.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt says, it should have Michael Jackson music in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know if that's going to be very possible at this point, unless they were working in secret, you know, more than a year ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I somehow doubt that is the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think all of us in studio kind of agree, though, we will pick up Sonic 4, at least check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I will, because I do love the old Sonic games, and I'm all about checking out the new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure, I know Jamie's gonna buy it, I don't even have to ask her.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, will you buy it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_11]: One holdout.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not, dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I haven't bought any of the Sonic games, I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not really a game that I really got into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe Loki will care about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I sure did, because I let out the biggest fangirl scream when I saw this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, seriously, I'm not even joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I saw this last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about out of right field.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this came out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sunsoft, remember they reformed not that long ago, announced that Blaster Master Overdrive is on its way out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, a remade new version of Blaster Master, although...
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not believe this is like a remake.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is actually a sequel of the NES classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just kind of forgetting that, you know, Blaster Master 2 on Genesis and the Game Boy One never happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is the sequel to Blaster Master will be coming out on WiiWare for 1,000 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what I think is the biggest twist out of this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said, oh yeah, and the game, it's coming out Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: as in tomorrow as in we've kept this a secret for however long we've been working on this and hey now it's out now you can buy it and there's even a little trailer out there that shows some of the gameplay I'm playing a little bit of it in studio because great awesome enough it has a remixed version of the theme I don't like the remix version of the theme they kind of like fucked it up you know what nothing is ever going to be as good as the original that's really what it is I don't like this one at all but this is not bad it could have been a lot worse
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can definitely see it's 16x9.
[SPEAKER_04]: The overhead stages look a lot different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, this game just kind of has more of a Metroid look to it, which I'm all over that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's like some of these overhead levels have ice themes and more cavern themes, whereas I don't remember that being the case in the first one.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, maybe, they'll probably be up Dan's alley Now, Loki, which would you rather play, Sonic 4 or Blaster Master Overdrive?
[SPEAKER_04]: Blaster Master Oh, okay I had to ask, I had to DarkSakura, what do you got?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it was bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that it was expected maybe sooner rather than now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Xbox Live is going to be canceling out support for the original console.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's going into effect on April 15th.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's also not just the console, but for games that are compatible with both the 360 and the old Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: and basically saying that because more people now are really on Xbox 360 that that's what they want to focus their power on and cut the support so they can focus more fully on the newer system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 2 Halo 3 Halo 2
[SPEAKER_09]: well they're saying also that the other big thing is that the changes that they want to make to the service are as I say incompatible with the original games with the old games
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: so that's one of the big things that getting rid of the original Xbox games and shutting down Halo 2 and so forth will free up and I would say by the end of the year probably whenever the patch comes out for Natal your friends list is going to get a big bump and you'll be able to have 250, 500, maybe even unlimited friends I don't know and I'm sure there are some other technical components that we're just not aware of because we haven't thought of them yet but there's some other things that they have to shut off these games for
[SPEAKER_04]: but on the flip side there's a lot of as you can understand ticked off people still playing the original Xbox still playing Halo 2 haven't upgraded Xbox 360 yet that are very sad about this news what do you guys think too bad so sad it's time to give it up and put it away or do they do they make a case maybe Microsoft needs to find a way to still support this
[SPEAKER_11]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously, how many people are still playing the original Xbox?
[SPEAKER_11]: Upgrade, get a new system.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's bound to happen that they're going to shut off servers.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, just because you're paying for it now, okay, great, that you're paying for it month to month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now you're not.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really feel sad about these people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do find it strange okay the original Xbox games couldn't be patched or whatever I get that but I do find it strange that Microsoft won't find a way to still let Halo 2 be playable on the 360 you know what I mean like via a patch or via you know because Halo 2 is an on-demand game it's a download game so that you could fix it so that you could still play it on Xbox 360 at least you know fix whatever is the problem with the friends list and play it that way you would think they would do that but they're not
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw does bring up a good point though in our chat room, chat.orangelawntrader.com People can still play Halo 2 multiplayer if they get the PC version So, you know, Halo 2 is not forgotten for everybody Let's see, Hitstun in our chat says if you have an original Xbox and it's not modded, it's time to mod it And that also makes me think of the fact that, you know, you could also go the way of the original Halo And if you really want to play your Halo 2 or your Halo, it's time to break out the LAN party
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we still do that sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we would have the TVs all over the house.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I'll tell you what's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan's bachelor party was really a bunch of people over playing all the systems all land.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru in chat is correcting me that Halo 2 isn't a game on demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I assumed that it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Halo 1 is, but not Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, but let me just say to that then, okay, make it a game on demand and make it so that it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seems a little strange to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Link in our chatroom says EA does it all the time That's true, EA shuts down servers for old games And we kind of go, well, they're old There's new versions of the game out And sure enough, there is Halo 3 and Halo ODST out at this point I did like what Sega did when they closed the PSO servers Is that for the people that were running private servers They actually gave them a way to transfer characters and things
[SPEAKER_09]: and I would think that if people are actually still playing that then there should be some other way to host your own server for it or something and have that be like an external for some reason I don't see Microsoft supporting that out of the companies like I could see why Sega would do that but I could see why Microsoft would not if that makes sense
[SPEAKER_04]: and SJ100 Matt in our chatroom says in the end nothing lasts forever and I guess that's another point as well is that hey you know that game you got a good six or seven year run out of it right no no wait I'm saying too much that's how long Xbox Live has been around Halo 2 has probably been going what about four or five years about it came out while we were doing this show I played Halo 1 for the first time and we were on the air so it's been around for five years five years that's a pretty good run
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru in chat says, Microsoft will more than likely make Halo 2 an Xbox Live Arcade title, if anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be kind of cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might actually bring me back to Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially with some souped up graphics and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, again in chat, you said it good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing lasts forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And someday they're going to shut down the servers for all the games we're playing today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably in five years when we've moved on to the Xbox 720s and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: There's TVs all over the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a TV on the kitchen table, a TV in the living room, a TV everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they all had Nintendos hooked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, what the hell is going on here?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie's like, they're having a LAN party, a local area Nintendo party.
[SPEAKER_04]: All these TVs had Nintendo systems hooked up and they were playing The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess they were having a contest to see who could beat The Legend of Zelda first.
[SPEAKER_04]: and some people were like already on the seventh dungeon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I think your husband was really far ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think Dan actually won that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure he did.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some people were still struggling.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were on like dungeon three and some people were in the overworld so I couldn't really tell where they were at.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just remember thinking, that is the fucking coolest thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I was like, Jamie and I are going to get along just fine because this had to be about a year before we started OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean it was a while before OLR but I just remember thinking, wow, this is all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of miss that house except I don't miss where it was yeah so anyway I just wanted to tell that story if you never heard it before here on the show because I always think that's hilarious and I would love nothing more than to see another LAN party happen somewhere somehow I think that would be a lot of fun so if there's ever if Dan ever decides he's doing another Nintendo party I want in
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to bring my FC Mobile.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind, though, we probably got three other NESs, and you have an NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right, I do have the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have that, but I don't have a Zelda cart, but we can get one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I've got like three of them hanging around somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the batteries, I think, finally died in one of them, but we've also got Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those batteries were only guaranteed to last like five years, but most of them have lasted like 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got a little tangent, but that happens here on this show sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, bring us back with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, Facebook's been getting a lot of games recently, and a lot of them have been pretty basic, and they're starting to get some better stuff, like with the new Civilization game and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now they're actually getting a first-person shooter game.
[SPEAKER_11]: This game's called Brave Arms, and it actually looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of like a...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if the Quake Online stuff, like Quake Zero or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's from 3G Studios.
[SPEAKER_11]: And apparently it's set to come out in March.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's kind of similar to a Doom, Quake, Halo, Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Patent pending.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, would you play a game like that for free?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'd check it out at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Quake Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played that for a little bit when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was cool because it was based off Quake 3, which was like the best freaking Quake they ever did.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, somebody in chat agrees with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah yes, ZenthralZen says, Quake 3 Arena, best LAN party game ever, period.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of the best over the internet games too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a lot of fun to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a good time with that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see how this Facebook game goes, but I'm telling you guys, this is the direction gaming's moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook as a platform for gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty soon you're going to be talking Xbox 360, Wii, PS3, PC, and Facebook gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and iPhones.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to throw that in there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook is like a serious platform for gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing to take very seriously, as a lot of people do, is World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some people take the auction house dealings very seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, some people kind of play the economy as like the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't really get into the whole auction house dealings, so I'm not sure exactly what they do, but I guess it's kind of like the stock market.
[SPEAKER_04]: You buy items that are plentiful, and then when they're not available, you sell them at a high profit, is basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, people that play World of Warcraft for the auctions and for the markets are in for a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Blizzard has announced this week that soon you are going to be able to manage your auctions from World of Warcraft using the Armory application on the iPhone or iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know much about exactly how this will work yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know the specifics like can you access your in-game mail too because that's the only way you get the money from your auctions or how would you post something if you can't access your character's bags or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know the answer to all the specifics yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just know that Blizzard is throwing out that idea of you could play the economical game of World of Warcraft on the go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, one thing they are saying with this as well is that it will cost money.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a premium-based service.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've said premium-based, which you know that means cost money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know if that'll be a monthly thing that you add on for your character or what I would assume would be the option would be you charge for the app on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to be releasing this on the iPhone, you're going to charge $9.99 for the app or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how they will make their money.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I know you're not a big WoW player anymore, but let's say they had an equivalent in Star Trek Online, or let's imagine you did still play WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think this is the kind of thing you'd be interested in?
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as it's free But it's not, so you wouldn't pay a premium for it?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I wouldn't Then again, this is the person who just bought, you know, a thousand cryptic points Why do you think someone would be into this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you think someone would say, hey, because I'm looking at this going, you know, as awesome as this feature sounds And depending on the cost, I might just, like if it is just like five bucks for the app, I might just buy it to check it out I don't see myself really using it, like it's kind of weird to be using that on the phone
[SPEAKER_09]: I was trying to look at the page for the interface and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they don't have that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all they've said now is an announcement.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used the Armory itself, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not that obsessed about the games I play.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's something for addicts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I know you're not a big MMO player anymore, but let's assume this was five years ago and this was a Final Fantasy XI auction house app.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's an app for an iPhone or something like that, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, but let's say it was something you could access on the web too or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not for you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I go into game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to admit, although I might be willing to kind of check it out just for the sake of checking it out, I don't know if I'd want to pay a monthly fee just to manage my auctions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's kind of what... And the other thing that kind of worries me
[SPEAKER_04]: This is like my one little weird worry and I don't know maybe the chatters can tell me if I'm being irrational with this but I kind of always thought this was how a lot of the gold farmers made their money.
[SPEAKER_04]: So by kind of allowing folks to do this without being actually in the game could you possibly be encouraging the gold farming community and the people that are hacking and stealing accounts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that an irrational line of thought or do I have a legitimate concern there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You tell me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com We'll get to some of that feedback in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll move on with the news for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, you remember when we were talking about Akira Yamaoka leaving Konami?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we know where he ended up.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's with Grasshopper Manufacture and is supposed to be doing music for an upcoming horror game that they're doing that's produced by Shinji Mikami.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: So, maybe it's going to be going back to, you know, more of the, a game that has the feel of the older Silent Hill, you know, not necessarily the kind of Americanized ones now, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: But just if it puts anything in perspective, Grasshopper did Fatal Frame 4 and No More Heroes 2, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you know that they have the translation project for Fatal Frame 4?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think we covered that a few weeks ago, probably about a month ago on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: If that's the kind of game he's going to work on, then perhaps it's a worthy thing that he's jumped ship.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know where I read this, and it's probably just one of those fan wank rumors, I don't know, but I had heard that EA was courting Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, EA is producing the game that Grasshopper's working on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it was kind of jumping to conclusions type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, maybe this would lead to Akira Yamaoka getting to do whatever Silent Hill-y horror game I'm sure EA would be more than happy to publish.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I wouldn't doubt that at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that man is pretty much Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going back to the chatroom, chat.orangelearnersradio.com and some of the comments from the auction app for WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt in our chatroom says, I bet there will be an auction house app for Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it will be interesting to see how Squeenix kind of embraces all this stuff that WoW is doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed for XI, especially towards the end, they tried to do some...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see other comments from chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xlink says, I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it also says that he thought of the same thing that I was mentioning with the gold farmers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's why he's not using it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also was a quick shout out there from HitStun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does Dissida have any Final Fantasy XI characters?
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Mac clarifying, yes, there's a quick cameo of a Final Fantasy XI character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XI is tricky to do because...
[SPEAKER_04]: There was no standard hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were the hero and you could look a variety of different ways, you know, because you could customize your character.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although everyone had the same outfit over and over and over and over.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the customization was very limited.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did like, so seeing the male characters walking around in their leather mantis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was always a, what were they called?
[SPEAKER_04]: The bronze, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it looked like mantis, basically, who was running around and it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: With a harness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's... But some of like maybe the boss characters and some of the NPCs that you interact with I could see being in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's what they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it is too.
[SPEAKER_04]: S2100Mac clarifies it's a TaruTaru.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one of the characters that's in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't surprise me at all, because Tarotaro is what everybody remembers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even in Final Fantasy XIV, they're going to have Tarotaros, but they're not calling them Tarotaros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is so weird to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is absolutely retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as the game is good, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call them Sexy Chocolate for all I care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sexy Chocolate?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to roll a Sexy Chocolate White Mage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how that works, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god, we need to do some release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quick, please, change the topic, help.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well this isn't anything to do with sexy chocolate, but I guess since next week is Valentine's week, and I guess it could be sexy chocolate.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're into that kind of thing for Dante's Inferno, because nothing says sexy chocolate like tortured souls in hell, uh...
[SPEAKER_11]: Star Ocean Last Hope International Edition
[SPEAKER_11]: Family Party, 30 Great Games, Winter Fun, yet another party game compilation for the Wii World Cup of Pool, coming to the DS Shirin the Wanderer, coming to the Wii, which looks pretty awesome, that's from Atlus
[SPEAKER_11]: and, of course, the big one for the week, Bioshock 2, making its way out on PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or, if you're a teenage girl, perhaps seeing Twilight is the big game for you this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: That will be out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want none of those or just own a Wii, then perhaps Super Monkey Ball Step and Roll will be your type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's coming out just on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you know how much it would amuse me, especially for the YouTube channel, if we were to follow you with a camera to one of those midnight releases for Dante's Inferno or Bioshock 2, because they're both coming out at the same time, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you walk up to the counter and ask for a scene at Twilight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except I wouldn't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: by the way the reason why that's called the Divine Edition is because the Inferno was part of the Divine Comedy by Dante Alighieri so that's why it's called the Divine Version there you go which I've read that in 5th grade
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was called the Divine Edition because it's like, you know, Sony's way of saying, hey, look, we have something exclusive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, we may have lost Final Fantasy, you know, 13 and, you know, Residents of Fate and all the other games that have come out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, we still got the Divine Edition.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not gonna be able to get that download content until later.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just trying to be all literary and cultured and shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they called it the Divine Edition because the Sexy Chocolate Edition just got rejected is what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, some other release dates for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game coming out on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sacred 2 Fallen Angel makes its way to Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm trying to see what kind of game this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, I can see that, but I'm trying to figure out what more about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this like a Final Fantasy-ish kind of game?
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphics look interesting, kind of like in a desert.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out here last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's like a not-Chocobo in the game there that you can ride.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't localize this for the U.S., though, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a Boca Cho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the reviews, though, I'm reading online, this game is massive.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's tons of quests, and the level cap is 200.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was probably written by the publisher.
[SPEAKER_04]: if you don't want to play that on the Xbox 360 you could check it out on PlayStation 3 because it's coming out there too as well as a game called Winter Sports 2010 The Great Tournament I'm assuming that's like coming from a company who didn't get the Olympic license but wants to cash in on it anyway so there you go if you want you can check out on the Nintendo Wii Mad World makes its way for Japan this week that is a Japanese localized release on the Nintendo Wii this week coming from Sega
[SPEAKER_04]: and unfortunately a lot of folks passed here but maybe if it does very well in Japan there'll still be a sequel so you might want to consider picking that up on the Nintendo DS this week Mina no Konveni comes out this week and it is a strategy based game but when I say that it looks like a little girl going cooking it's not cooking mama but kind of like cafeteria managing maybe kind of a version of Diner Dash I don't know kind of what it strikes me as from the pictures I see there
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly taking a look at the PSP, Shin Sangoku Musou Multirade gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is already out, but it's getting a little price cut this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Dynasty Warriors Strike Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you might know the game better as.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's going on overseas in the UK?
[SPEAKER_04]: The other way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, for the UK, we've got a few goodies.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Bioshock 2 on the 9th and on the 10th, Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the 12th is Bleach the Third Phantom, Half-Minute Hero, Phantasy Star Zero, Star Ocean, The Last Hope, and Super Monkey Ball Step and Roll.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, so this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently there is a developer resume, um, that's hinting at an Xbox 360 version of Final Fantasy 14.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um, apparently also this is, uh, was being, uh, removed a few hours later.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently this profile that was on a website linked in for designer Yuki Akama referenced work on Final Fantasy XIV for PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, only the PC and PS3 platforms have been officially confirmed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not only that, but Sony took great pride in last year's E3 at saying you can only play this on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And leading many folks to question if the Xbox Live hurdle proved to be too much for Squeenix to deal with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I'm sure Microsoft doesn't want to lose that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure we'll hear whether it's coming out on the 360 or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Earlier this week I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you ever use the website LinkedIn, Matt?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like a professional Facebook, I think is the best way I can describe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a profile on there, and basically it's kind of like a place where you can post your resume and do job searches, but it's supposed to be a way to professionally connect with your coworkers and people they know and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more like a professional LinkedIn, and there are quite a few of the gaming community uses that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've connected with quite a few other podcast hosts and so forth on LinkedIn.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure it will come out on 360 it only makes sense I mean more people that they can get on the service the better it is for them so I don't see why they wouldn't it just seems weird to me that Sony was so excited about it and then just to lose this again you know because this would be twice in a row with the whole Final Fantasy 13 thing going to Xbox that's gonna be a blow to the ego um we'll see like I said um
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a version of...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a version on the 360 could be eventually, but it would seem like that might come out later.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the other thing, Squeenix doesn't seem to think that Final Fantasy will do well on 360 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind, Final Fantasy 13, not happening on the 360 in Japan, or hasn't happened yet because the game's already out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe the same type of thing is happening where they're going to release Final Fantasy XIV on the 360 here in America and only here and maybe Europe too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe they don't want to hold up the debut of the game to make the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're going to do a worldwide launch this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: XI took like a year to get localized over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe Final Fantasy XIV they're going to throw it out there all at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Japan, US, and Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody gets it at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there'll be a 360 version someday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't it be hilarious if it became a 360 exclusive?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, no way.
[SPEAKER_04]: No way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be hilarious, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just considering how, you know, Final Fantasy XI was really created as a PS2 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: it was really made for the Playstation 2 I know a lot of us here in the states played it on the PC but part of the reason that game was so limited and finally outgrew itself and couldn't expand the way that WoW has continued to expand is because it's limited to the PS2 and that's why Final Fantasy 11 is kind of they're not going to really support that as much anymore I'm sure it will always be alive there will always be people playing Final Fantasy 11 but it's going to downsize big time when 14 comes out
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens
[SPEAKER_04]: is going to be announced at the Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's in a story that was run by the website VideoGamer.com from an industry source.
[SPEAKER_04]: An employee at a major international publisher, obviously anonymous as you can imagine, quote, just heard a rumor that you may be interested in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo are going to announce a new platform at GDC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some devs have already started work on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we don't know if that could be a redone handheld.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think we've already heard rumblings of a DS2, even though there's the XL still has yet to come out here in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've heard rumblings of a DS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some fanboys are hoping it's finally the Wii HD already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows what it could be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Could it maybe be an enhancement to the existing Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't want to joke the Vitality Sensor, but something in that vein?
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably nothing like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if they would do another Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, because it's selling like hotcakes right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: What would be the point?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, trying to put some now I'd see maybe another handheld system because maybe that's starting to slow down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I doubt they would be doing a Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to build one that you implant into your brain so you can just play until you have seizures.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unless they're trying to stay ahead, they're worried that maybe once these other motion controllers come out for Microsoft and PlayStation 3 and Sony, that you're going to have an even playing field and then they're going to just fail based on the quality of their product because now you're going to have these really pretty looking games that control just like they do on the Wii
[SPEAKER_11]: and people are going to be more apt to maybe buying those, which I don't think that's true, but maybe they're just trying to stay one step ahead.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either way, I'm not too excited about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: In our chat room at chat.org.com, MaginamiCon, I hope I said that right, says, what, a phone?
[SPEAKER_04]: The end phone?
[SPEAKER_04]: Could that happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: I somehow doubt that, but that would be an interesting idea, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting too, I kind of want to say, if this is true, I don't think it's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think some things might happen behind closed doors at Game Developers Conference, but I don't think you're going to see the major announcement until E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Developers Conference is not a media show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't strike me as the place to announce a new platform.
[SPEAKER_04]: The place to announce maybe a revision, I could see like a DSi XL or something there, even though it's already out in Japan, but you know what I mean, like a slightly altered version.
[SPEAKER_04]: An enhancement or a new tool
[SPEAKER_04]: I could see more Natal information coming out of GDC and some of the things that enhance gaming, but I don't see a full-on new platform being announced at Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a media show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for game developers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in the title.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know people think it's a media show and it's turning into one, but it's not supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really, really not.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think a lot of people resent that it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think if Nintendo is going to make an announcement, which I think it is the DS, I think the DS is going to get the revamp, you're going to see it at E3, not a Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, I know it is weird that I'm talking the DS revamp when we don't even have the XL here in the West, but I think Nintendo kind of knows that they could still put out the XL in limited quantities and it would sell if it was cheaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: it would still sell to the 7 and 8 year olds and the mothers that like to play Pokemon and whatever, the soccer moms and whatever new DS system that will be $50 more expensive maybe even $100 more expensive will cater to the hardcore gamer who wants their Mario and Zelda games ASAP, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, does that seem far-fetched to you guys?
[SPEAKER_08]: no
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's see I'm sorry I can't be too contrary about that And some other comments in chat here Talking about MotionPlus, there's a couple people bringing up MotionPlus Like, was MotionPlus a flop?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, that's a good question Was MotionPlus a flop?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think, Loki, from your perspective in sales?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just that people, as far as rental stores and stuff go They don't want to bring in games that have MotionPlus Because they're afraid that people don't have it
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of like the whole Guitar Hero thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: People don't want to bring it in because they're afraid that, you know, oh, it requires this.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not something that most people have.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it a flop?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if people are really all excited that, oh, God, this game has MotionPlus now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be better.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really think it means anything yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, there's only been a few games that have actually used it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure they're pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just it's not, like, game-changing or anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting comment from Blue Swim in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting creative idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Wii with groundbreaking DVD support.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think anyone's going to care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Most people are moving on to Blu-ray and stuff, and everything's a DVD player nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think that's a creative outside-the-box answer for the topic at hand, but I just lean towards no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Loki's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's a DVD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: DVD players are like $40, probably less than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't need a DVD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a creative answer, but maybe a Wii revision with something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, it's going to go the way of MotionPlus.
[SPEAKER_04]: The biggest problem with MotionPlus, it wasn't included with the console to begin with, so people are afraid not everyone has it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very hard to launch a peripheral.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what Natal's uphill battle is going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you read these articles and these rumors about the 360 is going to relaunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a new console per se, but they have to treat Natal like a relaunch of the damn system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't understand why they need to add on.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only thing I can think of is better graphics maybe soup up the actual processor inside there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because if they're hitting the limits of what they can do on that system, maybe that would help.
[SPEAKER_11]: But say the DSi for the Wii or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm afraid that whatever they do decide to put out is just going to be very gimmicky and stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just gives them an excuse to put out another Mario game, another Metroid game, another Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And look, oh look, it's new, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to get into the classic game of the week here in just a moment and wrap up part A of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do want to say hello to all the folks who are tuning in live tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the Super Bowl is over.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so now we have some folks kind of coming back to us now that the football game is over.
[SPEAKER_04]: So welcome, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glad you could tune in tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to recap quickly the things we have talked about tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to the podcast listeners and the folks that listen to us at the top of the show, but I want everyone to know what we've already covered.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic the 4 Episode 1 was already announced this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Project Needlemouse's other name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blaster Master Overdrive has surprised us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be out on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox and Microsoft is ditching live support for the original Xbox, so Halo 2 fans are pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the rest of us will gain a friends list with more than 100 friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook is getting a new first-person shooter game called Brave Arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook is a gaming platform, you betcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard has been announcing, teasing the idea of a premium auction house application for World of Warcraft so you can manage your auctions offline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akira Yamaoka has found a new home.
[SPEAKER_04]: He left Konami a couple months ago and now he's at Grasshopper working with the folks that did No More Heroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We covered release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIV, a developer's LinkedIn profile has clued us into the fact that it could be under development for the 360, but we seem to come to a consensus that if it is under development for the 360, it probably won't come out at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we just wrapped up talking about a story where Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Ew, it's sticky!
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's a video game that you all should be playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take a listen to Qbert and the awesome 1982 arcade noises.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, nope, he won.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he even got bonuses for the two discs on the side.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the little sound that the disc makes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's him cussing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, so Q-Bert was originally supposed to be a game about Q-Bert's big nose that could shoot projectiles.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he would hop all over a pyramid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was actually made by Warren Davis.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the high scoreboard, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi there!
[SPEAKER_09]: In big letters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome to the Noser Elite!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, so yeah, it is basically sort of puzzle and hopping around and, you know, the game actually gets really hard because, you know, your first few levels you only change it once and you've got enemies all over the board.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, then you move on to it changing to two colors.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to change the entire board.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it happens that you change to one color, and if you hop back on it, it changes back.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so you have to get them all to match the final new color, and there's ones that change three times if you hop on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's where the game just gets, like, disgustingly annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was really good at this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I had the Clico version, Clico Vision version for a long time, which I still have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had the Commodore 64 version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, but your, uh, little, uh, enemies are called Quailie, who's the purple snake, and Ugg and Wrongway, these little purple snotty creatures, and Slick and Sam that are the green boogers.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: You can ride the little discs up to the top of the pyramid.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you jump on the pyramid right, not on the pyramid, but on the disc right when one of the enemies are chasing you, or I should say Coily is chasing you, they'll hop off the edge behind you and die.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that great, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That used to be how you'd have to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'd have to lure them towards a disc and then jump up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like what you were talking about last week during the Classic Game of the Week, which was linked to the past.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you'd have in those dungeons, the guards would charge at you and if you were standing towards the edge, then you'd just run real fast and they'd charge right off the edge into oblivion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, um, the other thing about this, too, though, is that it was, um, produced by Gottlieb, who does a lot of, who did, I should say, a lot of, uh, pinball tables, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it also, um, the, the guy who developed it, uh, Warren Ellis, uh, Warren Davis, sorry, um, was, uh, the guy who was behind, um, Revolution X, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: and Terminator 2 and Lotto Fun, Joust 2 and Us vs. Them, which is a Laserdisc game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, he's been in... He was also on an episode of HouseMD.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, he's, you know, been around, you know, in the industry for a while and brought out some pretty big classics.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: It really is just a very simple little game, but it gets really hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as... There were other games that came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: For Q-Bert itself, it came out on the Odyssey 2, which I have that system as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Texas Instruments TI-99.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Commodore VIC-20.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Atari systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: The Atari 5200 version is ass, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Qbert was on everything from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was also a sequel, an actual sequel called Qbert's Cubes, which... Is not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then there was Qbert 3 that came out on the NES, but it was very much like the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there was a Qbert pinball, of course, Gottlieb put out, called Qbert's Quest.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a tabletop electronic game version.
[SPEAKER_09]: All kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also a version that was put out by Davis that was called Faster, Harder, More Challenging Qbert and it's actually now out.
[SPEAKER_09]: While he didn't put it into production, it's out for MAME.
[SPEAKER_09]: He released the ROM image.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wow, cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, there's the updated Qbert that was on... Crap, now I can't remember which of the... But it was a 3D Qbert, like a Qbert remix or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there was one on PlayStation, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there was one on PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was the 3D version of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I liked Qbert and all, and I would like to see this come out on the game room that Microsoft is doing, but I don't know if it will, because who owns the rights to the Gottlieb games now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't a board game company own them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't Hasbro own them or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something really weird?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: on the Commodore 64 version there was a mode where you could tilt your joystick 45 degrees so that way you used up, down, left, and right to control and then up went like actually to the upright and you know it made it a lot easier to control on the Commodore 64 trust me because trying to hit diagonal directions can you imagine trying to hit diagonal directions on the Xbox 360 D-pad no thank you hopefully if it does come out in game room you can use buttons for precision hopefully
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you know what else I remember, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Q-Bert cartoon when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had the Q-Bert board game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a board game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, somewhere I may not still have it, but I had a Q-Bert plushie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: With his big nose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well that's going to bring us to a close of Part A of Orange Lounge Radio, but we are not done yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still have Part B coming up after the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about a new console from Sega, but it's not what you think.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about a sequel to the Fallout series And some interesting developments over at Harmonix That's all coming up in Part B So those of you listening live, stay tuned We'll be back in a few minutes with more of Orange Lounge Radio Podcast listeners, you only have to wait a few seconds So we'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, everybody, to more of Orange Lounge Radio on this part B of our podcast, episode number 354 for this February the 7th of 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Super Bowl Sunday here in the States.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really watch the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really into football.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know a lot of people watch it, so I know it was keeping people away from the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now that it's over, you have no excuse.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hopefully, if you're listening live, you are here in our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, if you're listening to us on the podcast feed, you should try and make it for a live show sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be here next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next Sunday is Valentine's Day, which is also probably going to keep several people away.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the three of us have arranged plans with our significant others, so we will still be able to be here for the Valentine's Day show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, or as some folks like to call it, Singles Awareness Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're single, come join the OLR family.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll make you feel right at home here and talk about games or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep your mind off of what Hallmark wants you to think about all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, let's get back into some gaming news, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's do some quick, quick news stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, there will be a Heavy Rain demo coming out on PlayStation 3 soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not scheduled to come out until February 11th, but if you can't wait that long, you can actually download it now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the way you do this is participate in their alternate reality game.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Precinct52.com and then you can just look for the four pieces of evidence which are the short cigarette marked 11117B the origami bird
[SPEAKER_11]: Coffee Shop C, which you'll actually click on the one that says Diner on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then the Tire Tracks, it's 117H.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you click on the Tire Tracks, it actually expands it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Same with the cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_11]: You click on the picture of the cigarette and there'll be two different choices and choose 117B.
[SPEAKER_11]: Once you've done all that, you'll receive a code to download the demo immediately, which is better than waiting until the 11th.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Coming to the PlayStation Network, Fret Nice, which was a game... It's kind of a side-scroll platformer game that was actually a Flash game at one time that you played entirely with the Guitar Hero Rock Band controller.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, for whatever reason, they decided to go with this really...
[SPEAKER_11]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, PlayStation 3 this week, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then finally, Rock Band is getting some new download content, including... Well, tonight, actually, was the Who Super Bowl smash-up medley.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that was available for $2, or $2 in whatever respective points you're spending.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also this week will be another album as well, including Holy Wars, The Punishment Due, which is for also $2, Hanger 18, Take No Prisoners, Five Magics, Poison Was The Cure, Lucretia, Tornado Of Souls, Dawn Patrol, and Rest In Peace Polaris.
[SPEAKER_11]: All those are available for $2 as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's, of course, off the Megadeth Hangar 18, I believe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or, no, Rust in Peace, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, I've got some more news for you guys for some other types of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not music-based, but definitely a popular game folks are looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mod Nation Racers.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you know, this game is coming out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have a time frame when that game's coming out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that summer?
[SPEAKER_11]: It got delayed again, so June as of right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently, not only is there going to be a PlayStation 3 version, there's going to be a PSP version launching.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I've never heard this news before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally new news.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, just so you know, this game does have all the same tools that you'll find in the PS3 version, but of course the graphics are going to be scaled down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you still do get to make your own cars, your own racers, your own tracks, and you get to share them with the PSP Mod Nation community.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to go online with it and race and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: PS3 and PSP versions launching side by side very similar to LittleBigPlanet of course also has the PS3 and PSP versions but there was about a year break between the two don't expect to see that same large window between these two releases again totally new news to me I hadn't heard this anywhere before hey Civ Network is a popular anticipated Facebook game at least at my house I'm really excited to play Civilization Network but not going to get a chance to tell June
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's when the Civilization Network beta is apparently happening, is June.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Variety, of all places, is the one that made this report.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Variety, the magazine usually talks about movies and TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they have to talk about games, too, when there's big stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The beta for the new Facebook game, according to Variety, not starting until June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, by the way, this game was initially announced back in October, and that they were going to do a beta tester hunt soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So soon means nine months.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, it's like saying, you know, I'm going to have a baby soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other thing I got for you guys this week A game lots and lots of people are talking about Mass Effect 2 is obviously a hugely popular title this week And with good reason from what I understand I haven't played it myself But I hear it's pretty fucking epic One thing though that is not epic is the size of the text And if you're playing on a standard television You probably can't read it It's got the tiny text problem You know, you've heard about this in other games before It's not just Mass Effect 2 that's had this problem I want to say Lost Planet had this Some other games too
[SPEAKER_04]: and usually companies patch this problem so that you can actually read these on an SDTV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: According to the project manager, Michael Gamble, let's see, quote, we understand that on some SDTVs, the smallest text in Mass Effect 2 can be difficult to read.
[SPEAKER_04]: While this was not an intentional result, it was a byproduct of the enhancements to the user interface.
[SPEAKER_04]: After investigating potential solutions, we have determined that while this issue does affect a small portion of SDTV owners,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if you don't have a big team, you should just get one anyway, regardless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the PSP Go is apparently getting a relaunch, even though the PSP Go is kind of crap anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Game Revision is saying that they're definitely going to have a relaunch and that there's going to be a price drop.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe that'll work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: I still think it's crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, for our DDR fans, DDR Universe 3, Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3 is on Xbox 360 games on demand.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, get your $30 ready if you want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or save your money, because it was my least favorite of the Xbox 360 games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now, this is the thing that I actually bought a thousand cryptic points for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that you can play a Ferengi or a Federation Klingon in Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, it's like, you have to pay so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, get this.
[SPEAKER_09]: You pay 240 cryptic points for a Klingon, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: You play 80 for a Ferengi.
80. 80.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I suppose WoW charges you for certain types of faction changes and so forth, but I can't think of anything that's locked out without having to spend more money, except, I suppose, actual expansion packs themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the one thing that I want them to do is to make some of the pre-order special stuff available for other people.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, for some reason, my Liberated Borg isn't showing up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't tried looking in the thing again, but I haven't been able to make a Liberated Borg for my bridge crew.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I need to find out where that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I mean, I'm just saying that, you know, and the other thing too is that I bought more points so I could buy a third character slot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you only allowed two character slots?
[SPEAKER_09]: Two character slots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there multiple servers or is it just one giant server?
[SPEAKER_09]: One big giant server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wow, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the big thing is they were having, if you buy a lifetime membership, then you can have, you start off with four slots.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you have the year one, you get like one more extra slot, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't, I don't have the money for a lifetime, although I'd pay for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question from our chat room from Amaze Satsuma, chat.orangeloungeradio.com Do the female Ferengi wear clothes?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, they do, and there's an explanation for that, because keep in mind, all of our DS9 buddies out there, Ram's the Grand Nagus, and he brought in social reform.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week we invite you guys to send us your tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show us your tweets at username OLR and submit your topics for possible consideration to be read on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a few of them tonight, so I don't think we're going to read all of these, but I'll read a few of these.
[SPEAKER_04]: From PodCulture, Twitter topic, collector's editions of video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay or nay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I say yay depending on what you're into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the extras can be cool sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets a little weird though when there's like really game changing items that are only available in the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not cool to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean if it's a game I really like, sure I'm going to get the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if there's a Final Fantasy XIII collector's edition, I'm probably buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, Collector's Editions, yay, nay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It all depends what's in it and how much it's for.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even have to ask Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's thumbing through her Star Trek Collector's Edition right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came with an art book.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And a pen.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I get all kinds of cool stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If there's something that I really, really like, and you know me and I love stuff, I will get the Collector's Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: going through some other tweets here Alex Carson interesting question I don't know if we're going to have much of an answer to this on Twitter what podcast do you guys like to tune into please tell me one of you guys likes Dignation here's the thing and I don't know if Loki and Jamie feel similarly but I don't listen to a lot of other podcasts because I don't want to be inadvertently influenced by what I hear on other shows like I'm all for you guys how John Tesh of you
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm all for you guys listening to independent shows, and I think you should support other independent radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't want to hear something on one show and then inadvertently, without knowing, copy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do support folks listening to other shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are a few.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've listened to more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I drive to the Bay Area more often now because I date somebody that lives in the Bay Area, and it's about a two-hour drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have used podcasts to fill the gap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me check with DarkSakura and Loki, though, first before I answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have a couple podcasts I like.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Loki, anything?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was listening to the GrammarCast for a while and there are a couple more like a few classic gaming ones that I was you know listening to but for the most part I actually don't really have time you know I should set them up to download on my iPhone but I hardly ever forget to update my iPhone anyway
[SPEAKER_11]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really listen to their podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't at your work either because you're on the phone and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I know a lot of people listen to this at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm on the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Past the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's not... I just don't because...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, I just don't.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I probably have time during the day, but I just don't want to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that I don't think there's good stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't listen to the radio either.
[SPEAKER_11]: I listen to my CD player, or I guess MP3 player right now, that has like 10 songs on it, and I loop them, and I just don't care about adding new stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So same thing with podcasts, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, you know, I read the news.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's no, you know, for me, I'd probably listen to the game podcast and, you know, and I read news and stuff, so I don't really need to hear the news again.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's just... Wait a minute, you just told people to basically not listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, so be it, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just telling you why I don't listen to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like to talk about all the news too, not just, I mean, we try to report, like, usually we're not the ones breaking the news, but we talk about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there's absolutely no news breaking here other than, oh my god, you know, Mod Nation Racers on PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: as far as video game podcasts go um i i don't know how far i want to say this like i have tried listening to a corporate oriented podcast um it was a very niche thing uh and i kind of find my found myself a little bit bored listening to it it was kind of a niche gaming podcast i kind of thought the hosts didn't have energy like they they didn't sound excited about what they were talking about it's kind of like
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello and welcome to our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to talk about this topic today.
[SPEAKER_02]: As hosted by Bob Ross?
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I shouldn't say negative things, but a lot of corp podcasts, like, dude, you're even paid to be there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be excited.
[SPEAKER_11]: That and the corporate podcasts, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just like, hey, look at all these games that the game publishers just dumped on our desk with gold and money.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look at all this shit I get to play for free.
[SPEAKER_11]: They literally shove money into my pockets.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just like, oh, I hate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of them are such douches.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I'm not going to linger on the negative.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me move to the positive because there are some indie podcasts I've listened to that I like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, I like Bobby's show, but clearly I'm biased.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Friday Night Gaming, I think, is a great show too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually listen to, and I really like the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've listened to it like three times now on my drives to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the Warcraft Outsiders.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the spinoff of Video Game Outsiders, which is a show kind of similar to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a girl and two guys who kind of drink and talk about the video game news, except they all do it on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think one of them is in Canada, and I think the others are on the East Coast somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they do a spinoff show about Warcraft, and I think it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: The girl leads it, and she's like a hardcore raider healer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think her and her boyfriend play a lot, and I think they're pretty well informed of what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has energy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They enjoy what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although one guy on the show, kind of the running gag is that he doesn't really play Warcraft, so why is he there?
[SPEAKER_04]: But they make it funny, so it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they have energy.
[SPEAKER_04]: When she talks about her rating and stuff, you can tell she is having fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she's doing a show about something she really likes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the guy, too, and the guest host.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that want my opinion on what makes a good podcast...
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun on what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make people want to listen to you because you are excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: I try to have energy on this show every week, even if I'm having a shit week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And don't forget, we've also got the comic podcast too that Mar and Marvel and I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we giggle!
[SPEAKER_09]: And are excited!
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me move on to other comments on our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator says, latest rumor, Patrick Stewart is said to be a huge fan of handheld gaming, specifically on the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, did I really just read that joke?
[SPEAKER_04]: See, let it not be said that we do not let every gamer have a voice, even when we should probably throw tomatoes at them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Waka waka waka!
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, the bad joke of the week wouldn't be a good, or wouldn't be a bad idea, you know, that would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get the OLR tomato award of the night, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's one more Twitter question for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blue Swim asks us, any word on President Cat coming here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I can have Mischief Makers as classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as President Cat goes, we didn't hear anything after the whole little gauntlet of stuff that happened that week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was the negative stories about that it only sold 100 copies, which I still say were bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fail to see how that was possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe 100 copies were imported to the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no way it sold 100 copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, even the crappiest of absolute shit that comes out on the Wii sells a lot of copies.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why they release stuff on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's because people are like, hey, it's a game, it's cheap, let me buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it could be...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it could be a game about working at a call center or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the Twitter account Renowe has still been kind of making posts as of late, so they're still kind of, you know, there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think at this point I'm not holding my breath to see it released over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, don't give up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Continue to follow it and send them tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think the best case scenario at this point is that someone kind of caught wind of this whole thing going on and maybe we'll see a game like President Cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But remember, there's a certain charm that President Cat had, and when you make a copy of a copy, the quality declines.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just be very thoughtful in how you do that if you are said publisher listening right now thinking about cashing in on the President Cat craze.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, again, it would sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get back into some long-form gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll read more of your tweets next week at twitter.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mailbag's coming up, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know DarkSakura's going to tear into that in just a moment, but we do have some news before we get there, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: You may remember that there was awell, there's been a few knockoff Wii systems out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of them was Zone 40, which was just some, like
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks sort of like a Wii, but not quite, you know, and it had, you know, 40 little mini-games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well now, they have the officially licensed Sega Zone, which has 20 Genesis Classic games and 30 new games, 16 of which are playable with the devices, two wireless motion controllers, and, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and it's in wonderful black and blue with the Sega logo on the side.
[SPEAKER_11]: Trying to see what games are in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of hard to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me guess, Sonic the Hedgehog?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Sonic the Hedgehog, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that's, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, obvious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, looks like Alex Kidd, Sonic & Knuckles, uh, Columns 3, E-SWAT, Echo the Dolphin, Golden Axe.
[SPEAKER_04]: The same shit that's in every Sega compilation, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then, like, some of the other, uh, like, arcade games that they have, uh...
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a lot of this is just some generic stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like they have what looks like a boxing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Looks like Wii Boxing or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can actually see the little picture here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a blown up version of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: E-SWAT, Sonic Spinball, Golden Axe, Shinobi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then in the Sega games section, they have Cannon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, that's the 14 arcade games section right below that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Balls is one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomber, Cannon...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some bottle caps race or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like they basically just copied over some of the crappy games that were on there and put some Sega Genesis games on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then some interactive sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Wii Sports, but with 16 different games, including darts, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that curling?
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would all depend on what the price is.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it says, I guess it's priced at 39.95 euros, I believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's cute, but I think I'll pass on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I don't know how I feel about these games, but Wheel of Fortune and Jeopardy, you know these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually, I believe they're like Sony Pictures Entertainment game shows, but THQ has actually licensed the franchises to make video games based on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not like it would be the first time ever a video game has been made out of Wheel of Fortune or Jeopardy.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it would be awesome if they were, I don't know, one of the Xbox, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where I was going to go with this is that wouldn't that be cool if they actually, I mean, to make these games more fun, did the whole like 1 versus 100 route and made them like a little more interactive like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, 1 versus 100 is awesome and everything, but it's starting to get old.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, I thought there was supposed to be more than just one game on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And honestly, I've never played 1 vs. 100 on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fun-ish.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dan likes it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was number one one night on Video Game Trivia halfway through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I had a 26-question streak.
[SPEAKER_04]: And at one of the breaks, I was number one on the leaderboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I took a picture and posted it on Twitter and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I talked about it a few weeks ago on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But sadly, yeah, I finally failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the question I failed on was... Oh, I remember it was the ESRB rating.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the ESRB rating for Worms 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I got it wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: but anyway it's fun playing the Xbox Live one can be fun but yeah I get what you're saying though it does get old a lot of these game show things get old but if there was that variety I think it could be pretty cool especially like Jeopardy, Wheel of Fortune I think these could be cool games to do live you know with the whole like I don't think everybody would just watch three players but maybe if everybody got you know how like 1 vs 100 splits you up into parties of four
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe if these games did that, split you up into random parties of three, and you played a predetermined puzzle or predetermined set of questions, and then you can see maybe at the end who out of all the matches was like the top, who got the big, big score.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's ways you could do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it'd make it fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But sadly, I don't think THQ is going to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're actually going to be releasing them specifically on the Wii and the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in other words, get ready to spin the wheel with your Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're going to be as bad as successful as The Price is Right and the other games that came out, which were not very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I heard Press Your Luck and Price is Right weren't that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, later this year is when those first games are coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The statement, by the way, about these games came from the THQ Kids, Family, and Casual Games executive VP.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no hardcore Wheel of Fortune for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish they would go the live game show route though on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope we do get some more of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't it be cool to actually have a live Press Your Luck?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love that!
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a live... Old school.
[SPEAKER_04]: A live Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, imagine you could be in the audience with your little avatar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Higher, higher, lower.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have your little Plinko party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plinko party.
[SPEAKER_09]: there's so much more that can be done and I hope it is done well how about something that's good news for a lot of people there's Fallout New Vegas will be out summer 2010 there's actually a trailer up and everything it's being developed by Obsidian Entertainment the same people that gave us Knights of the Old Republic 2 Neverwinter Knights 2 and this is going to be a direct follow up to Fallout 3
[SPEAKER_11]: It looked kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just know a lot of people like Fallout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, Fallout's a hugely popular game, especially number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those games I have yet to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in my little rental queue, but I haven't gotten the game yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I hear it's Oblivion with guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: But so much came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have time to play every single video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll try to get around to it, at least before Final Fantasy XIII comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because when that comes out, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm worried about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really going to be playing anything else for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: So sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: All these games.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: You may remember back we talked a little bit about how Walmart and Best Buy were kind of getting into this kiosk trade-in type of business.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were going to be able to buy, sell, trade games, also rent out games, and I believe DVDs as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Problem is, though, the company behind it, Eplay, has ceased operations.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I don't know if that means closing or out of business or whatever, but they're no longer operating, if you will.
[SPEAKER_11]: So unfortunately, that will probably go away.
[SPEAKER_11]: which is too bad because I hear that their trading values are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not true though if you're doing that in Canada because I believe actually in Canada Best Buy actually handles their trade-ins in the store and not through a kiosk so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, GameCrazy, apparently the parent company, Movie Gallery, has filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy again.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're only basically going to drop it down to only 250 GameCrazy locations once they're done.
[SPEAKER_11]: And be liquidating close to 760 stores.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can vouch for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of depressing news in the retail world.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's something that hits home here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sure, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know yet if everything's going to be okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're thinking that the Cameron Park store is going to be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, good luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope everything turns out all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I like living in a house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, on to happier news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the comments in chat still talking about the whole ideas of game shows on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think SSJ100Matt totally has the winner idea of what game should be on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, yes, the match game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If only they could find a way to bring back Brett Summers and Charles Nelson Reilly from the dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a sad face news.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I'm big on LiveJournal, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my good friends that I've had on LiveJournal for years now ran a community on LiveJournal called Match Game LJ, which, you know, kind of did like a little LiveJournal version of the match game every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: He decided to close it down this week, and he's not going to be running it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me sad face.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what up, Mark, if you're listening, although I doubt he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yes, Match Game should be on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, on to some other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is definitely kind of an eyebrow-raising piece here from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix has apparently done some more licensing, and this really isn't a big surprise when you consider, oh yeah, duh, Harmonix makes music games, and you know, they license stuff for Rock Band 2 all of the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But look at some of the things they've been licensing lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all from the Royalty Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess some people were watching there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anteup by M.O.P., Say Ah by Trey Songs, Evacuate the Dance Floor by Cascada, The Way I Are by Timbaland featuring D.O.E.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are all like dancey poppy songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't belong in rock band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what is going on at Camp Harmonix?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Heroish Game in the Works DDR
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I've got to admit, you know what I'm tempted to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: My gut tells me it's a dance game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That they're going to try to take the dance game crown from Konami and now's a pretty good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, this is a topic that hits home here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show started over DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: The dance genre is really that popular anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I guess you've seen a couple titles that are really kind of stand out now, but they're a little bit different than DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just Dance is a title that I'm surprised is doing okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I have some co-workers, and I always talk about co-workers because that's my way to gauge the casual gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: some of my co-workers that I would not imagine played a lot of Nintendo Wii love Just Dance and think it's like great and I've heard some people on the show talking highly about it too some of our chatters and stuff apparently it's this big cult music game that's doing very well culty type I gotta play it at some point but anyway sorry what was the rest of your thought there no I'm just surprised that you know that's doing well so I'm not sure if they would be going like that route though
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee in our chatroom says, Konami doesn't have the crown, Stepmania does.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to say this and rip it off like a band-aid here and just kind of give you my thought here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stepmania is not legitimate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that probably sucks to hear, and I know it's got a big community and everything, but it's not legitimate.
[SPEAKER_04]: neither is in the groove do you well in the groove is a step above step mania in the groove was the way to try and legitimize step mania but let me put it this way you do not walk into a GameStop and buy step mania over the counter or do you really buy step mania at all I mean it's just not it's not the same step mania was always there to emulate DDR and then yeah they tried to kind of innovate it later especially within the groove and so forth but it's not I mean I could see Harmonix doing what Konami should have done
[SPEAKER_04]: about six years ago and reinventing DDR from the ground up, which supposedly is also happening by Konami right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't heard what's up with that DDR game they're supposed to be putting out with eight panels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't that supposed to be out last Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: It got delayed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was supposed to be actually out this spring, and it still hasn't been released yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think probably the second quarter.
[SPEAKER_11]: But even still, it's just, I can't get excited about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch, I go to DDRFreak.com and let's see, do I see anything about the new DDR game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, DDR Freak, Pump It Up Pro 2, Step Mania the Manga, DJ Hero Deal, Cobalt Flux, back in November, $40 Amazon credit with various hero bundles, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no news on DDR and even DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that is a sign about how Konami has fumbled and dropped the DDR crown.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if Harmonix were to show up at E3 with a new dance game with... I hate to say it, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I'm going to piss some of you off with this comment, but without the J-pop and the stuff that most people on this side of the ocean don't know, but stuff like Timberland and Cascada and people actually recognize from clubs, Harmonix is going to... They're going to do to DDR what they did to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Guitar Freaks, sorry, with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be what we're looking at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll just have to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it could be that Rock Band 3, I mean, again, this is all speculation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why my gut just tells me Konami's vulnerable right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: If DDR Freak can't even tell you the latest on what's going on with 8-panel DDR and this whole reinvention of the franchise, I mean, hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something is wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we technically do have 8-panel DDR, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doubles.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, just like quad mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did that ever catch on?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya is saying, So, Rob, are you saying DDR is dead?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well... Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of died about five years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Around the time this show stopped talking about DDR was kind of when it was starting to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to say it, but I don't think it'll ever die, but it's not what it was ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's face it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reality check.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, hey, let's get into some more pleasant topics and talk a little bit about what is going on in our email bag.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, every week we invite you guys to send us emails to our email address at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and every week DarkSakura likes to tear the mail bag open and read some of her favorite emails for us to respond to here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DarkSakura, dive into the mailbag and tell us what emails are we getting this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we got one recent.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was one of the ones that were deleted when I was getting rid of the spam.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'll go ahead and read it first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, OLR crew, AZHP here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was listening to your podcast from the 10th and heard Jamie brush off the Rockstar forced overtime deal because they would get time and a half.
[SPEAKER_09]: I work in the programming industry as well and I can tell you with 100% certainty that pretty much no one in the entire industry in California gets paid a cent of overtime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Furthermore, and this is generally the norm for the games industry in general, employees are forced to work 12 hours, 6-7 days a week, with no overtime pay, no compensation for PTO, no bonuses, and sometimes even no vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, PTO is paid time off for those who don't speak office speak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes even no vacation after a project is finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are also generally threats of dismissal if one does not go into work.
[SPEAKER_09]: These people are so fatigued getting one or zero days off that week, they make more and more mistakes, and they have to stay even longer to fix them.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is a law in California that says you can be exempt from getting paid overtime if you make more than $90,000 in a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, game developers generally make about half that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might seem like a decent salary, but when you're working 100 hour work weeks, it equates to about $14 an hour.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you might say, take it up with the law or quit.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, these people are so overworked that they don't have the time to file a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_09]: And getting into the industry is so hard because there are so few studios owned by even fewer publishers that it's 100 times harder to get a job in the games industry than it is any other job, especially in our economic climate.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry for the lengthy rant, but I was appalled at the complacency of the crew on reporting on this story.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted everyone to know the true nature of the beast so that they could understand what most game developers go through to bring you the games you love to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yours truly, AZHPPS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry about the terrible Silent Hill joke last time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just had to.
[SPEAKER_09]: My point is that it's because no one says anything that this shit continues.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of I sort of agree like I don't I don't want to say I'm complacent with this I mean it does strike me as very wrong but at the same time I feel like I don't know enough about that perspective because most of the people I know that work for developers aren't making these same complaints and I don't know if it's because of and it's addressing that email the fear of if they speak up they're going to get fired but if everything that's in that email is true that's bullshit
[SPEAKER_04]: of course it's bullshit and maybe the wives should be speaking up and somebody has got to stand up for these people and put a stop to this by the way though you don't have to make $90,000 a year to be exempt from overtime trust me I know
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no, if you are an exempt employee, then your overtime is counted in other ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are still boundaries.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like to talk a lot about my day job because I don't want to ever jeopardize that here on the show, but I will say these few key things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am an exempt employee where I work, but anytime I do have to work those extra hours, my company is very good about balancing it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get basically comped time, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: In a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I should reveal those types of things on the show, but there are ways they make up for it, and I don't feel overworked.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everybody should have that privilege.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've had times at my job where they say, oh, we've got mandatory overtime this weekend, and I'm like, I'm not coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have other things to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I made plans.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I'm not coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they'll be like, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they cannot make you work mandatory overtime.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just say mandatory because they're strongly suggesting it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they need to have the people there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And maybe it's mandatory for them to request the overtime.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's not mandatory that you take it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That you, you know, go in and work on your day off.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a law for a reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if, I'm sorry, I really don't feel very sorry for these people who...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, no, I don't feel sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, yeah, it sucks that they're having such a hard time.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as long as they're not doing anything to change it, you know, then they're just adding to the problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're adding to the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe that's why the wives are speaking up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe people, I mean, I can see what he's saying in the email there about there is a very real fear that if I speak up, I'm going to be fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's illegal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tough industry to crack into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it still doesn't change the fact of what the law is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get too political here, but is it... Just throwing ideas out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it possible that there could be a union of developers and people that work in the game industry?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, maybe that's what's needed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if it seems like... Do we need Sally Field to jump up on a table with her sign about starting a union?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that if anyone is working in that kind of condition, it doesn't matter how exhausted they are.
[SPEAKER_09]: If someone does not think enough of themselves, their family, and doing work that they enjoy to try to make their workplace a better place to be, then they don't need to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of our listeners in chat, I'll withhold their name here because they are saying something somewhat negative, says, it's hard to say no, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once it's okay, twice you don't get a raise and all the industry is connected.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's speaking to that same fear.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I get what you're saying, but I get what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got something has to give.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that goes back to the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you are unhappy with the environment, you change it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, one person may be one person, but for every one person that has a particular distaste for something, there are going to be at least eight other people around them, very close to them that have that same feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: and sometimes all it takes is for one person to say something before everybody else decides hey yeah we agree well this issue is long from over I'm sure about that maybe it's going to end up being the wives that take this on I don't know it's going to be very interesting to see what develops but for now we should probably move on to another email
[SPEAKER_09]: One comes from Lucky Nuts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Jamie keeps talking about her vault.
[SPEAKER_09]: I, too, have a vault that I've kept for the last 20 years or so, and I'm considering spending the next few months clearing it out on eBay to buy more grown-up things, like a new sailboat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you ever thought about clearing out your collection, and if so, did you later regret it?
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, grown-up is a concept.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, you're getting rid of one thing for recreation to get another thing for recreation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Grown up is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So drop that little attitude right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate that attitude so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: And no, I'm not getting rid of the collection ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love our collection.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go back and use all the stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm happy just looking at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like going in the vault and just looking around and going, damn, we got some cool shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at all this shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how I feel.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then she'll invite other people over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, Rob, come over and look at all my shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come over here and help me play with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: And by the way, if you go to our YouTube channel, you can actually see some video taken in the vault if you want to see what I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you are going to sell some of your stuff, though, talk to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'll have something I want.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just would say from a non-collector perspective, I've sold some of my stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never really regretted it though because I try to really think about it and not sell anything that I think I might remotely play again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I think I sold my copy of Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just knew I wasn't going to play that again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Misty said she was happy looking at it while she was visiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, I did get two emails from one other person, but I'm only going to read one of them because really the first one was all like, I like Silent Hill Shattered Memories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I say, though, real quick, though, if you did sell your collection and buy the sailboat, you know that you could say, I'm on a boat.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that's one of my ringtones on my phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the one when work calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you buy the sailboat.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to say, I'm on a boat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to be on a boat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to play my games.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: because then you don't have to do all the crap to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I'm smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should just be a financial advisor even though I kind of suck at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't buy a goddamn boat, idiot.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't need a boat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck boats.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rent it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Charter a boat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you need a financial advice podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck no.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be nothing but Dan yelling at me for spending too much money on comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck rent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy comics.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, my grammar has greatly improved, except you're not using any capital letters and you misspelled grammar.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was wondering if you guys have ever played the MMO Mabinogi.
[SPEAKER_09]: If so, why have you guys never mentioned it because we haven't?
[SPEAKER_04]: Never heard of it, ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not try it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's a lot like World of Warcraft except for Mabinogi is PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is the PS3 of the two you pay for nothing except pet and extra characters unless you are smart enough?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this spam?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's... Alright, just checking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really can't read this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know how easy it would be to... Okay, I'll come stand behind you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also on another note, the gift Rob got from Loki, where would I find when you can play an NES game on it?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an FC Mobile, look it up online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I make AMVs from video games and I was wondering, can you guys have any ideas for an AMV?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, there should be an AMV where the main character is learning proper spelling and grammar.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be fascinating.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, update the podcast more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, dude, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, spammers need to be raped with a flea warhead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that I can get behind.
[SPEAKER_04]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't read your email because it doesn't make sense in my brain.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll look at your YouTube videos, but your email hurts my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there any other emails?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there was another one written by the same person, but again... Yes, read it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, first off, this was the first Silent Hill game I've played, so be nice, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do I have to?
[SPEAKER_09]: Too late.
[SPEAKER_09]: You play as Harry Masons, whose daughter is missing, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: We know all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The gameplay is seamless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of the PSP, your trusty flashlight adds an extra compen...
[SPEAKER_09]: Commentary pending what you're looking at?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, though, but I do like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Nightmare Sequences are a pain in the ass without weapons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go back and play the first Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I try?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I try reading the review?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you mind if I give it a shot?
[SPEAKER_09]: Give it a try, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on one minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta bring it up here in studio here, and I will read the review for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, because it's really bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Silent Hill Shattered Memories?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be the one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Will this review involve...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, first off, this is the first Silent Hill game I've played, so be nice, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, this is a remake of the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: You play as Harry Mason, whose daughter is missing, and you travel through the mysterious small town of Silent while searching for her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gameplay is seamless of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your trusty flashlight adds an extra commentary pending what you are looking at.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a cell phone to take pictures of static memoirs and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: The most annoying part of the game is the physiest Trist who pops up and pisses you off and the nightmare sequences are a pain in the ass without weapons.
[SPEAKER_04]: The story changes depending on how you talk with the physierest you could get ending where she's not found or one where blah blah blah spoilers.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is more fuck with your head than super scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give it a 4.5 out of 5.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought for sure you were going to use one of the audio effects on our new mixing board.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: You went back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Echo voice, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Echo voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want echo voice?
[SPEAKER_04]: I own your soul.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give it a 4.5 out of 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's enough of that, for real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds like you're at the back end of a tunnel, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: New mixing boards are fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on then to the FUs of the week because sometimes we get angsty here on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That poor guy is never going to email us again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to have your emails ready to kill, please send them to mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just remember, we have Yakety Sax ready to go whenever we need it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We also have the angst music ready to go for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you, Cryptic.
[SPEAKER_09]: For your damn servers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make your servers hold more people so that I don't have to play a laggy STO.
[SPEAKER_09]: The end.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to people that break into my car.
[SPEAKER_11]: And apparently there is a dude, or somebody, I'm assuming it's a dude, that broke into my car last night because I had boxes in the back of my car to give to my co-worker who's moving.
[SPEAKER_11]: And those boxes were of a microwave and computers and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so they thought, hey, look, microwave and computers.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they broke the back window, pulled the box out, and go, hey, this is a box.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, under those boxes was my rifle bag with all my airsoft guns, and they decided to take that in protest.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I am without airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you gave a thief guns.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good move, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gave a thief fake guns.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I gave him guns without batteries or any of the ammo, because he didn't take any of the ammo.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just sitting right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever, you know, I don't care because I haven't played airsoft in over a year, so... Yeah, it's so sad, but... If I want more airsoft guns, I'll just buy more.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have arcade stuff to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have players often.
[SPEAKER_11]: The weather's been crappy, so... It's unfortunate, but it's not like... I'm not sad by it at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: um well if that's it for your FU of the week mine would be just more moving angst and cleaning and putting things in boxes and moving it and yeah it's everything that comes with moving but I'll be over it in a couple weeks when it's over I'm sure
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, things are good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have a lot to complain about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Life is happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Butterflies and sparkles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, a couple more news stories for you guys and then your chance to interact with us live on the phone on our Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio or 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Dante's Inferno is getting some download content, which I think is bundled actually with the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently someone got the game early, or downloaded the game early, and...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: so that's kind of neat but apparently if it's not in the PS3 version I know it's definitely not in the 360 version so if you do have the 360 you'll have to get it in April hopefully it is included in the PS3 version in which case you'll get it immediately but that's neat and I don't know if it's going to be free later on but it's apparently a trailer that's on the disc so
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to pick up Dante's Inferno, by the way, just before I get to my thing?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, because I have Borderlands, and I now have Bioshock 2 to play, and really I'll just pick up God of War 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although Dante's Inferno looked kind of cool, and I'm interested just to kind of play through it mindlessly, but not right away.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll wait for the maybe drop in price.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Final Fantasy XIII is right around the corner, so I really don't have time to play all these games.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: it's just too many games I'll probably put it in the queue of things to play like on my literal now that I use a rental game so I stop spending 60 bucks on games every week put it in my queue of things to play but you know one thing I'm learning you don't always get what's number one on your list right away it's not quite as effective as Netflix just so you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one other story for you guys, and this does have to do with spending money Buying stuff on your computer using one of those digital distribution sites You know Steam, they are probably the kings of what's going on But there are some other websites that sell games too And one of them is GOG.com, GOG.com Or you might call them the good old games
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, obviously some publishers are not having that, but GOG.com or Good Old Games tries to kind of legitimize that by selling DRM-free old games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they got some big lands this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got a deal with Activision Publishing to get some Sierra classics, because Activision has access to those classics now, that you can't even find on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of those games, by the way, that are out right now, the first two that were added, Arcanum of Steamworks and Magic Obscura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely an Obscura title because I haven't even heard of that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this one I definitely knew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gabriel Knight, Sins of the Fathers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you ever heard of this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard of the Gabriel Knight games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's pretty cool because Tim Curry does a voice in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of his voice acting gigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: 6 bucks for each one of those titles they are supposed to be doing like several titles a week over the next few months so a lot of these old school classic games if you are curious and checking them out you can go to GOG.com granted it's not the same as when that LucasArts pack was available for what like 9 bucks or something some obscenely low price on Steam over the holidays but you know you can still find some good old classic games
[SPEAKER_11]: I have plenty of games to play and I'm just trying to get through I'm still trying to sort my MAME ROM collection to eliminate all the crap I'm not going to use
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Several folks in chat chanting down with DRM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's one of their big things is that they don't charge or they don't have really DRM on the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you can buy them and it's legitimate.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can feel good karma and all that stuff and not have to worry about the whole abandoned ware and possibly getting viruses and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for the news tonight, and that's where we're going to go to our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is now open, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are taking your calls live on this Sunday evening, Super Bowl Sunday, February the 7th of 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: While we wait for some calls to come in, Loki's got some last-minute stories for us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, this is Spazinator Hi Spazinator, what's on your mind buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you guys saw my tweets earlier this week, but I thought it would be worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's an anime series that I think you guys may want to check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: As far as I know, DarkSakura is into anime as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold that thought, hold that thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because speaking of anime series, I totally forgot to get into this at the top of the show, and I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_04]: This weekend, I went to Japantown in San Francisco, and I totally thought of Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, well, A, I saw the taiyaki place that I know she really loves, and she likes to eat there, and it made me think of her.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we went to Japan Video and some of those places, and we were looking at...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anime, and I saw the Ragnarok anime on DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they made like 25 episodes of a Ragnarok anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they have a whole season.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've watched most of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it made me think of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, I should get this for Jamie, and then I'm thinking, no, she probably already has it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, no, actually, I downloaded it when it first started coming out on TV, and I never finished it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so it actually won.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pretty cute, pretty close to the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm already getting the new DS one, the US one, because I tried playing it in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a completely random tangent right next to all that stuff is a little store called Pika Pika, which is a picture booth store.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of the stores that's nothing but picture booths.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I met up in Japantown with a bunch of people that I play World of Warcraft with, so it's like we had an IRL raid.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we raided Pika Pika, and one of the photo booths there, and there was like six of us in the photo booths.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes like $9 to take a picture, but it's all like green platforms you stand on, and it puts in backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Picture Club.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, seriously, I think these only exist in big cities.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen one by Arcade Infinity, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: There used to be one right next door there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you have one of these in your town, it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, totally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, sorry, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got off topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what was the anime you wanted to talk about?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Dubslinger Girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if either one of you have heard of it, but it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: There's two seasons of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Both are like 13 episodes long.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the trick synopsis of it is this government agency over in Italy basically takes in kids that are basically dying and turns them into $6 million woman-type cyborgs and has them...
[SPEAKER_01]: Do assassinations for like assassinate terrorists and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So wait, Gunslinger... Hold on, Gunslinger Girl was the name of the anime?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever heard of this, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to try it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just haven't had a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this something available on the PlayStation 3 marketplace?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know anime is like a big niche that they have on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's season one and season two.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think there's...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like a lot of Season 3, but there is another season there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's like a reimagining of the entire series.
[SPEAKER_01]: You may want to call it Season 2.5 if you want to call it that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, like a special, sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I have the entire Season 1 and Season 2, and I just finished up Season 2 the other day, and oh my God, it's epic.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have to recommend that to the listeners and to the anime fans here in the studio as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gunslinger Girl, okay, so I'm really excited about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else on the PlayStation Network we should be checking out right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's something you kind of sort of touched on on your last show.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the new Music Guidance Sigma 2 table for Zen Pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just got that today and it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, personally, I think it's a little bit better than some of the other tables that are currently available for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Zen Pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'd definitely give it a thumbs up on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, let's get going so you can take more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you have a good week, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for the phone call and we'll forgive you for the bad joke on Twitter earlier, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you too buddy, bye
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess maybe you can still get a one-day ticket.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to PAX East.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, really, I have tickets.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually just bought a regular ticket.
[SPEAKER_04]: I decided I didn't want to do the media thing because, A, PAX doesn't really do much for media, and that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally am cool with that, and I think that's actually the way I wish E3 was that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so, you know, I'm going as a gamer, as a fan, just like the rest of you, and don't really want to have to work through all of PAX.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just going to have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'll be around at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try, when the schedule comes out, I will try to find like a gaming lounge time, maybe with the DS game I enjoy, that I'll go be at.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll let you guys know more about that when it gets a little closer to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good day, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Lieutenant Sal Tome of USS Takahashi, requesting permission to come aboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a Star Trek Online addict as well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I just picked it up last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Ranma, everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, hi, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sir, you getting the lag too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, I don't think it's my graphics card, I think it's their servers, but I had to wait in the queue of 118, and it takes like five whole seconds to move in any direction.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have not had that problem at all, and mind you, my video card is like almost three years old.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, mine's actually just under what the correct one is supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: But seriously, they say there's supposed to be increasing server capacity, but they haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I just haven't had that problem at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may also be the difference in locations that we're at too, because right now I just hit memory alpha and my character's all like running all over the place and there's a ton of people there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe it has to do with location too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably so.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is this what you called in to talk about tonight, Star Trek Online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that too, that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: First thing I want to talk about is something from a couple of podcasts before.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mentioned about how it's possible for Steam to sell so many games at dirt cheap prices.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe I have the answer for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I used to work in a video store and we would rent games, so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once the rental of the game got to a certain point, we could sell it at a price because all the rentals...
[SPEAKER_06]: made the money back on the purchase of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: My thing is, with Steam, once they have this game, they sell it at that price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once they've made the money back on selling the game, they can just cut the price to as cheap as they want and that's just extra cash for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I would still think that the deals are based on percentages of sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems kind of odd that it would work based on how much of it sells, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think maybe the whole retail strategy to digital distribution seems a little apples to oranges.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you could be right, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I mean, because when we rent these games, like there was one game, you know, we have like five copies of Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three of them will be selling for like $30 and two will be selling for, I'd say, $40 because of the rental turnaround rate on those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if they get a game, they sell it at this price, they make the money back off of, you know, the licensing, the rights, the time it costs that they invested into it, then there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: well I was also just the mindset I mean honestly I always and still kind of think the reason for the sale is that you know assuming it is based off percentages those companies are still making five dollars off a game they would have made no dollars off of had it not been on Steam on a huge ass sale you know some money's better than no money a long forgotten game that got booted off of shelves years ago so I don't know good thought though I mean anything is possible and unfortunately until we know somebody on the inside at Steam that knows the agreements of the arrangements we just won't know
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but we can go off of that for the time being.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to mention?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to say thanks for taking a chance to listen to my podcast over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to admit I downloaded it, but I didn't listen to it yet, but I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're looking for good titles, I recommend Kido Tenshi Angelic Lair.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's free on Netflix right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are some good animes based off of video games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember Tower of Druaga, that old video game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's become an anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe it's been licensed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they had kind of a renaissance of that game a while ago, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a new Duraga game, I think, on PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other quick question I have for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: A movie I saw at the video store that looked hilarious, and I don't know, maybe Jamie knows of this, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it was a Japanese movie directed by the same guy who did Ichi the Killer, and it was advertised as The Sound of Music meets Dawn of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: That, I don't know, but I believe the director was Takahashi Mike, or Miike?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looked hilarious from the box art, and I was wondering before I go out and either spend money on that or obtain it through questionable means, if it was worth my time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything along those lines of Ichi Tequila, I keep hearing is well worth the purchase.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm using a website I should have used a long time ago and looking up Ichi the Killer on... The Hills Are Alive with Sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: It has another name to it, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the little tagline, I think, to the... It's... The Family Something was the name of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Happiness of the Katakrys?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the name of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've not heard of.
[SPEAKER_11]: The hills are alive with the sound of screaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: The sound of music means still in the dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the box I saw.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's awesome because it made me lol.
[SPEAKER_04]: It made me lol for real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well maybe somebody else will call him later and tell me about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright Ranma, we're going to let you go so we can get more calls, but thank you as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hey, have fun on Star Trek, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Calm out.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR 1877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the one and only Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, how are you doing, Legend of Zaku?
[SPEAKER_05]: Recovering from almost a hangover this morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you drinking before noon?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was basically last night's drinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's just say that I drank to the point where I drank into places where...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay, you've got to stop typing during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, you can't type right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I just wanted to bring up that whole harmonic speculation about the licenses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, the way I see it is that Konami, the only thing they have going for them right now
[SPEAKER_05]: is lawyers.
[SPEAKER_05]: In other words, they sued Rockstar over ITG and they managed to win that case single-handedly and got their franchise.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it was a complete rip-off of DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could probably say the same thing for whatever Harmonix is doing with whatever they...
[SPEAKER_05]: We think they're doing with those licenses
[SPEAKER_05]: before the whole rock band thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix was also not sued over Guitar Hero because the look and feel from Guitar Freaks was completely different, whereas with I in the Groove, the look and feel was the exact same as DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, right on down to the backgrounds and animations and pretty much the way the arrows looked.
[SPEAKER_04]: They added mines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we also have to keep in mind that, I mean, you could have said the same thing for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that almost a ripoff of DDR with those arrows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, though, that went back, I want to say Konami and Namiro made an agreement many years ago because Pump It Up was actually first.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyhow, I don't want to rehash that old news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so the lawyers and litigation is how Konami keeps their franchises.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that all depends on how Harmonix is actually going to approach this, whether or not they're actually going to reinvent the same four-panel dance paradigm that we've seen for more than a decade, or they're going to go into a new direction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chances are, if I was a betting man, I would say the latter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because they're pretty good at innovating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty good at innovating within rhythm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of this is speculation, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could be licensing these songs for Rock Band for some weird little pop expansion they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see those songs in particular being something that would blend well with Rock Band completely.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way I see it is that they're doing something outside of Rock Band with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Rock Band 3 is something we haven't thought of yet Pax East is probably going to give us some clues because Harmonix is in Boston this is happening in their backyard so this is the perfect place for them to make an announcement I think Harmonix is the kind of company that will drop a bomb at Pax East
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I would love to go and see it for myself, but since I was unemployed up until last week, there was no way I would have gotten tickets well in advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, congratulations on getting employment though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good news, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, but I guess time will tell.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will give it my critical eye with my music games background and I'll let y'all know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, of course, and you have to make sure you don't want to, don't give them the benefit of the doubt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try to
[SPEAKER_05]: well try to like press them on some hard questions obviously not treading into NBA stuff but just try to challenge them that they're trying to sell you on something that you think is not going to be revolutionary I'll do my best
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Zaku, any other thoughts here before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't drink a 40 ounce of liquor because all that's going to do is purge your stomach.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happened to me last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some sage advice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go ahead and take one more call if someone wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, anything to tide us over?
[SPEAKER_04]: 250GB hard drives coming out in Japan in March.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably over here eventually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Santa Hedgehog is rumored to be playable in Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do remember something about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there was a new Tetris game in development, but it's not the Dish Network thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something about somebody was making a new Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if the two are related.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to cost you $2.99 a month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really, just play it free online.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't need to play it on your TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tetranet for life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else.
[SPEAKER_11]: According to Game Informer, LA Noire is no longer a PS3 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's hitting the Xbox 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Another one lost.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whenever the hell it comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Long ways away.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of something else that's not an exclusive anymore, High Voltage was bringing a brand new game, The Grinder, which is going to be a Supernatural first-person shooter game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Originally going to be a Wii exclusive.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, now it's coming to Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And will probably look way better than the Wii version anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last call, by the way, for phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to call into the show, it's an empty line right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Bowl Sunday is a good day when everybody's distracted.
[SPEAKER_11]: And cracked in a two-headed contest to have fans submit user-made graffiti.
[SPEAKER_11]: And one of the pictures that got, I guess, won was of these two male agents making out, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh, I, okay, whatever, hey That's all I have, that's it Alright I doesn't, oh, we just in the nick of time got another call Let's take this and we'll wrap it all up Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this is X-Link Hey, X-Link, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I'm glad to, I was reading Kotaku earlier on today and realized that they're coming out with a new version of Blaster Master come tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, well, did you listen to Part A tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a joygasm over it in Part A. Oh, did you really?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was having, we were having some issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we know, Super Bowl, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no, no, nothing with Super Bowl at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was with the Step Kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what is on your mind, though, at least about the Blaster Master game?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are your thoughts on it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I looked over the video they had out on YouTube and I gazzled myself pretty much because this was one of the first games I got back when I had my NES and I buy it with my own money and I absolutely loved it.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, I had the World of Power book.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was so good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All those novels by FX9 and stuff?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I have a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I had that one too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Simon's Quest book.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both were epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I had the Metal Gear one too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was missing this too because a lot of my books were burnt down.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of my old school stuff that the games I had, my PS1 games, a lot of those, I had back in my mom's apartment when I was moving from going from Orlando, Florida to Melbourne, Florida.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of that stuff got burnt down.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was an arson in my mom's apartment and a lot of that stuff got burnt down.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I had to go online and refine the books, which...
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of books I got, but the Simon Quest and the Metal Gear, if you have them in good condition, are really valuable and really hard to find.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of the text, though, at least, is available online.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can read a lot of those novels online.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the same thing, you know, collectors and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do, just a complete random-ass fact about those books.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those that don't know what we're talking about, the World of Power were these books that they wrote about old NES games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But since a lot of the 8-bit video games didn't really have stories that made for very good books...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of times the authors would kind of add their own stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for instance, I believe the plot about Castlevania II had to do with some kid, like, warping himself into that world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it wasn't even really about Simon Belmont, but somebody... To no end, the Game Master.
[SPEAKER_04]: His little sidekick.
[SPEAKER_04]: but there were some extra characters in Blaster Master to make that story work too and here's the interesting thing I believe one of the characters was Eve which was I think like the name of the car or something or like was one of the robot characters they actually the programmers of Blaster Master made Eve they wrote her into the official canon and she was in the Game Boy game
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's also from Part 2 from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_00]: I believe there was an actual Part 2 for Blaster Master and they brought the actual plot line from the book into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Blaster Master was one of the better books.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also the covers, a lot of times the covers were different from the actual game covers from the video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, because they took out the gun from the Metal Gear cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It can't promote violence.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a kid's book.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times down memory lane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to bring back those books.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I guess they do have them to some extent.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's books about Halo, tons of books about World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they're always bringing back the Chujo Adventures.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can see why they can't do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get the permission from the people and redo it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, I was just mostly, I know you were looking for some calls, so I was called about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was a guy really giddy about that, because I had a lot of my old school games, like Blaster Master was one of the first ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, Castlevania was another one, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Castlevania 2, I remember spending hours on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm giddy, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wish it was on PS3.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was burning out my friend's Nintendo NES, because we had it on for 18 hours straight, because we didn't want to turn it off, and we wanted to go through and beat the game, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm excited, but I'm trying very hard not to get too excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to set the expectations too high for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to set the bar somewhere in the middle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get too excited and then be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I hear you, I hear you.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd be one of those things, like, you get all gung-ho about, and it's like, man, when the heck did I do this in the first place?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to let you go so we can wrap up the show, but thank you so much for the call, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, when you called, like, about two other people called in at the same time, so you lucked out, so congrats.
[SPEAKER_00]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks, man.
[SPEAKER_00]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that is going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I apologize to those folks that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you do want to still interact with the show, remember, we do take Twitter topics every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do take emails every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any way you can figure out on the internet on all of our various websites to contact us, we will probably consider reading it on the show if you find us on one of those many, many websites.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go ahead and let Loki finish up any last-minute stories he has while we go ahead and shut down the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Terror Drome, Fighting Game, Horror Movie Characters
[SPEAKER_11]: I've not heard of this either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you've got, you know, Freddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've got Jason from the Friday the 13th movies.
[SPEAKER_11]: You actually have Ash in there as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chucky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of cool characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, here's the full list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's under construction.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they do have a demo available online, I guess, that you can download online.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'll have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if you want to check it out, it's at Terrordrome-TheGame.com That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to link something in the chat room that has nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you thought you'd link it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Come have a look.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually this right here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a big type nerd.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I like that there's this garage where they actually managed to get it where if you're looking right from a certain angle, everything is perfectly aligned.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as you go through, you see they've actually painted it all the way across.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is pretty nerdy, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those optical illusions.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, well, I'm also, you know, when I look at games, I actually have been paying more attention now to how they're designed, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: The look and feel of them, and I think that has a lot to do with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, you have to know your way around everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I still see you playing on the YouTube there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get your thing fixed, or what'd you do?
[SPEAKER_11]: I argued, saying that it was under fair use.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and the audio's back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, look at that.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, arguing works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you don't get our account closed
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a quick last minute sort of like update.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every year at Orange Lounge Radio, our friends over at Understation Live do their March Madness.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now they call it, I think they just call it USL Madness because it doesn't always happen in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all the, you might remember a few weeks ago we got some phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were collecting the top 25 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well they compiled that and they got the first brackets up So some of the games are now doing battle So if you want to check that out, go to Orange Lounge Radio And go to our forums And you'll see there's a whole forum for March Madness And it says 2009 because we can't figure out how to update it But it actually is all the posts for 2010 And you can see all the brackets And you can vote in the first round But voting closes tomorrow night, Monday night So you can choose, like for instance I'll read a few of these matchups that are going on right now Civilization vs. Time Crisis Which is better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 2 vs. Para Para Paradise
[SPEAKER_04]: Contra vs. Final Fantasy X Final Fantasy vs. Final Fantasy VIII Final Fantasy VIII
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be too late, but you can go vote in the next round and have your voice heard on what is truly the best video game of all time, according to the OLR Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we're done a little bit early tonight, but that's the way it goes sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes we have a lot to say, sometimes we don't have as much to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to wrap it all up and get on out of here for the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, we've got to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll start with my final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is I should go to the arcade or something, play some arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does sound like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe after moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Typography is life.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really funny how... Your mic's off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really funny how my mic was off.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that just a simple little instructional guide on eHow can get your YouTube video back up even though it has copyright music in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll be back to do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows what's going to happen next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tune in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until then, that does it for another week here at Orange Lounge Studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next Sunday for more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!