[SPEAKER_15]: Tonight, February 28th, 2010, which country has banned Heavy Rain?
[SPEAKER_15]: A date is announced for the Final Fantasy XIV beta, and a Nintendo press event brings us a barrage of Wii and DS news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello my friends and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio, that talk show on the internet, live every Sunday night, dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern Time at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: A big thanks to them for letting us steal their bandwidth every single week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one thing to say to the California government.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get into that in a little bit during housekeeping, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you wonder what she's talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not just an unbalanced budget, but there's other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've probably heard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's made those water cooler press stories this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And boy, do we have the response for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get into that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do talk games too, right, Tech Master Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Also here joining us every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, every now and then.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing okay Yeah, I'm boycotting him
[SPEAKER_10]: Nobody with any taste is.
[SPEAKER_06]: My grandma's happy, I'll tell you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get into our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, once in a while we do talk about video games here, and we let the gamers have a voice in our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, but don't worry, if you're not listening live, if you're listening on the podcast feed, there are a million billion ways to communicate with the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's a social network for it, we're probably on it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Twitters, the Facebooks, we take emails every week, all of it, and phone calls later on too, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I've had lots of homework to do and lots of responsibilities to take care of, so I haven't really played anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you've got to take a break once in a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I've tried to play my Sims 3 and it probably hates my mods, so I have to reinstall it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Loki, how about you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you been playing anything this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a lot of Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been trying to go through and finish Mad Moxie's Underdome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And unfortunately didn't get a chance to do that because the ones I'm on now are the 20 round matches.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which each round has 5 waves in it and it takes forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I made it only through seven rounds before I realized I'm not going to be able to finish it in the time that I had.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I quit that and played a little bit more just the standard campaign now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm almost maxed out as far as my level goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I am kind of trying to collect some weapons and stuff because I downloaded the new expansion.
[SPEAKER_02]: And unfortunately, the new expansion kills any mods that you have.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, more Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: And doing well on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still trying to move up the leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I broke 200 now for cumulative ranked deathmatches.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm, I think, almost like in the 60s for TrueSkill rankings, so it's going pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be up there pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only problem is, though, is those guys that are actually in the top of the TrueSkill ranks...
[SPEAKER_02]: They tend not to want to play games that they're losing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they drop out and so their rank doesn't go down.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I actually did run into some people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually ran into the number one player and the number six player and both of them did not want to play me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is too bad because I would have kicked the crap out of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm playing this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you still have a cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were sick last week and you're still sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you feeling okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you need some medication?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took two days off this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I play a lot of Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: And did other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't really go into that because wife would not be happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I had a week similar to Jamie's where a lot of real life stuff is coming into play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still working on the whole moving thing which will be done like tomorrow, so thankfully.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I did play a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did get into World of Warcraft, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: My boyfriend and I have been leveling together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I helped him kind of get started with the character.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: He started the character and by the time it got to about...
[SPEAKER_06]: about level 21, I don't remember, 23, somewhere in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We started leveling together and now we just hit 50 this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yay to leveling.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of fun to have somebody to always play WoW with.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm really trying to get as much Borderlands in this week because I have a feeling I'm going to have Final Fantasy XIII by the end of this week and oh my god, everything's going to stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is your connection getting that early?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I want to place an order if so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if we have extras, but I will check.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had this story where it came up at some point during the show that the former Midway games had all disappeared from Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joust and Smash TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I had a night where I just decided to play a bunch of retro games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went in and I played Joust.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I actually played Smash TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I started playing Gyruss for a while for some weird reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not a weird reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just really love that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of my favorite shooters from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually beat my former high score, which isn't very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to work on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Gyruss and a lot of the old arcade games, admittedly, is all about memorization, like knowing where the ships come from in every wave.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just really need to kind of work on it for a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I got a better score.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that made me happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I beat my score on another old game, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't remember which one it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember if it was Time Pilot or no, I think it was like Tempest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, though, my score is still not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to work on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, as I mentioned, one of the things I did while I was sick is worked on something that my wife would not like.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is I'm building up our top arcade cabinet for work.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's actually coming along pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: But for some reason, the Naomi version of Marvel vs. Capcom 2 still has slowdowns in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not by my computer because it's certainly fast enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me ask kind of like a random MAME question, because I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played MAME, the arcade emulator, in quite a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it ever get to the point where it does more things online, like the exchange of high scores or an online leaderboard or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I really see that as being some of the big appeal of Game Room to me, the legitimate MAME or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's really cool that I'm going to have leaderboards with friends and some of that medals and achievements element.
[SPEAKER_06]: MAME is just...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: They do have patches now that will save your high scores, but nothing that you can play online with each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other programs out there like Mess or Misfit Mame, which will run all sorts of hacked games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe those will have some sort of online play or something, but Mame does not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, it does make sense, though, that there's not a lot of frills because MAME is sort of in that really gray area of legality as it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's nothing wrong with the MAME program itself, but it's the fact that the ROMs are not legal except for a handful.
[SPEAKER_06]: There have been a few that the original creators of the game have come back and said...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that was like 25 years ago, and we're not going to make any money off of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we hereby release it in the public domain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woohoo, have fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: There have been a handful of those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think if MAME were to come in and say, oh, we're going to implement this online leaderboard for this game, it would really kind of start to push the boundaries of the gray area of legality.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would just be tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be tough to do it, and it'd be tough to make sure people aren't cheating in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd just be too difficult.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do believe, actually, that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Macaron or maybe Demol, one of the Dreamcast emulators, is actually doing online.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play multiplayer over the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know those do Naomi games, so like Marvel vs. Capcom 2 or...
[SPEAKER_06]: Did they ever perfect it on the NES or SNES?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think those have gotten better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play over the internet with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The same with MAME.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, the motherboard in it is really cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, anytime I overclock it, the ethernet stops working.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I've always said I would love Nintendo's Virtual Console if it was on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're going to get into this more later, but I'm honestly surprised at the release schedule that they have right now, so maybe they are coming around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because that's basically all the games that they announced at E3 coming out before E3 this year, so it's like, okay, clean slate, what are you going to announce for the rest of the year, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll get into that a little bit, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before we get into the gaming news, let me do some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have a whole lot of housekeeping here in-house, but something DarkSakura referenced a little earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kind of wanted to share this and throw this out there with you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, the California State Assembly passed a measure this week that is going to support anti-swearing week, or what do they call it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No cussing week, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: The first week of March.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So starting Monday, because today's the last day of February, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: So starting Monday, it is no cuss week in California.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you so much as say fuck out loud, you're going to get hauled off to jail.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, okay, it's not really like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What it is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some kid in a club in California started this no cussing club.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it caught on amongst all these people that think if you cuss then clearly you're not intelligent because only unintelligent people have to fill their vocabulary with cuss words blah blah blah I don't know something along those lines so somehow this got all the way to the state assembly while we are in the midst of a budget crisis yet again mind you and you know we can't even go to the DMV anymore because we're not even sure when they're actually open because they're closed half the time anyway sorry I don't want to get on the political tangent here too much
[SPEAKER_06]: So they found time to pass this resolution to support the No Cussing Week, and they're encouraging that everybody should keep a swear jar, and you should, you know, where if you say fuck or damn or whatever, you should put in 25 cents into the swear jar.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and you should donate this to charity, to Haiti or probably Chile now, and obviously our thoughts to everybody who was affected by that recent thing, and I don't have a problem with donating to charity, but I think I have a little bit of a problem with...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, the government endorsing something that sort of infringes on freedom of speech.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, call me crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you look at this dude's website for the No Cussing Club, they're selling books.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're selling charters on how to start your own club.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee, the guy's profiting off this idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they taxing him?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't knock him for profiting off of it because if people are dumb enough to pay him for it, then...
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's what capitalism is built on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Profiting off the stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: This state is... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I don't mean to get on the political train, but this does affect video games because this is the home of Silicon Valley and where a lot of the games are made.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if the state goes belly up, so are a lot of your favorite game publishers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but this non-cussing week is about as...
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk Like a Pirate Day has not been endorsed by the state of California.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk Like a Pirate Day is an internet meme, basically, that's gone crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it a 4chan thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It might as well be.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those things.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically about that important as far as... I would say even less important than Talk Like a Pirate Day because that's actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about that important like...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can say them and nobody can take that right away because I live in America which is great but I'm glad you brought that up because next week's show will fall during No Cussing Week so I do want to point out we here at OLR we do have our plan and we are going to bring you OLR Presents our No Cussing Week show next week so we're looking very much forward to that so stay tuned so OLR celebrates No Cussing Week in the state of California next week
[SPEAKER_02]: Celebrate?
[SPEAKER_02]: But why are we giving them more fuel for their fire?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like to challenge ourselves here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's challenge ourselves with some video game news tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to fucking do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I had to get that out of there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the PS3 developers have now 70 megabytes of additional RAM unlocked to be able to use in their games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony apparently has been upgrading the PS3 over the past few months and doing so they've dropped the OS's memory footprint from 120 megabytes to 50 megabytes and basically allowing the system to use less RAM and therefore being able to pass on the RAM to other developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, is that going to really make a difference?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll help.
[SPEAKER_02]: They won't have to optimize their code as much, but as PS3 developers have basically said, any bit of RAM helps.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess a little bit of RAM is better than none, but, well, I mean, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, there is RAM in the system as it is, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_06]: The more RAM, the merrier.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how is it that this console's been out for so long, and now they're saying, hey, we've unlocked this hidden RAM.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it just because they've optimized processes and systems?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they've just optimized their operating system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically found new ways to do different things, and now, because it's optimized, they don't need as much RAM.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I wouldn't expect that suddenly all these games are going to have uber better graphics and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, 70 megs of RAM is not that much when all is said and done.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's going to be like an extra, maybe an extra splish splash in the water effect or an extra little dangling light somewhere in Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised they're not using it for like, you know, more features in the operating system, you know, custom soundtracks in all the games, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: and CrossGameChat, which I think is still there now, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, video chat or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could be using that RAM for something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: These consoles, you know, have been out for a while and put more RAM in them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like gigs of RAM instead of like half a gig or whatever the hell's in these.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's not more than a gig.
[SPEAKER_06]: it's pathetic but they can't up it after the console's already out because then the games that are released may not work on the older system so it's just like you have a new console out there like remember like I'm thinking of the Nintendo 64 memory pack like didn't you have to have that little memory pack in order to play like Majora's Mask I think was the biggest game with that
[SPEAKER_02]: Some games, yes, but here's the thing is, like the PSP, they double the RAM that they have for their, well, it's mainly for their web browser, but it can be done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, all it would do is those games would run smoother.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see, but games would still have to be optimized for the lowest common denominator, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or else they're going to find themselves in trouble.
[SPEAKER_02]: But eventually they would phase that out, you know, phase out the old systems and...
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well one system that doesn't seem to be getting any upgrades in its near future is the Nintendo Wii, but that doesn't stop Nintendo from trying to crank out the big, big games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they had a big press event this week, we're going to focus on the next few stories talking about for a moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course some big, big titles coming out of this press event that happened this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: two of them being Mario Galaxy 2 and Metroid Other M sounds like Super Mario Galaxy 2 and Metroid Other M are both going to be out mid-year which was a little bit of a surprise because I think a lot of us were thinking even though Other M was shown at last E3 we were kind of thinking oh it's early it's going to be out this holiday season but no both these games have now been dated for mid-year so Mario Galaxy 2 I believe they've said they've even said like what May I think and Metroid Other M is going to be out in June yes
[SPEAKER_06]: So, June 27th, which is the day after my birthday, I believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, it's kind of exciting these games are coming out so soon, but what's that mean for the rest of the year?
[SPEAKER_06]: What big titles does Nintendo have left?
[SPEAKER_02]: They've already hinted that they're going to announce a new Zelda game that's going to come out at the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's basically what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to have a new Zelda game, probably running in the Twilight Princess engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that'll be the new game this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everyone will go buck wild over it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I guess some of the early impressions are out over these games, and Super Mario Galaxy 2 is pretty much Super Mario Galaxy 1, but some new worlds and new features and things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot of differences, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like the game has suddenly changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it has to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it has Be Mario, who's going to care?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, it was a good game, so you don't really need to change it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metroid Other M, on the other hand, finally we're getting some more details out of that, and it does sound like it's going to be a direct sequel to Super Metroid, which you know has me excited, because I think Super Metroid's the greatest game they ever made, so hearing that this is a direct sequel, well, I do also approach that with caution, because there's a part of me that goes, they could really screw this up, but apparently they have a whole rendered...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm certainly excited about Metroid Other M. I...
[SPEAKER_06]: If it is mostly a 2D Metroid especially, I'm really excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm cool with them throwing some 3D in there a la Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it's not that Prime was bad, but it's just I love Super Metroid and can't wait to see a game like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm sure we'll see more details on this in the coming months because this game is going to be out now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, we're looking at March?
[SPEAKER_06]: This game's out in three months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: and actually we're getting linked to something on YouTube I'm hoping this isn't a joke but it comes from Tiger Claw saying the Metroid Other M intro video was apparently leaked oh yeah somebody's got their little camera here at the press conference so Tiger Claw just linked this in our chat room
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to see, and I apologize because I know video doesn't make for great radio, but okay, we see nebulas and clouds and all that stuff here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me skip forward a little more in the video.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, whoever's holding their camera is having to hold it a little low, but we do see kind of like a rendered Samus in 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, those graphics look really good, especially for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know Nintendo's hoping this will be the game that changes people's minds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's the baby Metroid from the end of Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't it cute?
[SPEAKER_06]: And the mother brain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: That actually does look pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, remember how the boss shot the laser from her eye and everything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, whoever leaked that little piece of footage is gonna get busted, but that's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to check that out, the YouTube user that has this video posted right now is MetroidBlaster127.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where we got linked to by our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta say, maybe this will be the game that changes people's minds on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not necessarily that my mind needs to be changed because Nintendo does put out that one or two awesome games a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: If this does well, let's see a Team Ninja Zelda game or a Team Ninja Mario game.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this is about the DSi XL.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got a date and a price for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like it's going to be out on March 28th.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be $190, and I'm pretty sure I don't know if I'm going to get one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aren't they saying that a new DS is kind of rumored for E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like that could be one of the things that they announce?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's supposed to be one for $189.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to laugh if they do release a new one right after they do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I know we've gotten into this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did the micro after the DS was announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked my micro.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly don't think that they need to do another DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, granted, the XL, whatever, people might want a larger screen for something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're kind of posing this as like a secondhand e-book reader or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I think one of the new pieces of software they're going to have with this is like some sort of classic novel collection or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then again, I use my Kindle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was actually a... Or it wasn't the DSi XL that was necessarily kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a... I want to say it's a new DSiWare game that's going to be coming out where it's like a hidden pictures game that you have to search for different letters in this scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's kind of cool about it though is they almost do a pseudo head tracking with it using the camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually tilt the system around and the camera changes angles
[SPEAKER_02]: Based on how you have the system tilted Why don't they do this technology with DSi That might make it a lot cooler With different games coming out That you have this neat little Head tracking technology built in That would be really cool And kind of a way to differentiate Themselves with DSi Because right now it's like It's a DS with a camera They don't like to give us what we want
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, another big problem with this is the price.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, $200, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or $190 or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something like that is supposed to be like $20 more than what the DSi is now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now you're also talking you could get a Wii for the same price, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or at least an Xbox 360 low-end, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: For $199.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not really sold on, again, why I need the DSi XL.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have a DSi.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the DS Lite, was the last Nintendo system I bought.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I probably wouldn't have even bought that if I hadn't kind of bought it as like a knee-jerk thing when I was on vacation once.
[SPEAKER_06]: This...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would still have my DS fat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't understand the point of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, maybe they're in pretty colors, because that would be a big seller, as if they're in fabulous pink and sexy lavender.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know what the colors are going to be, but I think from what we've seen in the pictures, it's like they have a wine burgundy color.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and another one's bronze.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd get a bronze one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so like a third place looking color and then a Franzia looking color.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, if you want a DSi in a specific color, there are websites out there that will give you a DSi in any color you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you can go to Nintendo World Store in New York and they'll give you a DSi color.
[SPEAKER_06]: I almost did that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had like the custom DS cases and really there was a sexy metallic green one I kind of wanted but I resisted.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Almost As you should have because you probably already have a DS And there's no reason to purchase something because of the color There really wasn't Except the fact that it was one of the lights And I didn't have a light at that time So I almost bought that I did buy my Now I can't remember which letter is attached to it My pink one Because it was pink I do feel a little And I wanted to be different than what people expect
[SPEAKER_06]: Mine are very generic.
[SPEAKER_06]: My DS fat is gray and my DS light is black.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not my DS, my old SP.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not the SP, the one before that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I feel a little ridiculous having both of them at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, I just need to sell one of these, but who'd buy it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do what we do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get another room.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have another room.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just moved.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to downsize.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have as much room as I had before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got boxes everywhere still.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to get rid of things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take my DS to the dump.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so some other interesting stuff that came out of the Media Summit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo will be publishing Dragon Quest IX in North America, which is kind of weird if you think about it because Square Enix is over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why aren't they publishing the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: whatever it's coming out over here sometime in the summer and you know with Nintendo being the one that's publishing the game hopefully there'll be a better marketing campaign behind it so maybe that's good and because people buy blindly whatever Nintendo puts out so that's always good
[SPEAKER_02]: another game scheduled for May coming to the DS would be Picross 3D and kind of a cool looking game and of course you know Picross is kind of a puzzle game where you make a picture well now it's going to be in three dimensions as well and you'll break apart cubes to reveal different little cube animals and objects and stuff so that's kind of neat um
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Not in America, no, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of reminded me of some Panzer Dragon stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right around the corner, actually, Cave Story will be making its way out on WiiWare March 22nd with slightly upgraded graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there's going to be some download content as well being available, including a new Boss Rush and Sanctuary Time Attack mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: That will be available to download.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I guess I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I misread that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was originally announced as download content, but now it's being included.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you get it for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, extra stuff for free is always good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any news that particularly got you excited at the Nintendo conference?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we've kind of touched on most of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: There was some other interesting stuff, like regarding Monster Hunter Tri, or I guess they're calling it Monster Hunter Tri or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll talk a little bit more about that later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was very interested to see that both Mario Galaxy and Metroid Other M are coming out in the second quarter, which...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: New Zelda, OMG!
[SPEAKER_06]: and last year's E3 they came out within five minutes they were on New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii and they're like hey it's a New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: game that looks and kind of plays like the old school one and this is what gamers want da da da and guess what it's out this holiday woohoo
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was one of the big things they showed on the floor.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm thinking there could be another, like, gotcha this year from Nintendo, except I worry it might be the Zelda game that's already kind of leaked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm guessing it's going to be like a Pikmin 3, probably the new Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii Relax, which will be retarded, but it'll probably come out around October-ish, I think around the same time as Wii Fit Plus did this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think they'll probably treat it as... Oh, the Vitality?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think they'll probably treat it as much, you know, like the Wii Fit Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of... I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not going to do as well as we fit in general.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't see the need for that little vitality sensor, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would be really cool though is to do a new Zelda game, but new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: style where it's old school Zelda, but four player and teaming up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the four swords.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want a lethargy sensor.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about a Wii Vitality Sensor that shocks you?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not moving!
[SPEAKER_11]: Clear!
[SPEAKER_06]: Or just something like when you screw up in the game, it gives you a little bite with electricity or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe a new WarioWare game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or the fanboy in me would love to see an F-Zero game come out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to hold my breath though, but that would be the whoa crap game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm still holding out for an Excite Truck
[SPEAKER_02]: A real Excite Truck 2, not this Excite Bots bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's move on to some other platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, a big game going on right now is Heavy Rain on the PlayStation 3, which sadly I have not gotten my hands on yet amongst all my real-life stuff going on, but I do want to play it at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I heard, and this is kind of like breaking news as we're taping live on this Sunday, I heard something about PlayStation Network is down right now, I guess, and if you want to play Heavy Rain, you can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I don't know how that works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does the game talk to the servers somehow?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you have to be online?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how it could.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how it could because, you know, what if you don't have an internet connection and you can't play the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, apparently something was going on I guess there's some game crashing errors going on on the PSN and it has something to do with the dates reverting and now some of the data is corrupting or something and yeah, the issues are preventing folks from launching games like Heavy Rain so it sounds like the date or something might have got screwed up and now it's messing everyone up I wonder how that works Yikes Hopefully that's fixed soon
[SPEAKER_06]: Heavy Rain was banned in another country this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: United Arab Emirates.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will not be able to play Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an official ban there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you are in the Middle East and you want to play this game, you're going to have to import it or something because the game was banned by the country's National Media Council.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, Sony has come out and said, you know, the game is an 18 plus game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is strong content, but they didn't really respond to this particular ban.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have a feeling they might just cut their losses since, unfortunately, for anybody listening who might be in the UAE, it's not one of Sony's biggest markets.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they might just be cutting their losses and hoping you guys will import it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it wasn't banned because of the bugs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there's some bugs going on in Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has to do with just some technical things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some audio is out of sync.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is freezing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are some auto-saves that turn out they can't load.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for some reason, everybody's speaking French.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kidding about the last one, sort of.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the rest is all... Well, you've heard about how Heavy Rain was made in France and was developed by a French studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they have all these French voice actors, but they're doing English and apparently the accent is really noticeable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really noticeable.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation Network actually got hacked because on their website there is a directory called Dear PlayStation that says get Flash and or enable JavaScript and stop wasting my time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So PSN might be the victim of a hack going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, the game is locking up and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess Sony has kind of posted in their forums about it saying that they are aware of some of the issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're having a particular issue, you should go to the thread and post your information because this is the era of patching video games that are already broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: isn't Sony the same service that's running a show right now about finding a video game tester I'm going to talk about this more in part B yes Sony might need some more video game testers right now so maybe you all win yeah maybe everybody needs to win that show and go test Heavy Rain I don't know I will talk more about the tester in part B I have a lot of thoughts on that so we'll get into that a little later on in the program but for now more gaming news from DarkSakura and then the release dates in a little bit
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, release dates.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking forward.
[SPEAKER_09]: But instead of that, this is not something that anyone should be looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are 12 game stores, as in a big retailer in the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, more than that, 43 are going to be closing down in the UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: That means that 247 people are going to be laid off.
[SPEAKER_09]: or, as the article says, will be redundant, which I think is a horrible term.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also... Well, that's what they call it over there, though, redundancies, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think it's just a terrible word.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, hi, you're redundant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whose fault is that for creating a redundant position?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The same guy who's probably laying me off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's going to be a third of the stores out of a total of 682.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's including 12 game stores and 6 game station outlets and 25 Debenhams stores, the little concessions.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameStop GameCrazy GameCrazy
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't get me started on that, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I'm sorry, but, you know, it's... A bunch of GameStops closed?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, then there would be an adequate number of GameStops available, because right now there's way too many.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they're totally cornering the market, which I think is disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't we have antitrust laws and stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we do, but Google's not listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, GameStop's not listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did I say Google?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you said Google.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, Google's on the list, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Google's always listening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Google's just been on a decline in the past couple years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Google's being sued for violation of antitrust.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm a big Google fan, but I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wave was what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't need Google Mars.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Buzz?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you know about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Google Mars?
[SPEAKER_06]: Google Mars.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the maps on Mars, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's cool, but it doesn't look very good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And why do we need to... Can't we just go to NASA's website or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm okay with Google Mars.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's Earth in the style, but it's Mars in the style of Google Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about Google Veronica Mars?
[SPEAKER_06]: Buzz!
[SPEAKER_06]: Google Veronica Mars would be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buzz was bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buzz was a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was Buzz?
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't hear about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buzz was their response to Twitter, but the problem was it automatically added the, like, 40 most common people you email to your Buzz friends list, and if somebody went to your public profile, they could see the 40 people you email the most.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if one of them happens to be like an ex or, you know, a boss is emailing his secretary on a personal email, everybody can see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or a porn finder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, whoever thought that was a good idea needs to be made redundant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if they were going to do something like that, they should have it as an option that you could select.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now they backtracked, but they botched the launch of that thing, and now nobody's going to trust it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they might as well just nuke, nuke Buzz, nuke Wave, and start again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Google BuzzWave.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am sick of the social networking, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like I was posting on my Facebook earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sick of social networking, yet I'm compelled to still do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm just thinking like, okay, I get what they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like here at OLR, we try to embrace all social networking when it comes out because we want to be where every gamer has a voice and we want people to interact with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I get that Bizarre is trying to be on the cutting edge.
[SPEAKER_06]: So for that, I say, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's the other part of me that goes, God, as if Twitter didn't have enough bullshit on it already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, honestly, guys, I'm just straight up with this whole social networking thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've told people this.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you post important news about your life on Facebook and are going to give me a pop quiz on it later or expect me to know that, like, you are getting engaged because the only place you said anything was Facebook, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't fly with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you want me to know what's going on with you, text, email.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I like to think those are kind of modern things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pick up the phone, dial the numbers, and call.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to read this list.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's a poster that was done by The Oatmeal.
[SPEAKER_09]: The 10 things you need to stop tweeting about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you seen that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have not.
[SPEAKER_09]: One, what are you eating?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had meatloaf for breakfast.
[SPEAKER_09]: LOL, please, RT.
[SPEAKER_09]: social media the conference or event that you're at Twitter itself well now wait a minute though because Twitter like we did the tweet thing from E3 and I think a lot of people like that because we post pictures on the floor that was reporting news this example is using it's like
[SPEAKER_06]: So and so totally owned that last session on optimizing your Twitter background pic I get what you're saying You know what, there's a girl on my friends list And I love her to death I think she's amazing But she posts so many updates Whenever she's at like a concert for a former American Idol or something Like it just fills up my page And I can't see anybody else's list And I'm kind of just thinking like
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you post a live journal?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or somewhere where you can make long posts?
[SPEAKER_09]: The other one on here is your workout, your kid, dog, cat, goat, or whatever else.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking out of context, as in people who just say nonsense.
[SPEAKER_09]: Daily booth photos, emotional breakthroughs.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's a daily booth photo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like posting the daily picture of yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, like where it's the same picture of me every day, flexing and looking cute?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Emotional breakthroughs in the number of followers you have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's so tacky when somebody posts like, I have a thousand followers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'll have to tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you have 999.
[SPEAKER_06]: Click.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to tell you what hit me today.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I actually use Twitter now for more of professional networking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I follow a lot of other designers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I follow people in the comic book industry.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I actually get something out of... And yeah, it's not that I don't care about the people on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just that I really don't need to know how big of a poop you took.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure your baby is cute, but I would rather have something meaningful.
[SPEAKER_06]: I honestly I feel like the biggest hypocrite when it comes to Twitter because most of the stuff I tweet these days have to do with video games and I kind of use it like for OLR related things and to keep tabs on the OLR fans but I don't like reading that stuff like when I look at my fans list and it's like a bunch of other podcasters promoting their shows I'm like yeah okay I know you have a show I get it but as in here I am tweeting hey listen to OLR tonight you know well it's just Twitter makes me feel dirty
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's why I say, you know, we have problems with it, yet we feel compelled to use it, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it is now a part of our culture.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you think about it, it's really a great... Which is why it's not cool anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: In Facebook, I have a little bit more love for because I use that as my mini blog.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually, I go back and check on it because I usually just put my to-do list up there, like what do I need to get done today and refer back to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I've actually not even been, you know, I'm actually making a conscious effort not to use either of them so much and actually keep a notebook with me and use my live journal and my blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the thing that freaks me out is that CNN uses Twitter as a real source now, and that kind of weirds me out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like when Boner died this week, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: The celebrity from... He was Boner on Growing Pain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chekhov's kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, oh yeah, Chekhov's kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, unfortunately, very tragic, sad, you know, what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But CNN went to Twitter to see what all the other celebrities...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this is my thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can use Google and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: When they're doing editorials and want to get viewer feedback, that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the same reason why we have the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we talk about an actual story and we want to see what people think about it, I think look at it as that equivalent.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's a fine line.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a really fine line.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that's why I think there's legitimate uses for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, you know, a lot of people honestly are using it to validate themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas, you know, if you want to share something important with people, it's a good way to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to see what other people are doing in your industry, it's a good thing to find out other people that are in your industry.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm really just getting like so tired of the, oh, I had to poop today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, nobody's going to retweet you and then say, I'm so glad your colon is working properly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some people do reply to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, I post really inane stuff on there too, but I actually just detached my loud Twitter feed from my live journal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thing I hate most about Twitter is that it's invading live journal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Gold star for Jamie, I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Over the last few weeks, I would just go back and check my loud Twitter feed and I posted one thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just now do it to keep up with other people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or if I have something to announce that's important, like, come to my birthday party, or I'm going to be going to LA, I would like to meet up with my friends there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a little bit more reasonable instead of, oh, I had some Weetabix for breakfast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we're on this big tangent with social networking, but we're in a weird place right now where it's kind of like the honeymoon phase is over with the Twitter and the Facebook and now it's like, okay, I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have some thoughts, why not email them to us, mailbag at orangelandradio.com, or we'll probably get some phone calls on it later in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: For now, though, we want to get to the classic game of the week, but not before we do release dates and a couple more news stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's travel around the world and see what's coming out in the various countries.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, this week there's actually some pretty good stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sins of a Solar Empire, Trinity, actually, coming out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dante's Inferno making its way out on PSP was a little delayed from the other games by almost a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alice in Wonderland, they have that coming out in DS and on the Wii, the Wii version being more like the movie, the DS version being more like Beetlejuice the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least that's what it looks like in the picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lunar Silver Star Harmony Limited Edition coming out on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: DECA Sports on the DS this week SpongeBob's Boating Bash coming out on the Nintendo DS and on the Wii kind of a demolition derby type of game MLB 2K10 coming out on PlayStation 2, PS3, Xbox 360, Wii, DS, and PSP Also coming out from Sony, MLB 10 The Show, which is on all Sony platforms, PS2, PS3, and PSP
[SPEAKER_02]: Battle of Giants, Mutant Insects, Battlefield Bad Company 2, Silent Hunter 5, Battle of the Atlantic,
[SPEAKER_02]: Supreme Commander 2 coming out from Square Enix on PC as well and Lips Party Classics coming out on Xbox 360 and that is it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw a new commercial for Lips this week that I guess uses Lily Allen sort of as the centerpiece of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wasn't that impressed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I guess maybe I'm just more of a SingStar fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised anybody buys Lips, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I buy SingStar, I mean... Yeah, but I understand SingStar because there's an actual following for that, but Lips is not so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like they're trying, they keep putting games out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think Lips was kind of put out as a response to SingStar.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if Lips had come first, I probably would have been on the Lips bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just SingStar seems to be easier to use, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, SingStar also has the real... Well, I guess Lips does too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know SingStar just has all the real videos integrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a really great party game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thing I thought with Lips was it was supposed to be able to integrate any music that you had and kind of turn it into a karaoke version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just kind of wonky.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the greatest implementation.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically using one of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can use a filter in Adobe Audition to take out vocals too, but it's a little hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's even some MP3 plugins that do that for Winamp, but it's a little hit and miss because it's just looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how the science of it works, but it looks at a certain component of the track of the song and kind of removes it, and sometimes it works and sometimes it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, moving on to the Xbox 360 in Japan and looking at Japanese release dates Bioshock 2 comes out this week on March 4th as well as Nobunaga no Yabutendo comes out and I believe that was on the PS3 a couple weeks ago because I seem to remember talking about that game before but yeah, localized version of Bioshock 2 also on the 360 this week in Japan
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there's Nobunaga no Yabutendo again, so maybe it was pushed back a little, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there it is on the PlayStation 3, also Bioshock 2 on the PlayStation 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this is actually, you know what this is?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is different.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not the Dynasty Warriors, this actually looks like Nobunaga's Ambition.
[SPEAKER_06]: This looks like a next-gen version of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I can't read the Japanese, but just looking at the interface, it looks like they're picking the different city layouts and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you know the Nobunaga Ambition series of games, I don't know how to explain it in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically an RTS-ish kind of game that's about Japanese feudalism, I guess is the easiest way for me to sum it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a feudal Japan sim.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked the old school one on the NES, but boy that game's evolved quickly over time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had one on PlayStation 2 a few years back.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the last one I remembered that came out over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a new one coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Nintendo Wii, nothing this week, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But next week, Taiko no Tatsujin.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know our music game fans might be familiar with that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taiko no Tatsujin makes its way to the Wii next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's March 11th, not this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that another one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a sequel?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I thought they had one over there already.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought they had one there already too, but this must be... Is this the one with the inflatable drum?
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or this could also be a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: or it could be the game because yeah they're only I think this is maybe the game by itself without the drum
[SPEAKER_06]: is probably what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PlayStation 2 this week, nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Nintendo DS, though, a lot of Dragon Quest games are going into the Ultimate Hits collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be 4, 9, and 5 all get price reductions for Squeenix, as well as Final Fantasy 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a big week for price reductions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, there is Bomberman, Touchland...
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Bomber No Miracle World gets a price reduction as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And probably a big, big release this week in Japan, which is why everything else is kind of limited this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Ranger, Hikari no Kiseki comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is different.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not like the gold and silver in those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's what that means.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's a little description here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Pokemon nappers are catching Pokemon and involving them in shady activities.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are more than 300... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are more than 300 species of Pokemons.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokeporn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of them you've seen in HeartGold and Silver.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you tame them and you can get them to join you in battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not, like I'm just looking at the screenshots, it's not the same type of game as the other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: This looks a little more like action-y, actually, for some reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like a tactics game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, like, it looks like it's almost like mini-games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, this one looks like, see how it's kind of like first-person flight type of game there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then this one looks like some type of running.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one looks like they're drawing on the DS screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it's almost like a mix of mini-games and Pokemon or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly on the PSP, .hack slash link comes out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's another big release, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're a fan of the .hack series, the PSP gets a new .hack game this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They call it the grand finale you've all been waiting for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move to the UK, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can we move there?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I can't afford it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well on the 3rd of March we have Toy Soldiers, on the 5th we have Alice in Wonderland, and then Assassin's Creed 2 for PC, Battlefield Bad Company 2, BlazBlue Calamity Trigger, Dementium 2 on the DS, Picross 3D, Silent Hunter 5 by Ubisoft, and Supreme Hunter 2, and Sushi Go Round for the DS and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mmm, sushi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, sushi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just a couple more stories for you guys and then we're going to get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'll just give you a little hint.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to give away what DarkSakura's picked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to say it's really old.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: So apparently Activision is being sued for false patent marketing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what that is, is basically that Activision is filing patents for its products that are beyond the scope of what it's producing.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, there's patent 753, which is basically a DDR pad, which would...
[SPEAKER_02]: C1-6
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the group behind us, the patent compliance group.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're seeking, and this is almost to the point where it's retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're seeking $500 for each Activision violation.
$500.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, but apparently, um, they're also, you know, targeting other companies as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, just Activision happens to be one of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: And according to, uh, Mark, looks like, uh, Mathenitus, uh, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: The statute in question is one that actually penalizes false marketing that a product is patented or patent pending.
[SPEAKER_02]: The idea that those false markings might deter someone from trying to create something new in that area.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, hey look, we have a...
[SPEAKER_06]: Patent for a DDR controller You can't make any dance games It's like they're calling dibs on everything Dibs on this, dibs on this And then they don't do anything with it And we're going to get into another story a little later on tonight About something that they're like Nope, nope, can't have it, it's ours And they're not going to do anything with it As much as a silly lawsuit as this sounds I'm glad someone's calling them on it Because now Activision is going to have to respond to this Has Activision made a response to this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, they haven't made a response yet, but at the same time, I don't see how they can, you know, patent a DDR pad when a DDR pad's already been made.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, you can't patent something that already exists.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't say, hey look, I invented the rock, now you all owe me money because you have rocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: well maybe they changed a couple little things well that's how it works patent law in this country is really weird really weird they change one or two things and claim it that they invented the genre we know how that works we'll see what comes forth of that I'm really looking forward to what Activision has to say about that remember when Activision was like the best game company in the world because they made games like Pitfall and Kaboom and Keystone Capers
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Bobby Kotick came along His days are numbered, I'm telling you His days are numbered because he looks Just lately in the past couple years He's come out and looked like a buffoon He's douchey mcdouche Nobody likes their CEO to be a douche
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how about something for free?
[SPEAKER_06]: Free games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, this is the way to do business.
[SPEAKER_06]: Activision, take notes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I'll tell you even better than that, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free Peggle.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Free Peggle.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a promotion going on right now where you can get Peggle Nights for yourself or a loved one, family member, or even an enemy if you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: All you have to do, you sign up for PopCap's newsletter by going to PopCap.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: by the way of course that means they're going to spam your email with all the newsletters but hey I don't know about you I have an email just set up for spam so to sign up for different websites bug me not so yeah there you go if you want there's also websites too with disposable email addresses that'll last for about 10 minutes enough time for them to send you back your confirmation code and then poof it's gone nice
[SPEAKER_06]: I always liked the idea of setting up my own domain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a friend that did this.
[SPEAKER_06]: He had his own domain that he set up for email addresses.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what he would do is when he would sign up for websites, he would create a new email account on his domain that was like, you know, whatever his name was.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll say John dot and then whatever the name of the site was that he was signing up for.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Question from our chat room, Kossin, and I apologize if I'm saying that wrong, but Kossin says, what's the disposable email site called?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember, but I saw it in 2600 Magazine a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there's a few of them, because Gold Anthro follows up with Dispostable.com, and Robocoon says Meltmail.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dispostable, I think, is the one I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Toagak just simply says there are lots of them, so there's a few of them out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wherever they can stick a banner ad, that's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're going to get into a segment here on the show that we love to do every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And during the Classic Game of the Week, we encourage DarkSakura to dive into the vault of classic gaming and find a game that she says, you know what, kids and adults too, you should be playing this game this week because it's a classic game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're not playing this, you're a buffoon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, a butt-foon.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what should the non-buffoons be playing this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: The game is Venture.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's from 1981.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, that's old.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's older than most of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was five when this game came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So since this is such an old game, there's not a lot of music, but let's play some... There's actually plenty of music in this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: With some ambient noises and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's a lot of music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there actual music?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just listen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one posted here is actually the ClicoVision version specifically because I played a crap ton of this on ClicoVision.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the game is where you're this little guy named Winky who looks like kind of a sperm.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, kind of like a... Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: This little blob with a bow and arrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he walks around this hall with these big things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to call them boogers when I was playing this as a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're just these tentacled hall monsters.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't kill them.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't stop them.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just completely invulnerable.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: With that, you actually have to go into these four or five rooms per area, and then get the treasure that's in each room while you're shooting and avoiding the little creatures inside them, and each one has their own theme.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you touch one of the monsters, it's called, you're getting carrioned.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and you've got different types of dungeons.
[SPEAKER_06]: You cannot touch a corpse because they're smelly.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'll get carrioned.
[SPEAKER_09]: In level one, you've got the wall room, the serpent room, the skeleton room, the goblin room.
[SPEAKER_09]: In level two, you have the two-headed room, the dragon room, the spider room, the troll room.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can tell you the dragon room was pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Level three, you have the genie room, the demon room, the cyclops room, and the bat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: but I freaking love this game this is kind of weird because I noticed especially for being such an old game like you have this screen that's like zoomed out showing all the different rooms and then you kind of like go into one room that's the dragon room by the way pain in the ass but now this is one of those games keep in mind I had a ClicoVision for a long time like I remember MTV coming out and me having a ClicoVision
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember those in a span of, you know, when I lived in the same house.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mother used to play a lot of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, my mom's favorite game was Space Fury.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because I didn't have a click of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Space Fury was kind of like an Asteroids kind of game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the type of stuff that I bet is coming to Microsoft's game room.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they talk about like a thousand classic games, you're going to see somebody digging into the back catalog of a lot of the old systems like ColecoVision and Atari.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could probably make this in Flash now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously, I probably know enough Flash now to make this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's clones out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but honestly, this was seriously one of my favorite games when I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I love the little dinky music.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd go around humming this one to myself when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you know, the games that I had at the time, I had like Mousetrap and Carnival.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this one got tons of play.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one and Turbo.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: And it actually had pretty good music for when it came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: For 81, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go, your classic video game of the week, Venture.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an arcade game too, but I guess DarkSakura was really referencing the ColecoVision one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was the arcade version really different?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ColecoVision one I think came out in...
[SPEAKER_06]: 82?
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's some from the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just noticed this related little video here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kind of want to take a peek and see how it's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, it's very similar looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Almost like it's done on the same hardware or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except there's a little bit more animation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, when you go in the rooms it zooms in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it had the same gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But honestly, for me, it was all about... I mean, the rooms are all the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just they zoom in and out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this was totally like my game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Venture Venture Venture Venture
[SPEAKER_06]: My timeline from back then is not that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me check.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, look that up real quick because I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there are some similarities of sorts between the two.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've seen comparisons to Berserk as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the Hallmonster is actually sort of like the evil Otto from Berserk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is the bouncing happy face, if anyone's actually played that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't find Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe actually spelling it right would be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, we're going to take a quick break here at Orange Lounge Radio, but fear not, we'll be back with more in tonight's Part B. So stick around, folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be right back in just a minute with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for those of you guys listening live tonight, we're going to take a quick music break here in studio and then we'll come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just going to do some potpourri here of some various, I think we'll do some Bomani songs tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be right back in just a moment here live at All Games Radio with Part B of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a chance for you to get up and stretch and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you in a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: But we played a remix by Mr. T Not the I pity the foo kind from the A-Team But Mr. T that did Bomani remixes back in the day From Poppin' Music 10 He did a remix of Goonies Are Good Enough From Goonies 2 Which was also in the movie, the Cyndi Lauper song Now I can play a clip So let me play a quick little clip For the benefit of the podcast listeners
[SPEAKER_06]: F the Haters
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like an experimental thing because this is television essentially that was made for the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a reality show and I know we've reported on this on the show before so I think most of our listeners are already aware.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's this reality show where the prize is to become a game tester for Sony Computer Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is the prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, but one thing they also don't say very well, also a $5,000 signing bonus.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there is a cash prize that goes with it as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there is at least just that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll need it to offset the wages.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I checked out the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if you guys don't already know, I am...
[SPEAKER_06]: Unapologetically a fan of reality game shows I don't necessarily mean all reality TV But I loved Survivor back in the day I wanted to apply for Survivor actually way back in the day But I didn't have a passport or something So I didn't do it I remember when they were casting for the first season of Survivor But I just love old game shows And I like the whole idea of a reality game show I've done fan games online I even like Project Runway And my new favorite reality game show is RuPaul's Drag Race It's the most amazing show on television right now
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: But of course, obviously, hearing about the tester, I'm a little bit apprehensive about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm like, okay, I'm a fan of reality shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a fan of video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to check this show out and give it a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I downloaded the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about a 22-minute show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's suitable for a 30-minute broadcast, basically with commercial breaks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I watched it, and it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you surprised to hear me say that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a ridiculous concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm not going to get past the fact that we all know, if you've kind of had a friend that works in the gaming industry, we all know the prize at the end of the day is ridiculous, but at least they throw a $5,000 signing bonus into it, so at least there's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: The look of it was really good and it was put together okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The editing was really tight because it's only a 22 minute show so you don't really get a lot of time to know the people but the editing was competent.
[SPEAKER_06]: The show was put together well enough
[SPEAKER_06]: The biggest flaw about the show is that, again, the contest is so ridiculous to begin with that basically the whole elimination and everything that they did was over this one minor challenge that they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: That the judges, who were two guys that worked for Sony and Hal Sparks, which I don't know why Hal Sparks is a judge and not the host.
[SPEAKER_06]: But whatever, I realize they need to have some type of celebrity draw I actually like Hal Sparks, I think he's great on The Soup back in the day when he was doing that stuff And then the I Love the 90s and all those shows I think he's funny, and of course queer as folk So I think he's a good talent to have on there Although as a judge, I think he would have been a better host Because they have some no-name girl doing the hosting And she's a generic reality show host, whatever
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: but here's the other thing I want to say about this because I know a lot of people are saying like what the hell Rob you actually like the show I don't know if I go so far as to say like I like it I'm going to set a season pass on my TiVo I just think it was a competent show and quite honestly it's better than about 90% of what's on G4 television here's my problem is I the way I looked at it is when I heard that they're doing a reality show where people are going to get to play you know games and stuff like that you know that are you know first looks at certain games I saw that as
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey look, it's a 22 minute long commercial for Sony Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: No thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing, I was talking about Shermie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shermie just crapped.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, did she?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was her review of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I mean, they played it up okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I was expecting a lot worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: The bar was very low.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I got a show that I would watch if I was flipping through TVs with nothing to watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I stop on G4 TV and the show's on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's better than most of the crap on that network right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That still just doesn't sound like enough to make me actually put any effort into watching TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't recommend this show for you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think you'd like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I watch three shows with any variety of regularity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Supernatural, Doctor Who, and...
[SPEAKER_09]: I love drag queens so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: On Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that they're going to have the Microsoft Game Room thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: To bring back Starcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, you've got to think, though, this is, sure, this show is a little eh, but it could be setting the stage for something even greater in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, it's kind of interesting that, wow, Sony put all this together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who else might deliver their show exclusively on PlayStation Network or Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah, I'm all for Starcade coming back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or some type of old school game show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like 1 vs. 100, but Starcade where you play the games that they're playing during the show and stuff like that That was a great idea To answer Tigerclaw, I wasn't impressed enough with the first episode of V to give it any more thought And for the listeners that don't know what DarkSakura's talking about Tigerclaw said V next month, you gotta watch V So there you go Oh, Shermie took a duty in the hallway, that's no good
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's what she thinks of the tester A shit with no effort I can't believe the cat just took a dump on the floor in the middle of the show Dump where dump should not be on the PlayStation Network Which cat, when forced to watch the tester, takes a crap first?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, to explain, Shermie is an old lady.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's up there now in cat ears.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she just didn't make it to the litter box or what?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: She will do it either when she decides to poop somewhere that is not her box.
[SPEAKER_09]: She will either do it on one of the bathroom rugs right in front of the bathroom or on one of the kitchen rugs.
[SPEAKER_09]: She does not do it so much on one of the kitchen rugs because I yelled at her.
[SPEAKER_09]: She at least does it where it can be easily cleaned up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think she's making a statement.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think she's like, Mom, you should quit your job and pay attention to me 24-7.
[SPEAKER_06]: She cats it all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's stop talking about poop and talk about game news.
[SPEAKER_02]: She says this show is good for me to poop on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clearly.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about some rapid fire news, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's actually this is kind of... Real quick, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get your tweets in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I mentioned it before in the show, but if you have some tweets for tonight's Twitter topics, get those in now, now, now.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Meat Boy is coming to Xbox Live Arcade, and actually before the WiiWare version, which I didn't even realize there was an Xbox Live Arcade version, and now it's coming out before.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's scheduled to be coming out this summer, and that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for those who don't know, Super Meat Boy is a platform action game starring a little character that's made out of meat.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you splat around the screen and that's all fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then of course there's going to be a tie-in game with the new movie Kick-Ass that is coming to PlayStation 3 and the iPhone and of course this game kind of reminds me a little bit of The Watchmen The End is Nigh which I think did a little bit better on the PS3 probably because the Blu-ray was bundled with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: when it came out in retail.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the PS3 game will have Facebook integration as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game looks just okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks just like a beat-em-up action game, just like the Watchmen one.
[SPEAKER_02]: The movie, though, on the other hand, is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of what happens when kids decide to become superheroes, but they don't have superpowers.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just fight crime.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Scott Nicholas Cage acting weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then on the PlayStation Network the version of Castle Crashers is getting a brand new edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extreme Volleyball Action is coming to the PlayStation 3 version of Castle Crashers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they're including a cooperative and competitive volleyball game with online or offline play and Magic Attacks apparently will be directly applied to your ball as well as there's going to be some leaderboards
[SPEAKER_02]: Spiky Moves, and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is coming from the Behemoth Development Blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Jamie's having the great Lysol race in the hallway right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good thing I can't smell anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, you're congested.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't smell a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just being polite.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't want to sit here and go, Jamie, your house smells like poop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, no, I just smelled it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fucking Shermie.
[SPEAKER_09]: She just needs a...
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, I don't know, maybe all this talk about the tester made Jamie crap her pants.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to be rude.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it sure makes shit in the hall.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least go in the tub.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a reference to last week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You see what I did there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got some quick stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I did check out this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't mention it during my gaming week, but this is something I did check out this week, and that was Missile Command.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a brand new version of Missile Command from Atari.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's free to play, and it's on the web, and it's like a co-op.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a multiplayer thing by developer OMGPOP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Atari.com slash Missile Command It's free, can't complain about free
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not surprised 505 Games is the publisher I think
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, yeah, they are the publisher.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's developing it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Big Head Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did Chime on the Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was recent.
[SPEAKER_06]: No word as to what the game is at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: How would you make a game out of grease?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a karaoke game?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, hey, look, we bought the rights to something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, let's make a game out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not them, but other companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll buy rights for...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like stupid shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the smile.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know like the smiley face shirts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Smiley?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a company that bought the rights for that and made a game out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one remembers it because it sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember Faceball 2000 that had the big smileys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a nice day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, but that game was actually kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, for example...
[SPEAKER_02]: The Jelly Belly, they have like a Jelly Belly game because they licensed that because the license was really cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jelly Bellys are yummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or M&M's, they made some M&M games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, there was like an M&M racing game that was pretty terrible, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, Yo Noid was cool, but that was way back in the 80s when people knew what the hell the Noid was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't the Noid supposed to be making a comeback?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, how about a computer game everybody wants to play?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's tons and tons of people who want to play this.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarCraft 2, and of course the beta's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this is pretty happy stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are, for a pre-order bonus for Super Street Fighter 4, there's a classic costume pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so they are for Blanka, Guile, Gen, Feilong, and Dhalsim.
[SPEAKER_09]: For Feilong, he gets a kind of a Kato costume.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Feilong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blanka gets Dansgi costume.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this goes back to Street Fighter Alpha 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you ever beat Street Fighter Alpha 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I ever played Street Fighter Alpha 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of during that period when I wasn't playing a lot of games heavy.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the endings, Dan and Blanka are just hanging out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan can understand all of Blanka's grunts.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he's like, I see you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go out and play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rolling and rolling.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it has the two of them rolling across the screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where I get the rolling and rolling from.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, he's wearing Dansky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they like gay lovers or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just BFFs.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're BFFs.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Jay and Silent Bob.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Gen has a shirtless... Heterosexual life partners.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gen is shirtless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guile is wearing a ballistic vest.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's just all kinds of, you know, hardcore ops guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Dhalsim is wearing a, I guess, just more traditional dress for India.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very snazzy and lousy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He looks like... Who was that fighter in Mike Tyson's Punch-Out where the little ruby in his turban would flash and that's how you knew he was about to throw a punch?
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that guy's name in Mike Tyson's Punch-Out?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what Dhalsim looks like right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to link the picture in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody in chat will yell it out There's a tiger or something Shaoran in chat by the way says bromance would be the term for what Dan and Blanca have going on there Now I have an image of Dan saying snooch to the nooch You know there's actually it's funny the term bromance there actually is a term called romantic friendship Have you ever heard of that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have yeah I thought that was funny
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Tetsuya says Great Tiger was the name of that fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I love having a live audience because when I don't know the answer to something I'll just go chat help and they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Actdefta is wondering if they're starting a bad bromance.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I freaking have to listen to that song now after me really loathing Lady whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You cannot resist the power of Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't really like any of her other stuff, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just that one I actually kind of like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody's perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll come around.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: She'll eventually become perfect like me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twitter topic time, www.twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show us your tweets every week and we'll read some of our favorites here on the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, we can't read everything, but there's some really good questions tonight, so I want to get to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nutman wants to know if the podcast will be uploaded tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty please.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should be.
[SPEAKER_06]: There shouldn't be a delay at all this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I got to say, I had last week show up Monday night, but I should...
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been getting pretty good this year about getting this show up within 24 hours, so I'm going to try and continue that trend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Knock on wood.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft links us to a story that Harmonix might not actually be working on Rock Band 3 right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: There may actually be something else going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess this is a news story he's linked us to from rockbandaid.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, let's see, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Twitter from some guy, I guess, at Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix, the creators of the Rock Band video game, is planning on using one of my tracks for their demo projects.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, this is some other guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess Harmonix recently licensed hip-hop and dance songs, kind of putting it all together.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so now maybe there might be a new frequency or amplitude game is kind of the rumor that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which would make a lot of sense, you know, Frequency and Amplitude kind of came out when not a lot of people knew who Harmonix was And they were more experimental games, but they were great games And I think if they are gonna, you know, now that more people know what Rock Band is That they're gonna kind of come out with a, I don't know, what would they call a game around dance music and stuff That's in that Frequency, Amplitude vein, I don't know Frequency?
[SPEAKER_06]: Frequency 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: Frequitude?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows Applency?
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Hero?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh wait, no
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Salvax7 sends us a variety of tweets here around one subject.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me read these.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little longer than 140 characters, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I like the question here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Salvax7 on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, I have an interesting question for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Historically, which generation of gaming would you classify as the most contrib... It got cut off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming contributive to society's development.
[SPEAKER_06]: Regarding to the social interaction, the fun element, escape from one's reality, and moral values.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's complex, but if you could answer it, I would appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a nice one.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_06]: What generation of gaming would classify as the most contributive to society's development?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a tough question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Development of what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just the development of society.
[SPEAKER_06]: As in, and he goes on to specify, as in the social interaction, the fun element, the escape from one's reality and moral values.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pong.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the way back to old school pong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where would we be?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, where would the industry be if someone didn't invent pong?
[SPEAKER_06]: The zeroth generation?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd say like the arcade age or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe even like just the, not necessarily the 8-bit generation, but like, you know, even before that, probably the 4-bit generation, you know, the Atari, Coleco, Odyssey, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I think in gaming it'd be the day that we got on the radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have two answers for this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say I think it's the fourth generation of gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one that involved the NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: When the Nintendo Entertainment System first came to America because it came out at a time when video games were pretty much declared dead and dying and nobody was interested in video games anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, after the great video game crash of 84, 83, whatever you want to pay it as.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry I'm not from your country
[SPEAKER_06]: even people that don't do nerdy gaming podcasts every week or listen to them they know who Mario and Luigi are you know those characters I think it was really the first generation to create a character I don't think everybody on the street knows who Pitfall Harry or maybe some of the well maybe Pac-Man I mean that came from the generation before but I think I don't know
[SPEAKER_06]: Something about really bringing it into the homes and so forth with these really memorable characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was really the generation that defined current gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then again, Pac-Man did have a song written about him and Mario really didn't other than do the Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then my other answer to the question would be the current one.
[SPEAKER_06]: The current generation of gaming, I think, is huge to society because for a variety of reasons.
[SPEAKER_06]: A, the Wii has... As much as we love to hate on it for what it is sometimes here on this show, there's no denying that it has penetrated society in a way that most video game systems have not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Sports is like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Such a typical video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not even a video game to a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Sports is an activity.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's an activity simulation.
[SPEAKER_06]: People don't say, let's come over and play video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say, let's come over and play Wii Sports or the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just so interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then on the other hand, you have Xbox Live really kind of, in a way, almost killing arcades because people are able to communicate over the internet and talk while they're playing games and develop this whole community.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then you know some somewhat the PlayStation 3 in this as well but then now that video games are not just about video games but they're entertainment boxes there are these you know sets in our living room that do everything that now that they're they're getting their own TV shows for heaven's sakes I mean I think this current one is is shaping things up in in a huge way that's going to continue certainly it's they're setting it up to have a longer lifespan than the generations before it so we'll see
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind the networking side of it and the web play side of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember we had the X-Link back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had, well in Japan they had Satellaview.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not a new concept, it's a perfected concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's now, it's penetrating.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me, has penetrated the marketplace and had its effect on society that Sateleview didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody remembers Sateleview.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was a novel concept then is, and actually I didn't even have to say, one of the biggest games that came out that really brought that on was Phantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, you know, and I'm really trying to take that question as literal as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the biggest impact on society?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you ask, what's my favorite?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the Super Nintendo was my favorite console in that whole generation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo versus Sega and TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that was like right when I was in high school and kind of growing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was my favorite generation.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think it necessarily had the biggest impact on society.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was more of a bridge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games were still a niche thing back then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Master System, and Genesis
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an evolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's why I want to go back very far back to pinball, Rob, to pinball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some comments from our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, live on this Sunday night as we tape at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shaoran says, World of Warcraft just standardized both the best and worst of MMO tropes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, it's not necessarily about inventing a concept, it's about perfecting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think is an important point that was brought up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that was a great question.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to give an honorary gold star to Salvax.
[SPEAKER_06]: He gets a Twitter gold star.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we've given any of those out, but that was one of my favorite Twitter questions we've gotten ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So gold star for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Robocoon wants to clue us in on a Steam UI update.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a beta thing that you can opt into, and that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Steam could use a little bit of a facelift.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't read this story or familiarize myself with it in advance, but apparently you can take part in the beta by going into Steam's website and the settings link and then selecting the 2010 UI update under beta participation.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm looking at these screenshots and I gotta say one thing that does kind of worry me is I'm noticing in one of these screenshots there's like a list that shows community activity and it shows what games your friends are buying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I want that data out there and published.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want my friends knowing that I just bought the Amazing Unicorn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping there's a way to suppress that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Imagine fairies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there is a way to suppress that.
[SPEAKER_06]: but there is there's some unicorn game that's out there on Steam and my boyfriend's been tempting me with this saying you know you want this game you know you want this game when obviously it looks like such crap but it's kind of one of those things like I want to like buy it for you as a gift so you're obligated to play it and then you have to talk about it on next week's OLR during How Was Your Gaming Week like I think we actually had that conversation are you pulling it up right now or what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, I'm going on my Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look for the Unicorn Gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to get a text message in a minute that'll tell me what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: What magical unicorn game?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something about magical unicorns.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's an awesome... Okay, not even... Oh, God, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Choo-choo, tangent train, pulling to the station.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, this isn't a tangent train.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually... There's another magical unicorn game that's on... No, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I set a commercial for this because I watch Cartoon Network at Adult Swim sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is still worth sharing, so thank you for the tweet because now it's penetrated like Yahoo and it's starting to get onto the mainstream sites about this copy protection.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Robot Unicorn Attack is what the game's called.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Secret of the Magic Crystals, Rob, is the one that you're looking for.
[SPEAKER_06]: is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: it's also gone down to $6.99 oh wow that's a bargain hold on I just got a text message hold on I'm firing up my phone and the screenshot where you do crafting with a magic material called anus that's right one of the screenshots there's a magical crafting I don't know if it deleted his first text where he told me the name of the game but yeah that's the game what is that again?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I just found the name.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Secret of the Magic Crystals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a game about unicorns, and in one of those screens, if you look at one of those screenshots, okay, look, there, there.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a crafting material on that screen called anus.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you look at it, one of the, like you have to collect anus, but it's A-E-N-U-S.
[SPEAKER_09]: A-E-N-U-S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pink.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to collect all the pink anus you can.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know you want that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Add to cart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reverse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you buying the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, I'm buying it for seven bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations, Alan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I will have a full review of the gay unicorn game, complete with anus and horn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let us know how the anus crafting goes a little later.
[SPEAKER_06]: This might need to be our next cause here on the show that we yell and scream for everybody to tweet and Facebook about is to get this on the consoles because I want some pink anus on my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game apparently, the Robot Unicorn Attack or whatever, has a really interesting song that plays in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I haven't played it yet, but on the commercial it sounded funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: it's uh the chat room is uh it's erasure always oh yeah that was it yeah because i in fact i actually made a live journal post on this like a while back no i posted it on twitter hold on here's here's a little bit just so just so you have something to reference here loki this is the actual feel oh yeah yeah that's it
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually one of my favorite Erasure songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Erasure is a great synth-bop band.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this one too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you play this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: To unicorns?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, to unicorns running and farting rainbows.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here we go, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, Loki's fired this up in studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this a Flash game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is... Oh my god, your unicorn was all twisted in a big pile up in the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you post this link in chat, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you post this link in chat?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe put it on the Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you post it to the Twitter that we're talking about it on the show right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know the password and all that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please post that to the Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I just downloaded a song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta sleep eventually, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly, a tweet from Alex P. Carson wanting us to give a shout out to Alex Nicole.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's her first time listening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shout out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shout out!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope she didn't turn it off after the farting rainbows chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope we didn't scare her off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, Amazed Shitsuma in chat, yes he changed his name, Amazed Shitsuma says Orange Lounge Unicornio is the new name of the show apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who doesn't love unicorns?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like evil people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I hate to interrupt you because I know you're running to the Twitter right now to post, but Loki can you give us some more gaming news here on OLRB.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_02]: and those of course have to do I guess with Abyssia and it's going to have a let's see here Vision of Abyssia I guess will come out during the summer with the other two Scars of Abyssia and Heroes of Abyssia coming soon after that and each new area can be purchased for $10 on the PlayOnlineViewer
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised that there's still expansions coming out to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really sure what these new ballerinas are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is something that was added way after I left.
[SPEAKER_11]: I totally realized that I never finished my other Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not my Twitter topic, so rapid fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then we'll come back to it in a moment here.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But quickly, I wanted to say about Final Fantasy XI and its developments and what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: This should kind of squelch those rumors that Final Fantasy XI is shutting down in a couple months to make room for XIV, which I always thought was a little bit ridiculous, how fast that spread like wildfire.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this, I'm sure, is in part to shut up those rumors that XI is still being supported.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not going to fit in there, Shermie.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's Shermie trying to... Oh, Shermie's trying to... She's trying to poop on the mixing board.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not working.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's trying.
[SPEAKER_06]: End the show, end the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a little more for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Final Fantasy XIV will be going into closed beta soon, actually, starting March 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I believe that they did have...
[SPEAKER_02]: The VanaFest, I guess, the 2010 website, which was some, they had some news, I guess, about Final Fantasy XI as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: But on the PlanetLine website, there's also interesting news, I guess, that the betas will start on March 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I've already signed up for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say I've already signed up for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I signed up for it too, but my email box was empty.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about yours, but I saw that story and then I cried.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't got anything yet either.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still time, so maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's one of those things where I won't be in the first wave, but maybe a later wave.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be hopeful.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it gives me time to finish playing XIII because seriously, the beta for XIV is coming out two days after XIII.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two days between Final Fantasy titles in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and here's something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think about it, if it's going into the beta now, maybe those May release dates are a little bit more accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about May, but I bet the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like Final Fantasy XIV will be out by the end of the year, and that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was not expecting it that soon, especially with XIII having taken as long as it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, pleasant surprise, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go over to Dark Sakura and whatever stories we skipped over because of all our discussions on unicorns.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unicorn farting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully it'll leak online just like BlazBlue did.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then there's an online Digimon battle game that's supposed to be coming out in the US that's a version of the Korean Digimon RPG, which I actually think I'll freaking play that because I love Digimon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Digimon Zero 2
[SPEAKER_09]: and um well a couple of movies and I have um like the first two volumes of it on of the Japanese version on DVD someone I used to date a long time ago just went on a couple dates with made me watch the Digimon movie I remember that it's you should watch the Japanese one that's why it didn't last you should watch the Japanese one it's actually really good is it
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I saw the English one
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: so they reach this little settlement well now Activision owns it because of all the acquisitions that go on and so forth and Activision has demanded that this game stop completely they're not honoring the old agreement they have demanded that this cease and desist immediately Phoenix Online has been doing this game since 2002 and then yeah so Activision has basically said even though they don't have plans on doing a sequel themselves by the way King's Quest is pretty much dead
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they should release it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they don't want to get sued.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I can't say I necessarily blame them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Change the name and release it for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, we actually, I believe we had one of the developers on the show many, many years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you'd have to go back to old, like the To Go podcast from 2005, 2006 to find this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I want to say we had the guy on the show because I remember going to some virtual press conference online thing about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and we also hosted a mirror of one of the early betas for the game I believe when it was still called King's Quest I think one of the big things they were touting if I remember right again this is like four or five years ago so please my memory is a little shoddy was that Roberta Williams actually knew of the project and although she couldn't officially give it her blessing she kind of gave it a wink and a nod you know what I mean
[SPEAKER_06]: We hosted the beta for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't believe it went anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe it's still on our website at orangelaunchradio.com slash TSL.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't get a letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, do you want to see what this is all about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's kind of a douchey thing for Activision to do when they know they're not I realize they're in their rights to do it just like when Nintendo shut down the movie project the Zelda movie, we talked about this a couple months ago they were in their rights to do it but with Activision just having bought this saying they're not going to do anything with it but then putting the plug on this when they already stripped anything that was King's Quest related out of it that's just douchey Activision gets our douche of the week award there you go
[SPEAKER_06]: so I think that's unfortunate and you know my thought is I'm kind of with Jamie I say release it anyway as a torrent but if you're really afraid of getting the pantsuit off of you seriously go back change the name change some of the text change the characters nobody's gonna freaking know no Activision is not gonna seek it out that hardcore if you go in and change the information so it's hard to detect that it once was the silver lining I bet you you'll have it
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm curious to see if the game gets leaked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once it hits the internet, there is no going back.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what you have for us up next?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, in other news, we have a game called Voice Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Square Enix has filed a trademark for it in Europe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And maybe it could be a Final Fantasy vocal CD?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: But it could be something cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully it will be cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it'll be like a SingStar Voice Fantasy or something, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it could be a karaoke-controlled Final Fantasy 1, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe one that you have to sing to progress your game or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to fight!
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to cast holy!
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe you have to sing accurately to progress.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you still playing the fucking Unicorn game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amaze Shitsuma in chat says, Douche of the Week award, so Shermie will poop on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we give a big sure me poop award to the folks at Activision this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: The next time she takes a shit on the floor, I'll take a picture of it so we can just send it to whoever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, put down the game and read some news for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is not a big surprise because I don't think it's really taken off as far as I'm aware.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently advertisers are ignoring PlayStation Home, but they are interested in the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently a report coming from Brand Week saying that they're opting to pursue opportunities in Xbox Live instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently ad agency, looks like a publicist,
[SPEAKER_02]: Dineo, John Rafferty, they told the website for the moment one it felt kind of clunky and once you got through that there wasn't much there regarding I guess the robotic nature of PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think it kind of makes sense because there's a lot of places to advertise in PlayStation Home but if you're like me, you don't use PlayStation Home so you're not seeing those ads so it makes more sense to put it on like say banner ads that are on the PlayStation Network or banner ads on the Xbox Live Marketplace because you're seeing those as you're going browsing for other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you hit the nail on the head.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no reason to go into PlayStation Home except when they launch something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's usually you go in there once and you go, oh, huh, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like that, remember that salt that was on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Went there once.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went in there a couple times and played it and got some of the little things and I was like, okay, done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really want to pay for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a souped up version of a game I played on my 386 computer back in 1993.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, something that a lot of people are into is the idea of Nintendo starting over with a brand new Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it came out at the Nintendo Media Summit thanks to a GameSpot cornering Cammy Dunaway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, they say that there's not going to be a Wii successor anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently they're kind of looking for what happened with the PS2 is that they want to kind of re-emulate the fact that they're on top for years and years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cammy Dunaway was quoted in the GameSpot interview saying, quote, even though our install base is at this point 5 million households larger than the PS2 install base was at the same point in the life cycle, it still has a lot of room to grow.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you think PS2, there's been about 50 million sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii, close to 28 million sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: so it says to me there's still a big audience out there that we can access with the Wii so basically we still have sold shit loads of these systems so why would we start over with something new just because the core gamers are mad the soccer moms are happy so F you it's raining money at my world ha ha ha
[SPEAKER_06]: so don't expect a new Wii to be announced at E3 this year but I think in great Nintendo fashion their way around this would be releasing the Wii HD or something along those lines where it's not necessarily a whole new system but it's a Wii Plus like the DS Lite or something like that that's what I could see Nintendo doing and then saying well it's still a Wii yeah I don't know we'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow, we're going to get into that section of the show where we interact with your emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the mailbag segment here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week, DarkSakura opens up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com That's all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: M-A-I-L-B-A-G at OrangeLoungeRadio.com If you have an email you want DarkSakura to read.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks like a lot of people took the opportunity this week, didn't they, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, get to reading.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, OLR Kardashians.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just discovered that I could walk from where I live to Valve's headquarters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's a GameWorks in downtown Seattle that has BlazBlue, Street Fighter 4, Totsunoko vs. Capcom, King of Fighters 1 million, and a few pinball thingies.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you ever are up there for PAX, I recommend stopping by.
[SPEAKER_06]: We went there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did stop by.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had that whole room of Sega cranes, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I played a few.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, since I'm entering high school, I was wondering if I should learn Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it hard?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would kind of want to know what my important future is telling me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Typed with minor precision at 1240 AM, Austin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to let you know, Japanese is not an easy language.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, because honestly I think the biggest difficulty in Japanese is the grammar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily the vocabulary, but the grammar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little convoluted.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a Japanese major for a little while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I know a few sites that will give you beginner lessons.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can find them for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, I think one is called iLearn or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, just try a couple of those little online sites and see what you think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, it really is kind of a convoluted...
[SPEAKER_06]: in comparison to English it really depends on what industry you want to get into when you get older and maybe you're too young to know that now if you're just kind of like now going into high school which you're probably too young to listen to this show actually also depending on where you live because when I lived in Alabama it was good for me to know French
[SPEAKER_06]: And here in California, it's really good to know Spanish.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really good to know it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's a lot of jobs out there where they really want bilingual people that speak Spanish.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you might want to think about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, is Japanese really practical?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if you want to get into an industry that has to do with technology and possibly relocating to Japan or working closely with Japanese business or finances.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or going into the JET program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, any of that, then yeah, Japanese is going to be a practical language to learn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, you might be a little young to really know what you want to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was 15, I hadn't a clue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I did have a clue.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to be a game show host, but that didn't quite pan out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ended up changing my mind when I was like,
[SPEAKER_06]: I changed my major 8 times so don't even worry about it
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but I agree with Akuma JP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do it while you're young.
[SPEAKER_06]: Learn a new language because it's much harder when you're older.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I tried to learn a second language in high school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried to learn Spanish.
[SPEAKER_06]: And unfortunately, this is going to sound terrible because I am a teacher of sorts even though I teach in a corporate environment as my day job.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I think teachers do great things but I had a Spanish teacher that was so terrible she actually ruined Spanish for me like I was not able to learn a language because this lady was so bad thankfully she's not teaching anymore she didn't she didn't keep teaching very long but it's unfortunate that that one person kind of screwed it up you know
[SPEAKER_09]: DDoS servers
[SPEAKER_09]: It seems to me like that would be the perfect target for a DDOS attack to cause maximum damage.
[SPEAKER_09]: A normal DDOS would only disrupt traffic, but an attack against Ubisoft servers would cause everyone's games to shut off and swamp their phone line.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was wondering what you guys thought about this problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a side question, I wanted to know what you guys thought about having a homebrew, no piracy, and tech-themed show on all games co-hosted by me and Jaded.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, awesome show on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Togek DDOS DDOS DDOS DDOS
[SPEAKER_06]: New Blood, Fresh Meat
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I mean, I know they're open to having more ideas, and I know one thing that they don't want is they really don't want more general video game discussion shows, because they already have a lot of them, including us, admittedly, although we've been doing what we do a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think the idea of a niche...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know of a show like that on all games unless I'm really behind on who's on the network right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think that's always a good thing if you think of an idea for a show that no one's done yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey OLR Crew, AZHP here again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was listening live to your show on Sunday, though I wasn't in chat because I was putting together IKEA furniture at the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, when I heard you all report on the Ubisoft DRM that requires you to be on the internet constantly in order to play Assassin's Creed 2, my first thought was, are Ubisoft insane?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do they want people to pirate their game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because honestly, once it's cracked, the pirate versions will actually be better than a retail copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: someone obviously dropped the ball here and is completely out of touch with gamers I was going to buy Assassin's Creed 2 but after hearing about this I don't think I will anymore now I don't think I'm going to pirate it since I'm not really interested in the game but doesn't it seem like Ubisoft is actually encouraging people to pirate the game so they won't have to deal with that DRM yours truly is HP I just think they're stupid I really have no comment I agree with your email 100% I really have nothing else to say I think what you say is absolutely valid it's just encouraging piracy
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, next email It's kind of a cool email Hey OLR gang, a quick question here I'm a techie very much like yourselves and I have a few electronics in the house However, it's starting to become a problem as I have a few wires just dangling and crossing under my gaming desk My Wii, Xbox 360, computer setup all share the same space Do you have any personal home solutions or recommendations for organizing an otherwise jungle of wires as well as saving me the time and money in the long run eliminating a potential fire hazard Randy from Texas I do, I have a lot of suggestions because we do them
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get a switch box, first of all, for your systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can also, what we do in the studio is we have zip ties.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although we don't really use them anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we have zip ties for our cables for our mics and for the plugs and various hookups.
[SPEAKER_09]: That way we can minimize what's there to trip over.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can also get, I believe you can get them at Fry's or any electronic store or computer store or just in general.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can actually buy them online.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: They look like the plastic ring binders that go on presentation books and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you bind your cords together and wrap them around your cords and then it leaves them as a long trail.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can also duct tape them to the floor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can use electrical tape to bind them together too.
[SPEAKER_09]: My computer actually, when we put in my card, my new graphics card, we actually just...
[SPEAKER_09]: Electrical taped all the bonus wires together.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's lots of stuff that you can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And really, you can get almost any of these things really cheap.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can buy twist ties.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get leftover twist ties.
[SPEAKER_06]: These little zippy ties we use in the studio or at the 99 cent store, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought a pack of eight of them for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just have to look around.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really, the thing that you want to do is find something that's going to be non-flammable, something that can bind them together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, if you want something that's going to hold them securely, your best bet, get a switch box or if you have multiple hookups to your TV, I would get electrical tape and bind the ones to each specific system together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, if you leave them at the right length for your binding, you can, if you need to transport them, just unplug them and move them easily.
[SPEAKER_06]: and labels go a long freaking way even though you might be thinking oh what a pain in the butt or you know they're so silly if you just like label your wires at both ends oh my god you will be so happy later if you ever have to move if you use the electrical tape method just get a sharpie right on the electrical tape yeah PS3 you know it's very easy
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you've seen the box of cables that we have, Rob, obviously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where it's like you sort of have to look at the end and guess what it is and be afraid if you happen to find an N64 or a Super Nintendo thing because they use the same ones, practically.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or if you happen to accidentally hook up your Japanese PlayStation 2 adapter and then realize it won't fit in your US one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just going off because...
[SPEAKER_09]: it really does help of course we have big bins now in the vault where we keep all of that and don't know which one's which tape
[SPEAKER_09]: Also for speaker cables.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get these plastic pieces.
[SPEAKER_09]: For example, we have our surround sound wired.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we didn't wire it under the floor or anything yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is something I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't done it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can get these plastic strips that you can adhere to the floor.
[SPEAKER_09]: They use them in office buildings.
[SPEAKER_09]: To keep you from tripping over wires that happen to be spread for your speakers and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good suggestions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can find us anywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just make sure that you get something that's, you know, electronic safe and fire safe.
[SPEAKER_06]: More emails?
[SPEAKER_09]: One more.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, long email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Long email is long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't stop playing this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're still playing the Magic Unicorn game, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to have erasure stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be having nightmares about erasure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello there, OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is G-Ditz writing in.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm the Swedish dude who called a few shows ago and talked about DRM and seeing as exams are closing in, I can't really spare the time to attend the next live show, so I figured I'd answer the call for European to write about it, the high piracy rate over here, and what might be the cause of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a lot of insight on how game releases or pricing works in Italy, where the highest rate of piracy occurred according to the study presented in last week's show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do, however, live in Sweden, where the famous Pirate Bay BitTorrent site was founded, and where piracy is also frequent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now there are quite a few factors as to why I have many times been tempted to pirate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Release.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the biggest factors is for me whether or not I can purchase a product legally.
[SPEAKER_09]: When it comes to anime, for example, there usually isn't a retailer around here to supply them, and if there is, it's all dubbed or subbed in Swedish, which isn't how I like my anime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Agreed, I hate most English dubs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like watching them in Japanese with subtitles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another annoying thing is that the delay between US release and the European one, it's usually a week or just a few days, but once in a while a game takes almost a full year to get over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: One example is Rock Band 2 with the instrument bundle.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the time of its release, I didn't have any rhythm hardware for my PS3 and was stuck with a hard decision.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: As a side effect of this, I now despise Harmonix a bit for not being able to ship hardware in a reasonable amount of time.
[SPEAKER_09]: DRM DRM isn't different for us Europeans but it's still something to consider when buying a product even more if you want to lend it to a friend install it several times or just be able to play it without an internet connection the worst DRM I have to deal with on a daily basis is a CAD computer aided design program used for making mechanical parts and design requires not only a constant online connection but also requires said connection to go through the school network
[SPEAKER_09]: We're using AutoCAD?
[SPEAKER_09]: This means I have to VPN to the school network at all times when using said software.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't even imagine how such extreme restrictions would urge people to buy it when a pirated copy would mean a lot less hassle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cost.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is one of the biggest hurdles for many people, myself included, and it goes a bit beyond what Americans have to go through.
[SPEAKER_09]: From what I gather, a new retail game over in the US costs about $60, which would be the equivalent of $450 Swedish kronor.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, we have a value-added tax for each and every item we purchase in stores, where the rate for any item can be 612 or even 25% added to the price.
[SPEAKER_09]: In short, a video game costs a Swedish person 600 kronors, which is the equivalent of $80.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if I know the tax goes to education, government funding, and healthcare, it still leaves a big hole in my wallet every time I buy a video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Summary.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hopefully this letter gave you guys a better image of what gaming and the gamer lifestyle is like across the sea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if we sometimes get treated as less important market, we still like to support our favorite developers and actually pay for games we enjoy.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have any more questions, I'd be happy to answer them when I get the time, but for now I have to get back to studying.
[SPEAKER_09]: GDits out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck with your exams, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, good email.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a little sad, though, that it didn't come from one of the countries that was really high on the list, because I don't recall Sweden being in the top ten.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I do appreciate Sweden very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Without them, we would not have ABBA.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good email, otherwise, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's always good to hear different perspectives from around the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found the other email, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_09]: From our buddy, Robaba.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I haven't heard from him in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope he's doing well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure the trailers for Super Mario Galaxy 2 will be plentiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I noticed that the little starbursts don't say you're Mr. Gay anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now they say you're my gay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's almost sweet in its own way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Rob-a-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and yeah, also we got a random voice V-text, even though we've covered this, I'll go ahead and say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: From, um, I don't want to say the person's name, I'll just say from Sumiragawa-san.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three new characters have been announced for Super Street Fighter 4, Ibuki, Makoto, and Deadly.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, we've covered it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if that was sent during the show last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I still wanted to read it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was short, and why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: We like to read our emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hopefully we'll get some more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meantime, let's do our FUs of the week, because good lord, we have no shortage of angst this week after all these Activision stories we're hearing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think we all know who's getting this dedication tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you a hint, his name is Bobby and I'm not talking about the always awesome Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, well, okay, fuck Activision, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, fuck Shermie's poop for sticking up the house.
[SPEAKER_09]: I seriously have no idea what the hell is up with my damn cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's only started doing this in the last month.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just pooping.
[SPEAKER_09]: Randomly.
[SPEAKER_09]: She'll use her box, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then she'll be like, Oh, by the way, Mom, I have left you a little brown present in front of the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um... F you to stomach problems that kept me from going to the Purim spiel last night.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was looking forward to my first Purim, but I hurt myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe another time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're sorry, but our Purin is in another castle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to people that find it necessary to stop their car a good four or five car lengths behind the other car that's in front of them, preventing you from going around them because they're douchebags.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only that, they kind of drive slow or take turns really wide or take turns really slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So F you to bad drivers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really have a lot of FUs, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm relatively in a good mood, all things considered, but FU to moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just been the one thing that's been on my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will be so happy that next week it will be over and we can get on to other things like Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_01]: One more, one more.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you don't have to play the music.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now I gotta go.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't have to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I don't have to play the music.
[SPEAKER_01]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are you giving an FU to your favorite game or one of them?
[SPEAKER_08]: because it's not loading.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's because of my mod.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mentioned it in part A. A couple more news stories for you guys and then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brace yourselves, it's always an adventure where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Monster Hunter Tri is coming out April 20th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will also be available in a bundle with the Classic Controller Pro.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Classic Controller with the extra little grips on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That bundle will be available for $60 whereas the game will be just $49.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop will be offering demo discs starting March 8th for those who pre-order and also those who pre-order will get themselves a card for 500 Wii Points, so basically $5 back.
[SPEAKER_02]: but not only that the online play will actually be free to play as opposed to what's in Japan where you actually have to pay to play the game so it'll actually be free to play online which I'm sure is very happy news for fans of the Monster Hunter series I don't know it's neat looking that's happy news for anybody free is awesome no one likes to pay for stuff anyways
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes you have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how society works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn commerce.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, one more story for you guys and then we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio and that has to do with the teaser trailer that was released this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a new teaser trailer that just hit the internet for Pac-Man Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it looks like that early trademark that was discovered is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a new Pac-Man game coming out and it's called Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Outside of that, what else is this game about?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know because this is probably the worst teaser trailer I've ever seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 13 seconds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's the Namco logo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then... Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that noise.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's the logo.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sneak peek at Amusement Expo 2010.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the whole teaser right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't tease anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: We already kind of knew about the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a tease.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to tease you and let you think that we've given you a teaser.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, tease.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can see at least on the logo that there are four different colored Pac-Mans There's a yellow, a red, a pink, and a blue Kind of like the ghosts in a weird way Although I believe one of the ghosts is orange, not yellow, but still It's chasing a ghost But they are chasing a ghost So maybe it's some type of multiplayer Pac-Man CE That seems to be the popular thought as to what this is all about Plus they are showing this at the Amusement Expo 2010 So the thought is, hmm, arcade game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Arcade Games
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey Rob, this is Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey Footy Monster, how are you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh man, I tell you it's been a couple of days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now for those that don't know, Footy Monster is one of our listeners who lives quite a distance away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where do you live, Footy Monster, for those new to the show?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm in Chile right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's the big place that's on the news lately because of an earthquake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we've heard about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And where exactly in Chile are you?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm actually in Santiago, like in one of the major cities that was hit by it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, but you're calling into the show, so your internet's working.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, is everything cool?
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, my internet was working before my phone worked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't understand how that happened.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first thing I could do to tell like my mother in Argentina and like my friends and stuff that I was okay was through Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was the weirdest thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh, this kind of leads into that whole talk we were having about social networking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_11]: But didn't I say that there are legitimate reasons and then there's just the crap?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but it's still interesting in this context.
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly, in that context, the first click I did was to hit submit to say I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Ranma's idea that I call in to let people know in case they hadn't heard but
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's good to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you still doing a regular show?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you used to do the role-playing show, but I think you guys put that on hold, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, well, I moved here to Chile last year, and I had to put it on hold because of work and not knowing my schedule and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I didn't put it on hold myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: I gave the show, like the reins of it, to one of the co-hosts, and he decided to put it on hold indefinitely.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, I've been, like, about two weeks ago I was guesting on Video Game News Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, I was there if you care to listen to my musings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are those the guys in Cleveland?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or am I mixing my shows up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're the other guys that have been doing a show forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I think they've been on about as long as we have.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they've been doing this show as long as you guys have.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a very different show than us.
[SPEAKER_06]: You must have been calling in to talk about Halo 3 or some of the shooter games, or the Call of Duty type stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's more the type of stuff they get into, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: The best thing that they do is when they talk about nothing that's related to video games, honestly.
[SPEAKER_13]: They just go on rants about how one of them is a trucker, the other one is, you know, out of a job, and it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: How interesting that that would be the interesting part of their show, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly, they actually had a spin-off.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have a spin-off show that they called Midwest Wasteland, I believe the name, and that's all they talk about.
[SPEAKER_13]: They just said, you know what, we're going to scrap the video game part of it and just go with what people actually like.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's interesting you bring up spinoff shows, because, you know, Jamie was doing a comic podcast for a while, and I know she had to put that on hold, but there might be other spinoff shows in the works.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never know what might be coming, so stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, yeah, you know, I just wanted to call in about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't get heard more than, you know, Scraps, Bruces, that kind of thing from...
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, moving debris and stuff because one of our walls actually came down.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: That separates our wall, like our house from the neighbors and it fell down on our cars.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oof.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, our cars are now, like, you know, they're covering rubble and...
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they need to be repaired and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember Jamie had a wall fall on her car and it wasn't even an earthquake.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just about to say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that happening.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was at my old apartment complex.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had this sort of stucco and brick wall that was around the dumpster.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we had that windstorm and the wall actually fell over on the car.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it just dented one ridge on it from where it impacted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thankfully, the car was still drivable, although it looked like just an ugly thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: But a car is just a car.
[SPEAKER_06]: A car is just a car.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's replaced.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's the only thing I can be thankful of.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, I don't know, you guys are in California, so you kind of are used to the earth shaking, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not in Sacramento so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: The place we live is not nearly as bad with the earthquakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've felt a few, but they're usually not that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do go to San Francisco a lot, and I have a lot of friends over there, and it's a little more prevalent over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's weird how many earthquakes there have
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, actually, we've been having, you know, the earthquake itself here, where it hit here in Santiago, was about 7 point something.
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't quite 8, and at the epicenter it was 8.8.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got 2012, 2012, 2012.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you look at the footage that you will see on TV, it's most likely from that place, which is about 300 kilometers away from here.
[SPEAKER_13]: but still you know in earthquake distances that's nothing like it still hits pretty hard all around so you know it wasn't as bad as that but still what's funny or not that funny actually and that actually has me scared shitless lately is that every few hours there's going to be an aftershock and those aftershocks can reach 6.1 6.5 and all of a sudden you're just doing your things and everything's just shaking again and you know
[SPEAKER_13]: After we're waking up at 3.34 a.m.
[SPEAKER_13]: to an earthquake that fell the wall on your car, you get really nervous all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially for me, this is my first major thing because I live in Argentina and nothing happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's no earthquakes, no tornadoes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I heard they felt this one in Buenos Aires, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but I've been in Buenos Aires when we quote-unquote feel an earthquake and it's like, oh, look, there's a wind gust.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's like, it's nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: But being here, I was honestly just, I don't remember being afraid.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just remember running away outside, away from trees and walls, just, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Footy Monster, just do your best to be safe, and don't live in fear too bad, because if it's your time, then lightning could strike you when you're walking down the street.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything could happen ever, so don't live in fear, but always have a plan, and I think this is a good lesson for all the listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though we're a video gaming podcast, this is still a good opportunity to talk about if...
[SPEAKER_06]: I have one piece of advice in regards to that because it's been baffling my mind what people have been doing here.
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's an earthquake going on, if there's some sort of natural disaster going around you...
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't grab your laptop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't grab your DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just get out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Be safe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Put some shoes on because that's probably going to be dangerous if you're just walking in a place and try to get shoes at least.
[SPEAKER_13]: But other than that, just get out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everything else is replaceable.
[SPEAKER_13]: ransacking like supermarkets and department stores and they're taking LCDs with them when they don't even have a house anymore and then to feed themselves.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't even get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like some people are stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: They react stupidly to this thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that would be my advice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Be smart.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just be safe first.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then worry about everything material.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is some unfortunate but necessary advice especially for a tech savvy crowd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Footy, I'm going to have to let you go to get some more calls but stay safe, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you so much, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're all thinking of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_13]: You too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope that's the last of it I hope there's not another big earthquake coming Oh boy Oh boy, alright Well we still have time for some more calls 1-877-GAME-OLR Use name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio Feel free to call in, tell some dick and fart jokes To kind of relieve the tension a little bit, it'd be nice Or talk about the unicorn game with Loki Because he will not stop playing it over there I just found something else disturbing Sure, what's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Wonder Twins are on Smallville now Goody goody, what's that mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonder Twin Powers, Activate Oh god, wow Amazing, alright, let's go to the phones Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Ranma, what's up everyone?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey Ranma, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're good, how are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm doing good What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, a couple of things Well, I want to reference back to the beginning of the episode About how they try to pass that little ban on swearing for a week Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, uh-huh
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, a few months ago, they tried to do the same thing here in New York, but they tried to ban the N-word.
[SPEAKER_12]: It didn't get that far.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, free speech is free speech, so I wouldn't support that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's a huge difference between the N-word and the F-word.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still think people just shouldn't say the N-word out of good taste.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if we were going to say, you know what, we're going to have...
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to have our week where we're just going to start swearing profusely in protest of this law.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to say every dirty word we can think of.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to say fuck, shit, piss, so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still wouldn't say that word, you know?
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean there are times I find myself saying it by accident or depending on the company that I am with, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: But a lot of times I do find it a little bit offensive, but half the time I just don't care because it kind of falls into free speech and it just doesn't bother me at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like  and I read a comment from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 says, wait, isn't not being able to say the N-word censorship?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But my whole thought is that I just don't want to say that because there's a big heavy weight that comes with saying that word and a lot of responsibility like
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those don't write checks your ass can't cash kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're going to say a word like that, you better be prepared for the social repercussions that come with a very emotion-inducing word.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Chris Rocks, though, said that if it's Christmas Eve and someone beats you in the head when you're trying to buy the last Barbie doll, that you can call them that for 45 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: 4 o'clock in the morning within a two block radius and you have to show your receipt I actually listened to that very recently that was funny excellent from Kitsune in chat saying the n-word is disrespectful saying fuck is not unless you call someone a fucker
[SPEAKER_09]: I call people fuckers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I call my husband fucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I call people fuckers and motherfuckers all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes it's a term of endearment, like bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, God, Jamie, you're such a bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, back when I was hanging... But I mean that in a positive, you know... Back when I was hanging out with a certain somebody... Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually had a whole conversation about that, about how the only people who could use those particular terms are the ones that it applied to, contextually.
[SPEAKER_09]: They even had a mention of that in the Hebrew Hammer, I thought was absolutely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we used to go around calling each other, I guess, the H-word.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, what pray tell is the H word?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, cracker and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, because it was like, okay, well, so they can do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why can't we?
[SPEAKER_09]: We had that conversation, so we just started going around doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, as a point of order.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's not supposed to be insulting when you're the one doing it, when it's sort of like you taking it and turning it around.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the same time, you know, if someone else came and said that, it'd be like, oh, insult, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: I could go on a whole rant about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like some people like to or love to hide behind that anonymity on Xbox Live and just write checks left and right that are going to bounce, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, anyhow, Ranma, after such a deep conversation, do you have a dick and fart joke or at least a video game you've been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_06]: Video game, but before I get into it, I just want to know, did you hear me on my keyboard?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, you're fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I downloaded Blaster Master Overdrive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I talked about this a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_12]: My roommate, he's played it.
[SPEAKER_12]: His main gripe is the fact that in the original NES version, you could jump higher with Sophia.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't even catch that difference, but that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: He caught that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The controls were what pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: That whole strafing with the button.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: But otherwise you liked it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Classic controller right there, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they needed the classic controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were these few little imperfections with the game that needed to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: The fact of the matter is we have a sequel.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think we're kind of more excited about that than anything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least it happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Better than nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Ranma, I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls, but thank you so much, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: And have fun with Blaster Master and the remixed music.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can probably squeeze in one more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to go to Loki, though, if he's taking a break from the Unicorn game and see if there's any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, too, if she has anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm ranting in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the ESRB has revealed yet another lips game on the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently it's called I Heart the 80s and it will feature such songs including... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't really say, but they say some of the songs, of course, or lyrics that are in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a very kinky girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really need to love... I really love to taste her and you don't have to sell your body to the night.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even recognize those songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I recognize, uh, she's a very kink girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do recognize that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That one I recognize.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's take a quick call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good evening!
[SPEAKER_00]: You, uh, crossed the, uh, supposed, like, oh, what the fuck, I lost it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, hello there, oh my lord, this is Akira Bird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, it's the other Swedish guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, what do you think about this whole fact that now we have, like, a second Swedish listener?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you okay with that?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He called in a couple weeks ago, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have another guy in Sweden who listens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh damn Of course I know Sweden's a big place I'd be all like do you guys know each other But you know that would be like a little silly Because that's like when people ask me if I see celebrities Because I live in California When LA is like 8 hours away from here And even when you're in LA you don't really see celebrities Because celebrities don't really like to You know they don't really go out in public And shop at you know Vons often you know It's different But anyway what's on your mind I'm sorry I didn't mean to get on the tangent there
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I have a question for Jamie, actually, since, well, how would, if someone, if a Sims 3 player that plays Sims 3 quite a bit would actually attempt to try to play Sims 2, how would that feel?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, wait, say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking a step backwards, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you're a Sims 3 fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've gone back and played Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was fun picking up my old games because there's actually, because the mod community, you know, there's so much more out for Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could do a whole lot more in my games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really enjoy going back to Sims 2 every so often.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm, wait, Sims 3 is catching up.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, yeah, because I have been... Because the most fun I'm having is that since I have the World of Adventures expansion, I have this...
[SPEAKER_00]: I like having my sims doing the spar part against each other because the kung fu part is way entertaining, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have to share, I'm looking over at DarkSakura's desk and World Adventures is sitting right on the desk under one of her knitting projects right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then High End Loft Stuff is right there, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, I just got them together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to reinstall everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just funny you brought it up because they're sitting on her desk right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll take a picture.
[SPEAKER_00]: Speaking of high-end lost stuff, do you think it's worth it?
[SPEAKER_00]: The problem myself is that, well, because I was found like cheap...
[SPEAKER_00]: I found cheap Sims 2 games was that I found the original Sims 2 and a few expansions.
[SPEAKER_00]: The expansions for the second part is the animal thing, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: The pets and everything?
[SPEAKER_00]: Pets.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the travel parts.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the supposed annoying thing is that, well, the expansion in Sims 2 that I'm...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't have yet, since the expansions that I'm interested in are the year-round... The seasons.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seasons.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seasons and free time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because, well, at the current, my Sims 3 game I find is a bit boring, but in a way kind of funny, since...
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I like to have my Sims sleeping outside.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I know that for World of Ventures you've got the tents and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, my whole thing with Sims 2 was really just building houses, which is the same thing I do in Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love building houses.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's really all I do in it, is just build houses.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: or The Sims Resource, you can get all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you sort right for which expansions that you have, you can get all kinds of just really cool stuff that's all made by user-made content.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but here's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't even know if you can tell me, but the only thing I want to know in any kind of way is that, well, are the stuff that's included in high-end Loft stuff, are there actually a point better than things that you get in the expansion or the original game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I haven't actually got it to run yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine froze because of all the mods I have already installed because I have the no blur mod so you can actually see them naked I hate the blur, it just annoys me and I have a couple of slider hacks so that I can change different parts of the body and I think I might have to reinstall everything to get my games to play
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I can't say anything on that because I'm using no mods at all, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe she'll have a better answer for that component in a couple weeks when she gets all that fixed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But kind of going back to the original question, I think the best point that was made by Jamie there was the whole point about that if there's something you want to go back and kind of experience that was in 2, especially with all the mods that were done for it and probably a bunch of scenarios that exist out there on the internet and so forth...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really the best way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the fact it's dirt cheap now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can get... The whole Sims Uber collection's gotta be really affordable at this point, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you probably get like... I think they do like whole box sets now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Aki Ripper, I say take it to the extreme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go all the way back and play Sims 1.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think that's possible with my computer since I'm running...
[SPEAKER_00]: Running 64-bit Windows 7 at the moment.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about SimCity?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think that's possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aki Ripper, we've got to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thanks so much for the call, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun simming.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks so much, guys, for the call tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apologies to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a lot of stuff going on tonight, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, again, you can always send us an email and tweets and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Many ways to interact with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We always appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go around and wrap up any other last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: I cut Loki off for that call.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pump It Up Fiesta has been unveiled to be coming out March 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the brand new upgrade for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't this what happened to some of the folks behind In The Groove are now with the Pump It Up folks?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I thought happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, though, Fiesta will strengthen the intermediate steps for pump lovers, mania, and newly improved easy steps for beginners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Players also have the option of versus mode in Fiesta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Separated interfaces to better accommodate general players and pump lovers from the start.
[SPEAKER_02]: Users can play one of the custom-made steps by using USB, so custom stuff's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Fiesta is compatible with both personal USB and pump USB, whatever that... I imagine they're all about the same anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, go have a Fiesta with Pump It Up Fiesta.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they do have a partial song list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a siesta.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to see if there's anything other than Banya stuff on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, good old Banya.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tons of Banya.
[SPEAKER_02]: Banya production stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did a remake of Turkey March, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's been in pump forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of remakes and remixes in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though the game just came out last week, New Line Cinema has optioned the rights for the film adaptation of Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though the game plays out pretty much like a film anyways, I guess I could see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then... That's pretty much all I wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's going to bring us to the close of a show, but not until we go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, let me say a big thank you to everybody, of course, for tuning in and supporting Orange Lounge Radio and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't really make any money off this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, we pay to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we do really appreciate all you guys who help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_06]: All we ask, just tell one or two people about the show and help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, we always do love, love when people post kind reviews of us out on the internet, whether it be on
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for all the kind words about us on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll start with Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait to go home and install Hyper Spin 1.0 into my cabinet and finally drop down that list of games so I can actually play some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is Itchy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tasty?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's your final thought, Tasty?
[SPEAKER_11]: You said Itchy, I said Tasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Itchy and Scratchy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Jill, yeah, I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't want to end up a Jill sandwich.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back here next week to do it all again.
[SPEAKER_06]: So until then, that's going to do it for tonight's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great week everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week with another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_14]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_14]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!