[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of April 18th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, here we are again for another edition of...
[SPEAKER_02]: The Orange Lounge Radio To Go Podcast Where we talk about what's going on in the gaming world This is a podcast dedicated to what gamers really want to know about So we don't talk about games that suck Well, okay, sometimes they come up occasionally NASCAR 2005 My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky The voice you hear over there is the lovely Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers Ego++ And of course joining us as always is Loki
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're very tired, aren't you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Very tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: And why is it that you're pretty tired this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: For those of you guys who are listening to the Sunday night show, the three-hour program, it was kind of a sappy show this week because... It was full of pants.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it was our kind of goodbye to the studio as we evolve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is kind of evolving.
[SPEAKER_02]: This podcast is a big part of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're taking Orange Lounge Radio, our internet station we do on Live365...
[SPEAKER_02]: Best of Live 365 Nominated Broadcaster of the Year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those awards happen in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're taking our station on Live 365 and kind of revamping it to be a general video gaming station.
[SPEAKER_02]: This podcast is a big part of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, DDR fans shouldn't be too upset.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're still going to have Rhythm of Music Games be a big part of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I believe, DarkSakura, you said this a couple weeks ago, and I think it describes this whole thing best.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are gamer fans first, DDR fans second.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because DDR is a game, so we're gamer fans before anything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR is a subcategory of the gamer thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this podcast we do is kind of the kickoff of that, dedicated to other gaming things, and we're all here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All three of us are here live in person in studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody had asked a question a while back, do you Skype in any of your co-hosts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are all here live in the flesh so we can interact with each other.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually an artificial intelligent program here that just acts like me.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've nicknamed him Simone.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your game of the week been like, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: I ain't played shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually, I did play something, now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the Jeep Simulator on the Gorillaz site.
[SPEAKER_02]: You and your web games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun, because if anyone has seen the 19-2000 video, they're on this big stretch of a highway being chased by aliens and salvation and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you can actually drive the whole freeway that they're on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, promise me this week you'll tarry yourself on the website to play another game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got a house full of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Legos too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, you played the Lego game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the Star Wars Lego game and it was really cool because we got enough money in the game to unlock General Grievous and the next Star Wars movie he's supposed to have killed these four Jedi and uses their lightsabers as his damn weapons and he's got four arms.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he's like kicking ass all the time and I'm over there using like Anakin.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, I'm evil.
[SPEAKER_03]: No spoilers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, I'm Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the Lego game?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm glad you were able to tear yourself away to at least give that a try.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been busy with school.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a lot of crap up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not huge on Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: I respect the films, but I'm not like, oh my God, I wet my pants, Revenge of the Sith.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they're cool games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some good games that come out of the series, so I'm curious about this Lego... I think it's kind of hilarious, the whole concept, Lego meets Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's the dumbest thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was really stupid-looking, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun is what games are all about, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make a fun game that could be Star Wars, not featuring Legos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Intelligent Cube was a stupid-looking game, because it was like, oh, these falling cubes, but it's one of the most brilliant PlayStation games they ever did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rogue Squadron was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is why you don't see Tickle Me Elmo the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that would be stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that still doesn't stop them from putting Mary-Kate and Ashley games out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what's your game of the week been like?
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Luminous, and I played Ridge Racer for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ridge Racer's pretty cool because it's like a throwback to the old R4, which is the best one, I think, that was available for the original PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_01]: and then they have R5 tracks in there as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess you can unlock the intros for both of those games as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got to play it against my boss.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kicked his ass by 10 seconds.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had never actually played the game when I played him.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's not that much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, he's a gamer, but
[SPEAKER_01]: He's probably just not as hardcore as I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then Luminous is interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's so simple, but you can kind of screw yourself up pretty easy on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just something you've got to play, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I also put Robot Chicken, five episodes of it, on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doing the hacksaw thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lead hacksawing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's a feature of the PSP to put video on it, so that's what I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, my gaming week was kind of similar, where I actually played Donkey Konga this week over at my buddy's house.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were playing Donkey Konga, and I haven't played Donkey Konga a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, maybe this is like my second or third time playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was playing all the crazy songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like how Loki was kicking ass at Ridge Racer his first time playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I've played so many of the rhythm beat games, and since I'd played Taiko no Tatsujin before, which is Taiko Drum Master, which is basically the same thing as Donkey Konga, just in a different setup.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had no problem clearing the difficult songs, so they were going like, how are you doing that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Your second time playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, what's wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: Also during my gaming week, I also played a little bit of Luminous, which, wow, that game is just, it really is as amazing as everybody says it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so addicting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's seizure-inducing at times, but once you get the hang of it, there's some very good, I would highly recommend over on GameFacts.com, GameFAQs.com,
[SPEAKER_02]: They have some luminous facts, and you wouldn't think that a puzzle game would need it, but when you read it, it really improved my game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was not able to get past the second skin, but then when I read the FAQs, I was up to, like, skin number 10 on my next game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I highly recommend checking that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I have not been able to get the song Shinin' out of my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the song that plays in the first stage, the Mato Grosso song.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll be shinin' to do...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This is posted on PSPHacks.blogspot.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the PSP Home Control version 1.0.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's actually a way that you can control your DVD player, TiVo, and high-definition television all from your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's what some guy did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He made graphics in Photoshop and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's actually controlling devices using his PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not something for everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, it's using the wipeout hacks to be able to do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not something for everybody, but certainly shows the potential the PSP has as a device.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it can do this with a little bit of tweaking, it's only a matter of time before some of these features come into the mainstream.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the things that's actually pretty cool that's coming out later on is a game where you can actually make your own game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sort of the
[SPEAKER_01]: Memory cards and then probably upload it to the internet and all that wonderful fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's going to unleash a whole other community upon itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the RPG makers or fighter makers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or ZZT if you want to get really old school.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Port that to the... Oh, please somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop porting Linux and start porting ZZT.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why the hell... If you have any idea what I'm talking about, please port ZZT to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too many acronyms, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, put Linux on your toaster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, if you want to check that out again, it's psphacks.blogspot.com Moving on, Halo 2 is going to be getting a big update this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: This Monday, Bungie is putting out a brand new patch for Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be pretty big because they're actually going to alter the way some of the weapons work.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be doing some changes with the melee damage.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be changing the way grenades work a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fuse timer is going to be tightened up a little bit and the damage caused is going to be increased.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just changing some other things here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too many hacks out there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too many people taking abuse of the glitches that are on there right now that have falsified the leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one aspect.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pretty big answer here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd urge you guys to check it out if you're a Halo fan over at Bungie.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're basically going to reset to give everyone a fair shot since they are tweaking the rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although they say to the casual player, which would be me, I think I fall in this category because I suck at Halo, you won't even notice the difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something the hardcore players are going to notice the difference in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet neither of you care because you don't play Halo at all, do you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo makes me throw up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Halo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Halo, but it makes me motion sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, so you don't throw up because you hate the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I literally get so motion sick that I would like to, you know, remove the contents of my lunch from my stomach and offer it to the porcelain goddess on my knees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you're just not, eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I don't own the game, I don't own Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, then let's talk about a story I do know you would know something about, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI had some news this week because they are under attack!
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody is DDoSing them.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is also known as the denial of service attacks, where basically somebody is trying to overload the servers with information so that they effectively shut down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I can personally attest to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had problems logging in on, I think it was like Tuesday night, I was trying to log in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, you were playing and I was going to try to join you in a party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, I couldn't get in.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody was DDoSing the servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squeenix!
[SPEAKER_02]: As we fondly refer to them here on the show, they're putting the smack down.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're saying that they have notified law enforcement authorities in Japan, the United States, and Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: The attack started April 9th, and as of the taping of this podcast, they're still ongoing as far as we know, causing latency and screwy servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're not happy about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this just some World of Warcraft person that's just pissed off or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably one of those people that got banned for selling Gil on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to say, who would do this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would have the motive to DDOS Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because honestly, how many servers are there for Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's at least 20 servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not going to shut the whole game down.
[SPEAKER_02]: You would have to have the entire force of America Online DDoSing these people to shut it down.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what do people have to gain from this, do you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: And also each server is just... A server is not necessarily one computer either.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a cluster of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why you'll see a group of people drop and not everybody...
[SPEAKER_01]: IRC, you know, type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think this is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Disgruntled gill seller?
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft fan base?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just some loser kid that's trying to, like, I don't know, feel special.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone who's playing Rose Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, stop screwing up my game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: But... But...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's starring The Rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is starring The Rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Carl Urban, who is in Lord of the Rings, Return of the King, and Born Supremacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The director of this movie, Andrzej Bartokwek, I hope I... I know I totally mispronounced that, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he directed the movies Cradle to the Grave and Exit Wounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We, like, have, like, some, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: We're the hip-hop artists in this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to say, didn't both those movies star hip-hop stars?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know one of them starred 50 Cent.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting thug-doomed, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they're going to be having some hip-hop interlude action sequence or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doom, yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is cool if you're into art, modern art especially, and gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know this is one that might hit home for you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be doing an 8-bit art exhibit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to open April 19th.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's this week on Melrose Avenue in Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's at Gallery 1988.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the expo is running April 19th through May 20th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is perfectly timed up so that it's running through the last day of E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's opening on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so basically they're going to be hosting a party for E3 attendees as well on May 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's game-related art from more than 100 artists.
[SPEAKER_02]: The gallery is called I Am 8-Bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet there's got to be some Amano art there.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what's cool about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The opening will be hosted by Gerardo, also known as Rico Suave.
[SPEAKER_03]: 8-Bit Weapon
[SPEAKER_02]: We saw those guys at Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought one of their albums and did a marathon on my show.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: The art will be based on games Pac-Man, Street Fighter 2, Dig Dug.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got digital prints, paintings, sculpture.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be just awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the exhibits will be The Mourning of the Princess by Ryan Bubness and it depicts an unshaven chain-smoking link from The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um
[SPEAKER_02]: Tim Tomkinson made an artwork called Duck Hunter S. Thompson, which will feature the author, Hunter S. Thompson, who made Fear and Loathing Las Vegas, wrote that original story, over a backdrop of the NES light gun classic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to check this out when I'm down in LA for E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we've got to plan a trip to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, speaking of E3, Ubisoft has revealed some of the titles they are going to be showing at E3, which includes some next-gen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the next-gen games are going to be showing Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 3 and Peter Jackson's King Kong.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how they're remaking King Kong this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Peter Jackson, the guy who did Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be making games, and they will be on the next-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're finally starting to see... Now, they haven't said which next-gen systems, but a next-gen system, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: We're finally starting to hear some of the games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of games do you guys hope make it to the next-gen systems?
[SPEAKER_03]: More Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tekken.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next-gen Tekken.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, next gen systems, next gen, next gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about, well, we know Grand Theft Auto is going to be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need more Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I want to see, I want to see, even though I really want Silent Hill 5, I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to see more original stuff like Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that all these special next gen things will...
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wanna see more original games like Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wanna see original stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Use this fancy new next-gen technology you're developing to make something new.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need more treasure games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Treasure games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our pirate hunting games?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Treasure brought us Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the company treasure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chameleon Twist.
[SPEAKER_03]: They freaking brought us Silhouette Mirage.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need more treasure games, because treasure is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or as my friend says, Treshar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, do you know what gaming company is cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: At least according to themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Majesco, creators of the game Phantom Dust on Xbox, among other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are changing their NASDAQ stock symbol.
[SPEAKER_02]: This would be the stock exchange.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're changing it from M-J-E-S to C-O-O-L.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Majesco just wants everybody to know they're cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't they special?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not as cool as Namco!
[SPEAKER_02]: Or several other gaming companies I can think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them being Konami, one of our favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami just picked up another gaming publisher.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hudson Soft, Konami has picked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bomberman!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, the makers of Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games with the Bs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may also know Hudson Soft as.
[SPEAKER_02]: They made, what, Adventure Island back in the day?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what they've done recently outside of Bomberman, I have to admit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Konami and Hudson, they issued a joint statement saying that April 27th, Konami is going to purchase 3 million shares of Hudson's stock.
[SPEAKER_02]: This means that Konami will become the majority stakeholder.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're not quite fusing per se, but... It's a takeover.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know it's heading in that direction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not just here to fill you in on the latest and greatest in gaming news, but we're also here to better your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, if all we did is played video games all day, we wouldn't have any time to go out and, you know, get some culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: See art shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I did that today.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we encourage you to get out once in a while and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura brings you her advice column every single week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura, what are you going to be talking about tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: How to navigate a minefield.
1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep your eyes on your feet.
2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Freeze.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not move any farther.
3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look for spikes, detonators, wires, bumps, or discoloration in the ground around you. 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Avoid wires, bumps, or discoloration on the ground, and back up slowly in your own footsteps.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not turn around.
[SPEAKER_03]: Walk backwards.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what I always say in situations like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't freaking go to Eastern Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Avoid those minefields altogether.
[SPEAKER_02]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on in gaming news, you know there's a big movie coming out this summer, The Fantastic Four.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're adapting that comic book.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you a fan of The Fantastic Four?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was at one time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember The Fantastic Four in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember the last movie that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Activision is actually making a Fantastic Four game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've actually been recruiting some musicians to be on the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to have The Explosion with a song called I'm On Fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not the soundtrack to the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the soundtrack to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jurassic 5 with a song called Clobberin' Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go Betty Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an all-girl punk rock band if you don't know who they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everywhere, and ModRockers Taking Back Sunday will be bringing up Error Operator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the interesting thing is that the songs all kind of go with one of the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Error Operator for Mr. Fantastic, the girl punk rock group Everywhere for the Invisible Woman, Jurassic 5 doing the song for The Thing, and I'm on Fire, of course, the Human Torch.
[SPEAKER_03]: But how can a song called Clobber in Time not be for The Thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's his catchphrase.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's just kind of cool that they've got little songs to go with each character.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's really no other way I can describe that, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Man's coming back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Man is going to be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like we get a new Pac-Man game of some type every year, just something crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually not the Pac-Pix game, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is something different.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Pac-N-Roll, and it's coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I, for one, am impressed that there's actually a new game coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this that one that I was crazy about at the E3 demo?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that was the Pac-Pix one.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Pac-N-Roll, and what Pac-N-Roll does is that you basically play a rounded Pac-Man, and you go around colorful worlds.
[SPEAKER_02]: You use the DS touchscreen and stylus, so it's kind of like you're running Pac-Man through 3D worlds.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So pack and roll, we'll be using, of course, the stylus.
[SPEAKER_02]: You kind of roll it around there with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of like the trackball thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the one I was wanting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you were talking about the one where you actually draw the Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad, my bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was all about the Marble Madness looking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, when you went and saw the DS at E3, did you get to go... Remember E3 last year, they had the cool line, like random people got to go in the cool line that would see all the games, and some people got to go in the not-so-cool line where they only saw WarioWare?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the one I ended up being in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sort of snuck over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you snuck over?
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's how you saw this, because I didn't see this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw the Pac-Pix, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also saw a...
[SPEAKER_03]: A picture that someone snuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scandalous.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pack and Roll will include the original Pac-Man arcade game, just for the heck of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because just like Linux, Pac-Man has to show up on every system available out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the granddaddy of video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the granddaddies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's the Gradius game that we saw at friggin' E3 last year for the DS?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I wanna know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, I wanna see that too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what we need?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the whole Gradius series needs?
[SPEAKER_03]: A new Parodius.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or like KO Flying Squadron 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, there was one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need like a new KO Flying Squadron.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or a new Cotton game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have some news tonight, lastly, about the, actually, no, not lastly, almost lastly, Next Gen Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a couple stories here.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of these stories has to do with Tetsuya Mitsugushi.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the guy who helped out with Space Channel 5 and Rez.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't just help out, he actually produced these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually announced recently that he's going to be doing games for the Next Gen Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will not be music-oriented titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a big title coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of a surprise when you consider that Space Channel 5 and Rez are right there, probably the two most underrated music titles of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rez had the vibrator thingy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's going trans-vibrator all the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully whatever he does will be with the vibration still, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: He has commented in a recent interview that he sees the next generation consoles not just new machines, but as the point of a major shift in gaming history.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, I believe that we are at a historical turning point in gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we were to look back at today and the not too distant future, I believe that we will be saying to ourselves, ah, so that was the first step that led to the major changes.
[SPEAKER_01]: This time, the Xbox will fit not four, but six family members inside of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you been following the, what's that called, that Xbox thing, the online?
[SPEAKER_01]: The ARG.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, the ARG.
[SPEAKER_01]: The alternate reality game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, have you been following that at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Colony, is that what they're calling it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, thecolony.net or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I have this wonderful web board that I read called nonfiction.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: They do all the work for me, and I just watch it from afar.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of like what I do with Metacortex.
[SPEAKER_01]: I watched it from afar, and that's what I'm doing now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they showed, what was it, first we found out that the official name for it is going to be the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: That it has a really retarded looking white controller for it that's all shiny and it's got some stupid ball on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like a trackball.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pure and virginal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, then also the console system is rumored to look like one of those stupid...
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, we need to get rid of these console systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox is like, hey, we can stick our Xbox inside of those things.
[SPEAKER_01]: And boom, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still getting email for the Phantom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever happened to the Phantom?
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought the Phantom was supposed to be out by now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still getting email for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what the title game is going to be?
[SPEAKER_01]: Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a funny joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they're both never going to ever come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, speaking of the Xbox 360s, analysts are saying...
[SPEAKER_02]: 3 million Xboxes could possibly be shipped by Christmas, especially if the system is targeted under $300, which is where they are targeting this new system to be at.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will be priced around $249 to $299.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're also saying that the system will be out October or November, and they're analyzing there are 3 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is coming from Goldman Sachs Investment Firm.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a big problem with this system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're rumored talking about a portable hard drive for it to kind of be like sort of an MP3 player type thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like that one bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I buy an Xbox system for gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't buy it for a media player.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't buy it for, you know, all this crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's going to be a lot of gimmicky things with this kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, really, how many media players... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sort of see the Xbox as more of a hardcore console system and where...
[SPEAKER_01]: People that would have an Xbox would have these like an iPod or a media type thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really see – it's going to be very gimmicky, and I think they've made a lot of bad decisions with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We only have rumors to go off of right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have any opinions or thoughts, feedback, send us an email to go at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you been checking that email over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been chatting with a couple people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heard from anybody interesting?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's one of our UK listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: His name is Matthew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: He actually was interested in our PSP commentary, although the PSP isn't really out there yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll try to keep making mentions on progress in the UK.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, one of my full side projects I'm still working on is some sort of PSP integration for our website eventually.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to get my internet up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, speaking of Orange Launch Radio and our website, we did mention on the show tonight we've had this theme going on of...
[SPEAKER_02]: We are starting over.
[SPEAKER_02]: May 1st is going to bring a lot of changes to OrangeLawsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: This podcast really isn't going to be changing so much, but our 24-hour, 7-day-a-week live streaming station we have on Live 365 is going to be changing a little bit for the better, we think.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be more of a broad gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those of you guys that listen to this podcast have something to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, one more story here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is interesting here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games could possibly soon be losing their voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Online trade magazines are stating that the negotiations between the Screen Actors Guild and game publishers to renew voice acting contracts are kind of on the bubble right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this could possibly lead to...
[SPEAKER_02]: A future strike?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: How could this affect things?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's look at this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Charlize Theron is lending her voice to Majesco's Aeon Flux.
[SPEAKER_02]: David Duchovny, Marilyn Manson are doing voices in Midway's Area 51.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sean Connery is doing some voice acting from Russia With Love from EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marlon Brando did some voice acting, as you may remember, for the Godfather game before it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Variety.com making this report.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you be all torn up if actors, famous actors, had to leave video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: To me, the type of games I play, it doesn't really matter to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes, though, they make the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, like, the Buffy game?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how crazy I was over that?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had everybody except Sir Michelle Gellar, and that just sort of axed it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but look at a game like Final Fantasy X. I mean, some pretty decent voice acting in that game from basically folks who maybe they're big on the anime dubbing, but no screen actors really in that group and they're all pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, is that for The Godfather, you expect Marlon Brando.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: For Bond, you expect Sean Connery, especially since he's playing Bond in the new movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's supposed to be an older Bond.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't heard that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a stretch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where you heard that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Premier Magazine.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Avengers had Eddie Izzard in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: League of Extraordinary Gentlemen?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I needed to see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about they just have the wonderful movie Sean Connery Kicks Ass, and that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just him punching one person after another, you know, the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, before we turn into movie chat, I think it's time to end Orange Lounge Radio for this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back next week, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thoughts, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate moving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought, I've got so much laundry to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for listening, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you next time on the Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.