[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of April 4th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: Your internet radio home for discussion on rhythm and music gaming and all the news on video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to another edition of the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's going on in the video gaming world?
[SPEAKER_02]: And with you is myself, my name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky, and my lovely co-host Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am such a celebrity.
[SPEAKER_02]: And our other third wheel, say hello to Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to talk about some gaming news going on in the world, and of course, tons of PSP stuff, because, you know, this PSP has been this gigantic, like, Katamari Dimash-y ball just rolling down a hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's what's popular this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll talk about some PSP news, but first, what's going on in your gaming world, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing a lot of the games on the Gorillas.com site, like Widescreen Pong and Helidrop.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So no, like, consoles or anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked at Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't actually play it, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You looked at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just checked it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I moved my play online icon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been too busy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been doing other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, being a famous internet celebrity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you move it to the recycle bin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or where did you move the icon?
[SPEAKER_03]: Elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a lot of games anymore?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't be bothered with that kind of thing anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a famous internet celebrity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm busy being famous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought a PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sucker!
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I could afford it, I'd buy one too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm with the trends.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I got a PSP and I got two games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got the Wipeout Pure just because...
[SPEAKER_01]: I like to hack my PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: You bought Wipeout, period.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has nothing to do with the fact that you like Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_02]: I distinctly remember you saying you were disappointed with the Wipeout series.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hated Wipeout, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you just wanted to buy it because you know it's the game that allows people to hack their PSPs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I like Wipeout now because I've been playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried Wipeout 3 a while back and I tried Wipeout XL.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just didn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to bring over my pair of Negcons.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to play Wipeout with a Negcon.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Namco Controller, the twisty one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the one with the little dial is the JogCon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a JogCon that's completely useless.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have like three JogCons.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, I got Wipeout Pure and I got Twisted Metal head-on, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Twisted Metal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Twisted Metal head-on, though, is exactly like Twisted Metal 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, hey, if you're going to make a remake of one of the original games, Twisted Metal 2 would be the one to do it, because that was one of the best.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why didn't you get Luminous?
[SPEAKER_01]: because they weren't selling Luminous and I can only afford two games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, those were the two.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was either that or, you know, I get, like, some stupid NFL game or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, no thank you, I will take Twisted Metal Black, or not Black, Head On, and the White Belt here.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um, so I've been playing those.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um, I do not like, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not a huge fan of Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's really neat on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just like
[SPEAKER_01]: The other reason I got one, though, work-related, because my boss just got one, and I figured, you know, it'd be kind of cool to just, you know, play against him during, like, a break or something, or just to be able to actually play some of the games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, I want to drag it with me to E3, because you know they're going to have Wi-Fi hotspots there, and you know there's going to be, like, PSP crap there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, might as well drag my portable systems with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brown-nosing with a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as what's going on in my gaming world, I was, you know, obviously, since Loki's my roommate, I was checking out his PSP a little bit, so I played a little bit of Wipeout as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suck at Wipeout, though, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I kind of want a PSP, but I'm going to wait for some later games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really, really want Luminous, but it's not enough for me to justify spending so much money on a system at this point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe later.
[SPEAKER_01]: The one I want is actually, they have that cool one where you disable bombs.
[SPEAKER_01]: That looked kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the name of that one offhand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so I'll get a PSP eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was watching Spider-Man, even though I've already seen Spider-Man 2 twice and didn't really want to watch it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to see what the video looked like on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was quite impressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to admit, it's pretty nice looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also, though, download video from your computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was telling Loki he needs to put some pornography on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: GameStop's going to be carrying the one gigabyte cards coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, in order to download that stuff, I've got to buy an additional piece of crap that's got to go with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can just bring our cable over and you can borrow it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to get me a 1 gig stick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I'm not even... Because I don't know how much those 1 gig sticks are.
[SPEAKER_01]: What, they're like 200 some dollars or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yikes!
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Best Buy was having them for about $130 something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, fuck that, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can actually go out there and buy... There's a USB to Mini-B, which is the USB thing that's on top of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Adaptor for $13 and then hook up your wonderful flash drives.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: My flash drive is like, you know, 128 megs right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what, I bought that for $20?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why the hell would I go spend, you know, tons of money to buy this, you know, proprietary crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good idea in theory.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hope it works.
[SPEAKER_01]: In theory.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope it works.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I'm just interested.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now I've been like jumping on the Wi-Fi spots, you know, people that are neighbors and stuff that,
[SPEAKER_01]: Have internet and then they put wireless routers without passwords on them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, this is my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So instead I picked up a new DS game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, you know, I didn't want to spend $300 on a PSP, but I had to spend money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, that money was burning a hole in my pocket because I just did my taxes and I'm getting money back and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I instead decided to go out and buy a new game for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: The unfortunate thing is that the DS really doesn't have a whole lot of games on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, you know, I already have Mario 64 and I already have WarioWare Touch.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what does that leave?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already have Field of Magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was pretty much, it came down between Sprung and this other title, Yoshi Touch and Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I picked up Yoshi Touch and Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not impressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Touch and bye, as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki found some fun little customizable things.
[SPEAKER_02]: One's for the Xbox and one's for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you find, Loki, for the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, if you happen to love Hello Kitty, like we all do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, no, we all don't, but, you know, what a way to ruin a perfectly good Crystal, you know, Xbox case by shoving some stupid Hello Kitty crap on it for Hello Kitty Mission Rescue, the special edition Crystal console that you can get.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically... So, wait, wait, I just want to clarify, this isn't like a giant sticker you put on your existing Crystal console, which you can't even get in this country anyway, but it's a brand new Xbox that they're selling that is specifically Hello Kitty Mission Rescue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, with this crappy crystal... Cute!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a crystal console, which is, like, really awesome, but... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, so, you know, before they had a pink Xbox, why you would buy an X... Yeah, because, you know, I've been really waiting for the Hello Kitty game to come out for me to buy an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's been the game that'll do it for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyways, so they have this, you know, Hello Kitty crystal Xbox console that you can get.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's...
[SPEAKER_01]: It comes with a crystal controller, which hopefully doesn't have this pink crap on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the Mission Rescue game for $99.
[SPEAKER_01]: With the purchase of a selected Samsung LCD TV.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can only get it in Singapore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or on eBay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where people would be selling it from Singapore.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then, if you are the wonderful celebrity...
[SPEAKER_01]: They've been doing Simmons Jeweler Company made some accessories for the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: They debuted this at March 14th at the Pacific Design Center in West Hollywood, dubbed the Pret-A-PSP, whatever that's supposed to mean.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it says that brought together some of the hottest names in fashion, other well-known designers, including Marc Jacobs, Diane... Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a fashion show for PSPs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I correct here?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I believe you're correct.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: The top models including Maggie Reiser, Kirstie Hume, and people we don't care about.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, no gamer cares about these people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, so showed off the newest trend in fashion by wearing the sexy, sleek PSP accessories with the latest looks and fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I love about this is that it's bling for your PSP is really what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's bling bling.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, look at this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got this gold PSP and there's a whole other joke that can be made there about the golden PSP if anybody watches South Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get the gold PSP and you get these bling, bling chains that hang from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's tacky.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you want to know what... And you want to know how much this costs, folks?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because this isn't going to be for the average user.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why you'd want to buy one in the first place unless you're like some
[SPEAKER_01]: Overpaid rapper with no taste.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be $35,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: $35,000 to make your PSP look like crap?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, if I wanted to make the PSP look like crap, I could go to the craft store and buy, you know, sculpty plastic.
[SPEAKER_01]: And paint it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says A-list celebrities showed up to this.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is A-list...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how I know that, I just do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I don't know who bought this, but I know that David Arquette was there, and I know he's a big gamer, so he might have bought this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: He was one that bought one of those pimped out DSs, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: More power to him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pimp my game system.
[SPEAKER_01]: In other news... Yeah, let's hear some DS news.
[SPEAKER_01]: In other news in the DS, the other portable game world, we've been saying this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says the PassMe, which for those who don't know, it's this device that's actually made to be able to port your own code using the Game Boy code thingy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what websites is this all being documented on?
[SPEAKER_01]: on DSLinux.org.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, they ported Linux to the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first alpha for it should be coming out in about a month, they say.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, why, why, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, it's got a computer chip in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Linux can be installed on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as you could probably guess, they're already attempting to port Linux to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm personally porting Linux to my toaster oven.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, if Linux is so popular, why is it not outselling Windows?
[SPEAKER_02]: In other DS news, you know they did the new colored DSs in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have graphite black and pure white.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know we sit here and sometimes joke like, haha, Nintendo, you know, they just re-released the system in new colors to try and drive up sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what kind of idiots actually buy the system all over again just for a new color?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let me put this in a little bit of perspective for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sales for the week of March 21st to the March 27th, when these new colors debuted, 54,000 units in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: The previous week was only 21,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: More than doubled the sales just by rolling out two new colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and this kind of matches with that bling PSP story that there are people out there that will buy the gaming system to match their purse.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what's sad is people don't realize that you can actually go and find the mods yourself and do this for like a lot cheaper than buying a brand new system or paying $35,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see what happens April 20th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, for $35,000 I can make an all-in-one gaming unit with its own built-in like keg or something, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why pay $35?
[SPEAKER_01]: I would pay for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, why pay $35,000 for like a golden PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: A gaming system with a keg.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which as soon as you drop it will be $35,000 wasted.
[SPEAKER_03]: A gaming system with a keg?
[SPEAKER_02]: One day we'll be famous and spending that kind of money on gaming systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm already famous!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I forgot, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will see what happens to the sales of Japan's DS units on April 21st when Turquoise Blue and Candy Pink roll out.
[SPEAKER_01]: and then Barf Green you know there's people out there that want a candy pink DS just you wait for the transparent crystal DS to be coming out and then they'll have crystal pink and crystal blue and then there's baby shit yellow green look, moving on
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's some interesting news.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know the Four Swords that was out on GameCube?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zelda Four Swords?
[SPEAKER_02]: Certainly you've heard of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not a lot of people really played this game because in order to do it, you had to have the link cables.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you really wanted to get four people in on the fun, you had to have the link cables so everybody could be their own link.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did that at my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay, but only the hardcore gaming nerds like yourself could really participate in this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Something we'll see at E3 probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: April Fool's was this past week and of course a lot of websites rolled out their own ha ha funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that we would ever do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't participate at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we don't believe in April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't do anything on the site, nothing in LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would never make up stories about being bought or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd never do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would we ever sell out anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would never sell out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's some popular April Fools jokes you might have seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are all jokes, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Epic Games announcing Unreal 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Slashdot said that online support for the PlayStation 2 version of Final Fantasy XI is going to be discontinued.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to piss off the people who spent $99 on the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's beautiful, and actually that would be a dream come true.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft is going to incorporate, and this was announced on World of Warcraft's site.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are incorporating Slash Panda.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can get deliveries from Pandaren Express, and it comes delivered to you with a guy dressed in costume.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is an April Fool's joke, mind you, not a reality, but the pictures were so cute, because it actually had a little panda in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, also, other stories that were going on, we had OC Remix announcing a partnership with EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: and let's see, computer and video games announcing that Shrek 2 characters will be in the GameCube release of Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Barf.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I play this as the dragon.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I thought was really funny is something that GameSpot did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually ran an article saying that John Woo had actually bought the rights to the Katamari Damacy movie and it was going to star The Rock as the Prince of All Cosmos.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would actually pay to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to bestow the winner to the best April Fool's prank on GameSpot for the Katamari Damacy starring The Rock.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other really crappy nominations would go to Alakazam for saying that Final Fantasy XI and World of Warcraft merged, which fooled no one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Slashdot really sucked because they had a ton of, all the articles on April 1st were all fake, so that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still never checked GameFacts.com because they do something every year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like one year they did, this was a few years ago, they did Xbox Facts.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the one I remember, that they got bought by Microsoft or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think somebody was telling me all the mods banned themselves or something, but if you're not a member of the community, you may not have seen it, I don't know, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Orange Lounge Radio, we're not just here to talk about video games all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you live, eat, breathe, sleep video games, you're never going to get laid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're here also to give you advice on how to better your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who better than, I believe you could be, DarkSakura, the only podcast video game female.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could be wrong, but you may be.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she's here to give you her little bit of advice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what is the advice you're going to give tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's bit of advice is how to survive a nuclear explosion.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the event of a nuclear war or explosion, get to a safe shelter as quickly as possible and remain inside for four to six days after the last explosion.
[SPEAKER_03]: An underground shelter covered by one meter or more of earth will provide the best protection against nuclear explosion and fallout radiation.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you must emerge, limit your surface exposure to no more than 30 minutes a day for 13 days following the explosion.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have been exposed to radiation, immediately wash your body thoroughly with soap and water.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will remove most of the radiation particles, but not all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Water can be safely obtained from underground sources , that undergo natural filtration, or from pipes in houses or stores.
[SPEAKER_03]: Healthy looking wild animals are a safe food source if other food sources are not available.
[SPEAKER_03]: Avoid any meat close to the bones and joints.
[SPEAKER_03]: An animal skeleton holds more than 90% of the radioactivity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any last pieces of advice?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't live in Iraq.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked briefly about an April Fool's joke that involves Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's something that's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some recent details being announced on Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interview with a games producer revealed on the official Japanese Soul Calibur 3 site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some official things revealed.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will not be doing guest characters on PlayStation 2, although they have received offers.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've received offers, but the policy is we don't do the same thing twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crash Bandicoot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please no, please no.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the idea of having the prince of all cosmos, you know, just roll people over.
[SPEAKER_01]: What about Sonic?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, not gonna happen, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was already Sonic Fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the other bummer, a lot of people had their hopes up about this, but it was confirmed by the game's producer, no online play.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can go online, the PS2, who'd have thunk it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The official reason here, at the current time, the online infrastructure is extremely different between countries, and there's people that can't enjoy network gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've decided to concentrate on improving the game's offline content,
[SPEAKER_02]: and its characters so that people all over the world will be able to have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was nice of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it seems like just kind of a, to me it's more of like a, you know, cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we didn't want to do the online thing because we want to make offline better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course we want to make offline better.
[SPEAKER_02]: The idea is to do both really well, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've been holding off on doing online because we're worried about how Tekken 5 is going to beat our ass senseless.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's all Namco.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all Namco either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're getting the money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_02]: You just got game served.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom doing a little bit of ego inflation this week with a press release talking about their game sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talking about their series, how successful their game series are.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just asking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you're reading, Loki, so you can't guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you had to guess, what is Capcom's number one series of all time?
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you guess, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter is number two.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're on the sales chart.
[SPEAKER_02]: 24 million cumulative units over 53 different titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Breath of Fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Breath of Fire is number 10 on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: 13 titles, 3 million units.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck else did Capcom do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mega Man would be number 3 on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: 95 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Strider!
[SPEAKER_02]: 22.9 million units.
[SPEAKER_02]: Strider not on the list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strider's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a series so huge they made movies out of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they made Street Fighter movies too, but we don't deny the existence of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't get this right, you're going to end up in a Jamie's sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resident Evil!
[SPEAKER_02]: Resident Evil is the number one!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the dialogue in the first one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jill's sandwich!
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't want to end up in a Jill's sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, Barry, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_02]: 26 million units with 38 titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other titles on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 4, Disney titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Various titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number 5, Onimusha.
[SPEAKER_02]: 6, Devil May Cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: 7, Dino Crisis.
[SPEAKER_02]: 8, Ghosts and Goblins.
[SPEAKER_02]: 9, Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Devil May Cry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I have every Final Fight game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be all eight titles?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's eight titles?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have... Okay, well you don't need to... The first three I have it on Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Mighty Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's... Wow, having Final Fight Guy and some of the other stuff, those were rare titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doom 3 is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to pick it up at midnight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have that gaming division called Game Rush.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be doing a midnight sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Monday, April 4th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So by the time some of you guys hear this, you may already have your copy of Doom 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, this is the Xbox version, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you are so lucky as to live near the Game Rush on Hillcrest Avenue in Dallas...
[SPEAKER_02]: There will actually be some folks from ID Software there in person to give autographs because I guess they're famous.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not as famous as we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're internet celebrities.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I heard?
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is not an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's about games coming out and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take two.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have the rights now to Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that would be something else to finally see that damn game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Take-Two, I mean, I imagine they'd be able to be on top of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We might actually see this before the turn of the next millennia.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, couple quick stories to finish out on Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't talked a whole lot about Squeenix tonight, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squenix, or Squareenix, whatever you want to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: We like to call him Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squeenix!
[SPEAKER_02]: Squeenix is doing a brand new role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Code Age Commanders is the name of this, and it's going to be an action role-playing game set on a futuristic, post-apocalyptic planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that word, post-apocalyptic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't they all?
[SPEAKER_02]: Squeenix doing an RPG?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: A game is being produced by Naora Yusuki, who worked as an artist for many of Squeenix's games, including Final Fantasy X and Unlimited Saga.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very, very good Squeenix game and a very, very shitty Squeenix game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate the Saga series.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's no secret.
[SPEAKER_03]: A bunch of people really like them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why don't they... Screw other people!
[SPEAKER_01]: Why don't they, I don't know, direct their attention to, maybe, say, Einhänder 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we need Dew Prism 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Screw that.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about getting Final Fantasy 12 out in a timely manner?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just some suggestions if any folks from Squeenix are listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, by the way, Code H Commander, 50% complete, slated for release this year sometime in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real quick note before we get into our last story tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have any feedback for us, you can reach us via email to go at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we haven't done a mailbag section in a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't really gotten any letters that you folks want read on air, any questions that we can respond to.
[SPEAKER_02]: So,
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely would like to see some of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Togo, all one word, T-O-G-O.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why shouldn't they want their questions answered by us?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're famous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for the reminder, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't let you forget, we are famous.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a social responsibility as internet superstars.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just community service, this program here, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, mentioning Togo makes me want a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_03]: Togo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Togo, it's Togo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think of Sana.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want a Sana Witch?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, speaking of Konami, because we're talking about some of their artists there with Togo and Sana from the Beatmania series and various other Bomani series, Konami is going to be releasing mobile games in China.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be releasing 30 games annually, they say, starting with
[SPEAKER_02]: 3 classic 1980s titles at 2 yuan per download.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, that equivalents to 24 cents.
[SPEAKER_02]: 24 cents!
[SPEAKER_02]: Contra, Antarctic Adventure, and Life Force.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, Life Force Encontra!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we get anything this cool in the US?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because cell phone technology is like a million years better in Asia.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just spent $5 on a brand new download that Sprint had, because Sprint's my cell phone company.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have downloads for games too, and they sometimes have retro titles in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I deleted the games off of my cell phone because they sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I downloaded Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_02]: They ported Impossible Mission to cell phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, oh my gosh, that's the coolest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like the best Commodore 64 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the cell phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, waste of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just so people can die of, you know, what do people die of in that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Die of death.
[SPEAKER_02]: You caught diphtheria.
[SPEAKER_01]: Diphtheria, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, trying to remember why people die, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wolves ate you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you seen the commercial for Jamster where they're selling the, what was it, it was Rainbow Six for the cell phone?
[SPEAKER_01]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't pay attention to Jamster commercials because they're the devil.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Will somebody just bring the cool shit over here from the other companies?
[SPEAKER_02]: I will sign up with you guys so quick if I can get light force on my phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I find out that if I go to Japan and buy a Kei Tai and it freaking works in the States, if my sim will work on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it will.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still wanting to get one because you can get cell phones dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for this edition of the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around and see what everybody's final thoughts are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought is I hope I get paid soon because I need more games.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is DS, good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for subscribing to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will see you next time on the Orange Lounge Radio to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Orange Lounge Radio To-Go Edition is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.