[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, July 30th, 2006, E3 might be cancelled.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, cancelled.
[SPEAKER_01]: The latest news on the silver lining when we talk about the music of Prey in an interview with Nick Murray of Artistry Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome, everybody, to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are a video game podcast dedicated to what gamers really want to know, and we're here to help you through that.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me, as always, say hello to my lovely co-host in that corner over there, even though it's radio and you can't see it, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's me in the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that you in the spotlight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Losing... Anyway, also say hello... Losing up, you know, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also say hello, playing pinball, more likely than anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a lot of pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello as well to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also joining us once again tonight, crashing the program with his endless wit and charm, say hello to...
[SPEAKER_05]: 23rd Magus, Andrew Flattery will get you nowhere Do you have any sites that you're pimping out when you're here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have any sites you're affiliated with you want to pimp my show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have a podcast?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody has a podcast now I don't have a podcast yet I do listen to Warcraft Radio though WCRadio.com Cool We like independent radio Good deal
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's talk about some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But first, we always talk about what we've been playing in our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start it off with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: What have you been playing during your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: But loads of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Getting Lost in San Francisco this weekend, but that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that like Crazy Taxi or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played, we actually went to Santa Cruz this morning to play, actually just to go hang out at the boardwalk for a little while and, you know, have me not die on that little thing that goes across.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was this the girls?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was me and Disney Punk 10, Kristen, and her friend from L.A., Marissa, who's now my friend, very cool person, music nerd, like moi.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was like a girl thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a slumber party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a big slumber party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you go in your PJs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pillow fight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have a pillow fight?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we did have some... Ice cream?
[SPEAKER_05]: Talk about boys?
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually did eat a lot of ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had Dippin' Dots.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Star Wars Episode I Pinball, which is Pinball 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the Pinball 2000 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Revenge from Mars, Pinball 2000.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are the hologram ones, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played The Sopranos Pinball, which is actually pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the first Star Wars game, Pinball, that's put out by Sega, which is kind of a crappy table.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was another table that was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just had a brainstorm.
[SPEAKER_05]: It hurt a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why doesn't Sega put out a Sonic pinball table?
[SPEAKER_05]: They could have a little blue pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: pinball table there that wasn't working.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not Sonic.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I played Lord of the Rings pinball, which is also put up by Stern.
[SPEAKER_02]: One ball to rule them all?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pretty difficult table, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a really good machine, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, you are stealing my material.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically, Stern is the only company still making pins right now, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also, we got a new pinball table.
[SPEAKER_02]: I woke up Friday morning to see Dan face down on the futon, and in our garage is a Twilight Zone pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you can autograph it for a listener.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I decided that that Twilight Zone was destined to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you lift up the playfield to look at it, if you look at the very end of it that's facing toward the coin slots, you'll have two dates on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first date is the date that the board was cut.
[SPEAKER_02]: The second date is the date the playfield was assembled.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the date that the board on that Twilight Zone was cut was my birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was April 19th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually played DDR today.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not die.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played this other, it was a ticket game, but it plays like pop-up music with eggs, and there's only four buttons.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Rhythm and Something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really stupid, the music sucked, but it was like, this is pop-up music.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had a Tron machine that I didn't play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, say hello to our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funnydale is actually letting us know that Sonic did have a pinball game somewhere between 93 and 95.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's news to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had forgotten about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pin Mame
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could play it in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: NintendoManiac64 says, I have a pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Dark Knight says, give me the Simpsons pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a good table, too, because the bumpers were the big nuclear reactors.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a Funhaus pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate that machine because that head thing on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... They had a laughing cell at the boardwalk, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we were at...
[SPEAKER_02]: California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Playland used to be an amusement park in New York that they had to destroy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess they sold the property or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are people who made a Playland memorial or museum.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have games from there and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have two Laughing Souths.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I saw the one at Santa Cruz, I was like, oh, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The J-pop one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So our music gaming fans would be very happy at this place.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a new unit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't even played the... Well, I mean, I played it at E3 and the Konami Gamers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played, like, the final release version of it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually didn't play it because when we went to one of the little smaller ones just to play skee-ball, they had an Extreme there, so Chris and I played that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably lots of the DDR-free kits.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's played Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_02]: I counted three Spider Stomp machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, that's old-school DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they have a dock upstairs now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing the hell out of the Saints Row demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it was funny because I thought my magazine, the official Xbox magazine, I thought my subscription ended, but it has now after I got the demo, which is where it counts.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saints Row is
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they've improved on a few things, and there's a few things that are kind of not as great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for the most part, it's very enjoyable, and that demo we play for an entire hour each lunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are the things that are different?
[SPEAKER_04]: The things that are different, first off, the camera's a lot better with the right analog stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, if you have pipe bombs and stuff, you can toss stuff behind you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob Storrs
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, I've been playing a little bit of other Xbox stuff like Ridge Racer 6 a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really played too much of Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did finish the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's not that I read.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you didn't read it, then hell, who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: If I didn't see it, it's not illegal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so the game itself, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it plays very similar to the Xbox 360 demo that I played.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, graphics are a lot less Xbox 360, but they do the job.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an online game, completely.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you still roll down the window?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was an impressive feature in the Xbox demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of the stuff isn't finished yet because of this beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, all the interiors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I went, oh, okay, I'm going to look at the interior of the car and see what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just all glitched out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, okay, that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I look to see what my driver looked like.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no driver.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just the ghost car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they haven't finished that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's still beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's still fun, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can drive off-road just as easily as you can with this car.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 2 version, I probably wouldn't pick it up because I have the 360s, so why bother?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what's weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they drop the PlayStation 2 one, I think the 360 one is actually going to be cheaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's going to be $39.99, so why not pick it up?
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty cool, and it's definitely easy to get online with, which I haven't played too many online games, but I know there's been some difficulty.
[SPEAKER_04]: No lag, I haven't noticed any lag in it, but it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, HitStun also really loved your review there on the graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: The graphics are a lot less Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're very stripped down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very, very stripped down.
[SPEAKER_05]: How so?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's missing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a lot of detail that's in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely textures are, you know... It's just not as detailed as the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: It reminds me of the old test drive games, which...
[SPEAKER_04]: Last Test Drive I played other than this, which was a long time ago, Test Drive 3 on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's when the cars were blocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was going to say, probably the last Test Drive game I played seriously was like Test Drive 2 The Duel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_05]: On Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this was back in the day when Test Drive, you just basically had to get to the end of the map or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was a journey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I would always try to take the shortcuts through the fields and run over the 2D chicken or whatever and just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All you have is a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still going to be very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or even the PSP one, when that comes out, will be pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, they're worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I think, of course, more Grand Theft Auto and...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting to a point now with Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every day we play this game, the more and more frustrated we are at the developers and the more we want to kill them because of how buggy the multiplayer is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really sad because I wish I had a way to contact the developers at Rockstar because I have so much feedback I can give them on their game, both positive and negative, because I've basically played this game every single day for at least 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to give me a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anyone from Rockstar is listening, contact Loki at orangelongeradio.com L-O-K-I I hope to God, because this is built on the Vice City engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Liberty City Stories was, and now that Vice City Stories is coming out, you bet your ass they're not going to do anything to fix any of the multiplayer, because they're fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll still buy the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: When does the Saints Row demo get released for the rest of us?
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: April or August 1st.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: For whatever reason, it's not up that day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can always find it at the official Xbox magazine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mr. 23rd Magus, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_05]: Andrew, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was looking to make some crazy money, but instead I just sat my ass on the couch, sort of chair, yeah, chair,
[SPEAKER_03]: and played Tell Your Iris.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can tell that Nippon Ichi did all the translating because the script is absolutely hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell Your Iris, Eternal Mantle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a little dialogue with a cat girl asking the protagonist to sleep in bed with her.
[SPEAKER_03]: The response is, I can't, the ESRB would go nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, I haven't been doing much gaming, mostly because of the heat affecting my computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have been trying Fable off and on, and it's the first time I've actually played Fable.
[SPEAKER_05]: PC or Xbox?
[SPEAKER_03]: PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting, it's not what it was hyped up to be, obviously, but it's still pretty damn fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a completely open world like it was promised, but it is still pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It plays more like Knights of the Old Republic, with the whole good and evil thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually played quite a bit as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded the 99 Nights demo because I really liked the game at E3 when I got to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to remember when I actually played the full game at E3, it was a lot easier than the demo because I died like three times in the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I was doing something wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game's really fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked it a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a button masher, but it reminds me of a game like Final Fight or probably more rather something like Golden Axe
[SPEAKER_05]: But on a much bigger scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, in Golden Axe, you cannot kill 50 people in one swoop of the sword and things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can't stab somebody on the end of your sword and then use his body to attack other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you're fighting armies, just lots and lots of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the game's pretty intricate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really enjoyed the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I definitely want to pick up the full game, even if I suck at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed already in the chat room, though, some other folks didn't seem to like the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It definitely seems like the type of game you're either going to really like or you're going to really hate maybe because of its simplicity and the fact that it is kind of a bit of a button masher.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think some people are really going to get turned off by that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of people are comparing it to Dynasty Warriors, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is actually a lot better than Dynasty Warriors.
[SPEAKER_04]: It definitely looks a lot better because Dynasty Warriors 5 fucking sucked on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't really do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Samurai Warriors 2, when that comes out, that one's going to suck also because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Also another just port without any effort is basically what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks, to be honest, this demo looks a lot better than what I remember from E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a lot more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it just seems more fun than Dynasty Warriors was.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked back up Oblivion randomly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had tried playing this game a while back, and I thought it was very pretty, but I think the problem was I had someone hovering over my shoulder telling me what to do, like everything, and I think that might have ruined the gaming experience for me, so I went back and checked it out, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be that person, would I?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it wasn't really you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of everybody was hovering.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody else had played it but me, because a lot of people, and everybody was like, do this, do this, do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, shut up!
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had a chance to just sit down and sort of explore it for myself, and it's so... I guess the only word I can use to describe this game is vast.
[SPEAKER_05]: You really can do just whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: It reminds me of a first-person shooter, but with swords.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yet, the world is open, and you can go anywhere you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that vastness is kind of like a good thing and a bad thing because that vastness, I'm so used to very linear types of story in games, so it was really hard for me to go, oh, I could just go anywhere I want and do these other quests before doing the main quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I tried to just go, da-da-da-da-da, start doing the main quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got murdered ten ways from Sunday, like, so horribly because my character wasn't buffed up enough yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hadn't really practiced with spells and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: My character didn't have enough stuff, so it kind of took me a little while to get used to that, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great game, and I think it's a way for folks who are in the first-person shooters and that genre game, sort of like a really good entry-level RPGs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you're the type of person that's like, I hate RPGs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe this is more your style.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's different types of RPGs.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not a Final Fantasy RPG by any means.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is completely different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually, it really reminds me of an old PC, which makes sense, I mean, when you consider what the game is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It reminds me of an old
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Although honestly, I just don't know how long I'm going to be able to put up with it before my brain explodes from all that stuff to do and just a million other games I want to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if I get too far into Oblivion, I'm not going to play anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the best thing you've got to know about Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion, join the guilds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because when you join the guilds, you can clear off their entire shelves of everything and go sell it for money.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best part.
[SPEAKER_04]: I spent like a couple hours just clearing off everything until I found out about the dupe, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Sold back.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Kibbles and Bits in our chatroom says, Oblivion is one of those games you have to experience on your own.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just too damn huge to rush, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not like a typical gaming experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something you really have to invest a little time in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Andrew?
[SPEAKER_03]: You said you were having problems just getting slaughtered in Oblivion, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Oblivion, the way it works is the enemies level up as you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you level up, they're going to level up, and you're still going to get slaughtered.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought I remembered reading that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: The trick is to gear up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I need, because I'm still using the crappy gear you get in the beginning, minus what I raided from dead bodies.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, I need to gear up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, gear up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because when they hit me, I take massive damage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, I thought I was going to say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked up Prey, because I like the demo, but I haven't played past the demo sequence yet, so more to come on Prey next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait for them to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, real quickly, one other game I want to mention, Cloning Clyde.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked that up too from Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely reminds me of an old Super Nintendo puzzler with a sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I keep wanting to say like Krusty's Funhouse type game, except Krusty's Funhouse wasn't that great, but Cloning Clyde's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if you are curious if you're going to like Cloning Clyde or not, seriously, just check out the demo because I think it's got a really good demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about Galaga?
[SPEAKER_05]: Galaga I checked out too, thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very easy achievement points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super easy achievement points.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I had a friend on my Xbox Live list who got all 200 achievement points within a couple hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: The thing about Galaga is it lets you continue from the stage where you died.
[SPEAKER_05]: So getting that level 30 achievement or whatever is not a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all the monsters and those achievements, you kind of pick those up along the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's very few that require a lot of real skill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Galaga...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not really an arcade game that I remember fondly from the 80s, but I know other people do who are probably yelling at me right now for saying that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it just really depends what type of games you were raised on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there is an audience for Galaga.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I was it because I got bored of it pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blackwolf, Bobby, he was saying that be careful with the side images because it causes burn-in on your screens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's not a game I would play for an incredibly long time anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: What you just said reminded me of something, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: If anyone's ever interested in any of those Namco keychains like they were handing out at E3, you can actually buy them at Kid Robot store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Kid Robot has a site online.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the ones that were selling those big vinyl gorillas figures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have a store on Hayton Ashbury in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Namco and E3 and stuff, I saw some old pictures last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found some old pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found the pictures from the year that they were demoing We Heart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_05]: And remember when they had the giant Katamari and everybody was putting their stuff on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I found the picture of us putting the ferret on the Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also put one of our demo samplers on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a Reject False Icon sticker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, see in chat, GK128 says, Galaga sucks, you sir suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that Galaga sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It certainly led the way for a certain genre of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, it's not my bag, baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you can continue from where you died.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That kind of eliminates the whole hardcore factor of Galaga.
[SPEAKER_03]: They hit it with a nerf bat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't they put, like, Ikaruga on live?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I mean, that would be... But that's right, there's better stuff coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually just reminded me of the other pinball I saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Austin Powers' pinball.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we need Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_05]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Radiant Silvergun would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zaku has it as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gradius, greater than Galaga.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to see Gradius.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, I already have Gradius Collection on PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Gradius was coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there's some shooter that was in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Gradius and Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Contra and Super Contra are coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Contra was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know it was Contra and Super Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Contra and Super Contra and I think Gradius and I've heard some other ones and Street Fighter 2 next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw Time Pilot in that preview too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Time Pilot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Rally X is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week of course Street Fighter 2 which I couldn't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that it's finally here I'm very meh about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like I kind of don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that it's here it's like
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it really going to be that great?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, something else I think that our chat room might be vaguely interested in is that the person that we bought our Twilight Zone from was the guy who owned Working Designs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have a Goemon doll now that they were going to put out with the next game they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get them on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should talk to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll still get a copy of Sega Ages for Saturn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I thought that that would be just a fun little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie of the OL Army says Konami was a lot better than Namco in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it just depends what you're into.
[SPEAKER_02]: It depends on if you read a Namco arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just depends on the type of games you're into.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, enough about my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do some housekeeping real, real quick, and then we'll get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just some quick housekeeping things.
[SPEAKER_05]: OrangeDanceRadio.com had some website downtime earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not sure what caused it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was some type of DNS issue, tech stuff that goes above my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Needless to say, when stuff like that happens, our fearless webmaster, MrVXJasonXV, who we love and adore because he does the job for free, is on things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're sorry, but that type of stuff is going to be inevitable, that things go down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, it's all free to you guys, so just keep in mind, things are going to happen once in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are addressing some things with the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may see some real facelifts coming to the website in the future, but a lot of that is a long ways down the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't talk about much more than that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could, but it'd be a lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we'd have to kill you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd have to reveal what happens at the secret OLR staff meetings, and then you'd have to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the murders commence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, we want to say something about the podcast awards real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: The podcast awards nominations were announced, and we're not there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: The folks that were nominated, all five of them, independent podcasts, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we said, you know, we'd be happy as long as an independent won it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to hog it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can share.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, in all seriousness, folks that were nominated, there's some great shows in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know the folks at Gamertag, very passionate about what they do.
[SPEAKER_05]: DreamStation, huge community over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: VGN Radio, fellow all-games show, completely different vibe than what we do here, but that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think every independent show should do their own thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Podtacular, Halo, nothing but Halo, which for some gamers, that's what they do, nothing but Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good show over there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So,
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vote for an independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have a choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to vote for an independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we could invite the winners on our show so we could hand over our crown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like at Miss America, what they do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where is our crown?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's sitting on Jamie's fireplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is sitting on my fireplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's on my mantle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll come up with something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: have fun remember independent podcasts we're there to support each other I think every independent podcaster brings something different to the table and you look at those shows I previously named and they're all they've all got something different like you know we have the music you know we have that history being the music game and you know we go to anime expos because a lot of our fan base goes there's these other shows have their own spin on things that they do so you know it's great and diversity is what makes the independent stand out over the commercial stuff um
[SPEAKER_05]: In a way, though, I almost kind of feel sorry for whoever wins, because you're going to have to put up with that same backlash that we did last year from kind of the corporates who I think probably didn't like it that we won, because there was some nasty stuff written about us, including, oh, we're liars, we're drunks, da-da-da, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only on certain shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're still here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're almost at episode 200.
[SPEAKER_05]: You corp casts are not going to scare us away, and, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: So what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't get nominated.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fun to do an entire show of lies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lying and being drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drunken lie show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun with the podcast awards this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: And vote in the other categories, too, because there's some other independent podcasters in other categories.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some I've been listening to since, you know, that have nothing to do with gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been listening to since we started podcasting and good stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some actual gaming news now, and huge news, Jamie, huge news.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very big.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know how every year we get our butts into E3 and cover all the big news that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That has gone right down the crapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will be no more E3 as it is known now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an important footnote, as it is known now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there might be something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, basically, Doug Lowenstein, who's the president of Entertainment Software Association, is going to make the announcement that it's gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye-bye, kaput.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it kind of stinks that we're recording on Sunday, because there'll be more information on this tomorrow, Monday, but we won't be here until next Sunday to really talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, a lot of the reason being is that the publishers are, I guess, they're going, you need to pay attention to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're
[SPEAKER_02]: We want love, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, they whined, and E3 listened.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, no more E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there is talk of smaller shows next year, different, more focused events.
[SPEAKER_02]: There already are other shows that go on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, like, you know, the developers put on their own things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft did something recently, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the Microsoft Vision Retail Conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's got something coming up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I'm supposed to say that, but Konami has something coming up, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's other stuff, too, as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of the own developers put on their own shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft's X06 is coming up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to suck to not have it all in one roof.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it will keep, I think, a more even flow of information out for people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes it easier on us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, if we have the different shows come up, introduce their news, we're not putting out... You know, Loki was working his butt off on the PSP site.
[SPEAKER_02]: instead of having to cram everything in and get the information out there before the next guy there's actually going we'll be able to put it out in more digestible forms for other people I think did you see this coming did anybody see this coming yeah
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw them fussing about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they were just going to close it off to certain groups.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe that might be what they're doing because we've heard downsizing of the show mentioned a lot where it's going to be a very select audience meeting with developers in meeting rooms.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that kind of screws a lot of the small people out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It screws over the small press.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no way in hell we're going to get in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's going to screw over Kensha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody that had a show in Kensha with the exception of Red Octane is going to get screwed too, which is kind of sad because there was some pretty kick-butt stuff in Kensha.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are they going to get it out there now?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I mean it's hard to say because all we have to go off of right now is like kind of a, well, I wouldn't call it rumors, but a very cloudy statement is all we really have to go off of right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, for me, E3 kind of started becoming a farce when there was that whole line of people to see Paris Hilton.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, that was my first clue that something's up with the show that's going to change.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that whole freaking hours-long line of people to see Paris Hilton, that's not what E3 is about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Adam West, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Paris Hilton, not cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because she had a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how did she have a game anyways?
[SPEAKER_04]: Her likeness is in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blaze Revolution says, OK, Independent Gamers Conference in our chat room, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Independent Gamers Conference, something for those Kensha Halls companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a great idea, but will it be covered by the big gaming sites?
[SPEAKER_05]: And granted, we cover it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, you know, we'd like to think that we could take on corporate, but the fact of the matter is, a lot of people get their news from the corporate sites, so the corporate folks don't cover it, or give it as a little footnote in their magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact of the matter is, the corporates are the ones that are at the top of the press list anyways when it comes to these small little sites, or, you know, get-togethers anyways, you know, like, you know, EA's just have their little press event and stuff, and, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the smaller guys don't see invites because, you know what, in their eyes, the smaller guy doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: PooEater says, oh no, what will G4 do for one week a year?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bandit in our chatroom says, did anyone see the video of when E3 opened this year and saw how many people were running just to get to the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, the Wii was a great thing to check out, but that probably is part of the reason why E3 is changing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You put all that together.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you like to see happen from all this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do think the idea of independent shows being the more likely thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do like the idea of different specific companies putting out events where they can cater to their audience a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put more focus into it instead of just their little corner of E3 and having to compete with everybody else there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it'd be cheaper for them anyways because they don't have to make these giant elaborate booths.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can just rent out a building like Konami's Gamer Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: They rented out a club and they just had some machines set up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that was a lot less money for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because a club in the middle of the day when it's not open anyways, that probably didn't cost as much as running a multi-million dollar booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Banda in chat has a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Independent shows open to the public.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not have your Kenshiya show that's open to the public?
[SPEAKER_05]: Get everybody talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, haven't they been trying stuff like this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, like, well, you've got PAX, for example, which is kind of like an E3, you know, in a sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've also got, you know, that show that was in San Francisco, I think, that they had some stuff there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like a lot of small... There's the New York City thing they have, the October one that some of our listeners are trying to get us to go to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember the name of it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had the big DDR tourney.
[SPEAKER_04]: Visual Life or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard of another one in Pennsylvania somewhere that's a big show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not just do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know about this, but why don't they just do the mall tours again?
[SPEAKER_04]: The mall tours?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get into a mall and show off your new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go right to where the consumer is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be very interesting to see what happens as time goes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think there's going to be a show that's trying to take the E3 crown?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think what's going to happen is E3 will still be around next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just going to be a lot smaller and more retarded who gets invited.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of going that way anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Each year you go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first time we went there, we went there as general admission or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then everything was press only.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then you go there last year and we're press and you go there and know, oh sorry, you're not good enough press to get into our press little thing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So next year you come back with even more credentials.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry, you're just still not good enough as these people that have been doing it longer than you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets more ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our chat room is yelling...
[SPEAKER_05]: The East Coast Contingent is yelling digital life, digital life.
[SPEAKER_05]: October 4th through 6th, digital life is where the little guys get their chance and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe that's something that's going to take the place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our good buddy Bobby Blackwell from All Games reminded me of what the deal is in Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in Philadelphia, America's Video Game Expo at vgexpo.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently All Games is doing something with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that should be pretty cool because I don't know what's going to happen now to E3 Outpost Electric Boogaloo that was supposed to happen in 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say they do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: The E3 funeral.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, if you go, we'll go.
[SPEAKER_05]: The E3 memorial.
[SPEAKER_05]: E3 memorial.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have no idea what's going to happen with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just depends on what E3 turns into.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that we should save up our money and go to Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think the Tokyo Game Show will end up taking the crown on this stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: It does anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in a way, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it does in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even Tokyo Game Show I think is too big.
[SPEAKER_04]: I personally like these smaller shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, Konami's Gamer Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got to play the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was not lines to play stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was small.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the way it should be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody got to play the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got all the information.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of the bullshit of, oh, well, sorry, you got to make a meeting in order to see this game that we're showing.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell do you go to a convention for to advertise your game...
[SPEAKER_04]: and then you don't show your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the dumbest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I didn't understand that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like, especially with, you know, the Nintendo thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That kind of pissed me off a little bit because you go there to hype up your new machine so what do you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: You make a line and you hold it behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't get what they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to open up our voicemails of the week on this topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Showroll, there's something different listed, but I think with this breaking news, we should shift our voicemail of the week to this topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you want to give us a call, it's 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not right now during the show, if you're listening live, but any time during the week, give that a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you don't pay your phone bill, then you need to have somebody's permission.
[SPEAKER_05]: And give us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We want to know your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about this announcement with E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially, because there'll be more information on Monday after we've taped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really want to know what your guys' thoughts are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is E3 going to be as relevant as it once was?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this something that... If not, where do you think the must-be place is going to be next year?
[SPEAKER_05]: We want to know your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: So leave us a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 916-226-9671.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know where I kind of wanted to go because I knew Nellie wasn't going to let me go to E3 next year, but now she's even more happy that it's canceled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or at least, you know, possibly canceled.
[SPEAKER_04]: Comic-Con.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Comic-Con would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be interesting to see if Comic-Con picks up some of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Comic-Con had a ton of games there anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, they have movie stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could speculate forever, but we won't know for real until we get some more information.
[SPEAKER_04]: Comic-Con's talking about another show that's way too much stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of stuff that doesn't even have to do with comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on to another story here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We talked about independent podcasts and independent developers being hurt by E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to talk about this independent production.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had some folks from this production on our show a couple months ago, and it's a game that's being made called The Silver Lining.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, at one time, this was known as King's Quest IX, The Silver Lining, but there was a whole little bit of back and forth with Vivendi, who owns the rights to King Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Vivendi, there was a whole Save the Silver Lining campaign, and they were, you know, I'd call it a success.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vivendi is allowing this game to be released, only the title is now simply The Silver Lining.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they had a big press event today.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like a virtual press event, and they were nice enough to invite me, because we had them on the show previously, so I checked it out, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: I would call this King's Quest labor of love.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is so obvious to me that the folks behind this game just absolutely love these characters that I'm assuming most of them grew up with, you know, through the various King's Quest games.
[SPEAKER_05]: How can you blame them?
[SPEAKER_05]: The King's Quest characters were awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even I love, like, King's Quest 4, Rosella, and, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they have really just poured their hearts into this fan project.
[SPEAKER_05]: And their big news today is that they've actually released a playable demo that you can download for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to check this out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the other cool part about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio, we're mirroring that demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download it on our site right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check out www.orangeslaunchradio.com Go to the downloads page and you're going to see what you heard on the show recently You're going to see the Silver Lining demo available to you It's about 77 megs, it's free, check it out The art style is very King's Quest 5, King's Quest 6-ish It's kind of 3D
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not unfaithful to the previous games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an early build, but it just is a sign of things to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not just that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually had a guy write an original song for the game, and they released the song today.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have voice actors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like what you'd see going into a high-dollar production, but it's all happening on an independent scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.tsl-game.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it the Project Gotham 360 bundle?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Project Gotham 3 with the 360 being bundled and everything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Despite what all those other websites out there say, not happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Confirmed by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my thing though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not happening in the United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: All these sites that are listing it from what I've noticed so far, like Toys R Us I think was in Canada and I think the EB one I saw was in Canada too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe happening in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be something because maybe the 360 is just not selling as well as the United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you might see a bundle either being put together by retailers themselves or maybe being done in another country.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look for that, but it is not happening in the United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they really have to worry about dropping the price, especially with the PlayStation 3 being so expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really not worried about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eddie is one of our Canadian listeners in chat and says there is no EB game website for Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one site I saw, I assumed it was Canada because all their prices were wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they were listing everything at $69.99 retail for all the Xbox 360 games and that's way off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be happening in another country.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my only assumption that people are getting this from some place.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Microsoft is saying no.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, take it as you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have some things that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's refreshing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have more news about games that aren't coming out in this country.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, because they probably already have or will be around the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: So enjoy these UK guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: So these are the games that will be released first week in August.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the first, we have Pox Nora for PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we have, on the fourth, Monster House for various systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pro Stroke Golf World Tour 2007, ooh, golf.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Stroke.
[SPEAKER_02]: and SingStar Anthems on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a few things that are announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, SingStar Anthems is the gay one, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one that they're marketing towards the gay audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember talking about this a few shows ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still not interested, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But our listeners over there should keep their eyes open, though later on in the month there's going to be Dig Dug Digging Strike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guilty Gear, Dust Strikers, and Star Fox Command.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the United States, though, we're getting some pretty neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: First thing's going to be Flat Out 2 on PlayStation 2, Xbox, and also, I believe, the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that should be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we're getting Super Monkey Ball Adventure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're a fan of the Super Monkey Ball games, look for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many of those freaking Monkey Ball games are there now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Too many.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2, GameCube, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe there was also Barnyard coming out, which is based on the upcoming animated film.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, that just made me think of Barnstorming.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're an old-school 2600 player, you've got to know Barnstorming.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was one of the baddest games they had.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, bad meaning good, because this was the 80s after all.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the baddest games on the Xbox 360 was Barnstorming.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't they remake that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want Barnstorming 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Move over, chickens, here I come.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's basically the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really waiting for the week after that, though, where Dead Rising's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: 99 Nights is around the corner, too, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Rising's coming out, and 99 Nights is the week after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Saints Row at the end of August, as well as Madden.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was at a GameStop today, finally getting rid of Top Spin 2, because I just didn't freaking play it, and picking up Prey.
[SPEAKER_05]: and um they uh were taking the pre-orders for uh you know those games but they were like you know they had the demo or they had the um really nice setup there for 99 Nights coming soon Dead Rising coming soon all that stuff so and I checked out the trailer on Xbox 360 for Dead Rising very bloody very fun oh I can't wait parents are gonna be mad Jack Thompson's gonna have a stroke it's gonna be great ooh really?
[SPEAKER_02]: get that on tape somebody
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sopranos on Xbox 360 It got the big boot
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be honest, I totally forgot they were making this game, so no loss here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't watch the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think that the reason's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: THQ is saying because there's no difference between that and the PlayStation 2 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that hasn't stopped them from releasing other multi-platform games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then again, they're not EA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe this is a different developer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they just have a different outlook on this, a more realistic outlook of,
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we just don't want to upcode the damn thing and sell it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's just a waste of our time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they were saying that after they spoke to their... After a few financial conferences, they basically said it's discontinued.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation 2 version is still going to go through.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be out around Christmas or Yule or whatever holiday you worship.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just in time for the show to be going off the air, from what I understand, because I think their last season's coming up, or early 2007 or something, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the game is supposed to be sort of a GTA style, as in you go out and do jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't watch the surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I have to roll my eyes a little bit at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of seems like all these mob things are caught in between Scarface.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all copying the... Hey, don't talk bad about Scarface.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movie's a legacy, but I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope when they say GTA-like, it means inspired by, but very different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they're all kind of down in that sandbox games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically like a genre now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, speaking of Scarface, apparently the Xbox 360 version has been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I didn't realize there was an Xbox 360 version coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this thing was announced, what, back in E3 2005 for the 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I didn't even realize that they had decided to continue doing that because it's always been PlayStation 2, Xbox, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie in our chatroom says Scarface was never officially announced for 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I was kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently people have been writing the news stories that it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Therefore, it must be true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the press is saying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're not liars in the corporate media.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or drunks.
[SPEAKER_04]: After all, Final Fantasy XIII looks very much like VII.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: The 360 Scarface not coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP Scarface though is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, Scarface looks very similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess it's very similar to Vice City because Vice City ripped off Scarface.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it should be a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The voice talent in it is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just, I don't know, it looks very fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out in September.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other 360 news while we're at it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do a 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, there is... Did she say she could do a 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know how to read into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty pornographic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in, I can turn around in 360 degrees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jeez, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can do a 60... You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to finish the talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need to know that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so, 360, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're listening to KTMI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox, 360, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have nothing else about the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have something about PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Scarface is coming out on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sort of a stripped down version.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about this game, Dawn of War?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there's more.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has a different name, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Power Money Respect.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a turn-based strategy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, there's this Warhammer 4000 game coming out on the 360 as well called Dawn of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, to be honest, I remember playing Warhammer 4000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Space Marines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I used to have the actual miniatures and stuff, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Warhammer 4000 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This series has been around for a long time, especially in tabletops and PC games now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll actually be getting a 360 version, so that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're also planning on making a PS3 version, of course, whenever that system finally rolls out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look forward to that pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of nice to see them doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember actually Space Marines.
[SPEAKER_04]: They used to do a Space Marines game on the PC, and it had the really cool intro song, but yeah, Space Marines kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I have to mention the Scarface comment in our chatroom because it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of Zaku says, Scarface on the PSP, say hello to my little friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Little?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Pooeater's tagline here, Scarface PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might as well buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing else out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about, there's Vice City Stories coming, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's October.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Gun Showdown's also coming out that same month, though, in, you know, September.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there is stuff coming out on the PSP, but, and NASCAR, if you like NASCAR, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of things that are not funny, Gears of War is, apparently there's some users spamming on Xbox Live some Gears of War stuff, and people are thinking, oh, wow, it's some crappy viral campaign.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, well, we don't really know, but a lot of the messages have been pointing back to Gears of War forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently there's more messages on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently some giant announcement is supposed to be happening this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: How come I'm not getting spammed?
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of makes me feel left out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not getting spammed either.
[SPEAKER_04]: This makes me kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a Gears of War spam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently we're just not real press.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently not.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just not cool enough to be getting spammed.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's just some dick spamming a forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: It happens all the damn time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same people spamming on live, and it's basically some stupid little... It's the main characters' names, and they're Marcus Phoenix, or M. Phoenix in this case.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's, you know, we need your help, can't talk now, don't know who to trust, we'll send more tomorrow, and just kind of messages this very cryptic
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but Gears of War still looks cool, so I forgive it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you really need a viral campaign?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, people think the game's awesome anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, oh, let's hype up Halo 3 because people don't know about Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, at least it's not saying, this is Marcus Fenix, and I want you to check out my new Burnout Revenge clip that I have online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be sure to recommend it.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, Biker's War, coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, November so far, because we're not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: They might push it up, according to some of the rumors out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well now, every week on this program, we like to let DarkSakura, speaking of Gears of War, we like to let DarkSakura start grinding her gears over there and surf the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: That wasn't a 360 joke, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surf the internet up and down and back and forth and try to find a website that she wants you, yes you, our listener, to view promptly because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So DarkSakura, what are the kitties going to be looking at this week per your request?
[SPEAKER_02]: Our listeners are going to be looking at the best page in the universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: OrangeSoundsRadio.com?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's worth a try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, second best page in the universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, what is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: The address is Maddox, M-A-D-D-O-X dot X-Mission dot com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think that this guy's sense of humor is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's kind of controversial.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's controversial.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, even if you don't agree with what he says, at least it's remotely entertaining.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I meant to get his book, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Alphabet of Manliness.
[SPEAKER_04]: C is for Chuck Norris, and there's a whole chapter on him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let the Chuck Norris joke die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step away from the Chuck Norris joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's talking about how badass Chuck Norris is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking to you, Barons, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can dig it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But some of the editorials on here are as follows.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate Cameron Diaz.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Wars Episode III is Steaming Pile of Sith.
[SPEAKER_02]: If these words were people, I would embrace their genocide.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted a video game, not an eternal damnation in hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am a genius.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that was me playing Pink Pals.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are not.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 11 Worst Songs of 2004, which, by the way, they're all U2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ben Stiller should star in every movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And video games you'll never play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of video games will we never play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to pull that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about that backwards compatible Barbie game on the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one game I won't play.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about just the really manly suicide of ramming your head against the pavement?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what game I will play, though, that looks a lot like Barbie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead or Alive Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That trailer is minutes of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't say hours, because the trailer's only a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: He also puts up his hate mail, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently writes a whole article's
[SPEAKER_02]: Based on hate mail.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he did one about Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but then people will write hate mail just to be in the hate mail page.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently he's also banned in several countries.
[SPEAKER_03]: His website is not accessible from... I love what he wrote about Ikaruga, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you suck at video games, don't bother reading this review because this game is hard and I don't want whining retards who can't pass the first level bitching to me about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I say this game is hard, I mean hard like nipples on the playlist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I can't say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, way to go, DarkSakura, trying to earn this show an explicit tag.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Visit for yourself to read what was too hot for DarkSakura to say on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: And moving right along then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of hard, Final Fantasy XI's achievements are fucking impossible is what they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: So far, a lot of the achievements, all 32 of them, you know, are fucking impossible, including most of which are level up your character to 75, you know, excellent, you know, or just finish all the Promethea missions, finish all the changes, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: 30 shitty points for getting my bard to 75.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know how long that'll take?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, you're a fucking bard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bards are the easiest character to fucking level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can attest that they are not easy to level as I was a bard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't achievement points those supposed to be hard to get?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they're badges of honor, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because people bitch when they're too easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we just bitched earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Galaga's achievements are too easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if they're going to be hard, make them worth something like, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: 100 points or something instead of 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to play for 50,000 hours and go, 10 points!
[SPEAKER_05]: They've only got 1,000 to distribute though because that's the Microsoft laws.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: They shouldn't have put achievement points anyways because no one was expecting them and they had to go put them out there and now they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just mad because you'll never get them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not playing that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I canceled it yesterday actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, but I just wasn't playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: After you bought it on 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you can't return that sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I can't return it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someday I might go back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I quit once before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll go back.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: One hell of an expensive frisbee.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I can't addict.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish this would happen to just about everybody that played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I know some great people that play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't talk... I played it for years and years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you're addicted to another crack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have nothing bad to say about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was time for me to move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if there's ever a sequel, you know I'm going to be playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: White Mage, equal, party bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, all those people who are cheating, uh-uh, not anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you were basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: caught cheating.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've actually banned another 2,000 accounts for the use of third-party software tools.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they just don't want to be one-upped by World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because World of Warcraft put out that press release, I don't remember if it was this week or last week, saying they banned like 30,000 people from the game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Squeenix is like, well, we can't let them have the last laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's ban some people too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because we can.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI, honestly, you need the windower.
[SPEAKER_02]: It needs the windower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, but that's a third-party utility, and technically, didn't they ban people for that?
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically anyone who's using the windower is probably included in the ban.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's stupid, because why should they monopolize your resources?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I love World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: At first I was like, eh, but you can play it windowed.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do other things while you're playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I was playing Final Fantasy XI, I had my laptop set up beside me so that I could freaking browse the internet while I was playing a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have my laptop for World of Warcraft because I have Thoughtbot up on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe after years and years of Final Fantasy XI, I can't play a game in a window like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Ragnarok online for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also with Ragnarok, you can't click outside of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to alt-tab.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember kids, Alt Tab lets you switch between your programs on a PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: So which MMO do you think is going to ban people next?
[SPEAKER_02]: City of Villains.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toontown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Matrix.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, hi Sky, how are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I'm really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks so much for being on our program tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, my pleasure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now for those folks that haven't played the game Prey, what do you think they're missing out on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you're definitely missing out on a lot of aliens, Indians, and everything in between.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a great storyline intertwined with shooting and endless hours of fun, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now tell us a little bit about the three separate Prey soundtracks available on directsong.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, directsong.com, first of all, is a website that's been around for almost a year now that features video game music exclusively.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so when Prey came out, we really wanted to showcase the two volumes of the soundtrack for Prey.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's over three hours of music for the video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: and it's all done by Jeremy and Julian Soule who are British Academy Award winning video game composers.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they added the orchestral skills to the game's soundtrack which intertwined very nicely with the video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So those are both available for download on directsong.com and all you have to do is log in and enter your information and stuff like that and then you get the soundtrack and actually
[SPEAKER_09]: industry-leading audio quality.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's twice as good as iTunes and better than most of any of those other sites out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's going at a rate of 320 kilobits.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's almost CD quality.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll pretty much be undiscernible to any normal set of ears.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I know there's a third soundtrack available on the site as well, this Bite Me compilation.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a compilation of music inspired by Prey, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, this is a really fun project that we just put out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And basically what that is, is some of the music is from the video game, including the song that's in the end credits to the game by After Midnight Project called Take Me Home.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we also have original music from MXPX, Real Big Fish, and lots of other artists.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there's 13 artists involved total.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a new thing for video games, to have bands come together
[SPEAKER_09]: and write music specifically for a video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is kind of an industry first as well, where we really wanted to get bands of different genres, so it appeals to all different kinds of people.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got punk rock, we've got mainstream rock, we've got electronica, yet all the songs directly relate to Prey, whether it be through the musical instruments involved or the samples used.
[SPEAKER_09]: or the lyrics and the themes invoked in the lyrics and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of leads into my next question.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it, do you think, about the game Prey that inspires all these artists to create these diverse kinds of music that all come back to being inspired by Prey?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think one of the things that inspired everyone throughout this process is the incredible graphics and the storyline that's portrayed through that.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of these people got to see some video clips and some of the trailers that came out before, as well as we sent everyone an email that had the full storyline of Prey.
[SPEAKER_09]: So everyone saw quickly that this wasn't just a first-person shooter with no story behind it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the storyline was a big part in most of the songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now you yourself contributed two tracks to this compilation.
[SPEAKER_05]: The tracks Existence and Intervention.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did your experience with Prey inspire these tracks that you yourself contributed?
[SPEAKER_09]: Since I've been involved with Prey for about six months or so producing this album, it's been a part of my everyday work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been thinking about it and looking at videos and really been intertwined with it for a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Being inspired by it wasn't that much of a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really wanted to
[SPEAKER_09]: Combine the themes of the game in the music.
[SPEAKER_09]: So in the game, you've got Tommy, the Native American, gets abducted by aliens.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really wanted to portray to the music kind of the same feeling, starting off with Native American themes and then have it be pretty much abducted by aliens and come across with more techno or industrial type sounds and stuff like that and work that all together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I remember actually playing through the Prey demo and then later on the game, and I kind of remember the music was a really big part of setting the atmosphere in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So definitely, you know, music lends itself very well to Prey and is an important part of setting the mood in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we'd like to give our listeners... Oh, I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just going to say that Jeremy and Julian Stoll did a great job, in my opinion, of intertwining the music with the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes you don't even notice there's music going because you're just so...
[SPEAKER_09]: From the high desert in the great American Southwest, I'm Art Bell.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to start the night by opening up the lines.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can already tell you folks, it's going to get very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting some reports of strange lights in the sky from the Oklahoma area.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our affiliate in Oklahoma City is telling us that the state police, get this, are reporting mysterious lights all over the area and that they're having a hard time responding to all of the calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be a wild and woolly night, folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just know it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Caller, you're on the air with Art Bell.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Art?
This Art?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's our caller.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's lights coming in the sky right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right over my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're moving from north to south.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me what they look like?
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly what they look like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me about them?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some are blue, some are green, some are blue, and some red.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my God!
One of them is so kind of a real spaceship.
It's hovering right over me.
It's huge, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take the next call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Strange things are happening in my boat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think someone disappeared?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Paul, I still got my special line.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, now that was Intervention by Nick Murray here on Orange Lounge Radio Nick is joining us tonight to talk about the soundtrack So Nick, Art Bell is in that song
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember hearing that same sample when I played through Prey.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy is a legend in UFO culture.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you get him on board?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, he was actually signed on by Human Head to do some voiceovers for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Human Head Studios was nice enough to give all of the artists involved in the soundtrack a sound tree.
[SPEAKER_09]: And sound clips from the game ranging from aliens vomiting to
[SPEAKER_09]: and Gunshot Sounds to these voiceover samples and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it was really fun to try to remix that into the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now for folks that really enjoyed that song, obviously they could pick up the Bite Me music inspired by Prey soundtrack, but what about your own other music?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have another site where you have your own music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can just go to nickmurraymusic.com and that has my updated blog and streaming mp3s for all my songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, talking about one of the other bands on the CD really quick, the After Midnight Project, of course, has the credit song from the game Take Me Home.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually a whole music video that you can see on the website about this, and I guess you guys, it was on G4 and some of the other TV stations.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did that happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you guys think, oh, let's do a music video out of this?
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, working with After Midnight Project has been really great throughout the whole process.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've been really well integrated
[SPEAKER_09]: Really nice to us, really involved and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really good with promotion.
[SPEAKER_09]: And one of the guys that works with us and actually works with the video game company, who's one of our main connections, named Jaron Moore.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has a film background and really wants to get into film directing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he managed that whole project, the whole music video.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he went out to LA and filmed the band and actually did all the editing and splicing and the game footage and all of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it was a really, really good effort by Jaron.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it turned out really well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, congratulations on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know this has been getting airplay I read about on the site, so that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, talking about the website as a whole, directsong.com, I noticed that Prey isn't really the only thing available there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's several game soundtracks like Oblivion, Dungeon Siege 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think are the advantages of digital distribution for music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, one thing is that games are digital, so we're staying within the same realms as
[SPEAKER_09]: What gamers are used to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Second of all, what we hope to do is give the users more game music expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: So right now you can download expansion packs for Guild Wars on our website, one of the first games that we put up on our website.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that music is brand new music that will then work in game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's a really fun piece of technology that we're offering.
[SPEAKER_09]: besides just downloading the soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It all needs to be digital so it can work into the online games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed that's a really exciting addition I noticed to the site is that you can actually download these new soundtracks for games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And especially when you think about an MMO type of game like Guild Wars where you're hearing the same music over and over, this seems like somebody should have done this a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one of those ideas that you say, man, I wish I thought of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you guys did, so congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun raking in the money there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, now, just kind of out of curiosity, going to the other side of it, because, you know, we're talking about game soundtracks as a whole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people in the past have complained that, you know, why is it that you have all these B-movie soundtracks sitting on store shelves, yet there's no game soundtracks out there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think that, in the end, there's a market for game soundtracks in a CD-based traditional format?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is digital distribution where it's at, and where things are going?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm not quite sure about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've had some distributors come and talk to us about putting these on actual CDs and putting an online store on our site, and that stuff may all be in the future as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: But right now, like I said, this site's only been up for about a year, so that's just basically what we've been rolling out first.
[SPEAKER_09]: In terms of long-term industry, hard for me to say on that one, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: The gaming music is progressing so much as a whole that it will start getting as much clout or as much respect as movie scores as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Myself, I actually just bought an Xbox 360 because I was waiting for my other standard Xbox to die out and it finally just crashed way too many times for me to even handle.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I was stuck playing FIFA 06 on my other Xbox, which actually I've been addicted to that game for months now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, personally I'm more of a sports game guy than a shooter kind of person, but
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you ever do gaming on live?
[SPEAKER_05]: You go online, do any of that stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really got into that yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope to get into that soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of waking up to that whole world of online gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyway, if our folks want to check that out, it's music from Prey.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's two soundtracks as well as the Bite Me music inspired by Prey soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's available on directsong.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nick, thanks so much for joining us tonight on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: My pleasure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there anything else you wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know definitely the music in Prey and Elder Scrolls and all that kind of stuff is actually pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyways, speaking of music, I know Microsoft's been trying to very eagerly keep this whole Zune thing kind of under wraps because of their...
[SPEAKER_04]: surprises and how they're going to basically take over the whole you know music and portable markets well anyways Microsoft exec let's see one of the top ones actually he is basically dismissing the PlayStation 3 and the Wii launches as just pretty much who cares because we're going to be you know launching with our brand new Zune and all that stuff and our system is just awesome and
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, it was just kind of interesting, this was actually being run on MCV Interactive Entertainment Weekly and they were talking about how because the PlayStation 3 price being so high and how that the Wii is basically not able to compete with them processor-wise and graphically that Microsoft doesn't really have anything to worry about as far as winning the next-gen console war, which I think is a bit I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a very good way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe in this country.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of said this a long time ago on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very interesting what this next-gen war is going to be on a worldwide scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Xbox is still struggling in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised that they don't look at it with the success of Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't take great graphics and stuff to make an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at the upcoming...
[SPEAKER_04]: Castle Crashers or whatever that was.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's simple graphics and just fun gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't need to be all... Yeah, seriously, one of the most anticipated titles, Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Street Fighter 2, yeah, perfect example.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just all about gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, they were comparing the GameCube or the Wii, it's all... Although the Wii is almost a GameCube with a DVD drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo... Is Nintendo going to have enough quantity to satisfy the demand?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're talking about shortages.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the
[SPEAKER_04]: Pot calling the kettle black, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But basically they said, you know, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got a lot of Quarter 4 surprises coming, of course, with the Zune and whatever they're going to be, you know, possibly linking the Zune with 360 and PC Vista, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to wait and see, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there actually is a little bit more about a Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, people by now know that we've had our little bit of excitement over Osutatakayo and on getting a US release as Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's a list released, a partial list, I should say, of songs that might be in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Stereogram Walkie Talkie Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, by the way, coming from Bin Mani Style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deep Purple Highway Star, Eve Six Inside Out, Ricky Martin, Livin' La Vida Loca.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Savage Garden, Truly Madly Deeply.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weird Al Yankovic, Hardware Store.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weird Al Yankovic, that's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Linkin Park, In The End.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, just lost interest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the song that should be playing while you're playing, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's for the MySpace kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I was actually going to say why you're playing R-Type.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Offspring, hit that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Queens of the Stone Age, Go With the Flow, Kylie Minogue, Locomotion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why can't they pick any of her new stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guns N' Roses, Sweet Child of Mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can dig that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bare Naked Ladies, One Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spirit Snare in our chatroom says, LOL, Emotendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Emotendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's also some new features that are going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's single-card multiplayer now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there will still be multi-card multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also send the equivalent of the E3 demo, which is Walkie Talkie Man, Highway Star, and Tutorial Mode from the Japanese game by download play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's two new scenarios.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a young man trying to win the heart of his dream girl, and a construction worker who's behind on a project and has one hour to finish it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, Hardware Store sounds like the song for that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it sounds like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was most... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: This gives me more incentive to import.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, what's most interesting about that song list is it kind of really makes the Japanese ones stand out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, these are really two different games.
[SPEAKER_05]: TechnicBeat TechnicBeat
[SPEAKER_05]: Luminous 2 Heavenly Star Tetsuya Mizuguchi and his team actually created the song and it
[SPEAKER_04]: Supposedly insanely catchy, and also I'm going to have a really awesome video to go with the background, which features an alien singer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was Hollaback Girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Incredibly catchy song with alien singer?
[SPEAKER_04]: A simply stunning video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Hollaback Girl would follow on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he says he was inspired by Take On Me with...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: If there at any point is a reference to Luminous 2 going, this game is bananas, B-A-N-A-N-A-S, I will have a video on YouTube of me smashing my PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else that sometimes makes me want to smash something is Myspace.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, join the Orange Lounge Radio Myspace.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Myspace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Kotaku ran a very interesting observation earlier this week on their site capturing a very interesting MySpace ad and you guys can maybe see that ad here in studio a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess, I don't know if that's a guy or a girl or something, whispering to a hot chick, quote unquote, and then there's another hot chick sitting there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like, you know, everybody's dream of two chicks, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not my dream, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think those are two chicks about to make out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the text on there says, horny gamer girls looking for fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm wondering, is this like targeted advertising by Myspace?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I know whenever, you know, it's no real secret on this program, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And whenever I log on to MySpace, that's all I ever get are gay personal sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, how many freaking times I could see these ad banners is incredible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, I will probably never see this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'll get a Horny Gamer Guys, but I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't seem to be the... Is this an incentive for me to unblock ads?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: MySpace has some pretty funny ads, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know why we brought this up, but I suppose gamers are being targeted in advertising on Myspace, so keep an eye out for the ad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just don't click on it, because then that shows you support this, and there'll be more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you want there to be more, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I support hot, you know, gamer girls making out with each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: I support that fully.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my endorsement.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pig.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other thing I support fully is violence!
[SPEAKER_04]: And much violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now this, this, I can... This I can
[SPEAKER_05]: I think all of OLR can agree on this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Violence in games is wonderful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Violence is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, in Iowa State researchers have found violent gaming sessions can reduce the psychological response or physiological response of real-life violence in the short term.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I question this still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, going this further, they basically had a...
[SPEAKER_04]: 257 college students and they were made to play certain games and they were following with real life violence 20 minutes later.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they were showing them and seeing what their reactions were.
[SPEAKER_04]: The games they made them play though, well these are just a bit old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's a very good representation of games nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Carmageddon, Duke Nukem 3D,
[SPEAKER_04]: Mortal Kombat, Future Cop, which were on the violent side.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've never heard of these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glider Pro, 3D Pinball, 3D Munchman, and Tetra Mattis on the non-violent side.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm reminded somehow of that scene from A Clockwork Orange.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember that scene where they're forcing them to watch all the movies?
[SPEAKER_05]: For some reason, this whole story reminds me of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're shoving all these violent games down someone's throat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Duh, they're going to be numb to the imagery after a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's not a matter of violent games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a matter of boring games and non-boring games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say, for example, Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that's much more exciting than 3D Munchman or Glider Pro, a game which sounds like it's probably on a hang glider and you're just flying around doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, those games are boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas, if I'm bored to death and all of a sudden someone shows me a shot of someone being shot point blank, I'm going, whoa!
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas, if I'm kind of awake, I might go, wow, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm not going to be just like, oh my god, that's really offensive because I've been playing Munchman instead of, oh my god, I destroyed giant mutant pigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: That does not offend me in any way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't Munchman the name of the little guy on Square One TV?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mathman, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Munchman, I believe, is a knockoff of probably Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if they did this exact same study, but instead replaced it with the nightly news, Pulp Fiction, Reservoir Dogs, any zombie B-movie flick from the 70s?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, wouldn't it all have the same effect?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this study seems to be kind of, I don't know, like targeted to kind of blame games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like it's skewed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like it seems like there needed to be a control here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are games more desensitizing than the nightly news or than movies?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the study I want to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Show me a comparison.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't just throw these numbers at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my problem with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, do you have a thought on this at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the desensitization goes, there's already a lot of exposure, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like you take the child who grows up never able to watch the news, never able to watch TV, never able to play a video game, and how are they when they grow up and see what the real world is like?
[SPEAKER_02]: They go pretty nuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you take one who may not have been allowed to play video games, but they watch the news with their parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they'll be just as equally...
[SPEAKER_02]: and Desensitized Remedies, someone who's an avid gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been desensitized to violence, but not from games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can control the action on a DVD player too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can rewind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can freeze frame.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole thing is, just like with Saw, for example.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take Saw.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a perfect example.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a basic movie where someone is kidnapped and they have a giant device on their face with spikes in it that's going to basically...
[SPEAKER_04]: Slam into them and kill them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and they also show, you know, someone sawing off their foot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a lot more violent than, say, Duke Nukem 3D, which has pixelated graphics that look like a cartoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, did anyone throw a fit when, you know, the Roadrunner, you know, got Wile E. Coyote to fall off a cliff?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hundreds of feet that he fell to his death.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, oh, sure, he came back later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what happens when you shoot the pig.
[SPEAKER_04]: It spawns later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't see what the big deal is.
[SPEAKER_05]: for me um i i've been gaming a long time i've played a lot of violent games and a lot of you know funny violent games like i love mortal combat but like real blood like my brain totally knows the difference between game movie and real life because like i could watch somebody cut their cut their hand and they need stitches and i freak out like i'm like oh my god it's real blood uh gross gross you know i get all freaked out you know i'm totally one of those i get
[SPEAKER_05]: You drive by a horrific car accident and I'm going to cry if I see a body.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even watching the news, you see a lot of horrible stuff on the news and I just feel depressed.
[SPEAKER_05]: My brain knows the difference between the two.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can feel that reaction to real blood, but then I can play a game and I think it's funny because it's not real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, yeah, you're smart enough to know it's not real.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is wrong with people if they don't know what's real and don't know what's not real?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the bigger problem, not being desensitized to violence, being desensitized to what's reality and what's not reality.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the big problem right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think if people are that retarded, well, they need to be put in some sort of mental hospital because obviously they're not fit for society.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that, again, this goes back to parental responsibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is their job.
[SPEAKER_02]: When they brought that life into the world, they had an unwritten contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: They would make sure that this entity would grow up to be a functional member of society.
[SPEAKER_02]: That if they could not become a functional member of society, they would help them seek the treatment they need.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead of going, oh, therapist, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not noticing if there's anything else that might be causing the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I think that a good parent will pay attention to what their child... You know, I admit, a child is going to be sneaky.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a sneaky kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to be able to be there 24-7, but if a parent takes an active interest in what their children are doing, participates in their life instead of dictates their life, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they'll be as much of a... They don't have a right to blame a game when it's their responsibility for making sure that their child turns out how they feel is right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if they think that the game is going to desensitize them to violence later and want them to retain a feeling of sensitivity, they need to limit how much their child's going to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's the problem with human nature these days.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are far more apt to blame other things, other objects, blame the TV, blame a video game for what's really the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Your kid is just a maladjusted dick.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a lack of accountability.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think it's a lack of self-accountability.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you, I'm sorry, cops, the TV, this stuff is out there all the time in any of your dramas, like 24, I mean, how many Law and Order, police, you know, dramas out there right now, this stuff is all over the place, like, and people aren't probably surprised about that, because it's like, yeah, I've seen that before, you know, it's kind of like, you know, um, I don't know, it's like, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Pamela Anderson naked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen that before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like, wow, oh my god, I was not expecting her to have breasts under there, but it's just, you know, it's not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to be... For example, if you're like, you know, playing these boring ass knockoffs of games by the sound of the generic names that they have, 3D Munchman, you know, if you're playing that, then all of a sudden they show you, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Prison Fight, I'm going to be like, hell yeah, this is a lot better than 3D Munch, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, so I don't know what the hell they were expecting.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, I got to let our chat room have a say here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Over at OrangeLawnTrader.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie of the Oil Army says, my mom played Halo for a few weeks with me when I first got my Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for your mom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you know, the family that plays together is closer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds...
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost dirty, though, but that's not true.
[SPEAKER_05]: GK128 says, There is a difference between violence in a video game and violence from, say, a real video where a dude is blown to bits from a torrent.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gross, but true.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya says, Hello Kitty drove him to violence.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello Kitty drives everyone to violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funnydale seems to think Munchman was a knockoff of an 80s porn film, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave it to him to make the funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other thoughts on this topic?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd love to get your thoughts in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com If you want to send us some emails, Jamie's going to be digging into the mailbag in our next segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sure will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this time I'm going to need an extra thick hazmat suit this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe some asbestos gloves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just one last thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they want to test whether people are desensitized to violence, they don't need to show courtroom battles, cops, that kind of thing like Loki said.
[SPEAKER_03]: Show some pictures of some guy with his head blown off by a shotgun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuff you would see on shock sites.
[SPEAKER_03]: That will test your sensitivity to violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Courtroom Battle made me think of Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Objection!
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: People don't need to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen pictures of people eating babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty disturbing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Courtroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or outbursts in a courtroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never seen that in a movie before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cops, oh my god, never seen cops before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I object to where this show is headed, so I think it's time that we have a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of violence real quick though, I need to get this out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't listen to the rebroadcast of Orange Lounge Radio over on allgames.com, there will be violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we'll poke you in the nose and call you a poopy head.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, we're moving times over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There have been some schedule changes over all games.
[SPEAKER_05]: East Coasters are going to love this.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show is now Mondays at 5 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pacific Standard Time, which would be 8 o'clock for you East Coasters.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if we're making you stay up too late on a Sunday, you can always listen to the show in its entirety, parts A and B, over on allgames.com on Monday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's right after the big live show they do, All Games Interactive, which is taped live at the Arena Interactive Lounge, home of the E3 Outpost.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know what's going to happen with that next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see in light of what we've talked about earlier in this segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back a little later with more of Orange Lounge Radio.