[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_09]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio episode number 192.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're back here on this part B of our podcast and after a very exciting and
[SPEAKER_11]: Strange Part A. We're back here to bring you some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're brand new to the Orange Launch Radio podcast, welcome.
[SPEAKER_11]: We podcast our show twice a week on our podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is the second half that you're hearing right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to download the first half, you need to fire up iTunes or whatever you're using to get your podcast and just head on back in the archive and you can download the first half of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or you can always listen to both parts back to back when you listen live to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can listen to us live on Sunday nights,
[SPEAKER_11]: at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pacific Standard Time on OrangeLoungeRadio.com or if you missed that because you're watching Big Brother or something that's on Sunday nights, you can always catch us on the All Games Syndication and that's available at AllGames.com Monday nights at 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pacific Standard Time right after All Games Interactive or a couple times throughout the afternoon on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're here to talk about video games and get right back into the news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's starting us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Queen DarkSakura, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, we've got some good news for our European listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it's also good news for our American listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a release from Nintendo of America stating that there was a small number of DS lights that had a crack in the casing on the left-hand side of the hinge.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's just above the power connector and it's like a .02% of the units have it so they're fixing those for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Nintendo of Europe basically has announced that any faulty DS lights will be repaired for free as long as the fault in question is covered under the valid warranty.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically they're saying that if you have a problem with it you need to contact the local customer service area for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: The DS lights carry a one-year warranty for manufacturing defects.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's covered under the warranty, it will be repaired for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you live in the UK, the number to call for Nintendo's customer service, and I have no idea how the phone numbers work, is 0870-6060-247.
[SPEAKER_05]: Open 830 to 7 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: at national rate.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can also email at nintendoservicecenter at codestorm.co.uk And that's center spelled American way, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: ER.
[SPEAKER_11]: The whole My DS is on Crack saga is very interesting, what's been going on with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo kind of first came out and said it's not a problem, but then just a couple days later they kind of did this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not just in the UK, but I know they've got something similar going on in the US as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Both the DS lights I've seen, Miklatov has one and my roommate Extifer has one,
[SPEAKER_11]: and they're not cracking yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine's neither.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, oh, that's right, you got one too.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could look at it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't seem like it's this huge epidemic, but it's very interesting that Nintendo is kind of listening to the internet buzz and kind of...
[SPEAKER_11]: Saving their ass from internet skewing left and right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's good customer service, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they might actually be skewing the numbers of how many DS lights are cracked.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, this was pointed out actually by MaxConsoleReader, there was a photo taken at the New York City flagship Nintendo World Store, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Six to seven or six to eight of the DS lights in the store had the cracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of them were hairline cracks that were developing, and some were just full-blown cracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that doesn't sound like .02% to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, food for thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, speaking of other things, including the DS here, we've got a brand new game coming to the DS, which is actually kind of an interesting name.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's...
[SPEAKER_08]: Translates to Mario Nation Gears, and there's going to be 100 varieties of mechs, which not all of them will be simple two-legged robots.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of the machines will resemble insects, while some others transform the vehicles, and they'll have a variety of weapons, from bows to firearms.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says the game's going to be played in full 3D.
[SPEAKER_08]: The bottom screen is going to show the mech controls, which can be operated using the touch stylus.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, I don't know, very interesting, especially with this game also kind of with Mario Nation Gears, maybe a Mario-themed mech game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Mario has to be in everything!
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, but yeah, I don't know, it's a different type of game, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to have DS download stations at Toys R Us with six exclusive virtual gifts.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get a one-up mushroom, a star, a fire bar.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you love fire.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gold flag, a question box, and a pipe.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can use this to decorate your virtual house and make all your internet friends jealous that you went to Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get these downloads through July 29th at your Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to do that, Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I might, just so that I can...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to probably get rid of my bathroom that I'm building in my house and make a Nintendo room so that my HRA score goes up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you ever rebuild your shrine to fire?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I did not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a bathroom and I have a room with a bath in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the outdoor bath.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have my huge-ass Japanese room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a classic room because I always make a classic room.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have a green room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although the green room might be turned into a shrine to fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do, however, have the bonfire.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just haven't used it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: For those that don't know, DarkSakura on the GameCube version of Animal Crossing had a shrine to fire that I always felt compelled to visit.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of the items was just a giant campfire, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: A big bonfire.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then you had all these drums that would play and all the little gyro thingies or whatever those are called.
[SPEAKER_05]: They would gyrate around it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bowing down to the fire and the music was like boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the Japanese festival music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Scary, scary stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it had like Biwa Lutes in the back and yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: HitStun says you should play Second Life and get a Shrine to Fire in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one of those virtual world games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've checked out briefly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Email me a link to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie at OrangeLoungeRadio.com I think our buddies at All Games have something set up there, and I think our picture's in the game because of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know if there's an Orange Lounge area.
[SPEAKER_11]: There should be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't we just kind of hang out in the All Games area, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you, Andrew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew's going to make us one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, let's keep it moving, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I like Animal Crossing a whole lot, as you well know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, guess what I'm all hyper and excited about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dobutsu no Mori, the movie!
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who don't know what that means, it means Animal Forest, which was the Japanese name of Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually own that game, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the GameCube one in Japanese, but that's another story.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was a Nintendo 64 game originally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Originally it was, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have the whole unlock disc thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, the reason I bought it was to help my reading skills go up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, they have released... There is a...
[SPEAKER_05]: A movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a cute trailer online.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, if you want to go see the official website for it, it's at doubutsunomori-movie.jp I'll spell that out for people who don't know how.
[SPEAKER_05]: doubutsunomori-movie.jp
[SPEAKER_05]: slash index.html It has interactive content online and also the trailer is available online if you do not know how to read Japanese, guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a quick follow-up on the Second Life thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, All Gamesville actually was taken down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Funnydale says the guy who set it up had to delete the Arena Lounge from Second Life because he needed to save money.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll just have to build it again!
[SPEAKER_11]: Except this time it'll be the Orange Lounge Megadome.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, we'll have all games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hordom, of course, as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anywho, I was going to mention there's some actual new Wii pages that were on the Nintendo site.
[SPEAKER_08]: The official Nintendo site there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Super Secret stuff was on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, it's kind of funny because the Wii pages ended up being on there, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: We Music is a full-blown game for the Wii, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Wii Music, for those who might not remember, during E3 was kind of like that demo where you're conducting an orchestra.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Among other things, of course, more information about the Wii Connect 24, and just kind of talking about some of the upcoming games, most of which were announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: But of course, if you want to check it out now, you can't because Nintendo pulled down the site and all the links.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know someone saved the cache file.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but I do have screenshots, and I will hopefully upload them later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get to check this out yourself before they took it out?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I got to check out the screenshots of the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be honest, it wasn't anything that we hadn't already really known.
[SPEAKER_11]: No earth-shattering news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing new, no new games announced or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if you are excited to get your chance to play the Wii, you might get your chance a little sooner than you thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: According to Punk News, the Nintendo Fusion Tour this year, you know how Nintendo sponsors this tour, the music fest every year they take around the country?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think, didn't they have Evanescence one year, I want to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I'm on crack, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they have different artists that do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're actually going to feature the Wii console at
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo Fusion, and you will be able to try the console for yourselves hands-on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully no five-hour lines like E3, but seeing as probably that many people that were in that line wouldn't be able to fit into a freaking arena, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully your chances will be much better to actually get a chance to play the Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you're not feeling so hot about the bands, hey, go and you could play the Wii while the main band's on stage.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then again, that is an awful lot of money just to play a Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you really have to be a true Nintendo fanboy or fangirl to want to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, if you go, have fun and email us and tell us how it went for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, just about two weeks or so after the October 18th day.
[SPEAKER_08]: And remember how we were speculating October 18th would be the actual launch day for the Wii in the United States?
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes sense that there would be a two week delay until the Wii came out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_11]: I seem to remember we talked about some story on the show before, though, that supported a six-week delay for the UK, and that's why, because some release dates had leaked for the UK, like Red Steel or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to go back in the archives a few episodes, but that UK delay seems to shift...
[SPEAKER_11]: around when they bring up these different ideas for release dates?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, but to be honest though, November 3rd as the release date for Need for Speed Carbon sounds... I don't know, it sounds a little bit late to me, because I know Carbon's coming out in October in the United States.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, if that were true, if that actually was the launch date for the UK, I would say that the 18th is pretty feasible for
[SPEAKER_08]: The United States, but right now it's just completely rumor-based.
[SPEAKER_08]: And even rumor-based based on saying that this date... I mean, because there are obviously titles that come out a week or two later than the release date, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to say so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, as far as the release dates go...
[SPEAKER_05]: Release dates go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually do have the list of release dates for the 28th in the UK, if anybody is interested.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure, I want to know, even though I don't live there, but I know our friends that live there want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Civ City Rome is coming out, Civilization IV Warlords.
[SPEAKER_05]: Field Commander, Formula 106, Juiced Eliminator, Pac-Man World 3 on the PC, Shin Megami Tensei, Siphon Filter, Dark Mirror, The Ant Bully, Tokyo Extreme Racer, and Tringo on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm, alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: isn't getting much more stuff being released, but anyways...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tekken Dark Resurrection, which is going to be a pretty big game, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Painkiller Hell Wars is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So far, I think that game actually might be delayed again, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Civ IV Warlords for the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Civ City Rome also on the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other than that, I think, what was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ant Bully is coming out on the consoles and the portables.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a big, you know, blank space there until...
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the undead.
[SPEAKER_11]: You must be interested in Dead Rising too, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, getting to kill zombies with anything you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I especially love watching them.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are a zombie some days.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some days.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've seen you in the morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have seen me in the morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like... It's like that scene in Shaun of the Dead where he's just getting up and stumbling to the door.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: So do I.
[SPEAKER_11]: All righty, well, thank you for the release date news.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, I feel sometimes left out when we do release dates, because DarkSakura does them and Loki does them, so I'm going to figure out, like, what our third... You can do the Ugandan one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot to mention some stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to confirm a few things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a rumor control, or not rumor control, retail radar thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: PS3 is not out until November 17th?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sorry, I thought you said PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: PS3 is in November.
[SPEAKER_11]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that was really interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_11]: As I was saying, I feel left out when it comes to release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to figure out what our third most listened to country is and do the release dates for there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's Australia.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should do the Australian release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll look into that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe I could rotate around some of the other countries that listen to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, maybe we should start covering Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, that's not a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe we could go back and forth or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see what to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll have to tutor you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, if we go there, then we're switching.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can do Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll do UK release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's easier for me because I've never taken a class.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, we'll talk about that at our next staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_11]: For now, let's talk about what Microsoft might be talking about at their staff meetings.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blu-ray and what the hell they're going to be doing about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, Major Nelson actually interviewed Amir Majidimur on his latest podcast, I suppose, or I'm sorry, blogcast, as he calls it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And his group, Amir's group at Microsoft, oversees the audio-video compression technologies and had something interesting to say about Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_11]: According to Majid Amir, Blu-ray moves the recording surface very close to the top layer of the disc, protected by just a very thin coating, and this makes maintaining the high reliability of discs during the actual manufacturing process much more difficult.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, this factor is a really big difference between Blu-ray and HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, HD DVD, like traditional DVDs, actually protects its data between two layers of protective plastic, above and below, thus making the manufacturing of the discs much more reliable.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, kind of interesting there, the differences between the two formats, because
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess when you look at them on an HDTV, there probably won't be a whole lot of difference, but it's hard for me to say when I haven't seen a lot of demos of Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we shall see if Sony's next format takes off or ends up going the way of UMD.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been hearing not good about it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm thinking maybe it's just because it's easy to pick on Sony right now, but I try to keep some hope, but it gets harder and harder every day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, there's some actual funny stuff coming out here from EA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I should say an EA employee who admitted to releasing crappy games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know EA is kind of a scapegoat here, but
[SPEAKER_08]: They do have a lot of games that are just ports, especially the next-gen stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember the Xbox 360 launch and how a lot of the games were just ports of the current-gen stuff with slightly more high-res graphics or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyways, there's actually a YouTube video out there now that you can play.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little bit of a funny little thing there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, crappy games do not make us happy gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when we're not happy, we get ranty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't you start us off with our favorite segment, the FUs of the week, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, it's so hot!
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to the hot!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear sun, piss off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want it to be dark, even more I want it to stay dry, and even more than that I want it to be a nice 72 degrees outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: With slight overcast, and, okay, maybe not dry, maybe a little touch of water in the air so that it doesn't hurt to breathe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried breathing outside, and it felt like I was breathing plaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, an FU goes to our 113 degrees today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even worse that it's nighttime and 95 degrees.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had our thermostat set down to 70.
[SPEAKER_05]: It read 85.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Celsius, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a sub-FU to everyone who complains about the, quote, humidity, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, screw off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Piss off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Piss off right back at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not humid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to have to say F you to my cable being out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or not my cable, but my internet being out at home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comcast decided to take the crap because... Did you pay the bill?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I paid the bill.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, because that's why my internet stops working and my cable's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I didn't pay the bill.
[SPEAKER_08]: That doesn't make any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, so yeah, that really sucks and I couldn't read.
[SPEAKER_11]: My FU of the week goes to Coldstone for being a diet's worst enemy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a victim of deliciousness, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew!
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's been awfully quiet this segment.
[SPEAKER_11]: Surely you have something for this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, I'm going to have to repeat that FU to the hot with a few things added on.
[SPEAKER_12]: FU to the shitty air conditioner that is in our house.
[SPEAKER_12]: The temperature climbs up, air conditioner decides to take a shit, and it's only 95 degrees in the house.
[SPEAKER_10]: No wonder you're here tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's so hot, it has never been so hot in my house that my computer will not run games.
[SPEAKER_12]: My video card overheats and takes a shit, locks up the system within two minutes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is that hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you gonna do?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to have to run to Target and get a room.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think I will spend the night in the lawn and sleep in sprinklers.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is the only course of action for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, good luck to you, sucker.
[SPEAKER_11]: End the angst.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, yes, let's end the angst.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's end the angst and get to our listeners, because they rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: We love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we have a segment that we've been doing for a couple weeks now called the Voicemails of the Week, and we'd love to get your feedback.
[SPEAKER_11]: on different topics.
[SPEAKER_11]: And last week's topic that we gave to you guys for the voicemails of the week was, are games too easy?
[SPEAKER_11]: We have two voicemails we want to play for you tonight, and here's the first feedback on the, are games too easy topic.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Jack Monkey Upload, and basically answering your question of the week, and games back in the day were a lot cheaper to make, and you'd only have like two guys, two or three guys, and it would take them a couple months to make a game, and
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been most of their time making the game itself and the levels were like really easy to make and wouldn't take that much time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But nowadays, the levels for like the new games are spent with like hundreds of maybe thousands of people and like a lot of them are artists that just maybe work on just the levels and some of them might only work on the end levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you spend like tens of millions of dollars on a game, you want everyone to play like the majority of the way through.
[SPEAKER_06]: because if most people only play through like half a million dollars worth of your game, then you might as well just spend half a million on it instead of spending 10 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think this trend's also going to increase because next-gen games are getting really expensive, so you're going to see games that anybody can complete just so they'll get through the majority of it and see everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's all I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll listen to you guys this weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: CopyCode
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I actually, at Classic Gaming Expo, I went to a panel for the guy who did... Oh, God, I can't remember the names.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who did, like, Combat, and Pac-Man, and Battlezone, and a lot of those old Atari classics.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're basically saying about how they were expected to crank out as close to perfect versions of arcade games, and how...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I think, though, that now, because we have such a greater capacity, a lot more does go into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you do have more people you gotta pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does cost more.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, they have to make these levels cost-effective.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on top of that, you know, they also have to think about the attention span of the average gamer today, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anders, you have a thought, too?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, my take on it is, nowadays, you know...
[SPEAKER_12]: Game making is a big business.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's not so much that we're playing games anymore, it's that we're watching them, we're experiencing them.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've got to have the deep storyline, all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: You take how hard games like, say, Ghouls and Ghosts was, and then you compare it to, you know, this isn't a completely fair analogy, you compare it to Prey, which just came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not so much you're playing a game anymore, you're playing a movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: So much went into it,
[SPEAKER_12]: and there's just one way that they want you to play through it so you experience the way that they want you to do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now Prey is one of the most easy first person shooters that I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which isn't saying much, but it's just there's one way that they want you to play it and usually it's the easiest way because they want you to finish it.
[SPEAKER_12]: They want you to
[SPEAKER_11]: Prey is also interesting when you talk about those big budgets and stories because it doesn't... I was talking about this in my review of the demo last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's no real cutscenes in Prey, at least it seems like.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything is very seamless.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they took a cue from Half-Life 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, from Doom 3, really, in its engine.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, it all kind of comes back to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of like the cinematic element games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Prey is a beautiful game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anyone ever play Berserk on Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say Berserk on Atari 2600 with the bouncy happy face, but no, I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it came out before we got the anime over here, and I started actually picking up the fan subs after that and downloading manga scans just because it was like freaking playing through the anime.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was so perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was so much good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the games that give a more in-depth story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that it has a lot of the action that you want, but at the same time, you're compelled to keep playing because the story is so good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's hear another voicemail from our second voicemail and last voicemail for tonight on this same topic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, what's up, Orange Island Radio?
[SPEAKER_00]: This is SpeedyF40 from Michigan.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I think about the video games getting harder.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think they're getting harder.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they're getting less accessible for people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like back when Pac-Man and stuff was out,
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a ton more objectives nowadays.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the controllers have so many more buttons on them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even though it's easier to beat the game, they're just harder to play.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I just think video games are now less accessible to the average person.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just easier to us because we're gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of talking about the accessibility to everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very valid point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I think that's the point that Nintendo is trying to do with the Wii controller, trying to simplify things and make it to where it's more attractive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, in one degree, it's not as simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: To another degree, I think it's very simplifying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you move your hand, that's all you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that that whole accessibility thing of being able to actually get into it, being able to pick up the controller and know what to do with it, I think that that's a lot of the issue that we have these days.
[SPEAKER_12]: and make it more accessible to people who don't have the patience to read the damn manual.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of people don't.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, you're going to have a hard time telling a non-gamer to read the manual.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, that's bitter tech support coming through again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, thank you guys so much for the voicemails of the week and of course we don't always have enough time to play everything that we get but we do try to listen to all of the voicemails.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, we do listen to every single voicemail and we really appreciate you guys calling in.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to leave us a voicemail, the number is 916-226-9067
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't let DarkSakura influence you.
[SPEAKER_11]: We want to know what you think on this topic, so please call us anytime during the week and leave us a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of entities that suck...
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like Sony's trying to make our friends over in the UK bend over and take it, just like they're doing for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a notice that was out that both the 20GB and 60GB versions of the PlayStation 3 are going to be out in the UK, however not both of them on launch day.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're working by consulting with some of the different merchandisers to basically set up the different SKUs for both.
[SPEAKER_05]: Both items.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a note that though it may not necessarily be both at launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, there's a quote here from David Wilson for Sony UK saying that he actually doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: He explained that Sony has to face what the challenge would be of offering a choice without confusing the consumers.
[SPEAKER_05]: meeting the needs of the retailers, etc., blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, they are actually saying, though, that for pre-ordering a PlayStation 3, it is going to be £150.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a retail suggestion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's expensive, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, poor guys in the UK getting screwed on those prices.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is their tax rates higher over there too?
[SPEAKER_11]: They get double screwed, don't they?
[SPEAKER_05]: The final price is again, it's November 17th in Europe, 600 euros converting to 425 pounds in the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're going to need to make all the money that they can because according to an IBM engineer, he's making a comment about their chip yields for the cell processor and how hard it is to get these chips to
[SPEAKER_08]: Be made right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, he's saying that for every sheet that they press, 10-20% of them work.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it costs, say for example, $1,000 to produce a wafer with 100 chips on it, and if only 10 or 20 of those are going to be working, that increases the cost of the system significantly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not very good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, it
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we going to see a lot of these consoles at launch?
[SPEAKER_08]: And is the launch even going to be happening when they say they are?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now, I think this story just barely missed the cut for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I seem to remember reading somewhere that the PS3s have actually gone into production now at this point, finally.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, unfortunately, I don't have a lot more details than that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, that's all you pretty much need to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: PS3s are finally on their way.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I mean, you see that Sony's gearing up for this, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of people are starting to get nervous.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, are they going to have enough time?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now, okay, maybe they could do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, if the defect rate is 99%, you only get one chip per wafer, and it costs you $1,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, if 10-20% of the chips are working, that's pretty expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's assuming there's not going to be any glitches or whatever with this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not good, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that they're going to be able to find some way to keep the costs down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, they know what they're doing, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you know I got a look at chat room going on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blaze Revolution says it's 17.25% in the UK for the tax.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's vicious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: OL Army Eddie says $200 to pre-order a PS3 here and I know he's in Vancouver because I was talking about my recent vacation with him.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blaze Revolution simply says push back the release date then go back and fix this crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to do that, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Raven's Dolphin says it's a rumor, Sky, a rumor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything's a rumor until they come out and say it, and they're not going to.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll just find out when the launch happens, and we'll see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here comes the doom and gloom, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have Anoush says, or I'm sorry if I pronounced that wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: I always have to apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anoush says the end of Sony Core is close, and Quicksilver says I think Sony is screwed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to be the end of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they're a huge company.
[SPEAKER_08]: They still have Vegas.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the whole thing is they could come out with something really remarkable that we don't know about that they're just kind of keeping under wraps.
[SPEAKER_08]: The thing is right now though, it's kind of just the trend where everyone's posting doom and gloom stories about them.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not going to know until we actually see the launch of what's going on because say for example...
[SPEAKER_08]: Laser in our chatroom says, no, Sony has a good plan, it's easier to just replace everything than it is to QA
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember when all we had to worry about was disc read errors?
[SPEAKER_12]: Now look at all this shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember back for the first PlayStation how you'd have to end up turning your system upside down or sideways because the laser mechanism wasn't aligned right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: They started actually just selling replacement parts for $13.
[SPEAKER_12]: This might be it for Sony and PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if I'd go that far.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, anyway, we've been talking a lot about chips, and this is something interesting you can do to that chip inside your DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know how you can overclock your computer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, a Japanese gamer has figured out a way to overclock your DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, obviously, this is not an easy process, but if you want to check it out, you can head over to Engadget.
[SPEAKER_11]: They ran a story on July 19th on how to overclock your
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this process will probably take you several hours.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to open up your DS Lite, drill a hole in the side, solder several different areas on it, and make sure you don't touch too much of the bad areas that will break the whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now this has been translated into English.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to take a look at this, I believe the site is ndshotmod.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: But of course, remember, this would be violating your warranty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice proof of concept, but what exactly is it supposed to accomplish?
[SPEAKER_11]: Homebrew.
[SPEAKER_08]: Overclocking?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just for homebrew stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Essentially what this hack will do, reports are saying, it will actually physically increase the speed of visuals and sound between 1.4 times and 1.7 times, which means it's pretty much unplayable.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's uncontrollable, high-pitched music, and rather a pain in the butt to be playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is something you do.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you thought WarioWare got fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Only because you're like a hardcore hacker.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like the same type of person that would install Linux on a toaster.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, VX, JSON, XB.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is something he'd do, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually I know several people who are engineers who do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Personally, I think the better hack that they had was for the original DS where you can actually make it as bright as a DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Using a firmware upgrade.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still plenty pleased with my Game Boy Advance and Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And speaking of awesome, I have another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cartoon Network has a new massively multiplayer online game coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're working with, I guess it's Grygon Entertainment, to make one that will have Blue, Ben 10, Mac, and the kids next door.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love Kotaku because the writing is so honest and takes no prisoners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically saying that it sounds like a formula for instant crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, there's a couple... Toontown Online?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Disney has a Toontown Online thing for... Stop distracting me!
[SPEAKER_11]: Shush!
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the ferret when we need it?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_11]: He died.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is going to be a free download.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually... You'll have a subscription service.
[SPEAKER_05]: PeeWee's Playhouse Saved by the Bell Rock
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, I want to say Extra for Sister and Miklatov were watching Pee-Wee's Playhouse the other night and I kind of caught a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So freaking funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the kind of crack we were fed as kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: That show was badass.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember being so freaked out because what was the cowboy's name?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, but it wasn't Lawrence Fisher in the play.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cowboy Bob?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure someone in chat is yelling it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember being young and being freaked out by him.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cowboy Curtis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cowboy Curtis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, I can't do the pajama party because I sleep in the nude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember being so traumatized by this when I was little.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really traumatized, just thinking it was...
[SPEAKER_11]: He's naked!
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what fucking traumatized me about Pee-Wee Herman and all that stuff when I was little is the movie, Pee-Wee's Big Adventure.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love Pee-Wee's Big Adventure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you remember the scene when he gets in the truck and there's Large Marge?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the story.
[SPEAKER_11]: And she does the face.
[SPEAKER_11]: She does the face and it looked a lot like this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like this!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: The whole thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was dark and stormy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It scared the shit out of me when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, my God.
[SPEAKER_11]: No wonder I came out so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gameplay HD
[SPEAKER_08]: GameplayHD knows what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_11]: This channel needs to make it big.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds like they know what they're doing with this network, and I'm very excited to see what comes of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think a lot of us that feel like G4 was a joke, in its later years anyway, are going to be much happier by what GameplayHD is going to bring.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, basically this agreement right now with GameplayHD, like I said, includes the three circuits of the 2006 World Series of Video Games, the Land War Competition in Louisville, Kentucky, which is being held June 16th,
[SPEAKER_08]: DreamHack Land Party DreamHack Land Party DreamHack Land Party
[SPEAKER_08]: PGR 3, Guild Wars
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Perfect!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what we need!
[SPEAKER_11]: Is a game station run by a gamer?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think he runs it, but I don't remember exactly the relation, but I apologize, but I'm going off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have notes on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you happen to get Dish Network and you have HD, the channel can be found on Dish Channel 9485.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_11]: It makes me want to switch to satellite.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: The only reason is because I save on the internet by having the game on the internet through the same company.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be damned if it doesn't seem like every week we're hearing about some damn Wii button, Wii flap, Wii secret compartment that you can put your weed in.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what they're coming with.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your weed?
[SPEAKER_11]: Get it, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was a new promo picture in the latest issue of Nintendo Power that seems to indicate that there is yet another damn Wii button.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it looks like it's some type of new Z button, kind of like the one that's on the GameCube's controller, like a little teeny shoulder thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: No idea how the hell you're going to reach it because you'd have to have another thumb growing out of your thumb to hit it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe it's like a volume control for the internal speaker.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a theory that's going around right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if that's going to be one you're supposed to frequently hit in the game,
[SPEAKER_11]: That is going to be a pain in the ass, as if playing with a remote control is not going to be weird enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, I don't know, when I played at E3, it felt okay to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: It didn't feel like the wrist cramp that it sounded like on paper.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if it's just me that felt that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, we're going to open up the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click on Interact With Us and you can call our show by calling username OrangeloungeRadio or by picking up the phone and dialing 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_11]: Feel free to comment on anything that's been brought up throughout the show and we'd love to get your feedback and opinion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, I will ask before we open up the Skype line, are there any last minute stories we have from anyone tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's one.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: At least for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Luminous 2 soundtrack has been revealed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd also like to thank Tiger Call for the link.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to be in Luminous 2, we have Beck, Black Tambourine, Black Eyed Peas, Pump It, Chemical Brothers, Star Guitar, Fatboy Slim, Gangster Trippin', The Go Team, Bottle Rocket, Gwen Stefani, Hollaback Girl, yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ruba Stank, Born to Lead, Junior Senior, Take My Time, Missy Elliott, Lose Control, another blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some random song by New Order, which New Order I can't go wrong with.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is so weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just a weird lineup.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Luminous is definitely going mainstream.
[SPEAKER_11]: As long as Mondo Grosso is coming back, I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, those actually are going to be the ones with videos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, ones without videos are going to be Junkie XL, Breezer.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Stigmato Inc.
[SPEAKER_05]: with Reality Check.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also there will be more tracks from the Japanese artists Mondo Grosso, Ken Ishii and Tech Writers.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's go skypline.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a couple calls have already come in that we've missed, but we want to get the Luminous 2 news out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So call back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, it's Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: The UMD.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want to talk about with UMDs?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about the UMD is dead because of BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your theory there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mentioned this before and I said that I've been getting all my movies and all my stuff on BitTorrent and this is what Sony should do.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should put everything on BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you basically admit that you steal your movies?
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least you're honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not trying to say it makes you a bad person or whatever, but you're what the MPAA is not happy with right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: So let me ask you this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me turn around and ask you this.
[SPEAKER_11]: What would be a way that you would legitimately pay for movies?
[SPEAKER_11]: What would make you stop using BitTorrent and legitimately pay for movies?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably going to sound really cheesy as hell, but the Sony Connect service.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I really think they've got a good model and I think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so on one hand you give Sony a little bit of shit for the UMD, but on the other hand you give them some props for the Sony Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think they got a good plan going with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they try to connect this with the Xbox Live model, but not like it, like charge little games for the PSP, and like movies, I think they really have something to go with, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, it's interesting you bring up Xbox, because I'm waiting for the day when Xbox does this.
[SPEAKER_11]: All they need is a bigger hard drive on that thing, and, you know, with the active downloads and everything, you could totally and easily download movies on that thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, you can already download...
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, one more thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was surfing Singular.com and they have a little ringtone for The Internet is for Porn from Avenue Q. Why did that make you think of us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's so random.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, and I'm going to purchase it soon so everyone that I walk down the street for my phone raises going, The Internet is really, really great for porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have some crazy listeners at OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's also one of her Cage Band songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, ages ago, ages ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, Raven Stolfen, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate your insight, all right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I hope they don't come after you and sue you, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they won't.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just a pseudonym, not your real name.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they try to sue you, you can countersue them for invasion of privacy and for search without a warrant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Legal advice from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you go to law school?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I've taken a lot of business law, but honestly, the people that were countersuing the RIAA and the MPAA were using those tactics for countersuits.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just the fact that, you know, seconding the whole UMD thing and the whole format wars as we'd like to see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, at the end of the day, you know it's going to hurt the consumer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to stick with the DVD regardless.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because no one's ready to shift, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No one's ready to shift to a new format, especially when there's, like, God knows how many are already out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Should the PlayStation 3 have had a UMD slot?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, it really, I, I don't know, I don't, then they'll be copying Nintendo and trying to, you know, trying to play a portable gaming system on a console.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they do with the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm talking about for movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, for movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gaming is one thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I guess hypothetically, why not play the games too?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, but then.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's that copying Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they did it with the Game Boy, you know, the Game Boy player, the little device that, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if I call it copying, I just call it smart.
[SPEAKER_11]: Make your games playable on more systems or more and more places.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the bottom line is this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Hollywood is pretty much split on both formats.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like half is going to support, you know, HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other half is Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_11]: The same thing happened with DVD and DivX, though, and look how long the war lasted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, DivX got out and, you know, only lasted three years while DVD's still running.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because DivX downright sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really never got your opinion on how mobile gaming works.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, what's your take on mobile gaming?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I can say a lot about mobile gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not a big fan of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want to know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, granted, I already started a job in the mobile gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Make games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we've got licenses for stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, don't put games that were built for PlayStations and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't put those games on mobile.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game that I'm working on already sold a million.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm working on the Spanish version of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is it, Bejeweled?
[SPEAKER_11]: Those are the types of games that work on mobile because those are the type of people playing mobile games or uber casual gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: The gamer gamers have a DS or a PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless they created some sort of cell phone similar, you know, exceeding the capabilities of the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it had, you know, the marketing and hype to back it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, the problem with the N-Gage is that it was a phone first, gaming system second, but yet it thought it was a gaming system first in the marketing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, two platforms in the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_03]: One is the proprietary one, which the games are based on, and also Java, if I recall correctly, Symbian.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they were like, you know, it was three platforms, two of which were pretty open.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're working on the Spanish version of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Habla Español?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, you know, I understand a lot more than I speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: I lost my fluency when I came here.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, buddy, we gotta let you go, but have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll take one more call if you want to call us.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click on Interact With Us, or you can always pick up the phone, 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and here comes a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, this is Eddie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I just wanted to comment on another part of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, what I'm really confused about is how Sony is doing this whole huge homebrew war on the PSP, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: And on the PS3, they're now using Linux as their operating system on the PS3, which is kind of opening the door for homebrew.
[SPEAKER_07]: So why is it that they're battling homebrew on platform and then welcoming it with open arms on another?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to throw this to our homebrew expert.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, do you have a thought on this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the PlayStation 3 is a computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: So?
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's why.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why does Sony have one policy here and another policy here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm sure that they're thinking that their bases are covered with the PlayStation 3 and the fact that the PlayStation 3 needs all the help it can get to sell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well...
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, but how long before a Nintendo emulator comes out for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Two days.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, exactly then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then shouldn't, like, when that happens, shouldn't, like, Sony be battling that too?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be a lot harder for them to do since they're using Linux.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I remember correctly, they can also boot into other operating systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're even saying they can maybe install Windows or OSX or something on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be hard to regulate unless they have some sort of crippled version of Linux on there that doesn't allow certain things to run or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how they're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, PS3 version running Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be the great irony.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, that's all I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, thank you very much for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a good one, and we'll see what happens with Sony's policy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of think the gimped version of Linux is a more... I think that's kind of what we're looking at is the reality of what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, not a problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, sorry, I'm trying to fix my mouse here.
[SPEAKER_11]: The batteries just died during that call there, so I'm trying to
[SPEAKER_11]: Get reorganized here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate your insight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you didn't get through tonight, or if you were that person that had connection problems, you can always leave us a voicemail.
[SPEAKER_11]: We love voicemails.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can listen earlier in the show if you want to see how to leave us a voicemail of the week and what our topic is this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any more last-minute stories, folks?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, a couple things about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: As I mentioned in the story before...
[SPEAKER_08]: well before about the secret pages on the Wii I did find those finally someone had them on file share or let's see here we've got a few things with of course they're saying the Nintendo Wi-Fi service is going to be free just like it is for the DS and they were saying you know of course the frame code system and that type of thing what I also found was interesting they renamed WarioWare to WarioWare Dojo now instead of Brawl
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or not WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, on top of that, that wasn't the most neat thing I found.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was kind of an interview in GamePro with the people behind Red Steel.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they were talking about the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically the creative director, Nicholas Eppert,
[SPEAKER_08]: He had this to say about the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, You'll have up to four players.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they play together in split screen, we can only say that the fight will not only be on screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's maybe either referring to the fact that six people on the couch flailing about.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be very difficult to do in that kind of environment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or that there's going to be some sort of different type of multiplayer in room or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Games on Mario Party Wii are about to get very violent in this house because Mario Party, as it is, is a cutthroat competition around these parts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mario Party Wii is just begging for violence.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that my mouse works again, I was reading some comments there in chat room and Blackboy commented, I need OSX on my PS3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of a shout out to an old operating system that some folks have forgot about.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that the same Blackboy I met at Arena once?
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder if it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, that's not too much, not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I think we talked about this last week, about how the Xbox 360 is possibly going to get a bundle with Project Gotham Racing 3, a 1,250 point card, and three month...
[SPEAKER_08]: of Xbox Live Gold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's sort of been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's starting to appear in retailers' computers now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have the PGR3 bundle in Toys R Us computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's being sold for about the same price as a premium system and also was confirmed to be... Let's see, that was in a Canadian Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently there's another chain called BJ's.
[SPEAKER_08]: that's going to be carrying it in Circuit City's flyer in the newspaper.
[SPEAKER_08]: They show the price for $489.99 US for the Project Gotham Racing 3 bundle.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says it includes a pro console, a second wireless controller, play and charge kit, and a copy of PGR3.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that sounds more like a bundle that's being done through that site.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apparently online they have the same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's like a $30 off web deal or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But
[SPEAKER_08]: Something that may be coming soon?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll probably find out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just reading in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Jinai said, I downloaded the Paris Hilton game and PKAcura88 goes, get out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And PK, somebody said something and PKAcura88 says, no, I mean, get off my internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_11]: Harsh folks in chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I got a question for you because you were just talking about Project Gotham.
[SPEAKER_11]: So speaking of racing games, somebody was sending me a private message, I think it was CKY Mike, asking about Burnout 5 on PS3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you heard anything about Burnout?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's probably coming out in the fall.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it is coming for PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure they're... Yes, it's a given.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, duh, they're coming out with another Burnout game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's going to be Burnout something.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is coming out probably in the fall.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of a given.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like saying, oh yeah, next year Madden 08's coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on, that's...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: But my guess, if anything, it would be probably coming out in March-ish.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's when the Xbox 360 one came out last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: And obviously it's not coming out in September like it did last year for the current gen stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I were to guess, I'd say March, probably for Burnout.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: September is going to be a packed month for games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And October is even worse.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy XII crack, finally coming in October.
[SPEAKER_08]: You won't see me for a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's getting pushed more and more towards November.
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's coming at Halloween.
[SPEAKER_11]: How much further back can you push to November?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I swear to God, Squeenix, if you rob me of Final Fantasy for another year, I am... It's not going to be pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to stomp and pout.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will stomp and pout in front of the Squeenix building, and there will be video on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: All it comes down to me is just Saints Row and fucking Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be my games for August.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know, there's a lot of games coming out in August, but a lot that I don't want, like Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it looks like Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that could be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I found out I gotta buy cars on the 360 for Nelly.
[SPEAKER_08]: For achievement points?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but she wants that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up with Nelly getting into games lately?
[SPEAKER_11]: You've talked about her playing Bejeweled, cloning Clyde, now she wants to play Cars.
[SPEAKER_11]: She wants me to buy Elite Beat Agents for her.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is she slowly becoming a gamer?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this marriage thing corrupting her?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think she'll be into the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to say anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: You shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_11]: From my experience, she's very into the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate you all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want this show to end now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, thanks so much for sitting in tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though you were a little quiet, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate your insight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We appreciate you leaving the bad jokes at the door.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
Whee!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: My eardrums are still ringing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's freaking hot in here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm, like, sweating just sitting here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm trying to end the show so we can get out of here.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_05]: Reject false icons and poo on the sun.
[SPEAKER_11]: And my final thought is... No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a great week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_11]: and Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bring it, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, that's the only thing about Chromounds Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder if they actually just have multiplayer, like standard multiplayer, not that online, perpetual online thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta check that out, because I haven't really delved into the multiplayer that much.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be fun, though, an inter-show battle royale.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm all for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm all for an inter-show battle royale at some point on one of those games and stuff, and
[SPEAKER_11]: We've talked about doing a tournament thingy using all game, but we'll save that for another show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We want to end tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_11]: So have a great night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you so much for downloading us and supporting Internet Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys are awesome, and we do this show for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!