Years after Big Picture, Steam Link, Steam Machines and in advance of the Steam Deck,
the Steam App gets a big update that updates the look and functionality of download status.
Big Picture started in Overhaul 9 years ago, 6 years ago Steam VR pushed out a little bit
further and we're finally getting closer to a full visual refresh of Steam by default.
And this is just one change in a sea of gaming news, now it's time to welcome back your
hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers and Loki as they bring you two weeks of gaming news
starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Best of all my friends out there on the internet, welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio live once again back with you after having last week off with episode
number 883 of our show for this September the 12th of 2021.
We are back live to talk about video games, gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle.
My name Rob Roberts and I'm joined as always say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
Hello.
Hi, how are you?
I'm alright.
How was your Labor Day?
How was a week off from OLR?
Well I actually, I did my usual stream just an hour early and by then a certain Cenobite
had been out in the Dead by Daylight universe.
Ah yes, Pinhead, yes.
Well the Hell Priest, as his official name is.
But other than that it was Rosh Hashanah started on Monday and so that is the Jewish New Year
so to all my fellow Jews out there, Happy New Year and Yom Kippur starts on Wednesday
evening through Thursday evening and so for anyone observing have an easy fast and may
you be inscribed in the Book of Life.
Alright, let's see I'm trying to think what else to ask you about the time away but I
guess holidays and things can keep a person busy that's for sure.
And I spent a stupid amount of money on Copic markers.
On what?
Copic markers.
What are those?
They are probably the best alcohol ink markers that you can buy.
They are very expensive and I went looking for deals anywhere that I could find them
so that I could build up my collection of markers and start drawing again.
Oh fun.
Which I've been doing some drawing.
I felt like I saw one of your art things like Dead by Daylight fan art basically.
I need, not really.
I did one piece of fan art.
I did Julie.
Okay yeah that's what I saw.
Like in one of those outfits.
That's what I saw.
But I also did my own little avatar for my channel which I'm really not, I like kind
of rushed it out because I finally redeemed the points to be on Hydro's raft.
Oh cute.
And it's on my own Twitch channel right now.
I have one just like a little piece on it but it's sort of like a combination of like
me I guess with my hair the way it is.
Wearing a pig, wearing the Meg pig mask and a combination outfit that's kind of like one
of the pig outfits and one of the Legion outfits.
Cool.
And that is what I have chosen as my Twitch avatar.
You've been having a very artistic year between that and as you know many folks know you've
done a lot of the music that's used here on OLR and on your own streams and such.
So the artiste has come out over this.
It's not like it's a new thing but you know I feel like we're seeing it more in this last
year or so.
And I also am working on the guidebook for DerpyCon right now.
So I have many irons in the fire and maybe not enough hammers.
Well speaking of fires and hammers that sounds a lot like Minecraft and I know that is the
jam of the one and only Techmaster Loki.
Yeah that's been the jam.
Don't sound too enthusiastic now.
Ari I skated for four hours today so I'm tired.
Oh my gosh well first off let me say happy belated birthday Loki.
Your birthday was yesterday for those that may not know.
So you got to go skating for your birthday or was that just a treat for the kids?
Oh my gosh it's it's everything's always a treat for the kids.
Did you at least get to have a good meal or something for your birthday?
We got Tahoe Joes to go and they were an hour late.
Oh my gosh.
There's only one person working the the register it's not really a register I guess but like
and then she didn't put the whole order in the system because apparently their web system
doesn't talk to their POS system and so they had to manually put stuff in there.
So it's a POS.
Exactly and so it was a mess they were they were slow and stuff and then it was then they're
the way they cook their steaks it's like medium or more well there's never like a medium rare
because of the way they I don't know they cook them in an oven or something and this
is certainly on the well side unfortunately so.
Sounds good to me I'm that freak that likes a well done steak.
What's wrong with you?
Where do you want me to start?
So yeah otherwise it was all right yeah that's fine.
All right well happy birthday and I was I was saying this on Twitter but if you want
to show Loki a little love for his birthday follow him on YouTube and while you're at
it follow Dark Soccer and I on Twitch we all it's not our birthdays but it will be at some
point so follow us.
I actually am planning on doing a sub-a-thon.
Oh that'll be fun.
Yeah I actually got a little bit inspired by a couple other friends doing their their
sub-a-thons and I especially like what Maru did with his.
I don't know who that is but I assume a good person yeah.
Yeah which honestly enough I'm actually friends on Dead by Daylight with Anjaina now.
Oh yeah because some of those drag queens from Drag Race do yeah I mean especially during
COVID when performances weren't as you know prevalent so well yeah but Anjaina is a total
sweetheart so actually it's because of them that I might play survivor oh good finally
yay I'm excited to see how that goes maybe I was like are you considering doing cosplay
because shout out to our mutual buddy Isaaco was doing a Resident Evil Village Lady Dimitrescu
cosplay it was so fabulous I don't know if he's still going he's no he's still going
he's only about halfway through the game oh gosh and he's been saying Isaaco is not streaming
today it's all Lady D not that I encourage people to switch the channel but you can open
up a new tab and take a look because I thought it was definitely definitely lurk in Isaaco's
channel Isaaco is a sweetheart I think we should give a shout out I mean honestly though
it's it's abs and Isaaco pops into my channel sometimes just another sweetheart and and
of course his roommate Nick and Prince yeah so lots of great people we've been finding
on Twitch through this silly little game that's for sure absolutely absolutely but um but
at any rate I kind of am getting a little bit inspired and I want to do something I
guess to give back to people who've been with me you know helping my my channel go
you know and so I kind of want to do something entertaining for people um it'll probably
be on a day that I can actually legit do a marathon so stay tuned all right uh meanwhile
um oh I should I should mention um uh since everybody asked uh I'm back from Dragon Con
I was no what I was at uh Dragon why are you still in Atlanta uh it was uh Dragon Con
was interesting this year you know um obviously it was COVID and you know a lot of people
had concerns about that people didn't want to go because they didn't feel safe which
is fine everybody has to make their own decisions um it was a little bit surreal um because
and this is a good thing everybody was masked and people were incorporating into their cosplays
and things like that which was super cute um but you know again you know for being in
the middle of Georgia which you know might have a reputation in the south one way or
the other about mask usage or mask compliance the good news is that Dragon Con was very
good in that department um I did test for COVID after I got back um a couple days after
the con to try to give it enough time I was negative so I was very thankful about that
um and um yeah it's uh even though it was a weird year like just for my own like mental
health getting to see people interact with people be extroverted and do the panels again
which were well received and thank you to anybody that showed up actually I will share
this with you guys and shout out and I'm so sorry I forgot your name in the moment but
somebody came to one of the panels on the digital media track that I was doing and he
actually came up after the panel and was like hey I just wanted to say hi I've been listening
to you guys I first found you guys in middle school and I'm thinking this guy's like gotta
be in his late 20s you know it was an age check he said I found you guys in middle school
and just I recently rediscovered you guys and I just wanted to say thank you so so passing
it he's and it was funny because we had talked about on this panel that there are a lot of
people who will lurk and they don't necessarily interact with the show and that's fine we
volume them them too and he kind of admitted I'm one of those people I'm I never have sent
an email or joined live or anything like that but I listen almost every week and I really
appreciate what you guys are doing and that you've kept the show going through COVID and
all that so I was that was a that was a big hug and and the the fuel I need to keep going
for another 20 years you know so it was good it's good so I thought I'd share that with
you guys that there is there's there's love for OLR out there for sure not just live here
on Sunday nights in our chat room because we do tape live every Sunday night at the
voice of geeks network twitch.tv slash vog network vog network six o'clock pacific nine
o'clock eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show and Mike Deft is in chat poking
fun at something I put on twitch this week saying excuse me not twitch twitter saying
Rob isn't in Atlanta isn't he replacing Bobby okay so I went to Dragon Con but I stayed
an extra night after Dragon Con because the airport is less fucky on a Tuesday than it
is on Labor Day so I stayed at you know Manor Black Wolf for an extra night and of course
I had to go see his studio in his setup I'd seen it before but I guess the computer isn't
usually there anything so long story short I took a picture in Bobby Black Wolf setup
so it looked like I was now hosting the Bobby Black Wolf show and I made a very tongue-in-cheek
tweet that said Bobby has been replaced on the show you know something like that that
wasn't meant to be taken seriously but you guys want to hear a hilarious punchline his
mom texted him like three hours later going I just read on Twitter that you're leaving
your show what happened I felt so bad I wasn't I was trying to punk people like SSJ 100 Matt
and Mike Deft and Tiger Claw, Dark Tetsuya, all the loyals that have been here for so
long all of you I was trying to punk that crowd I wasn't trying to punk Bobby's mom
sorry sorry Mrs. Black Wolf sorry sorry anyway but uh yeah so Dragon Con was great thank
you if anybody has discovered the show because of some of my appearances there what have
you I had a great time and I'm I'm really hoping to be back next year let's let's hope
things go on a positive trend when it comes to COVID and we can welcome more people back
to Dragon Con next year fingers and toes crossed let's get into our kickoff topic though let's
get into some games and something a lot of people have been talking about from this week
some big news Loki if I feel like we kind of got the PlayStation E3 event this week
pretty much yeah it's a little bit late but that I mean COVID COVID fucked everything
up so what is time anymore so this was the PlayStation's showcase where they showed off
a bunch of new trailers for a bunch of brand new games lots and lots of stuff to go over
so starting off we have of course they announced the Star Wars Knights of the Old Republic
remake that is coming to PlayStation 5 isn't that ironic when the first one was an Xbox
exclusive on consoles it is but yeah I mean they gotta have something so you know yeah
so that's the thing that's coming we've got spider-man 2 announced which looks pretty
awesome because that kind of mixes Miles Morales in there as well and then they also hinted
that venom is gonna be in there I would like to commend Sony and insomniac for not making
the easy play on to spider-man's on spider-man to spider-man's you know spider-man I I'm
just I don't think yeah no I'm thankful they didn't along with insomniac working on that
game as well we have a brand new game that they announced which is for Wolverine so that
yeah as well that you want yep we got a video for God of War Ragnarok so that looked pretty
sweet as well this game called project Eve which is kind of like almost reminded me a
little bit of like Nier automata or diet Bayonetta was the vibe I got yeah yeah so that's the
thing that's coming to PlayStation 5 as well we had a new trailer for tiny tiny Tina's
wonderlands which now has guns so it's even more border lands ish but it's still different
that looks interesting as a show 100 Matt and chat says I'm really hyped for that tiny Tina
thing gonna be the hex and for Borderlands you know I gotta say same and I was interested in
it from the first little tease they did it was the game awards or something a while back they
did that first tease and I was like you know I don't super get into Borderlands I don't dislike
it I've played a little bit of one and two but I'm really curious about this one I think the
setting is so much more interesting to me so I got to check it out we haven't the announcement
that the uncharted legacy of these collection is coming to PC as well as PlayStation 5 which I
think was kind of hinted at before we got a trailer for game called four spoken which was
kind of that project it was like yeah it was the game that they were kind of shown like the tech
demo stuff for PlayStation 5 with so that was way different now though but like in a good way like
it really like you can see the progress made and I get that that is definitely something that's on
my radar that game looked incredible have you seen anything with that dark soccer that project
athea nope or I'm sorry now it's called four spoken I can't want to call its all name look
it up when you can it looks really awesome take a look at the trailer it's cool okay I have like
limited PlayStation 5 exclusive with that as well the Alan Wake remaster yeah I hope that the baby
thing is less annoying I sadly I think the baby thing is still there but they they do have the
licensed music is all coming back and that made me so happy the only thing that's not coming back
is the awkward sponsorships from like energizer and Verizon that stuff's not in there now do you
know when when Dan was playing through that the whole baby thing I would just leave the house yeah
I could not stand it sadly they're not gonna change the plot or anything like that well no I
just mean that they should do something different or have an option for something different because
that sound is just really really terrible well with it coming to PC that's gonna mean mods so
where the the remedy games may not deliver modders might so I cuz I bet you're not the only one
annoyed by that so something that's changed what if they want them mod it to be the Nelson laugh
let's change it to watch it to was it a Randy Macho Man Savage like they did in Skyrim that's
what he's a teen shouting Jason instead yes all these all these great ideas yes ghost wire Tokyo
looks crazy so they have a new trailer for that it's been delayed to next year but but it looked
good off the wall crazy rockstar games has done the unimaginable they the bold brand-new IP
Grand Theft Auto 5 is coming to PlayStation 5 will actually delayed to March 2022 I'm with so
many changes to it like so innovative it's so so innovative it's so risky exactly did you see my
sassy tweet on that is that I hope that there's a collaboration between Grand Theft Auto 5 and
Skyrim in the near future so that they can release those fucking games again you know the thing
though like with the five like all like even the stuff that was in the trailer like all they're
like kind of bullet points of like what's different or not they've been in the game
forever like when they're talking about you like instantly switch between characters that's been
there since like PlayStation 3 but it's it's instant because it's faster it's more instantly
but you can do that now on PC with an instant hot coffee oh wait it's a consider you know so they
have that or like explosive action there were explosions and all the other games I don't
don't try to tell me explosions are new to Grand Theft Auto they are new to Grand Theft Auto like
more explicit is it explosion error I mean I don't understand and oh and then of course Grand Theft
Auto online not to forget that I mean they certainly won't want to like shove that down
your throat or anything so that's coming we had a new trailer for Guardians of the Galaxy which
looked okay I'm a thing called a kid Amisgna or was a kid it and oh the Radiohead thing yeah that
was interesting that took me back Radiohead yeah there's like a Radiohead heck yeah the album like
Kid A they're turning into some digital experience it was very vague oh I'm down I don't even care
I'm down I'll check it out I like like Radiohead was a big thing in like college for me like that
album the Benz that got me through a lot in college but the Benz okay computer yeah okay
and Pablo like the Benz okay computer and Pablo honey were like my rotation yeah this this is
definitely made for 40-somethings I feel I'm sorry I feel like it's the Super Nintendo and they just
released a Led Zeppelin game like or a no a Pink Floyd game that's yeah that's what I feel actually
a little bit more accurate might be sort of like an ELO game it's Zanna do the game sorry Logie
all right Grand Theft Auto are not great though Gran Turismo 7 has a release date now coming March
4th 2022 yep it's Gran Turismo I mean I'm less excited about that than I am with like Forza
Horizon 5 so I'm Blood Hunt got a new trailer that's kind of PlayStation 5 as well there's
this game called Chichiya or yeah Chiya I don't know how you pronounce it they look pretty awesome
it's like a kind of a cartoony adventure game and then I guess Rainbow Six is finally jumping
well not finally jumping the shark again with Rainbow Six extraction which is basically your
fire team going against aliens now so there's aliens in Rainbow Six that's coming out in January
all righty um yeah that's pretty much it lots of stuff I mean very packed yeah it was some it was
a lot of stuff um I you know nothing that made me go oh I gotta go get a PlayStation 5 today
which by the way I'm gonna do it quick and yeah well yeah I can't and I want to do a quick tangent
real quick because some very important news broke while we were out for two weeks and I need to
update you guys on the situation because it is gonna affect my gaming weeks for some time to
come I don't know if y'all heard but my favorite band of all time is really a new album out after
these songs already yes the first two singles are out and it sounds like the 70s which is funny
because the B side and we're talking about ABBA the B side sounds more like old-school ABBA the
don't let me down sounds more like old-school ABBA than the other one because the other one
sounded like grandma singing me a bedtime song but I mean that no but I mean that in the best
possible way like I know fucking adorable like I just like I know what you mean so here's the
better like the B side better so yeah the B side was great so they're doing this whole thing with
the ABBA thing that they're gonna do like a Vegas style show but in London and they're doing
holograms and all this stuff right so it's gonna be hologram ABBA at this thing that's actually in
the Olympic Park Park in London what Jamie Loki you guys may not know yet while I was at Dragon
Con a friend oh no I posted on Facebook so you probably did see our friend melody bought me
tickets to go see the ABBA show on my 44th birthday in London what so Alan and I are gonna go and I
talked to Alan about it and we decided we will scale some even though we have some big finance
stuff on the horizon which I haven't really talked about on the show but I will soon I have the thing
we thought you know what between some raises at work the fact that we've been saving money
pretty well London's gonna happen next year so for any of our listeners overseas I need to hear
from people in London because I I'm like trying to look at like where should the hotel be what
should I don't fucking know what I'm doing so I would love to hear from our audience over there
on any tips but that is so late June next year is when my birthday is June 26th which is funny
because that means the 20th anniversary of this program but I'm gonna try to schedule it so it's
right before I leave so that way it doesn't interfere with things too much so yeah but anyway
I say that because and yes this relates to gaming one of the things I had to say was okay I'm not
gonna get a PlayStation 5 this year that'll help roll the money into you know those expensive plane
tickets to London so but I'm really excited you know and as much as I joke about it's for ABBA
and don't get me wrong it is for ABBA it's it's fucking time for us to go across the Atlantic like
neither neither of us have ever done it I'm we've never been on a big trip like that if you could
see our other friend Rob I I would love to see our other friend Rob I in fact that's one of the
people I hope to hear from but yeah and and folks over there but it's one of those things if COVID
has taught us anything it's like we need to just fucking do it so there you go it's gonna happen
all right um let's see yeah I'm looking at comments in chat thank you for the positive
affirmations there in chat so and SJ 100 Matt no this isn't Rob a baba that's a diff that's
an emailer is Rob a baba who I think lives in the Midwest I want to say Ohio but with a giant
question mark sorry Rob a baba but this is raw what's what's his online name I know his real
last name but I was shouted on it has to do with his last name okay then I'm not gonna say it but
there's there's overseas Rob is different yeah okay all right anyway um so I'm sorry where do
we leave off in the PlayStation Showcase before Rob went on an Abba tangent that was very important
we got everything oh oop so dark chakra do you see you said you saw some stuff in there that
looked cool like the Wolverine thing yeah pretty much the Wolverine thing in the radio head thing
yeah yeah there's a lot of good stuff in there I I you know I'll be sad to probably miss
fourspoken when it releases but I look forward to checking it out I'll probably finally get like
after London next year I'll finally get the PlayStation 5 I'd say by next holiday because
if there's any truth to this Final Fantasy thing also happening next summer although I don't really
believe it I obviously have to get a PlayStation 5 for next summer so by the way also one of the
things I've agreed to wave to make London happen is that the Tron machine I'm gonna forgo if it's
above a certain amount which I think it probably will be so we'll see anyway all right enough
about the PlayStation Showcase I hope you all saw some great games and some things to get excited
about let's talk about our gaming weeks and the types of video games we've been playing this week
dark soccer we'll start with you how was your gaming week um it was dead by daylight lots of
dead by daylight um I also picked up a game hold on let me open my steam I picked up slay the spire
oh yeah I see that get one get streamed a lot yeah I was watching Isaac oh play it and it
actually looked like a lot of fun and I figured it's time for something new and I've also picked
up a couple of other games on Steam just in the interim I I actually won a $10 steam card in in
another in another chat and so I redeemed like some a couple little games so I just I'm trying
to pull up my steam which is now like taking five years to connect so I can remember what
all that holds up I was gonna ask you quickly about your thoughts on pinhead and dead by
daylight like do you do you like so killer or you know help I haven't played him yet I haven't
played him yet or I guess they're referring to him as the cenobite yeah you know we all know
game yeah yeah so at any rate um I haven't played him yet I like him I I have seen him in the PTB
and which is the play test build for those who don't know I have also seen him since PTB and
here are my thoughts I believe that they've done a lot to balance him from the PTB and in the PTB
he was glitchy as fuck I'm just saying he was glitchy I have some fun clips saved from other
people's streams like having like like his Maury is great and very faithful to to the films and it
actually looks a lot better now and again for those who don't know a killer can get an item
and an offering called the memento Maury that they can basically just kill somebody with without
sacrificing them so but anyway it's very very faithful but the thing that I do not like is that
the the voices are gone because it used to be and there's something about that by the way this is
what I heard but in the PTB like it there's a mechanic in there where you solve the lament
configuration I don't know if anyone has seen the movie we can just leave it at that yeah yeah
but at any rate he goes you know when someone solves the box then he says you've opened the
box and I came you know line straight from the movie and there were some other other lines that
were there and those got removed because apparently the lines were causing some sort of glitching
like I'm wondering if it's maybe because of the code that runs everything that's audio in
Dead by Daylight is because of their spaghetti code that has been more and more postified over
the last five years of the game's existence it's it's absolutely yeah but in any rate there are
they released also the cosmetics for him with the live build and from what I understand by the way
playing him is sort of like a combination of playing nurse and and hag kinda at least that
was my impression because you can use like a I know and twins nurse and twins which I suck at
and I hate twins because you can actually use the box to cast a chain that you follow like it's its
own its own player right so yeah at any rate so going back to it there's been a few a few little
glitchy things but the mechanics seem to be a lot better ironed out and then Gideon the game level
the Gideon's meat plant from saw and dead dog saloon and RuPaul's drag department or sorry
RuPaul's police station Raccoon Police Department have all been taken down but now Gideon's is back
up with I think they had a graphic overhaul on it I didn't really notice much at the time either
but they do have the new pallets the new graphics for the pallets and whatnot in in the game is
pretty good but dead dog is still down and I think dead dog is also going through a graphic overhaul
and actually no I know what was going on with dead dog okay and this is hilarious far down the dead
by daylight rabbit hole because not everybody plays it so quickly okay well I've only got two
things yeah so what would happen okay there's a move where a survivor can come out of a locker
and knock a killer back and it's called head-on what was happening is that when head-on hit a
killer in the dead dog level it would shoot them outside of the map like out of bounds hmm like
cartoon style it's hilarious so yeah so that went down well I mean not for the survivors I guess
but and then RPD had an exploit in it where there's a place that survivors could clip and
make it out of bounds and then run to a certain area and automatically escape the level oh yikes
um yeah and so RPD was taken down to have that fixed and so that is the state of dead by daylight
maybe I should just make that a report the state of definitely did you did you find those games on
steam you were referring to earlier no I didn't that's right but um but I do know that I did pick
up slay the spire and I'm gonna give it a go see I'm still playing through Oh Fantasian I'm still
playing through Fantasian oh and I finished my yeah I finished my grindy bit and I'm going to
be moving on to doing the next quest so on Tuesdays 630 I will be playing Fantasian nice and I like to
say it in the mean girls way on Tuesday we play Fantasian all right let's go to Loki and your
gaming week it's been minecraft been playing lots of Minecraft did lots of big projects in the game
working on filming for that that content and then um yeah she'll be putting out something
soon for that because yeah I built a huge drowned farm which was a challenge and then
they have some other farms in a shop it's like I'm running tons of shops on the server now because
people keep abandoning their stores in fact we just added like a brand new discord channel
where it's all these shops that are being sold because people just not coming back
that's fun um and then of course uh yesterday I took a break from playing Minecraft to
do a little bit of game dev so I finally after progressing for months um finished my update to
pixel poops number two that I wanted to do so that's revision b which is out now um on uh itch
io and it should be out on steam pretty soon it adds 10 new levels there's two new playable
character models and a less punishing continue system so no longer will you have to restart the
whole world when you die in the level you'll actually be able to restart the level you died on
so um hopefully it'll make it a little bit easier but yeah so that that's out free hooray you already
bought it or it's you know available now and that's probably gonna be the version that gets
put on the cartridges at some point all right shout out for pixel poop number two on itch io
uh and steam nice yep congrats all right uh my gaming week I had to take notes I've played so
much this week I'll try to keep it brief though I'll do my best yeah I played a crap ton of stuff
this week so I got to try a playstation 5 for the first time um while I was staying at manor
blackwolf uh he has that very nice setup in his basement um and so I finally got to try a
playstation 5 for the first time uh and I got to do the astro bot that as astro's playroom I'm
sorry I forgot the name of the game in the moment I'm sure somebody in chat will shout it out
um but um I got he wanted to like show me like the controller and how that whole thing kind of
worked and it is neat I was playing this one level where you kind of had to like like climb up uh
and those that have played the game like climb up a rock wall and it's got a neat little mechanic to
it um uh yeah and sj100 matt and chad says astro's playroom is a really cool tech demo yeah it is
that was a cute little fun game to play and it really showed off how that controller is great
and then of course the other game I wanted to play on his playstation 5 I was like show me
no man's sky because I played that game way too much and I wanted to see how the rumble
fit into that as well and it was it was neat I see why people are really into the controller
like I don't I don't think I'm like oh my god I'm missing everything by having an xbox instead
but I I get it it's cute tech uh and uh when I finally get around to getting a playstation 5
uh I'll I'll appreciate that tech as well um so that was that was time in black wolf theater
playing those games uh when I got home speaking of no man's sky expedition 3 and no man's sky
started so I've been streaming a little bit of that I streamed some on uh was it thursday and
friday yeah because I was a little bit sick yesterday uh so I didn't really stream yesterday
and then uh I didn't stream today because I've just I've run out of time um so uh but I will
stream again tomorrow I've been starting expedition 3 and by the way for those that were watching the
stream we were talking about does it end monday or tuesday and folks are telling me it goes
through tuesday it does but it's tuesday at 6 a.m pacific 9 a.m eastern so there monday tomorrow
night will be the last um chance to get twitch drops uh that are happening um as well so um
yeah the no man's sky expedition has been going very well it's weird because now you play it all
on one planet um and you uh don't uh get to really leave that planet it's all part of uh
what the expedition is about and it's not a very kind planet either but you start with some
protection so it's interesting it's it shows some different elements of the game and refreshes
things it is also interesting that the expedition has nothing to do with the frontiers patch they
put out I was full on expecting there to be like the whole like uh you know society thing that they
started building in the towns and stuff that's not in it which i thought was interesting um so
i'll have to uh explore that elsewhere um bobby is uh mentioning in chat some additional things
that i checked out at his house yes there was the eufy dlc for final fantasy 7 i got to play maybe
the first i don't know hour or so that dlc um so that was cool to experience um it's it was done
very well it was it was hard for me to reacclimate to final fantasy 7 because i haven't i haven't
played the remake in a year um but it felt very good on playstation 5 and it looked very good
um so um you know i'll pick that up as soon as i get a ps5 um for sure um but i didn't i didn't
you know we only did like maybe the first little section of it i didn't you know play too far to
get to any major story stuff or anything like that how's the voice acting for her it's good
yeah it's continuous the game's had a strong voice cast and i'd say that continues for her
uh and then bobby does mention this yes i guess i should i should mention that i didn't have it
written down but i should mention uh he has that mandalorian table i played it and i did beat one
of his high scores now so he's a little bit like he shows up to my house and beats my high score
but we need to clarify i didn't beat the high score i beat one of those categories of high
scores because it keeps different you beat a mode yeah i beat a mode or something like that i think
it was like one of the mini games i got the highest score in a particular mini game so um
yeah there was that but um his his arcade and stuff like you know i'll defer to his show for
him to tell you all about that stuff but i did get to see him his little arcade room is super cute
like it's all black light it's got the carpet it's got the arcade one-up cabinets and there's
definitely room for more in there um cool dark soccer if you ever get out to man or black wolf
i think you'd appreciate his setup and then you'd be like if this was mine i'd have this here this
here this here this here but it was nice setup yeah well things things may work out next year um
be awesome just saying all right um let's see continuing on my gaming week final fantasy 13
hit uh xbox game pass finally on uh xbox uh series x and all that stuff i think it's might be pc as
well but i'm i'm only really focused on the console i really wanted to check this out because if you
missed it when final fantasy 13 became backwards compatible they actually did some up rezzing from
like the masters of um the cutscenes in the game and what i kind of learned from playing through
it um the textures look great the characters look great i almost feel like i'm playing an hd
remaster of the game now i don't want to get expectations too high because there are some
things that still definitely show their age a little bit like the ui but i was really impressed
by how good final fantasy 13 looks now and i think that game is really underrated in the
final fantasy series and now that i'm playing it again i see so many clues about a big plot twist
that comes up way later in the story that really changes the context of one of the characters there
are so many hints in the beginning of the game that i that like spell it out and it's one of
those you don't know unless you're looking for it and i thought that was very clever uh so anyway
i'm having fun with fantasy 13 um i played the warrior where demo i liked it now i know the full
game came out i haven't picked it up yet just because i've been occupied with a bunch of other
stuff i will pick it up in this next week i like the demo you didn't like it right loki
no i thought it was okay okay i didn't care for it no i bought the game my son beat it already
oh wow yeah i remember you saying that your son beat it really quickly yeah like he beat
he beat the whole game and like i i bought it on like friday evening and he beat it saturday
morning so it's like it's short um bobby blackwolf in chat says i'm the one who didn't care for the
demo no i a lot of people didn't care for the demo i felt like i was the only one that like
was like oh i like okay i like i i i understand the twist in the game um there's some like neat
modes and stuff that they have where you can lock like a battle mode where you're basically fighting
all the different characters almost like smash brothers sort of uh which is kind of neat um
i don't know i kind of like the old mario or the warrior games where like it's just like one type
of game and you just play the different themes and stuff not necessarily like oh i'll play it
as this character or i'll play it as this character and it plays differently each time
it's the i don't know it just gets you have to get used to it i guess but it's fine it's still fun
i will check out the full game this week i've just been that no man's sky thing kind of
blindsided me and i've been focused on that uh pretty much a lot of my gaming all right two
games left on my list um one of them i'm gonna give a shout out super metroid oh yes i played
super Metroid this week because on the flight home fired up my switch went into the super
Nintendo and i'm like what game do i what game could take me about four hours to play
and i played super metro but i only played super Metroid for maybe about an hour and a half
and i can't i can't speed run it yet it's been a long time since i played it but um i was having
a good time with it memories good times all right oh rob here's the last game on my list and i'm i'm
so mad about this but i can't resist these games the last game i've spent way too much time playing
this week is cookie clicker because no girl yes cookies girl here's the thing they did this game
is like 10 years old right but they just released it on steam and there are there are seriously like
300 achievements in it uh and all this other stuff and it's just you know you pay it's in it it's
silly because you're paying five dollars for what is free but it's also nice to support the
developers and they put a soundtrack for the Minecraft guy so it is a little weird to hear
like a Minecraft song because it's it's straight up a song out of Minecraft it's weird to hear that
while you're playing cookie clicker but it's not it's certainly not bad um and uh yeah and i've
i've been obsessed it's like if you look at the vog network discord it's gonna show on the right
hand side rob roberts is playing cookie clicker right now because yes it's idling on the other
computer in the other room right now so i can have more cookies when i get back so i can cast
my spells to generate more cookies on my way to uh having an empire of uh grandmas and all the
things that go into cookie clicker um if you don't know this game um that's probably a good
thing i'm not going to tell you anything about it so you can stay the hell away no uh it's it's an
idle clicker game that y'all probably remember the idle clicker it is the well one of two i would say
the other one was the one i talked about like six or seven years ago when it was on playstation 4
clicker heroes was the other one i was obsessed with for a long time yeah so i would say those
two are like the idle clicker games and there's there i'm sure every discord will light up this
week with other people mentioning idle clicker games they like it's a genre of games the idle
clicker game um and uh yeah the cookie clicker is like the classic and it's available on steam now
so shout out to them getting it out on steam and uh a whole nother stupid game for me to get into
but i'm having fun all right sorry i know i took up way too much time but that was my list i had
a lot on my list all right let's get to some other gaming news quickly though quickly um
before we get into more news i have to mention i'm like legally obligated and required to as somebody
who is an affiliate on twitch here uh with vog network it is sub timber here on twitch and that
means uh subs are a little bit cheaper i believe uh please click 20 yeah 20 off your first time sub
or gift subs are 20 off as well and i did see some folks donating subs earlier so thank you very much
for that super appreciated we'll shout those out after the recording as we usually do um but i
would be i would be remiss not to uh mention that subs are a little cheaper right now in those
circumstances uh if you do subscribe uh here at vog network which you're not required to do
obviously we don't paywall uh anything with our podcast that we've done for the last 20 years
but if you want to see the video on demand the vods that is something kind of new as of a couple
of years ago that is behind the paywall uh as well as some bonus videos uh for example if you
want to see us reacting to episode one we're on episode 883 tonight if you want to see dark soccer
loki and myself reacting to episode one a couple months ago uh you can actually check that out um
in the archives so and i just i just saw more subs go out there thank you thank you bobby
blackwell yeah i'll give out more uh shout outs later on so thank you thank you um all right
enough of that let's get into gaming news loki we'll start with you tonight
ah yes um along with the whole announcement of all these wonderful games coming to the
playstation 5 and whatnot sony also announced that hey you know that free ride we've been
giving you with all those playstation 4 to playstation 5 upgrades well it ain't free
anymore we're gonna charge you ten dollars for it which is dumb it really is dumb like
especially when you consider that games on the xbox you know you can play them on xbox one you
can play them on the xbox series consoles you play them on pc for the same price it makes no sense
but that's they want to charge extra money just like was it madden and stuff like that charging
for their next gen versions like 79 they want to charge another 10 for those upgrades um
um yeah i don't know so basically saying you know i also want to confirm that moving forward today
uh playstation first party exclusive cross-gen titles including uh will both digital and physical
or offer a ten dollar um digital upgrade option from place digit for the playstation 5 this will
apply to the next god of war and grand tourism of 7 any other cross-gen exclusive games uh published
by and uh any other cross-gen ps4 playstation 5 titles published by sodi interactive entertainment
and it should be noted this came after this whole hubaloo about horizon um not horizon zero dawn
horizon god damn it what's the name of the sequel forbidden west took me a minute and that whole
hubaloo about uh it was like it didn't were they gonna charge were they not and so they kind of
got cornered into having to give away that upgrade and i think that's what made them
say this statement is that like horizon is the last free one and from now on it's gonna cost
ten dollars for the upgrade um i think you make a damn good point about the fact that microsoft
you know very obviously doesn't really have the same stance on things um i kind of think sony
can leverage their position here a little bit and they're resting on the strength of a game like god
of war and so on that people will pay that ten dollars here's the problem though like yeah and
i get that like that they're charging now i are these games also like seventy dollar retail games
are they charging 69.99 for these as well my assumption is on ps5 yes but on ps4 no it's like
that's where the difference is there's like games and it's their choice to do that i think it's a
poor choice but like there's games like for example madden nfl that just got released with
you know the next gen prices as well and you ain't getting a next gen game it's like it's very
corners cut and stuff like that but it's these people thinking that well it's our franchise and
we we feel that you should pay seventy dollars for this game even though it's basically the same game
as each year it seems it's funny it's it's always these like sports titles you know like the nba
series um madden you know all this stuff that they seem to feel like that they should be charging for
this extra fee up front um zen monkey you can take that in consideration when you're buying
picking your consoles i guess zen monkey 11 in chat says it makes sense to me current gen games
are like 70 something bucks i think they need to let ps5 bps5 and let ps4 bps4 um you know and
i don't know it's it's hard for me to say i agree with that but at the same time i think
the reality is people are gonna grumble grumble grumble about this but they're gonna pay it
like people are not gonna vote with their wallet if they if they do i'll be pleasantly surprised
but i think people are just gonna pony up the money because i think the reality is got a war
gonna cost 60 bucks on ps4 it's gonna cost 70 bucks on ps5 so they're not gonna give you a
free pass if you buy the cheaper ps4 version you gotta pony up the difference and on that level
it does make sense you know 4k graphics and textures they ain't free uh and so forth but
i do think they are giving microsoft something to needle them at at the end of the day i will
say that i think microsoft can needle them on we don't have that price difference however i
don't think it's gonna matter because playstation still has got a war playstation still has grand
turismo and all the games that are affected by this are only games you can play on playstation
they're the playstation studio games so that's it they gotta they gotta lock on it yeah well
i mean they can do what they want me if people are willing to pay that price then i guess they
can charge that but i think it's it's silly and it does like i said sure it's not really an issue
right now because no one can get any consoles um but when it does become more available and
stuff and you're comparing you know the cost of the games on those systems granted those
exclusives are few and far between that's fine but you know especially when we've got like
microsoft purchasing all these studios there's gonna be a lot of exclusive games coming to their
console pretty soon sure it's a drought right now but like you know halo's nothing to really
you know balk at i mean you've got lots of big games coming granted yeah it's not got a war
but there's that there's their franchises over there as well i mean so and those i'm sure won't
be charging 70 per game plus you know you have games pass you could just get all that you know
with your subscription so i don't know and i was hearing them like talking about like was
it playstation now and stuff and how they're adding different games to that i'm just like
thinking yeah that's not appealing to me uh fifth dream in chat says i'm tired of sony trying to
cater to ps4 when ps5 is out too bad you haven't upgraded but that's how games have always worked
no one was demanding super nintendo games work on nes i to a point i agree with you there is a
point where sony has to leave the playstation 4 behind to really push the games on the ps5 and
the cutting edge tech here's the big problem you still can't really buy a ps5 i know i know you're
gonna y'all are gonna needle me on that point because you're gonna say i have a ps5 you had
to work to get that playstation 5 i don't think they can truly leave the playstation 4 behind
because remember gamers are not just you and me and the audience and the fandoms that would listen
to a show like this gamers are the families and the living rooms you know that are more casual
and play that type of stuff uh that you know look for these things as holiday gifts until you can
walk into target and pull a playstation 5 off the shelf and put it in your cart i'm not sure i
totally agree with the you could just upgrade when you want i don't think you can we're still having
to fight scalpers and all that stuff will this work itself out in a year i think so but i also
thought it would have fixed itself by now like i think if you go back to last year's show we're
sitting there going well by summer 2021 this won't be an issue anymore hmm so i think that's
something sony's still got to work out but at the end again i say all that and at the end of the day
i sort of go but this ten dollar none of it's gonna matter people are gonna pay it they're
gonna be fine and you know they're gonna rabble rabble and they're gonna pay it and that will
show sony that they did the right thing i guess so anyway uh just some thoughts on that okay
let me move on i want to talk about uh xbox i guess a little bit in the next story which has
to do with a controller update this is really funny because this is about the old xbox controller
and i instantly thought of when ronma called us i think it was the not the show before we but like
the show before that maybe 881 i think he called us and was talking about that he was trying to get
an xbox one controller and we were like just get the series x controller dude it's better and he's
like no i want a one controller it's what i want and one might say this news this week justifies
rama's position because a firmware update to the xbox one controller not the series x but the one
controller came out this week uh and it's out for insiders right now uh but it allows the uh
xbox one controllers to more easily paired at windows 10 ios 15 and android devices because
you know for the cloud stuff they want the um controllers to pair with the mobile devices as
well uh also um the xbox one controllers are going to get older controllers that will remember your
phone or pc so that you can switch over from a console uh and then there's also input latency
similar to what they have on the xbox series x and s is the dli is what they call that is also
coming to the xbox one controllers so if you have those controllers still sitting around you might
want to check for those upgrades uh as of the the article midweek it's only out for the insiders in
that program um but uh i'm sure this is going to roll out to a wider audience very soon and you
might actually be in the insiders program i know i am um so i'll have to update my old controllers
because you know why not uh and did your own medicine chat says by the way i got my xbox one
controller well there you go now there's a brand new firmware to put on it if you're well will you
put the new firmware on it rama i'm curious about that anyway i thought that was that that just made
me laugh especially considering that show a couple weeks ago made me laugh uh all right
let's move on dark sakura so the the thing that has been the bane of uh many a streamer the hate
raids well twitch is finally doing something about it something at least um as as a lot of
people know we had a strike on sept on september first um to protest against twitch's lack of
response um and so now uh twitch has filed a lawsuit against two of the people involved in
the hate raid um it uh it was uh their their names are only known as creatine overdose and cruise
control uh believed to be from uh austria and the netherlands respectively they have suspended and
permanently banned their accounts um and they've used alternate accounts to uh to keep going with
their hate raids and so now they um have uh been sued basically to prevent anything else from
happening and to seek some i guess some reparations about it but um the big thing that i think
a lot of us want to see is it's not just these two i mean maybe these two are the big ones behind it
but and it's a start it's a start but they need to do something to fix the potential abuse for
the system yeah um i i say this news is deserving of one clap thank you uh now let's tackle some of
the other issues that broadcasters are asking for um and you know meanwhile this news comes out and
you know you think it would shut things down i was followed by eight of those hoes while i was and i
call them hose hose the name starts hos so they're hoes so i was reading it as as hoss i know because
it's hoss but i yeah but and i realize that's probably not what they want you to call them
but you would only call somebody what they want to be called when you respect them because i don't
respect them i'm going to call them what i want to call them and they're hoes well it's okay because
everybody else has been calling them hoes anyway yeah they're hoes so eight of those hoes followed
me while i was broadcasting no man's sky and so i had to go blah blah so it's like the issue is
still going on i'm kind of surprised twitch allows you to create a name with hoes in it right now
um because they're all but i at the same time if they banned that name they just moved to
something else we all know that um well and now like i had one that was like hose something
underscore winner and then ha ha ha ha ha yeah and then the moment though that i went to because
you know i keep my channel open all the time so i get to see anyone who's followed me while i'm not
live just you know just there you know because i also go in and host a lot of other people
and i saw both of them there when i went to ban them they had already been deleted yeah so
something is happening as which you know again okay clap but it's still it's it's like not enough
you know yeah but i i you know what i will say i appreciate that they're taking the legal angle
with it and trying to sue the pants off of them and most most importantly out who they are because
these individuals when they are named they will get to own that imagery those words that hate
will be tied to those individuals and the other thing even though even if we don't have public
spanking anymore these two are going to be publicly spanked by the internet sorry dark soccer
well the other thing though that makes me think on the other side um and
it's the same thing as i mean i don't want to compare the two but it's sort of like the
publicity that a mass shooter gets or a cult leader gets okay i can see that is that it also
does lead to copycats we shouldn't be making people famous for doing shitty things okay i
okay i i can respect that side of it i mean there is a part of me that thinks
that they need there needs to be accountability you know and these two need to own it but i
completely understand the whole sometimes these people get turned into martyrs because of that
and that yeah that's that that's a valid concern but i i just i feel like there needs to be that
accountability too so where do we find that balance between making these people accountable
but not making them famous and i think that is where we have to hold the media the reporting
and all of that accountable is that when these names are ultimately outed they are only used
in a negative context in the media you know and that we instead we say we uplift the marginalized
creators that have been so attacked by these raids you know as the good guys and the hoes are
the bad guys so it's gonna be a balance i think to do this right yeah i i i definitely don't
i would rather in this case that instead of their channel names be listed even though they
are perma band that they just straight up give their name if that's gonna happen
yeah all right well to be continued i think we'll be reporting on this nearly every week
until it's resolved so we'll see all right at least though it is something i i would say i
would put this as a two clap okay one clap for the lawsuit one clap for the other thing i already
forgot oh the banning the the banning that we're noticing is happening so one one one clap for
each all right twitch has earned two claps we should have a clap counter all right anyway
uh moving on unfortunately and i don't want to i don't want to laugh because we're about to go
into another story that um is here here we go another week of this but it this is a necessary
topic especially when we talked about everything that was going on with activision blizzard king
a couple weeks ago which by the way i just want to remind everybody the demands of the employees
at activision blizzard king have still gone unresponded to but i mentioned when we talked
about that that this is a symptom of the industry not just one company and loki i think you have
some follow-up to that right yeah it's more companies so uh wargaming the community manager
has quit alleging toxic corporate culture so there's been issues with wargaming for a while
especially like even how they um treat their kind of uh i don't know why their their partners i
guess and they have decided to leave with remember there's a whole thing about um there's one of the
ships that was being given away as part of a loot box or something like that instead of being given
there's like a direct way to purchase it or something like that and you may remember that
there was um a promo code that was sent out or a code that was available that um basically uh
translated to you know uh fucking turi which turi i guess is one of the um streamers who was also
um kind of fed up with what was going on so there's like some abuse you know they were
basically targeting their partners and stuff um but basically yeah so you know these folks are
leaving since i've fortunately been given the opportunities to advance on my own career amazing
things um but they have to make the decision because of the recent termination of an employee
on my team they believe um to be a kind competent individual for a reason i personally perceive them
to be um to be an illegitimate incredibly persistent campaign to unfairly scapegoat him
by leadership so there's folks just like i guess dog piling on this employee and you know he blames
like toxic corporate culture perpetuating cycles of serious errors stretched back at least four
years well before the person's time on the team and as well as um you know his pay grade so
yeah this was uh zachary cabmec doig and um he has like a whole letter here if you want to
you know check that out but basically saying yeah if there is just some campaign to target
different people um to try to like kind of push them out so that's unfortunate that that happens
so that's one company and then uh there's another one uh talking about uh paradox
so paradoxed uh which is a swedish publisher there was a survey conducted by the swedish
unions that spoke to 133 of the 400 about 400 employees and they alleged that 44 said that
they had experienced this form of mistreatment of those surveyed 26 were women where the um
statistics were much worse they said 69 of them have experienced abusive treatment as well
so this is an international industry problem as well you know this kind of yeah definitely um
points the the finger on it would be understood like wondering if it's just like it's not even
like just the gaming industry i think in general like there could be a lot of toxic behavior out
there but it is it is the tech industry um yeah you know and gaming is is certainly a part of that
you know i i overheard a very interesting conversation alan and i went to dinner the other
night at a um a ramen place here that we really enjoy that recently opened up a huge outdoor
dining area and it felt great um but the people behind us um there were two girls that were um
students at at the local university i could tell they were talking very loud like i wasn't trying
to eavesdrop but they were i don't know a few drinks in or something they're talking very loud
and it was very interesting to hear them talk about the tech industry because i think they
were both in it or like studying to be in it and they were kind of talking about you know some of
the weird things that dudes do in the industry and you know i i you know there's that there's
that part of me that kind of wants to be like you know there's some good people too but you know you
don't want to not all men that type of conversation and it's just i think you know you get to be a fly
on a wall for a very realistic and um a perspective on things and how creepy some people can be
yeah it's unfortunate um and then of course paradox has uh responded to these allegations
saying obviously the results of the survey are deeply concerning it's like bog standard uh pr
speak there the management team wants to ensure this data is acted upon but um taking immediate
direct um action is legally difficult thanks to the informal nature of the survey
and yeah fun all right well it's unfortunate that this is continuing but at the same time
it has to be kind of like it's been happening so this stuff has to come out it has to be identified
if companies are going to put out their canned pr speak okay but it has to be called out so it
can be fixed um so again i sadly don't think it's going to end here and they're going to have more
of this so we'll see uh meanwhile let's talk about some good news i think with the studio
let's talk about um the recent purchase by playstation studios of fire spite
excuse me not fire spite fire sprite uh fire sprite is the studio that made playroom uh the
playroom vr and the persistence and they are now a part of playstation studios and honestly i think
the most surprising part of the story to me was that they weren't already because everything
they've developing is pretty much exclusive for playstation but uh who who can forget how
important the playroom was to those early days of broadcasting on the playstation 4 that i remember
that was a thing yeah that's a thing so it makes it very i'm curious what uh what they're gonna
bring to the table uh for playstation in the next experience um but anyhow home hey i'd love that
but we'll see um some developers will go back to sony with this deal but um quite a few develop
because quite a few members of fire sprite apparently came from the wipeout developer
studio liverpool and then uh sony bought that when they were like psychosis and then they shut
them down in 2012 anyway um so yeah sony and fire sprite have been kind of hand in hand uh ever
since then uh all of that said is the team is working on something new but we don't know what
it is uh we only know that they did the playroom and they had a vita and mobile title run sackboy
run i played that i think that's one of the endless runners they do the astro bots games as
well where the different studio they did not do the astro bot playstation 5 game which is
interesting because that all all that stuff came from the family yeah because playroom like one of
the things i liked playing on there the most with like my kids is they had an uh bot game it was
like throwing ninja stars as ninja bots or something like that it's like throwing ninja
stars on like a runner type of game and that was kind of fun to kind of show you like the motion
um controls for the playstation 4 it should be noted though with fire sprite the the playroom
and run sackboy run those are the only titles that haven't really been vr related so it's very likely
fire sprite is working on something to launch playstation 5's vr headset whenever that happens
that makes i would say that's probably what they're working on and so and we don't know if
that means another like astro bot playroom related thing hey i i always thought playstation home like
the shift to vr would make a lot of sense for that but um yeah so uh and then uh jumping in as well
to to save the day and chat bobby blackwolf is in chat saying um astro bot is a soap a soby studios
not to be confused with osobo who made flight simulator so there's a little bit of a correction
there from our chat and by the way yes you just saw a new camera angle here on twitch so that when
there's chat stuff to shout out we have that available all right uh let's move on with our
next story which i think is dark sakras even though she's got delivered dinner i think
it is but there's no mayonnaise on it good hey it's my food and i like mayonnaise i get cubie
mayonnaise um so um you know a lot of people really enjoyed sonic colors i don't know why
but some people liked it and so sonic colors ultimate um uh came out on the switch but um
apparently the switch version has a lot of buggy bugs and glitchy glitchies
and so a twitch user sorry twitter user named vex contacted nintendo to try to get a refund
and they were all like yeah we know about it here's your money back
and so apparently you can now call nintendo and get your refund unless you're enjoying the game
or have played a lot of it then don't do that because you got your money's worth right so right
but apparently there's a lot of issues with the nintendo version of the game that are not present
in the other versions of the game and i don't know if that's part of the tech specifications
of the switch or what have you but i guess it's just it's it's having problems i haven't played
colors ultimate myself sonic colors ultimate myself so i can't tell you what that's all about
but um that's interesting that uh nintendo is offering that it's it's it's the cyberpunk of
sonic games clearly i reckon all right uh let's move on loki so this is kind of exciting but
apparently there is a working playstation 4 emulator now um that's right playstation 4
now it doesn't play a lot of things obviously it's not a full-fledged um you know emulator for
a lot of retail software but you can actually play some of these 2d games in fact i saw um some
examples of what was it shovel knight being played on it which it's still kind of got some graphical
issues and whatnot but right now what they've been kind of playing on there is a lot of these
different 2d games um but there's still you know a lot of different hitches with it like for
example there's stuff you have to dump from a playstation board and files that you need to run
um in order to be able to do that and then transferring the game as well um you have to do
that as to get that to run on pc but it is an exciting start at least to see them being able
to play like you know some games on there and it was actually running at like pretty good speeds
aside from the graphical glitches i mean it's pretty respectable for where it's at now when
we get into 3d and when some of those graphical things are enabled that may you know cause the
games to run a little bit slower but it's still not a bad start so far um and bobby in chat uh
by like asked an appropriate question saying so if it doesn't play many things is it really a
working emulator um from well it has it plays a hundred it plays lots of indie games so they
said that right now the emulator has uh hundreds of indie games that are supported by it so it's
basically 2d games that are running on it right now and so uh when okay so i've i've mentioned
on the show before that back in the day i was a little more heavily involved with emulator scenes
especially when the nintendo emulators and super nintendo emulators really were starting to gain
a lot of ground um and usually it's kind of like a checkpoint along the way for a lot of the
emulator developers because it's one thing to like have the hardware going and have the hardware kind
of like run but it's another to actually then get the game working um for example um many a very
popular nes emulator back in the day and i'm going to date myself a little bit here because this
isn't the one people use anymore was nesticle was the the big one that uh a lot of folks used right
it was nesticle and there was genesis because the developer had a sense of those are the ones
although i think i used a different one than genesis because genesis wouldn't play panorama
cotton and that that you actually put what it is so nesticle was considered a working emulator
but it didn't play every nes game because there were nes games with custom mappers custom chipsets
um like and it had a lot one of the the big things back in the day i figured out how to get
castlevania 3 running on nesticle um by changing some things in the file specifications
and um that that got the vertical scrolling stuff to work that was considered working
even though it wasn't 100 perfect so there's kind of a difference between the emulator works
and the emulator is 100 now i would say the nes emulators you see nowadays like the things that
are playing pixel poops number two and stuff those are 100 emulators basically but i i also get you
know i i i don't know if bobby was saying that tongue in cheek or not but i also kind of get it
but just coming up from a long time ago a working emulator is basically like when it plays one game
it works it emulated a game now it's building it out from there to 100 emulation yeah so and
in the emulator because i didn't mention the name it's called spine and they did update some of the
game library on the first of september but there's you know still quite a bit that needs to be worked
on um there are some games though that are running i like persona 5r is running like i said though
lots of graphical issues right now but at least it is booting up to the game and it's able to run it
they have a whole like spreadsheet of all the different games and like where they are like
whether they'll boot at all where if it gets to like the title screen or in game that type of
stuff so it's not perfect obviously but it is progress just think that guy that wrote nesticle
probably got to be in his late 40s now probably a family and he's like i'm the guy that wrote
nesticle anyway shout out to that guy hey that guy got us through our college years so shout out
and i i hope he's doing well even if nintendo probably wanted to sue the pants off of them
back in the day i hope i hope he's having a good day all right moving on let's talk about this
next story which has to do with a steam update so steam got an update this week uh which uh has to
do with managing downloads and storage uh makes it very easy to move games from one drive to another
which i appreciate because i sometimes need to get things off my solid state drive onto the non-solid
state drive to get a different game on the ssd uh these changes have been in beta for a while
but it just came out for all users uh as a stable release it will now show installation progress on
top of download status um and now there's instead of view news there's view news there's patch notes
um there's also a storage manager that will show you how much space you have left uh for moving
gate sorry guys for moving games around and things of that sort i still want to know why it
takes my computer so fucking long to patch a game do you know that dead by daylight pinhead thing
and this happens with every dead by daylight patch that comes out it takes my computer like
it takes an hour and a half to two hours to download and patch that it's crazy and i don't
know does that happen to anybody else when let's hear it for stadia i never have to deal with that
yeah but you know i i also don't have that weird frame rate thing that comes in when the cloud gets
skippy so i don't have weird frame rate things remember usually when i'm playing i am streaming
at the same time yeah um okay so bobby and chat says it happens for some of my games but not
others i guess that is that whole uh uh uh sorry i lost my train of thought uh it's that whole um
dang it sorry it happens for some of my games not for others is what bobby glacol said it
really depends on if the game is packed rather than just flat files is that spaghetti code
coming into play again when it comes to dead by daylight that's for sure how about that
dj rama s found the guy that did nest he works for ea as a senior software engineer now well good for
him congratulations that means he's making money good for him all right and steam update hooray
uh bobby says it really depends if the game is packed rather than just flat files well dead by
daylight's definitely a packed game all right let's let's go to a simpler time when we didn't
have to have a download manager why because everything was on a cartridge or i think in
tonight's game case a cd so let's get into no not even a cd something special all right let me uh
let me play the official transition and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where i'll
dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it it's time for the classic game
of the week and what did you pick this week dark soccer i picked blue stinger a game i've talked
about a whole bunch and have never apparently done so um and happy belated birthday to the
dreamcast with this one right seriously yeah the ninth so basically um this particular game came
out in 1999 uh for the dreamcast it was developed by climax graphics originally published by sega
and then outside in japan and outside of japan it was published by excuse me hiccup activision
um the game is entirely 3d you heal yourselves real time with you know food and drinks and
in the game um and of course uh you have to buy them from vending machines so you can only get
to heal when it's actually safe to heal um you can buy weapons and ammo the same way out of a
vending machine including uh you can get rocket launchers napalm uh triple barreled shotguns you
can get a freaking lightsaber that was my favorite weapon um you have two characters you have elliot
and you have another guy named dogs who has a crossbow and so there's also like the beat so
it sort of combines some shooter elements and some beat them ups so basically uh a long ass
time ago a meteorite hits and wiped out all the dinosaurs and then now um this biotech company is
uh trying to make things happen i don't want to just say too much because it's been a long time
since i've played this game i beat it when it came out um and then um this like creature arrives
that is seals it in this dome of energy and so elliot's trying to solve this mystery
um so as far as the game goes there the big thing that's notable about it is that the
cinematography in the japanese version was
it it basically drew from cinema uh cinematic techniques um
and it really added i think to the drama in the game added some tension in certain scenes
um but um in the us version it had some pretty terrible dubbing um
and this fixed camera system it was a behind the player third-person view
um kind of tomb raider-ish um or almost resident evil-ish but like there's this one scene because
i played through both the the us and the japanese version i had the japanese version first
um there's this like tower that you're on a spiral going up and the camera would zoom far out
and like almost like a drone looking around it you know it was really really cool it was hard
as fuck to play you kind of had to pay attention to where you were but then in the us one it's just
falling around and it's so fucking boring it's boring as balls but the game itself did not get
a lot of great great ratings okay like it maybe was middle of the line it had a 28 out of 40 from
famitsu um you know it didn't like the highest rating it got was an 8.4 out of 10 from ign
so it's it was pretty average um but it was novel and it was a fun actual little game i
i wasn't mad at it i played through the whole thing i thought it was fun i had a great time
with it and it is one of the early full 3d survival horror games you know i honestly
like to say that blue stinger paved the way for code veronica to come out um i just really
thought that the game was a neat little game i thought that it had unique elements to it i
laughed my ass off that you would have to buy all your shit through a vending machine
that you could buy a rocket launcher in a vending machine go fig so um
um yeah i would say that um if you can find the japanese copy of it however you find it
give that one a play you can play it in english um it it's not a difficult game by any means i
i had an easy time of it i played all the way through it in practically one sitting um actually
i take that back it was a couple of sittings but it was it was a nice fun little game and it had
a decent story i mean yeah the graphics now are going to be kind of dated it is very early dream
cast but it was absolutely a smash to play i had a great time with it so there you go it's blue
stinger i'm not sure it definitely kind of um set the stage for like cinematic type of games like
you know i see a lot even though yes it's a little bit clunky and old looking i still see
like a lot of modern games in this yeah and like even this one little scene here uh now this is
i want to say this one is the japanese version yeah it is um because you can see how in some
cases it starts off with these like more cinematic elements um it was it was very
novel for what it did that's that's what my thought is it was very novel for what it did
it certainly set the stage again for this for this type of play and it was all 3d
very true yeah so some comments in chat bobby blackwell says i bought this on launch day at
the dreamcast just for the intro movie it really wasn't my kind of game so i never really played it
much further and then ssj100 matt in chat says yeah i got the game around uh launch uh as well
wasn't a fan at the time but appreciated it later uh i think i ended up trading it i can't believe
for nfl blitz so it kind of sounds like you know with uh you know kind of what you guys are saying
there it's kind of one of those things where it's like you you you it didn't maybe it wasn't the
greatest game but if you only played the us version you missed out but so many things that
it did kind of set the stage for later stuff too but there probably will not be any hurry to make
a remaster of this game or anything like that if they did that there's a lot of potential in it okay
all right your classic game of the week blue stinger all right let's travel around the world
quickly and check out some other rapid fire news so loki i'm gonna go to you all right
so uh you know me i am a big fan of legos and so there's a brand new set coming out now
for super mario 64 and it's actually a giant question block with a bunch of micro builds of
the different levels in super mario 64 as well and it all folds down into one neatly uh shaped
question block and they've got like peach's castle baba uh battlefield cool cool mountain
and lethal lava trouble are the levels that are kind of featured in there so that's pretty awesome
it's coming out october 1st for 169.99 at uh lego.com or the lego retail stores
not sure if i'll pick this up because i have no room for any more sets unfortunately but
i would if i did um and then this is kind of fun so we always hear like you know patches for
different games to block cheating but in this case um cookie clicker has been patched to help
with cheating so they have a patch now that it was to address some memory leak issues due to
some audio stuff uh when using auto clicking and so now they've uh fixed that so now you can use
auto clickers with less uh i do not use auto clickers for the record no but i do want to check
out some of the mods that's i should have mentioned that when i was talking about my gaming week
is it cookie yeah cookie clicker now embraces mods and that's another big thing of the steam race
that's interesting yeah i'm just i'm waiting for titty clicker
nothing yet sorry podcast listeners but the look dark soccer just shot me while she's mid sandwich
uh bobby blackwolf in chat says ttp clicker yeah i don't yeah anything's possible thanks to mods
yeah so check that out i will uh let's move on uh dark sakura uh when you're able to uh
chew on that sandwich uh you i think you have a couple things that were i do shout it out in our
discord yeah so um one of those is that um platinum games wants to bring star fox zero to the switch
and um starfox zero was on weu it came out in uh 2016 and it was one of platinum's games and they
want to bring it back it'd be cool if they did actually actually they're quoted as saying it's
not cool that people are aren't able to play older games because they're locked out on the platform
and so of course if anything was possible we'd like to bring over any of those older titles to
the newer platforms and in other news arcade one up has a uh a tabletop uh a mortal combat
and the marvel uh versus capcom table and everything they are now up for pre-order
and there was much rejoicing well it's so these games were never on tabletop that's what struck
me as interesting about it is that these games yeah cocktail cabinets they're fighting games
somebody's yeah somebody's gonna be screwed on the wrong side i'm trying to look at this picture to
see oh look at it the sprit this the screen is split in half oh so one person gets they have a
they have a mirror of the screen okay okay i'm pretty sure that they had a street fighter 2
cocktail cabinet at one point not street not street fighter this is mortal combat 2 well
and the other one is marvel versus capcom separately i think loki's talking about these
are new i think there has been a street fighter one but i think also like in in the real world
quote-unquote that game was so fucking popular you can't really understate like what that game
did for arcades in 1992 or whatever year it was uh i actually that one i wouldn't be surprised if
it had a legitimate cocktail cabinet at one point it was just that big of a game even if it didn't
make sense so um sort of on off topic you know those like little tiny arcade cabinets oh yeah
the ones i collect these little arcade classics there's other different types too well you know
we were getting some of them um i found at tj maxx of all places a galaga cocktail table size
like a full arcade one up machine no no the teeny ones oh but but a cocktail
yeah but a cocktail huh it is tiny but of course you know i i had to buy it i mean
normally those things was uh uh well i think they were like 20 bucks and this was like of course
because it was tj maxx it was like 10 yeah wow i know yeah i might have to go on a run
i didn't think to check stuff like good luck tj maxx but yeah don't go to big lots because they
um are uh hate paid oh shit i didn't know that all right but they're very i think of those types of
stores you know they contributed to uh you know who oh all right what were you gonna say logie
oh i was gonna say uh we uh this a while back okay we had talked about another company that
was bringing arcade games to the you know home uh was ice um so that got me thinking like did
they ever put up their page to sell arcade games they have actually so you can the thing is though
is i don't see how these are like home versions of arcade games these just look like arcade games
so like for example they have jurassic park pro you know that you can bring that game home for
ten thousand dollars that's just the arcade game at that point that's not like that's not a that's
not a deal that's just arcade game or like you can get a skee ball that's like five thousand dollars
it's like that's a skee ball you know like i don't get it but they are selling them now so so
that's a thing but all righty sadly it's a a ten a nine thousand two hundred ninety five dollar thing
and not a five hundred dollar thing which is what i was really hoping it was all right let's travel
around the world and check out some release dates and some games coming out um pretty soon so logie
we'll start with you in the us thank god death loop is finally coming out so i don't see any
more stupid trailers for it but that's coming out on playstation uh five and pc and the speaking of
a stupid trailer we did get another one of those during the playstation event because god forbid
they they have to you know shout that game out since it's the only Bethesda game they're getting
i i i'm actually gonna agree with Loki on this they're they're they're setting that up for
disaster by show it's like i get the no man's sky vibe from that sorry which is funny because i love
no man's sky now but we all know that when it released it did not like really buy into all
that hype because they hyped it over and over and over again and i feel death loop isn't a death loop
pun intended yeah it it was annoying so but it is coming out though so look for that this week
uh we have bang dream girls band party on nintendo switch all right punctuation is key there
um eastward on a pc mac and nintendo switch metallic child on pc and nintendo switch skate
bird on pc nintendo switch and xbox one and origami 2 on pc playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox
1 and xbox series x and last but not least nino kuni 2 revenant kingdom princes edition on nintendo
switch all right heading over to japan uh a few games this week on september 16th uh for the
nintendo switch sins memories off the starry sky on that same bang dream girls band party for
nintendo switch also coming out but you know what that's a music game that looks it's it's got that
like uh you know uh rolling grid with the notes on it now it kind of i'm like oh i'm curious i
want to see more about this if it has some songs i'm into i might be into it um attention bobby
black wolf nino kuni 2 revenant kingdom is being released on the nintendo switch this week in japan
but i think it's actually also due for the us uh so there's that as well on the switch this week
a game called kiwi uh not like the fruit but key we is out this week charade maniacs is out as well
and metallic child is also out in japan this week and uh that is what you got on the nintendo switch
checking the playstation 5 real quick uh we have death loops japanese release is same date as the
u.s release on the 14th uh some overlap as well with kiwi uh we have space space star topia and
that is it for oh i'm sorry aliens fire team elite is also out in japan this week
and that is it for japanese releases dark sakura how about the uk
i think you're muted dark sira no i was oh i know okay um we we have on the 14th we have
cruise and blast and death loop uh 3d billiards pool and snooker um that's on the 16th also in
the 16th we have panda hero rims racing nino kuni 2 for switch um that's on the 17th also in the
17th is oneria crimes i guess and then picaminosa also on the 17th and that's it all right uh let's
get some more news stories and then we'll open up uh for calls if you want to join our discord vog
network dot com slash discord uh and uh in the green room is where we'll uh field for calls but
we do have a little bit of time still it's probably gonna be a few minutes before we get there we have
some more stories uh including uh this one from loki about some international news right
yeah so there was some news while we were out about chinese the chinese government cracking down
on uh basically gameplay relegating children to only allow them to play like i think it was like
two or three hours a week during specific times and or under the age of 18 yeah and so because
of that um locked or the kind of crackdown there is uh several lots of money being lost
from uh chinese companies so uh 60 billion dollars in losses from net ease and ten cent
uh because of their stocks and the sell-offs that they had to do during that time because of this
announcement um that's a lot of money that they lost but yeah so um along with that though of
course um there's new restrictions in place where basically because you know china is really um
controlling for all of you know their gaming and everything so you have to put like in some id
number or something into the system when you play and um but you know people are gonna circumvent it
so what are people doing well kids are taking their parents ids and putting them into the system
along with their names and playing games under their parents profile instead so they can get
around the two-hour limit that they have because like no one would have figured this out i guess
but yeah um it's interesting apparently though the ten cents also rolling out a time-sensitive
facial recognition system for some games uh they're calling it midnight patrol aims to
prevent um kids posing as grown-ups by scanning their face between i guess the hours of 10 p.m
and 8 a.m i mean they don't live in china i know i was gonna say i get how they probably get away
with that on smartphones but how do they do that on desktops i guess i guess there's a picture of
maybe put a picture of their their parent like next to a webcam or something like that and then
just point the webcam somewhere else there's get away with everything it's just really unfortunate
like i understand that you know the gaming addiction problem is real and it's real here
it's not just real um overseas but sometimes some of the the culture with the the cafes and stuff
really exacerbate that whole thing um but i i just don't understand like why do they regulate how
many how long you can watch a movie do they regulate how long you can read a book do they
really what kind of movies tv shows i mean yeah they do they do really the kind of movies but
they don't really regulate the length they also they've been regulating the kind of games for a
long time you know uh most popular story that comes to my mind is world of warcraft had to
kind of get rid of the undead in order to release um because that is very frowned on and that
culture is like the the i guess animation of like bodies or things like that so they had to
really change it they're called the forsaken and they're just they're different they're not so um
you know uh uh zombie like i guess so um but they're of the unliving yes
uh s2100 matt suggests as another way to get around the uh scanning print out your parents
face and wear it as a mask there you go or just say you know dad come here can you look at the
camera all right anyway gonna have a staring contest with this camera for a good i don't know
eight hours well i play some world of warcraft all right uh let's talk further about legal uh
issues and uh this has to do with a kickstarter there was a hand-drawn nintendo entertainment
system game i already know what happened here yeah yeah right i don't even need to finish
well actually you know what's interesting they're not naming the company that sent the lawyer and i
wonder if that's for legal reasons everybody is assuming um because it's interesting because
even um you know i'm i'm looking at a source here from kotaku that got corrected after the fact
saying a previous version of this story jumped to conclusions regarding the parties involved in the
shutdown i found that very interesting because that means somebody contacted kotaku telling him
to change it out of possible legal concerns there so this is a very interesting legal game of chess
that's going on anyway what happened uh it was a hand-drawn game guides kickstarter uh by creator
phillips summers uh and he knew it was a risk to do um but uh the kickstarter happened the
kickstarter got uh well funded over three hundred thousand dollars but then had to be cancelled
again they did not name outright what happened but in an update on kickstarter uh the creator
phillips summer said i was basically he was contacted by a lawyer and so from there he made
that decision to pull the project and i i totally got his reasoning because if the kickstarter had
gone through and that money got pulled from everybody's bank account he'd be legally obligated
through kickstarter to come through with the backer rewards and this is kind of what he went
through in his is a message uh and so he didn't want to find himself in that position so he pulled
the plug before the kickstarter finished basically um everybody is jumping to conclusions about who
that lawyer was and who they were representing um but i also think um i think nintendo quite frankly
whether it was or wasn't them um nintendo has earned that reputation of everyone jumping to
conclusions that it is them for a very good reason and i think that speaks to something as well is
like you know whether that lawyer was or wasn't from nintendo we all assume it was because
nintendo has this reputation now in the industry that being said
i'm not surprised at all and this was a pretty bold move to try to do this guide using all of
these different ip's from a class you know from classic nintendo era here's the interesting thing
when people are selling their prints of samus and mario and things they draw at a convention or
whatever there's kind of a wink and a nod and an under the table type of thing i think the
scale of this type of project definitely drew somebody's attention um and that's why it
ultimately got shut down but because it's all legalese we'll never know exactly who it was
and exactly what was said but i think it was smart of him to preemptively pull the plug because he
made a damn good point if he had continued it he would have had to deliver on those backer
awards and he may not have been able to do that legally so something wondering if like because
like i'm looking here and looking at the different guides that they have and they have like contra
and there's like ninja guide in and stuff like that i'm wondering if like
couldn't just take metroid and zelda out of there and just do like some of these other guides
perhaps but the reality is he needs to get permission from the developers in order to
sell something like that on that scale so anyway all right moving on dark sakura
uh the stupid mute button doesn't want to work anyway um uh we have uh uh ueda
rita who was the uh jet set radio artist and the director of yakuza is back at sega
yay and this was like a while it was like 10 years or so um he posted the news on facebook in may
and he was thinking his uh co-workers at yahoo where he'd been working on some mobile titles
that he was going to go back to making games at sega and um apart from being the art director
for jet set radio and jet set radio future um like i said he was the director on the first two yakuza
games um and uh he is uh it's kind of coinciding with the departure of nagoshi toshiro um who was
the current yakuza creator that is exactly what came to mind yeah yeah and he's leaving uh for
a chinese company called net ease so um other games that are under ueda's belt uh are rise of
nightmares uh panzer dragoon uh uh the panzer dragoon series uh including panzer dragoon as a
uh panzer dragoon saga um which was in japan panzer dragoon rpg and panzer dragoon orta and
some of the sonic and sega all-stars racing games so who knows what'll happen i'm looking forward
to it all right welcome back that's going to be interesting that how much yakuza's changed and
now you know like a dragon is going to be the direction for the main series uh so it's
interesting the original director is kind of walking back into that where this big change
has happened but uh it'll be interesting i'm very you know just because i enjoyed the last game and
yes i still need to finish it and you know i've just been distracted with all these other new
shinies um but um i am really uh curious about that next game i'm i'm definitely on board uh for
the next yakuza game because i i enjoyed like a dragon so much and i still need to go back and
play the old ones too so anyway we'll see where that goes uh meanwhile loki so we just talked
about season this is from nintendo so i'm just gonna say one name and you'll already know what's
gonna happen rockstar games so uh and actually take more of take two interactive so we've
mentioned so many times that take two has gone after modders for different things and so now
here's yet another uh grand theft auto underground that was taking the maps from three and vice city
and kind of bringing them together and so because of that you know they cease and desisted it again
because they're probably going to re-release these games or i'm sorry they're going to um
not really yeah they're going to port them over to playstation 5 or something like that and it's
gonna be just like the mobile port but did we already know like grand theft auto 3 vice city
and all that was getting some type of i think it's rumor i don't know if it's like we know that's
coming back yet but like it's i don't know but it's annoying though that you know the modding
scene with grand theft auto is what kind of keeps grand theft auto alive honestly because i think a
lot of like the roleplay stuff and all that that people play like in five and online is through
the modding scene and i know a lot of the attention game gets us through the modding scene as well
like they wouldn't i don't know it's it's really dumb i don't know what happened with take-two
interactive and okay well take-two interactive has always sucked but like i don't know what's
happened with rockstar games i they're not the company they used to be unfortunately
uh fifth dream in chat says i'd play grand theft auto 5 if they added all the other games into it
lol a big grant grand theft super game yeah that was the thought before was like online was
supposed to kind of expand to like oh you can go liberty city now or you can go to vice city
or something like that i think they're making so much money off of the the garbage that they're
doing right now with it that they just feel that they don't need to make those kinds of updates
because that's a lot of a lot of updates and for what kind of return are they going to get
not probably much more than what they have now so we'll wait and see i guess there'll be another
10 years of grand theft auto 5 at least we'd make the joke about older scroll skyrim and being
re-released all the time at least we know there's a new game coming i mean that's been confirmed at
least so you know they have kind of lead there at least on the bethesda side but like rockstar like
we don't know anything yeah it's uh we had it's been a while since we had a really big update
from rockstar you know exactly i used to be a big champion of the grand theft auto series
and now it's like i just can't play online anymore like i don't have any interest
whatsoever it's such a grind fest and they have like such irritating things inside there like
i mean you have to pay to you know you have to pay rent in your apartment you have to pay to
keep your cars in the garage and you have to pay to have your maintenance guy you know fix your
cars and also it's like it's such a grind just to make it a grind so that you have to buy those
shark cards is what it is and that's just i'm not interested in that no thanks all right let's get
to one last story tonight and that's catching up a little bit with what's going on with epic games
uh on one front we have the house party app um which i have i had never heard of until of this
but i guess some people were getting into house party uh during the pandemic um i guess it was
some type of video chat calling thing although i've pretty much i've heard zoom i've heard
facetime i've heard skype i i never had heard a house party but i guess it was one of the others
involved with this and then epic actually bought house party uh and now they're going to be shutting
it down at some point in october in fact it's already gone from stores uh i had no idea that
house party was integrated into fortnite but apparently that was the thing uh and that will
be going away as well um what's also interesting is that um epic is kind of saying as part of the
reason why it's going away they are crafting meaningful and authentic new socialization
features that will be useful at a metaverse level across epic game titles that makes me wonder if
they're building something for the epic game store and if this isn't something that they want to
build into that because you know epic wants to launch their game store on mobile devices
and they just like first put all the features in the store i feel like their store sucks compared
to see i'm sorry heart yeah or like a wish list there's so much other ways to browse it
it really is maybe maybe we shouldn't try to reinvent the chatting in the games and like just
finish your stupid like they they had a roadmap for their store like come on that is so stupid
but it has been noted that you know fortnite has gone through this interesting shift where now
a lot of the recent reporting hasn't been about battle royale and that game but about things like
the ariana grande concert and uh you know party royale and things like that so it's interesting
to see what might be uh coming through on that space um something that i referenced there that
obviously we'd have to mention on the show at some point there was an update this week on the epic
epic versus apple thing um and there's all sorts of reports out there some are saying apple lost
some are saying well epic kind of lost it too here's the reality of that whole thing and why
i'm not making a bigger deal out of it um it's not over epics already filed an appeal which is
which when you consider a lot of the headlines have been apple lost uh the epic is appealing
the decision because there were some things in there that were very unfavorable to epic
here's the reality this has got a long way to go uh it's gonna go through appeals court
it's gonna go through a state appeals court and it's gonna end up at the supreme court
guarantee it i'll bet money this ends up at the supreme court now whether they hear it or not
is another i won't play place money on that but some this will get petitioned to the supreme court
i guarantee so i mean we're all drawing conclusions about what is going to happen what isn't going to
happen it doesn't it's not going to stick so why why are we wasting time this is this is one hurdle
in what's going to end up being a much longer legal process so get your popcorn anyway
that's my thought on that um anyhow uh we're going to open up the uh discord uh vog network.com
slash discord uh if you would like to uh give us a call in the green room uh while i peek at
discord and see if anything's there i know we also do emails around this time uh let's get to
okay wait a minute because i think we have one email tonight but i don't want this individual
is also sitting in the green room so you know what this is what we're gonna do let him read
his own email yep hi you're on orange lounge radio who's this hey it's the one and only ron
how's everybody doing tonight uh doing well how are you i can't complain um i for some reason my
camera is not working but you know it is what it is that's okay uh i'm trying to find the right
shot here that has uh there we go there's the one that has me and discord there um now here's
the thing this is why i brought you into the room uh rama um you actually emailed the show tonight
say what now you you emailed the show tonight right yeah the funny thing is i've been meaning
to work send that email earlier this week but i have been working on my google certification
for the last couple of weeks so my brain has kind of sort of been mush you know here's here's what
i did some folks are saying this is an orange entree go first i would like to give dark sakura
a break tonight and i would like to invite you to read your email on the show tonight rama
do you have the email in your sent folder i haven't but at least she won't get mad at me
for how bad my email is i talk and she's not the first person to tell me you need to type your
emails better okay no no no no no here's here's my problem here we go ellipsis you use ellipsis
when it doesn't need to be an ellipsis a period will suffice
i blame it on the new york state uh educational school system i i blame it on typing the way i
think i do it too and it's because i'm literally typing my thoughts and that's the point of an
ellipsis is when you are actually fading out on something and leaving something unsaid
maybe i am dot dot dot anyway like what i just told you a moment ago but and i left it that way
all right so so rama do you have the email if you don't have the email i'll i'll ask dark sakura to
read it but i thought it would be funny i have like i can just give a complete summary on it
all right works for me all right so from the last time we spoke i contacted amazon and told them
that i got sent the wrong controller so they apologized sent me another one got the package
opened it up it was not another xbox series controller put it back in the box with amazon
looked around couldn't find i saw the same ad pop back up they said screw it decided to go to
game stop just take a shot in the dark they had one and it was cheaper so i went and i bought that
got the controller opened it up and it was a modded first party xbox one controller i mean
they changed the buttons on it it didn't have the right battery case on the back and you can
look at the label because someone basically popped that open just to open up the controller
to change the buttons how funny the thing is i wasn't really mad i just found it amusing because
i got it from game stop but i'm not surprised this happened can you imagine buying a modded
system at game stop i'm sure it's happened where somebody bought like a system that was modded but
anyway anyway well there was a time when there were banned consoles they were selling and didn't
realize it by the way some folks in chat are uh having a little bit of a discussion about um is
there even actually an xbox series controller at this point and uh here's the thing yes there there
is xbox controller and i don't think they differentiate between the different ones but i
think we are saying it to differentiate because we know there are different versions of the xbox
controller for example the latest controller circa 2020 or whatever you want to call it
has the share button uh hey you're on cam now hey rama uh the one before at the xbox one era
controller does not so there are subtle differences anyway i just wanted to clarify that uh sometimes
it's not necessarily about the official name but how we differentiate between them which is does
play into uh rama's uh situation is that you specifically wanted an xbox one controller and
despite the fact we're all sitting here going why what it doesn't matter it's what you want
it's your money get into the reason behind that okay um so i went back on i sent the controller
back i contacted i went to amazon i looked again found the controller same ad link that i bought
it from before but i looked again it was a different reseller this time so i went through
them two days later i have a perfectly working xbox one controller now you've got it yep i
thought you'd have to hit up garage sales to be honest but you got it if i was to hit up garage
sales i would probably be dressed in a hazmat suit walking around to make sure because i don't
trust some of these people around here you'd find much more than a modded controller you'd open up
the back and be like who put rocks in here i can tell you i've had some people hit up garages and
find some amazing things you know so i'm just like all righty then all right yes so how how is
it though to hear now that you got your xbox one controller there's a whole new firmware for it
because i do when i read that story i instantly thought of you and i was like wow if this doesn't
scream justified to rama's situation so yeah so here's the thing i know there are new controllers
that are out but let's say for the sake of it i happen to sell my xbox back to game stop or
amazon or whatever i have to have the original controller that it came with or else amazon will
send it all back saying we can't resell it or game stop will take off 40 bucks because they
have to put it in one of their controllers to resell the unit one of their unknowingly modded
controllers yes i okay when you say it when you put it that way i kind of have an aha moment okay
but the thing is i'm when i get my series x i'm giving my xbox to a couple of friends of mine
they're not gaming savvy so i want to make sure they have the right controllers and the right
everything so they'll be good to go you know so another long story short you're doing this
because you're a good friend yeah basically okay and that is that is not the reason why i even
called it all right why did you call in what's up all right i'm not sure any of y'all covered this
or anything like that because i know from time to time y'all will take a good night off for various
reasons and for our show we've been taking a couple of weeks off here and there because we're
just exhausted like mental health issues and it's something that we talk about on our show if we
miss a week or if a certain host hasn't been around we're basically open about this because
we all have issues one way or another so i'm wondering have you loki or jamie have
you just been like you know what i i just don't have the mental energy to do a show i'm just going
to go to bed or do something else you know um i'll start i i think for me like having that
night off last week and doing the dragon con even though i know it was weird this year and
you know was a risk in some regard um that was so important for my mental health like just being
able to have that break and do that thing was so necessary for me that i feel like that was a way
to recharge my batteries um quite a bit um but um i'll let my co-host take the question if they
want to add anything further to it i mean i'm always like that so it's fine well loki i know
this show has oftentimes for you been a chance to kind of escape your normal monday through
friday type of life and like gives you something kind of different to do so yeah i think i get i
mean yeah but like i'm not really escaping anything because you know usually the kids
are behind me or like you know yeah not really leaving the house so it's not so much an escaping
or especially since i work right here in this very desk and computer and spot and all that stuff so
it's not really so much an escape anymore um plus it's it's important to note too that none of us
are required to be here none of us are paid to be here um so if anybody wanted to take a night off
for any reason um they're entitled to it uh that's that's what it is it's a little for my medical
conditions it's a little harder when it's me because yes all the production stuff is still
being run out of my house even in the covet area and so forth um but hypothetically it could be
done without me we just haven't really had to cross that bridge yet um so you know but dark
sacros up on and loki they both know how to stream so it wouldn't be that hard um so i am
i don't know uh i think in some ways this is kind of like a regular thing to kind of gravitate back
to too it's in a way it's a bit of an anchor um so it's kind of like you know that thing that
well there's still always olr on sunday night um yeah yeah i sometimes don't know what i would do
without having this on sunday yeah any thoughts on that rama totally get that it's for me as a
twitch viewer it's there are certain uh people i watch on certain days and it's like if they're
not doing a show on that day it's like well what do i do with my time and it's like and i get a
tap on the shoulder and it's like the spirit of my 500 video games like pick one or something like
that but as uh as a content creator i have like this rule of two if it's only two people to do
the show with i just cancel for the week because i'm like you know itchigo is not feeling up to it
she's things have been happening she can't get into doing the show or taco chan's the same i'm
like you know what we'll just do no show we'll just enjoy the tuesday off we'll come back next
week refreshed and we'll explain you know we needed some time off and this is what we do and
so on and so forth you know we try to be as transparent as possible yeah um i appreciate
a lot of the things you guys are saying in chat too like pod culture and chat says olr has been
my rock during some rough times uh fifth dream says i don't leave the house now so bobby blackwolf
and olr are kind of the marker that it's a new week um i deeply appreciate those comments and
i'm so thankful um that being said i also need to prepare folks for the reality the show isn't
going to last forever there is going to be a day what there is going to be a day when we say
um you know thanks for playing but roll credits you know type of thing for whatever the reason
is um so i just the only reason i put that out there is i say i say thank you for that but also
um it sometimes can be a little bit of pressure um and i just you know there's a reason why we
also say you know please support independent podcasting um i hope one day when this show
does inevitably end you all will still continue to support other uh indie broadcasters and any
podcasters and so forth and show the love that you've shown to us to somebody else who also
deserves it so they okay pod culture says we know we know i i know but i just i i still feel some
sort of weird obligation to kind of say like please please understand please understand
you know i i'm happy that we have been able to be there for you but we may not be able to be next
time so you know i i totally get that um in regards to you know how everybody sets their
schedule to olr on sundays something that i've been talking about in therapy about trying to
have like some type of schedule a routine and stuff like that and i use outlook to kind of
put my week together even though i know what i'm doing every day i actually have like olr
listed in outlook so when i open up my calendar it kind of helps me because you know still
job hunting and so forth you know at least when i get up it's like i have something to do
and i'm okay with it and it kind of puts my mind at ease and and as much as i love being a content
creator streaming and all that i've actually said to my group that day when i wake up and look
around my room and say this is not fun anymore i i'm done i don't want to do this anymore we will
just wrap it up and just go out on a high note and i think that's what we have to aspire to do too
you know when it inevitably is is done so yeah well hey i still have to wait to hear back from
guinness yeah i was gonna say anytime we have 20 years looming uh it would be a shame to miss that
but um if if i i think we'll get there but if we miss it one episode before 20 years there you go
so i'm i'm curious which gaming podcasts are chomping at the bit waiting for us to go off
the air so they could take the crown of longest running game because i actually don't know who
it is i don't know who comes after us i have there's like a list of five that i think are
up there i don't know who it is you know longest doesn't really seem to i mean it's i'll take
longest but like longest running show that no one knows who yeah exactly yeah i i've actually used
to say on my show from time to time the number one anime podcast in the tri-state area and it's
like well at least it's something we go to convention we can't even say that anymore because
another podcast said they're the number one in sacramento so we can't take that oh no no no no
we are we are the one the one i but i don't i don't want to pick a fight so i just kind of
smile and nod and say that's that's cute so pick a pat on the head yeah not pick a fight and you
play uh mario party online you know team team play you know but why do we have to fight for
what we know is true yeah i think i think you actually put it best before with this topic came
up years ago when that which i actually think they dropped that along i i don't know if our
shady shade came back around or what i actually think they dropped that a long time ago so to be
it's it's it's it's pretty bold to like call yourself the number one like like no is anyone
calling you that like was there a poll i mean like it it's just it's it's weird to call yourself
that but it's like it's almost like nominating like stuff for like hey this is the number one
podcast in my house i don't i i gotta watch i don't want to go down a shady slope i wanna i
want everybody to prosper but um i would say uh you know um i forgot what i was gonna say
damn it all right whatever i've been having train derailments all night
so you do listen to our show on a regular basis i remembered quick the train got back on rails
i liked the angle that i think it was dark soccer somebody took when this issue first came up years
ago um was that well why aim for just our city when we can be number one in the world and i
think that's where that i think i did say that that's where that whole number one podcast in
the galaxy and that whole joke came up yeah i think it came out of that so i'm so clever
was it that one town that was able to say that they're like the the central hub of
video games or something like that it's like it was it like in nebraska or something like that
where the video game hall of fame is or something like that where like it's like the self-proclaimed
you know capital of video games like what um sho 100 matt in chat says may not have a ton of
listeners but we're all better than most of the people out there you don't want as fans honestly
i'm starting to discover that as more and more true as the years go on you will notice knock
on wood i don't want to um curse things you'll notice no hose have showed up to this channel
now i think the reality is i'm going to just say it's because we're not using the lgbtq or black
tags which is why the hose have not shown up um or other marginalized communities um but you know
that's that's the type of attention we don't want so anyway we distanced ourselves a little
bit from your original question rama is there anything else you want to talk about
you need to jump on your iphone and download bang dream girls band party and play it and have fun
with it i want to see this switch game i looked at the screenshots i'm like this this looks like
ddr but like amplitude to me it's more like um i would say more like beatmania meets guitar here
the way it comes down because i have there's a free game uh the love live game for playstation
4 it plays kind of similar but it's kind of it's like buttons around the screen and you just got
to tap it out it's a it's a fun time waster so no i i will check it out i didn't know it was
something on the phone so that's a very easy way to check it out yeah it's that's where it started
and i mean there's tons of like rhythm games on the mobile device especially anime based ones
um i'll say this if you play the love live one don't get too deep into it because it's a mix of a
rhythm game dating sim and then you have all these like mini games and stuff i have known people who
get very competitive in it and it's like yeah take my phone away please all right uh so rama
uh rama i'm gonna let you go because i see somebody else in the green room i want to get on
the show but um thank you as always for your call everybody check out anime jam session on tuesday
nights and any other thoughts you have for us rama uh no i i think i am good okay take care
buddy thanks for the call appreciate it and congrats on your controller find be well all
right bye all right let's go right into another call before the video looks all messed up for
a little while so let's bring in our next person and hi there you're on orange launch radio who's
this uh this is yyr hey yyr welcome to the discord call-in thing we're trying how's it going sweet
it's going okay and i can unabashedly say that i have the number one game about shitting all over
people i have the number two game about that you have the number one number two game and then loki
has the number two number one number two game my head is already spinning but yes that part
what's on your mind uh well actually uh unfortunately i missed the earlier parts of the show
but uh i did wanted to i did want to bring to some people's attention
um the wonderful audience of this show uh that there are some updates to pixel poops and pixel
poops number two this week uh did were they uh with some of those already mentioned loki talked
about the updates to number two but he didn't talk about the updates to the main game if you wanted
to get into that oh okay well actually the updates to the main game are very small really um but
actually all the updates are now live on steam so if you did purchase number two on steam the next
time you open up the steam client you will notice if you have things set to automatically update
that you already have the new version of number two so get on that um but yes i decided i would
go ahead and add something to uh the base game that actually you requested rob oh shit and
literally this okay okay which one which one is it though because i think i've requested multiple
things well usually i'm pretty quick on the draw with like an episode number and an audio clip
but unfortunately i don't have those this time uh i will mention though that probably a couple of
months ago you mentioned and this probably followed a discussion about mortal combat
and the blood code and things like that and you probably said well you know i think it'd be pretty
funny if pixel poops had something like a strawberry ice cream mode where uh yes i think
i was talking about making your game family safe yes exactly so it's so is it pixel scoops now
okay this is funny because you probably haven't caught up to the episode yet but um just two weeks
ago or the the show before we took a break the little parody bump to the intro show was pumpkin
spice pixel poops oh my god i should have i thought when you said that you were putting that
in i thought that's what i got was my pumpkin spice pixel poops but this is totally updating
it again i'm i'm totally gonna like do that tomorrow i don't know but um yes uh
you have power rob um so yes there there is a now there is now a strawberry ice cream mode in
pixel poops along with a second bonus mode that my wife suggested and it's terrible and horrible and
should not have gone in there but it only took two minutes to do after doing the first
one and someone will find it funny so that went in there also and uh they're accessible via secret
codes oh remember those yes of course are they are they codes we're gonna be able to figure out
or do we get a hint or what oh no i'll just straight up give it to you um okay okay cool
insider info for olr listeners yeah i put on the patch notes that if uh if you want the codes now
you should listen to the orange flounce radio podcast but i will publish them publicly uh in
the future i guess all right cool so these are type-in codes so you'll need a keyboard to do it
and the reason i say that is because you know some people they'll game on their tv they'll
only have a controller in their hands so yes you will need a keyboard uh to enter these codes but
you enter them on the game over screen which you know it's the first screen that comes up
when you start the game when you start the app really uh and also it obviously comes up when
the game is over uh but you know don't have any menu open just be on the game over screen
it can be cycling colors or whatever to enable strawberry ice cream mode type in a b a c a b b
b isn't that like the blood code just like in a different order no it's the same oh it's the same
it is exactly the same as the sega genesis mortal combat blood code yes great great so the the
family-friendly strawberry ice cream mode is uh the blood code perfect yes exactly okay and and
for the other terrible thing that my wife suggested just press the period key six times
okay it is exactly what you think it is okay and uh both of them all they do is change the
color of the poop and uh they take effect until the game is quit and then restarted
and then it goes back to normal okay i love that do any any insight what the pumpkin spice code
might be um well right now i just have it set to use the a b and c and the period keys so
um and it's ignoring everything else and so i might just make a variation of the abac abb code
just have it be about my favorite band i don't know just that's invincibility in
akari warriors it is invincibility in akari warriors well that just makes it even funnier
and i hear from the other room abba
so even no it's abba it's not abba it's abba you get to be a dancing queen on your way to
shooting people angrily i love it just to make sure it's not too easily guessable i might just
have you have to type it in twice abba abba okay the more the better exactly so uh yeah please look
forward to that i will pumpkin spice that's hilarious i have to send you i'll have to send
you the image because i i changed the little taco cabana into a starbucks um it's really horrible
for well i'm sorry uh a um square dollars um coffee store uh and uh i all i did i did a
horrible paint job with the color over so i was like when i saw it on the uh video preview i was
like god damn that turned out ugly that makes it plenty yeah it does i realize i agree part of the
charm of the opening segments of the show is how did rob destroy photoshop this week which
plot twist i don't use photoshop i use snag it okay i expected you to say microsoft paint but
uh don't i i i'll try but snag it's kind of that also i use snag it a lot at work because it's
actually very powerful software for for those types of screenshots yeah and i'm on a mac i
don't have that problem all right uh yyr i totally appreciate the update and i'm flattered as always
that you know again you not only come to us with all the latest and greatest with your games but
that you you fucking humor us in the first place we don't deserve it we truly don't you know what
though i and and i continue to insist that if i ever do get discovered and you know things
actually start to you know i i actually make enough money to pay for my daughter's college
out of this uh i will still come to olr with all the news and updates and and uh yeah appreciate
that and appreciate you my friend gotta know your roots all right as long as you're still around
yeah yeah after that last last conversation i probably scared everybody huh uh i don't know
i think we should do something for 888 because it's triple infinity i know it's come it's it's
weird all these episode numbers i never thought we'd get to are coming up before we know it a
thousand i think i already figured out episode 1000 was going to be at disneyland no no no no
like the actual date was something like 2023 i think it was around 20 november i think if
we actually plotted the right days off it would actually be 20 november of uh 2023 but anyway
all right while we are my friends you take care we're gonna go wrap up the show and uh congrats
on uh pixel poops i hope everybody will buy it to play pumpkin spice uh strawberry ice cream and
other modes in the game ah well i'll just remind you that you don't even need to because the game
is free to play ah that's right that's what you should still you should still buy the extra stuff
anyway support the game do it all right awesome well enjoy and uh yeah have a great week take
care of my friend see you later bye-bye see you rob i did it i did a thing it wasn't free for me
because i paid for the commodore 64 version as well as pixel poops number two that i i
i would happily give yyr five dollars if he asked for it anytime maybe not every day because i do a
broke but you know i'll buy so i did a thing by the way what'd you do i i had my first pumpkin
product oh i did not i did not have a pumpkin spice i had a pumpkin product good enough i
had a pumpkin cream cheese muffin oh yummy and it was delightful one of the ones from the place with
the mermaid yes i only ate the top of it gave the rest of it to dan that's like i was looking
at the drinks and i was like a pink drink um that apple flavor is really good i know i'm so i want
to have it in a chai i don't like caramel that's fair yeah so i want to have it i hear it's uh
actually uh another probably mutual friend of ours out of other people's streams um uh
i never know exactly how to pronounce the name like gaga stirs not anyway not a name i recognize
yeah i never know how to pronounce it but i always remember seeing it um but that was a suggestion
that they made so i was like i have to try that i like chai and i like apple and the flavors would
be complementary yeah the apple stuff comes from like a brown sugar type of base see it's very easy
to dodge the caramel um and get just like that brown sugar apple stuff they use it's really good
so yeah now i did buy apple cider good call like a gallon of apple cider and i actually wondering
if i can make chai with it um since our green room is now oh by the way if you want to send
an email because i didn't shout out the email address we had rama read his own email tonight
but participate at orange laundry.com is the place to send an email for a future week uh participate
at orange laundry.com and we won't make you read your own email unless you want to join discord
and do it that way i mean why not all right we'll do it that way um let's hey rob what
one last thing since this is video for us right now okay do you see what's behind me
uh i'm trying to make it out wait my cursor's right on top of it uh because you're up on the
tv if you were if you i know it's been a while since you've been here but you're up on the tv
i put my huntress mask on a wig oh oh that's okay yeah yeah i see it now yeah once you said that i'm
oh i see it i am now prepared for at least a stream version of huntress cosplay
and i'm close to being stream uh version julie legion cosplay i have a pig mask
all right because i am a pig mane for life um i want to check in with last minute stories uh
loki do we have any last minute stories tonight or jamie if you have any no oh i didn't just
i didn't mean to have stella put away that's fine she's she wants lambie like at all hours
of the day so she loves you you're her daddy yeah but like she she knows when i'm on calls
like meanwhile i had mr smoosh dramatically laying on the floor in the kitchen like he was dying
because his feeder's time has been pushed back a half hour because one of his dads me accidentally
unplugged the uh long ass cord for the feeder when i was shoving my suitcase into the closet
no anyway um so uh nickelodeon ulcer brawl uh had a a box art kind of leak i guess on the e-shop
and so we kind of get a look of what you know ang korra uh ren and simpy look like now uh because
they've got you know the character art on there so uh that's the thing no new like actual like
leaks as far as like new characters or anything from that but um yeah it's neat to see like at
least what some of the characters look like so they have that um also i should mention that
steam's 18 years old now what today's i think the anniversary of that um so yeah that's a thing and
um hot wheels unleashed is gonna have lots of dlc including stuff uh ties in with uh
street fighter superman wonder woman masters of the universe and barbie and batman as well as
car companies that game looks kind of cool i'll have to check it out when that actually uh comes
out but yeah that's it uh dr c in chat uh says about the nickelodeon fighting game um that they
had videos of spongebob his moves are on brand and ridiculous i noticed the taunt wave gashing
the taunt was that meme you know with that that was really funny i thought that was perfect that
game looks fantastic so uh one other story i did see was that the animal crossing series one through
four amiibo cards are being reprinted and i do want to say that i was i i tend to hang out at
target on fridays when my son goes to his coding class and um they do have those cards in stock as
well as the hello kitty and san rio cards are in stock now okay you'll pick those up if you want
those cards i haven't seen them near me so if you would pick me up a san rio pack i would gladly
pay back yeah they have multiple san rio packs do you need all of them or just one um i guess i
would need all of them i mean what do you mean by multiple like like do like they're each one card
they're well it's packs of cards but they're different like steps i i have to look at it
again but like uh i did see those before and i was like why would people buy these because
it's just for the posters right so um but yeah i'll pick them up i can thank you
so that's it all right did you have anything else you want to talk about loki
or last minute stories nope all right then i guess we'll go to um wrapping up the show for
the night um let me uh go around and get everybody's final thoughts but before we do that
let me say thank you guys as always for listening to orange launch radio and supporting our show
we are the show where every gamer has a voice um so if you wouldn't mind helping us spread the
word uh tell a friend or two about the show um and that goes an awful long way an auto host here on
twitch for vog network also goes a long way in supporting the show and you certainly don't have
to but we do have a shop available over at vog network dot com slash shop if you want to buy some
merchandise some of the stuff i wore dragon con i wore the orange launch radio shirt to my friday
panels and the vog network shirt to my sunday panels so um you can check those out uh over
at vog network dot com slash shop um so uh anyway uh let's go around and get everybody's kind of like
final thoughts and wrap ups here so we'll start with uh dark sakura um i will be doing um hope
i'm gonna try to do it this month i'm gonna do a subathon um or a followathon or a bitathon
whatever it is because uh i want to do something to give back for any help that i have received
so keep your eyes open um and i also have been making merch specifically for dead by daylight
fans so let me know there will be other things in coming to the vog store for other games that
we have been discussing that aren't dead by daylight great i may even be doing a variation
of my last release for mine specifically for vog okay fun yeah nice all right um let's see uh so
i think i think you're probably gonna head off because you're gonna start your stream i am
i gotta switch uh from cammo to obs cam so we'll see you next week
meanwhile while we say goodbye to dark sakura loki what's your final thought for tonight
my final thought is i did put up a new episode of my minecraft series last week and then i have
a new one coming soon i've like i said i did a ton of stuff this week so i just i i filmed
everything and i didn't like it so i'm gonna film it again it's just the way it works um
perfectionist but i get it that's not it's not it's just like it just didn't it my last few
videos have been kind of rambly and long and i've been trying to tighten that up a bit it's more
just because i'm like i'm like i just want to just get it out you know and so i just got to do this
like mental dump type thing and i don't know if that necessarily generates more views or not but
um it is what it is so yeah the last episode was pretty cool because we decorated the shopping
district and so now it looks all pretty and everything nice and then um yes so that's a
pretty cool in the watch um but yeah there should be some new stuff coming i do want to start
streaming because right now my channel is not growing at all i mean i know you're supposed to
let the algorithm do its thing but like that takes like a couple years does take to do its thing so
it's like i hear you so we'll see maybe maybe streaming will be better i don't know or not
um well speaking of streaming i will use my final thought to give my own channel
at rob roberts here on twitch a personal plug i'm gonna be streaming no man's sky again tomorrow
night i'm trying to get a little further in expedition three who knows maybe finishing it
probably not tomorrow but at least one more night of twitch drops and then probably later in the
week if i have the time i'm gonna try to do a stream of the new warrior wear game i'll start
that from the beginning and play a little bit of that so that's my plan for the week um and then
a shout out for my husband at allen alchemy as well because excuse me he's been doing a lot of
streaming and just finished his resident evil 2 uh play with leon uh last night and he was using a
mod so that leon was running around in nothing but uh tidy grays uh not whities but tidy grays
basically it's uh of course a big pervy mod um but it was really funny uh so he played the whole uh
leon campaign with that and it made for some very funny and awkward cut scenes so now he's doing
claire um he doesn't have a similar mod for claire well it is he has a tifa mod for claire
so claire is dressed like tifa from final fantasy 7 it's still claire but wearing like that you know
white top and the yeah so it's kind of funny so check that out on his channel all right that's
going to do it for another episode of orange launch radio thank you guys so much for listening
to and supporting the show uh thank you for coming back this week after we were off last week
we will see you in seven days we will be back next week and we'll do this all over again with
next week's news have a wonderful week everybody goodbye you've been listening to orange lounge
radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr studios to join us for a live show
tune into fognetwork.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m eastern the views and opinions
expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio
or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
so