Orange Lounge Radio
Here's your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Tonight we have gaming news of a possibly 35 year old bug, re-examining a 15 year old bug, and PC builders doing their civic duty for today's reality and remake new content
Stay tuned for the recent articles about old content and news starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio, live tonight with episode number 815 for this April the 12th of 2020
Happy Easter out there to those of you that celebrate it
To other folks out there, including our very own DarkSakura or Jamie Summers, a very happy bunny day
No, it's still Passover so Chag Pesach Hasanah to everybody
Oh yes, there is that still going on as well, I thought that was midweek
Which ends before my birthday
Well happy that to you as well
I get cake for my birthday and it's gonna be a carrot cake with no raisins and I'll be on the show too
Oh good, well I mean
This is next Sunday
Good and not good, I mean I know you'd probably rather be out at the Cherry Blossom Festival or some of the things you usually do on your birthday weekend
But it's a weird year, we're doing different things
Yeah, I mean I haven't gotten to see any cherry blossoms at all this year which is usually like what I live for, you know
But hey, to my Jew crew listening, Chag Sameach everybody
And something I've been telling all my friends that have a birthday around this time is that you know
At least you completely have justification to get a make up birthday when this is all over
So we're gonna have a lot of birthdays come July, August, June depending on when we're allowed to gather again, who knows
Girl, you know what it's gonna be, right?
We're going to Disneyland
We're all going the fuck to Disneyland
I would be so down for that to be quite honest, so yeah
I don't care how many humans are there, I'll deal, I'll just you know
I don't know though, I mean this is probably gonna be a while, it's probably not gonna be until next year
I mean being logical about it, they're saying you know 18 months at minimum before you know a vaccine is out and kicked in and spread amongst enough people to be effective
Right, well we'll see
We'll play it safe and play it smart
You know we'll listen to the scientists, you know I think yeah
Running and going to Disneyland will probably not be the first thing because Disneyland's gonna be one of the last things to kind of come back
Just like you know I've got my eye on Dragon Con and I'm hopeful that Dragon Con will still happen
I'm hopeful that testing and all that stuff will be at a good enough place, they can do contact tracing and all that stuff
But if the scientists say don't do it, then it is what it is
You know we're gonna listen to science and make our educated decisions that way
I haven't heard anything on DerpyCon either so I mean that's not until the end of October
But certainly next year since I'm not doing, I'm not gonna do Dragon Con anymore because I'll be perfectly honest
They've kind of done one of the groups that I'm in a little bit dirty and on top of that I don't want to support
I mean it's enough that I watch the show and I'll leave it that way, I'm not gonna support someone who does fracking and has been such a shit to other people
So I am probably gonna do Dragon Con next year
Don't say it if you don't mean it, don't say it if you don't mean it
I need to talk to you about you know what the situation for us going and you know panels and crap but just we'll talk
Between Bobby and I we'll make it work, we'll make it work but yeah don't say it if you don't mean it because you're gonna get my hopes up
I'll put it this way, I do absolutely mean it and I will do whatever is in my power to make it happen
Besides that, I have been contemplating some epic cosplays for next year
There you go, there you go, alright
Including a character I'm probably way too short to portray but hey I really like Zaki
Well somebody else I'd like to get that kind of commitment from, say hello to Techmaster Loki
Yeah, Loki
And Loki might be on mute, hello?
I'm sorry my key binds aren't working
Oh that's okay
It wasn't working for a second because I was typing in chat
Alright well, oh okay, well you're multitasking, that's fine
And you're reminding us that we do have a live chat room because we do tape live
Every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at the Voice of Geeks Network
Twitch.tv slash VOG Network, V-O-G Network
You can also visit us on the web at VOGNetwork.com because we have a lot of friendly podcasts that we're in this network with
A lot of awesome shows that, you know, not only things we host here at VOG Network on Twitch, things like Girls Gone Wow and Anime Jam Session
But the interesting, not that this quarantine situation is a good thing at all
But if you want to look for the diamonds in the rough, shall we say
Some of our podcasts that have gone on hiatus, you know, just because life gets in the way sometimes
Have found the time to record again
So The Geek Card just put out a new episode this last week
And I'm told another one is coming
I don't know if I'm allowed to say what yet, but they're in chat probably so maybe they'll say something
But yeah, so that's, you know, not the way I want shows to come back
But you know, hey, if it's like the one piece of good news in this situation then I will stink and take it
Anyway, so Loki, one of these years we gotta get you to Dragon Con as well
I mean, it probably won't be until the kids are 18, but we'll hope for it
Yeah, well I would have said, yeah, definitely
How has your week been personally? I know usually you do family stuff today
So I know things have kind of changed this year, but were you able to take the kids out to a park to do
Have a good dinner or anything like that?
No, we just, well we had kids this morning
They looked for them in our house, so we did that
And then we went out to the park just to ride, they rode their bikes and stuff
But like, I mean I cook all week, so like, you know, I made my
My honey butter chicken that stuff is like cracked, so
That's right, you talked about that last week, that's awesome
I made that yesterday, yes, I bought four pounds worth of wings and I made all of them in the house
So good
I love it
Alright, yeah, it's interesting how this
You're going to leave some on my doorstep, right?
There's not going to be any left
It's interesting how this situation has led people to doing more cooking
Alan cooked this morning, he made some lemon poppy seed muffins, they were really good
So he doesn't always do stuff like that, so it's cool
I'm making bread with passovers over, but I decided I think tomorrow night, I'm going to try my hand at matzah
Mmm, yum yum, matzah is penance
So yeah, lots of food to eat while we're playing lots of games
And I know there's been lots of game playing amongst the crew this week
We'll get into that in a bit, but we like to start usually with a kickoff topic
So this week's kickoff topic has to do with Nintendo Switch
Which has, you know, is already probably the most popular console out there
I think that would be a fair statement to make right now
Especially because we know PlayStation 4 and Xbox One are kind of on the, you know, they're on their way out the door
As we know, PlayStation 5 and Xbox, I keep wanting to call it the XX, but Xbox Series X are on their way in the door
Just go with your instincts
That's right, go with what you know
So the Switch is probably really the king of the hill right now
Especially when you consider things like Animal Crossing is just like, it's become like this pop culture icon amongst this situation
It has proven to be like the ultimate form of escapism
So, so many people want to get their hands on a Switch
And it's actually come to the point where the Switch supply is really low
And like let's be real, Nintendo isn't the greatest when it comes to hardware demand and all that stuff anyway
And this situation, you know, I'm not trying to make light of the situation
But this situation just isn't helping what's already usually a rough ride for Nintendo
What I mean by that, Nintendo announced this week that they suspended shipments of, excuse me
Can't do anything about that, sneeze is live on air
Nintendo suspended shipments of the Nintendo Switch system in Japan
This is only a temporary thing because if you're not aware, the COVID-19 situation is increasing in Japan
We're probably a couple weeks behind where we've been at in regards to, you know, how it's spreading through the population and so forth
So this is just a temporary move, Nintendo says
But it does mean that devices are not shipping outside of reservations
They don't know when shipments will resume
They are saying that this move does not affect consumers in Europe and North America
But I feel like that just can't be true
And I don't know if that maybe goes all the way back to when China has been going through some of these things
And the factory and the productions there were kind of seeing the trickle down effects
But I know people that are trying to get their hands on a Nintendo Switch
And it really isn't the easiest thing to do right now
To give you an idea of the situation in Japan
The Switch stock is so low that retailers are starting to do lotteries
So a Japanese store named Yamada Denke put up a lottery to potentially buy 130 Switch consoles
And 900 copies of Ring Fit Adventure
Which is another really hard thing to find right now
Probably because it involves hardware
It has that little ring that goes with it, that resistance band
And so it probably limits the number of those that Nintendo can put out
200,000 people entered the lottery
199,000 of them flippers
No, I'm just kidding
But I'm also probably not sadly
But 200,000 people entered the lottery
That is for one retailer
So yeah, Nintendo is trying to ship more units
But that gives you an idea how crazy the supply and the demand is right there right now in Japan
So what is it about the Nintendo Switch that is driving people crazy for it
I can tell you
Let me come to you, Dark Sakura, for your opinion
But I just want to say, especially now in this quarantine COVID situation
These sorts of things we expect to hear around the holidays, around the launch
But we're not talking the launch period
This is like two years into the system's life now
Dark Sakura, what's your thoughts?
Animal Crossing
What is it about Animal Crossing?
Well, and I'm looking at it sort of as my two years of psychology before I changed my major type stuff
The issue is that right now a lot of stuff is out of control, right?
We don't have a lot of active control over what we can do in our lives
We can't go out, we can't do things
We can't see the people that we want to see
But Animal Crossing has been this way to remotely visit people
I mean, for me, I've been hanging out with my friend Gwen practically every day
We were college roommates and haven't seen each other since a couple of years since I moved out here
But we chat every day
She used to be in our WoW guild for a while
You remember? She's actually on Final Fantasy XIV right now
Yeah, I know she is, yeah
So anyway, I've been playing with Tiara
They've been really good company
I can do stuff in my town
It's something that I have a more active control over
Something that I am doing, something that's giving me that immediate reward
And on top of that, now some people have been absolutely cutthroat with the game
But it's been a lot of people cooperating with each other
It's taking that stuff that we're trying to encourage people to do in real life
But we have this controllable environment that kind of does let us be in the presence of other people to interact
Yeah, that's a very interesting take
And I like that, the fact that even though in this situation you can't control things
In Animal Crossing, relatively, you have control over things
I mean, maybe not everything
The other day, Rocket threatened to move out of my town
And I basically said she's not allowed to do that
And if she leaves, I'm going to burn down the town
But she didn't, so I'm very happy about that
Because Rocket and Ketchup are my two favorite villagers, just for the record
I especially love Ketchup, I will die for Ketchup
Octavian is pissing me off because I invited him for a second time
Because he's my favorite grumpy old man octopus
So now I have to invite him a third time to try to convince him
I gave up on Dina
Dina, I think, has moved on to other levels of her lesbianism
I'll tell you what, Brad, Pod Culture and Chats says, how do we send Ed to Jamie?
You shut your whore mouth, okay?
As the island turns, like bells through the hourglass, these are the days of our horizons
But you know what I did find amongst my amiibo cards?
I found Julian
Yeah, no, you had a crap ton of those amiibo cards
And I have the actual figurines
Do you know what I actually have that now apparently is really valuable?
I have a sealed copy of Wii U Animal Crossing with the Isabelle amiibo and the other guy in it, still, sealed
Oh, what you mean the amiibo festival?
The little dog, yeah, amiibo festival, that's it
Those are going for like hundreds of dollars on eBay
I have the game, although I've played it because I actually think it's legit fun
Yeah, no, I never opened it and I was thinking about opening it the other day
Because this is the hilarious part, Alan got it for like 10 bucks on a Target clearance
Because that was one of the last games in the heyday of the Wii U
So that was kind of on its way out the door
And now everybody wants their hands on those amiibo
And Wii U games in general are becoming collector's items
I don't know, I don't know if I want to keep it, sell it, what do I want to do? It's tough
Well, I'll tell you what, nothing has financial value until you try to sell it
I guess that's true
Anyway, I want to get some of the comments from our chat room over at Twitch
And then good fucking luck
Over at twitch.tv slash vog network because a lot of folks have some comments on this
So Mel Chan in our chat says
I have mine but I've been trying to find one for my client to keep her busy
I'm assuming this is a switch
Between tons of families suddenly stuck at home and the biggest game for it in a long time happening simultaneously
It just added to it
Let's see, Fifth Dream Today says
Someone I know from the Goth community I'm in and barely knew since Animal Crossing New Horizons came out
We've been talking and trading and having conversations about other things
Well, you know, sometimes video games really do bring us together
And for me it's always been about MMOs
Like some of my closest friendships were formed because of MMOs
And being able to play MMOs online with people
I mean, hell, even like Loki and I before we lived together we were playing Final Fantasy XI a lot online
So, you know, a lot of times video games can definitely bring us together
And although I wouldn't call Animal Crossing New Horizons an MMO per se
There definitely is an important multiplayer component about it, for sure
YYR says it was definitely the Animal Crossing New Horizons release above all
Also, despite Nintendo's selection of multiplayer games, you need multiple systems to really take advantage
So a lot of thoughts there on the Nintendo Switch shortage
And then when it comes to Ring Fit Adventure, SHG100Matt says
I've been playing a ton of Ring Fit Adventure
It's the best thing to keep me active without going outside
Which I do at midnight when no one is around
But Ring Fit Adventure offers a great workout
And yeah, I think that game in particular
You know, that game was getting kind of hard to find anyway
And you hit the nail on the head
Like some people, like I do go outdoors once in a while
And I go to parks and I still play my GPS games like Orna and Ingress and stuff
But I find that I'm going to the same parks and the same places
And it's getting a little dry for me
So Ring Fit Adventure is something a little bit kind of like different I think
You know, you're working your way, it's digitally different but it's still something different
And then of course they added that music game mode
Right after the last direct
That kind of added something to it as well
So I think Ring Fit Adventure feels a lot different than taking a walk around that same neighborhood park
You've taken a trip around many, many times before
So yeah, SHG100Matt says
Folks can't go to the gym, Ring Fit offers a great alternative
Loki, let me go to you
What do you think is the Switch fever?
What is it that's making everybody crave one of these right now?
Because they can't have it so then they want it
I don't know, I think it's just
It's popular, I don't see Animal Crossing as a system seller but
I don't know
I really would think it would be a different game or something like that
But I don't know
I don't know what the
I think people finding maybe more time to play games now
And so they decided that they want to get Switch
Maybe we're hearing more about the Switch because
Xbox and Playstation 4 are so easy to get
And I would normally agree with you that
Animal Crossing I would not have thought would have been a game that would be a system seller
In any other, that doesn't mean it's a bad game
I just wouldn't have seen it as something that moved
I mean there's always going to be the hardcore fans
But I would have seen it as something that moved a lot of systems in any other circumstance
But in this particular world circumstance now I'm like
Oh it kind of is though
Yeah and I don't even know necessarily it's just because Animal Crossing came
I mean I think it's just the timing in general
And I think it's because Nintendo has historically had a poor
They've done a poor job at fulfilling orders for their systems
And yeah I know they're blaming it on the COVID stuff now
But let's be honest I mean they're going to blame it on everything
I just don't
It'd be interesting to see like the actual numbers of how many systems have been sold
I mean I know Nintendo does well and I'm not just going to say that
I don't think it's dramatically different
I just think that because now everybody's
The demand has gone up that now they're having supply issues again
Whereas I'm not sure
I assume that the demand's gone up across the board for all systems
But I think that they're able to handle their supply a little bit better maybe
I don't know
But I'd be curious to see how the other systems fare as well
Yeah I think Animal Crossing 2 is very different from a Zelda
Very different from a Mario Party or Mario Kart
That's already on the Switch
Because I think Animal Crossing is a game where you know
As Dark Sakura was kind of explaining with her old roommate
You can kind of get together and do things in a space
Whereas you know that's not really what you're doing in Mario Kart
I mean yes you can play that game online with friends or Splatoon even
I mean that doesn't make those games bad at all
They're great for what they are
But they're not like existing in the same space
And building this space together that's almost like
Fulfilling this need that many of us are not getting in the real world right now
It's something very specific about that game
In many ways Nintendo could not have timed it any better
And I know that sounds like a really crass thing to say
And nobody would have ever wished this situation on anything
But it's just how the pieces fell for this particular game and this circumstance
And it's really worked out in this game's favor
It is what it is
I sound like a horrible person when I'm saying it that way
But that's just the reality
You don't sound horrible at all though
That sounds absolutely accurate
I mean not that they purposefully timed it like this
But the timing was perfect
No one knew that there was going to be a pandemic
But the fact that this came out just at the right time
Has been a godsend for a lot of people's sanity
Yeah in many ways
And it's interesting as Bobby points out
They did delay it
It was a November game last year
And in many ways
I can't believe here we are now saying this
But thank god they delayed it
Right?
And I'm hoping
I know that there's another company that's hoping
To get the same kind of fire lit under their game
Because it's come out a while ago
And hasn't done very well
But now they're releasing it on Steam
And that's Fallout 76
It's finally coming to Steam
But
It's Fallout 76
Yeah
Number one it's Fallout 76
And I feel like most people have already made their judgement on that
I mean good luck to them
Well they have the Wastelanders expansion
And not to say they can never be good at some point
It's just
I'm gonna send my thoughts and prayers to Fallout 76
But the reality is
What it doesn't have that Animal Crossing has
I think is a sense of accessibility
And by that I mean like
Kids play Animal Crossing
It's very easy for adults
We have the famous grandma that plays Animal Crossing
And it's not that these folks can't play Fallout 76
Although I don't know if you know with the violence in that game
It may be appropriate for audiences
But it's just something about the accessibility
Of an Animal Crossing game versus a Fallout 76
Where it's like
Fallout 76 you'll never be glamour
Like you'll never be glamour Fallout
You never will
Animal Crossing has
That it factor
That X factor
That accessibility
That universal appeal thing
That like
I'm sorry Bethesda
But Fallout 76 doesn't have it
Now for a certain audience
And a certain group
And certain people
That will you know turn their nose up at Animal Crossing
And yes Fallout 76 will play to that audience
But the reality is it's not as big of an audience
So there's
Yeah I figured as much yeah
Yeah
Well and I've got Dan back into playing Animal Crossing
Which he had no interest in since
You know the GameCube one
Where you had all your NES games in there
And he and I have been
I've been though
Whoring him out to you know pay off all of my
You know bridges and inclines and stuff
By making his own tarantula island
But for him I think he's
Found some things in it very therapeutic
So it's brought people back into that
That fandom too
And the fan art community has been a delight
I am all about the stock market
I am all about
Stonks
The stonks
Turnips
I heard you like turnips
Because I am that person that like
I have a little group chat with like
Shane and some of the other people
I play Fallout SE 14
And like just before noon in the AM
I have this picture of Tom Nook holding a gun
It's like it's the gun meme where somebody's holding a gun to the camera
And it's Tom Nook holding a gun
It says give me your turnip prices
Because I'm trying to find where I can sell those turnips
And right now I have a turnip room in my house
And it's only barely enough to hold all the turnips right now
So everybody kind of has their different way of playing
I don't like to do the tarantula game
But everybody has their different way of doing it
For me it's all about turnips
About turnips for one reason
To get ants
Because that's how you get ants is you have to leave your turnips out
And the ants are cute
But then Dan took my ants and I went back and the ants were gone
And I was so mad
And Sia Tabiri says
I finally got into turnips this morning
Yeah and that's
I love like talking to people going to the different groups
What's your turnips, what's your turnips, what's your
Hey I heard you like turnips
But what I don't like
And I'm gonna be downright honest
What I don't care for is like
I read this article about how somebody set up
A security team on their island
That would block the door to nooks
Until you like left a tip
That you'd I guess promise to give
All this like crazy stuff
And I'm like that ain't it
For me I mean if that's how you want to play
Hey it's your game do what you like
But for me like I don't believe in tipping
In Animal Crossing
In the real world completely different
But in Animal Crossing no no no
It's about the exchange of
You know you scratch my back I'll scratch yours
And I had
And this person has friends
What society should be like in Animal Crossing
You know what Bernie Sanders
Bernie Sanders ran on a turnip platform
And look what happened
Alright anyway
But I will say this
You know I've started a Facebook Animal Crossing group
That grew much bigger than I thought it was gonna be
But everybody there
I have to give them credit
Everyone there has been a delight
Everyone has put out public codes for everyone
And these are the kind of people that I like to play with
And I encourage everyone just to be
You know don't make it a burden for other people
Help each other out you know
And then play that into real life please
We need it
Yeah for sure
Yeah and like when my turnips were going for 90
Like they were selling last week at 90
I was just like yeah open up come visit
Cause then I was like yay people will visit
And if they write on my board
Or they talk to my villagers
And that's reward enough for me
So but I understand some people have a more capitalistic approach
To things
Gosh maybe I was a democratic socialist this whole time
And didn't realize I don't know
I'll throw something out there too Rob
Because you know and not
People I guess just don't actually realize this
But if you've held something in your inventory
You can order it later as long as it was a DIY
So that's what Gwen and I have been doing every day
Is that we'll find something we're not sure if the other person has
And we order each other our music
Well I did that for you
You needed the meme shirt
Yeah we did
Yeah so I sent you the meme shirt
And then I immediately took it over to Gwen
So she could put it in her inventory for five seconds
And I could get it back
I'm all about that that's cool
And so that way we've been you know
If someone wants something
Yeah maybe you can't pay the 64,000 bells for an arcade machine
But you can hold it for five seconds
And save up for one for yourself
But I will say this and I think we're starting to bleed into our
Video game weeks a little bit
So I'll advance the ticket over here
But I will say this much
As far as like all that stuff goes
Is that I don't really open my island to everybody
Because and I think one of the big drawbacks about Animal Crossing is
Surprise surprise Nintendo's mediocre online system
Because it takes like freaking two minutes
For somebody to get to your island
And another two minutes for them to leave
And that can be like let's imagine
Just imagine my turnips are selling for 530
One day just imagine
And I go to Twitter and I write
Hey my island's open
My turnips are 530
People are never gonna get in
Because every 30 seconds
Bing bing bing
Please close the window
A person's trying to connect
And it would just be crazy
That's why I only open my island with dodo codes
So that I know who's coming
I have it controlled to a certain number
And then like I don't have to worry about that
Connecting and disconnecting message every 30 seconds
It is the most annoying thing they need to fix
Big time
Bobby Blackwolf in chat talking about his experience with Animal Crossing
Saying the fun part with me
Is that my wife is playing more than I do
And we have one physical cart
So we can't play at the same time
She's unemployed so she's playing a lot
And I get like an hour or two a night before my shop's closed
Well we all play at our different pace
Like Dark Soccer came to visit me this week
At Animal Crossing
And she's like, where's your Able Sisters?
And I'm like, don't have it
I've been doing things at my pace
I'm like, I think I still need to build somebody a home
I don't know
And she was like, oh
My kids use it for Minecraft
And so I never get it
Yeah but it's just, I've been playing 14 and near
And 7 Remake and other stuff I'll talk about shortly
So it's like, I've just been playing Animal Crossing at my own pace
And like I said, I'm all about the turnips
I want to have my basement
Because if Dark Soccer isn't going to have a shrine to fire
Then I will, in my basement
No, I have my bonfire
Once I finish getting my townhouse planned up
I'm going to be, well I've got my Stonehenge right?
And I'm going to put fire all around my Stonehenge
With my cherry trees in the background
And we also don't have any bridges or anything leading to it
So my animals can't go, you know, mess it up
So, yeah
And I have Baphomet Point, don't forget about that
Where my lighthouse is
That's right
You know, and to be fair
I also kind of want like a
I don't know if I want to say a sex dungeon in the basement
But like a pervert dungeon
I think is what I want in the basement of my house
So, you know, I'll be thinking about that
Because I'm that sicko that likes to do things you really shouldn't do in cutesy games
What can I say?
Should I order you the bondage outfit then that they have in the game?
Oh, do they have one? Yes
Because today I got that
I got that human skeleton that like you could
It's like the anatomy thing
Yeah
Yeah, I thought that would be funny
Do you need like the actual skeleton?
You know, if you poke at it, it raises its arms like it's trying to scare you
Oh yeah, I knew one of those, send me one of those
Okay, I can order tomorrow, so yeah
We'll talk about that later, but I'll send you the bondage outfit too
Let's talk about the rest of our gaming weeks
I mean, clearly Animal Crossing has played a big part in our weeks
Just like everybody else's
DarkSakura, would you care to continue?
How was your gaming week? Animal Crossing or otherwise?
Animal Crossing
All the Animal Crossing
And actually, my lungs have been doing a lot better
Yay
So I've actually considered getting Yoga Master for the Switch
Just to give myself a little bit more motivation to get up and do my morning yoga
So, you know, I'm not all stiff and terrible
And hopefully do that to, you know, get my breathing back where it was
You know, like I said, it's better
But I moved like three bags of dirt that I got at Target
Because, you know, I'm planting my apocalypse garden
And, oh, I was a mess right after that
So yeah, I'm hoping that having like a yoga game on my Switch
Will, you know, help me get back into doing my breathing exercises and all that
Kind of sounds like it's trying to hit on that Wii Fit market
That doesn't totally exist on the Switch right now
Although, I mean, there's Ring Fit certainly
But Ring Fit doesn't really have a yoga in it
So, which was probably the most popular and well-known element of Wii Fit
If we got a Wii Fit, though, that would be absolutely amazing
Because I think I would play the hell out of it
You know, again, just because of not being able to get up
You know, I've got free weights in the house that I could be using
But while I'm healing up and my lungs aren't as strong
Doing yoga and certainly, you know, doing it in a game
Would probably be easier and more enjoyable
Alright, anything else with your gaming week?
I, no
Alright, then we'll go to Loki
How was your gaming week?
So, this week I didn't play a ton of things
I did end up playing some Final Fantasy VII Remake
So, I'm not very far in it
I'm about just an hour and a half or so into it
So, I think just in the middle of Chapter 2
And I'm liking it so far
I think it's pretty amazing
Just an incredible looking game
And I remember Nelly was going
Like, is this a game?
She's like, it looks so real
But yeah, it was fun
I tried to get my kids to watch because I thought it'd be interesting for them to watch
But they only had the attention span for like five minutes
But, what else?
I also played a little bit more Beat Saber
I did a little bit of Step Mania
I've been going through my song list
And trying to pare down some of the songs I have on there
And try to remove duplicates that I have in folders
Because I just dumped a whole bunch of collections together
So, I've been going through that
And also, I repaired my Nintendo Switch this week
So, I had Drift on the two Joy-Cons
So, I actually got the parts from iFixit
And took them apart
The Joy-Cons replaced the analog sticks in them
And then I was having an issue where I kept saying my SD card was being removed from the system
Even though it wasn't
So, I took the system apart
And the way they engineered that thing is so stupid
It's literally being held in by a little bit of foam
And the tension from the actual back of the device is pushing this connection down
And so, it can come loose if your child then drops it on the ground
So, literally all I had to do was push it back in the connector
And then everything was fine
But the fact that it's not like held in
It's not like a ribbon cable or something that's attached in there
It's just like this little thing that's held on by pressure
It's absolutely stupid
At least I know if it ever breaks it's easier to replace
So, I did all that this week
And then I've been just kind of getting my laptop still set up for gaming and stuff
I got an external drive reader for my 5TB drive from my old laptop
I tried fixing my old one but I think it's shot
And then I got a brand new 2TB one
So, I got like 8TB of storage on my PC now
It's great
I'm putting tons of games on there
So, that's been my week
Okay, awesome
Well, enjoy filling up the 8TB drive with games you'll never play
Absolutely
Okay
My gaming week
Let's talk about Final Fantasy VII Remake
Because I'm also playing it
And I'm on chapter 6
We have it on order by the way
Well, here's the thing
So, I was supposed to get it on Tuesday
Because Amazon's running behind
I get a lot of my stuff from Amazon
And they're running a little behind
And I really was okay with it
But then when everybody was getting the hype going on Twitter
And all that stuff
And I was thinking about
I don't really have a lot to do this weekend
I was like, you know what?
Fuck it
I'm just gonna buy it digital
Even though, yeah
So, I did it
I hit the button and I bought digital
And I'm actually kind of glad I did
Because it's been able to fill quite a bit of time this weekend
Maybe about like 7 hours in
I don't know
I'd probably play more if I had a better attention span
But I'm very much like
I sit in front of the TV for an hour
Then I need to go sit in front of the computer for an hour
And then maybe I need to go like
Go in the backyard for just a little bit
To get some fresh air or something
Like, I can't really just keep staying in one place
For hours and hours and hours
Like I used to be able to
When the original Final Fantasy VII came out
But anyway, I have played through a good chunk of the game at this point
I mean, I don't know how many chapters there are
But I'm up to chapter 6
Obviously, I'm not gonna spoil anything
Let's talk about that to begin with
Because you might think
Well, Rob, how can you spoil things
Because this is just a remake of Final Fantasy VII
So it's the same plot, right?
Wrong
There are a lot of things
That people are getting very wrong about this game
And I'm going right for it
One of them
That you guys are getting really wrong
And when I say like you guys
I mean like Twitter
And some of the, you know, hot takes, trademarks
So forth about the game
Is the hot take that I see
I do not want to buy that game
Because it's only 10% of the story
You are completely going about that assessment the wrong way
Period
It is not a one for one remake
You're thinking probably of a remaster
You're thinking of that game that you wanted
When you saw that PlayStation 3 demo
That rendered the opening sequence of the game in high definition
All those years ago
That first led people to talking about
They wanted a Final Fantasy VII in HD
Let me be clear
This is not that game
This is a different game
And I think maybe part of the problem
Is that they called it Final Fantasy VII Remake
Because this is Final Fantasy Reimagined
This is Final Fantasy VII Reinvention
This is
They took the plot and they took the characters
And they made a brand new game out
They made Final Fantasy XVI out of it
Is what they did
This is what should have been
Well in a way
But you couldn't do this game on the PlayStation
Full stop
As long as that bitch dies
As long as there are guys I'm happy
Well and who knows
And I don't think that part would be covered in this game
But I really feel like anything goes with the plot
I have her
Obviously I want this to be a spoiler free place
I have heard the ending is shocking
Which it shouldn't be shocking
If you've played through the original
So apparently they've done something
But it wouldn't surprise me
Because they have done all this different stuff along the way
One of the things is that they have completely fleshed out these characters
Who were very much
I don't want to say throwaway sidekicks
But they were just
They were not really a part of the story before
I'm speaking mainly of Jesse, Biggs, and Wedge
Who are completely fleshed out full characters
They're not playable
But I'll be damned if you're going to tell me they're not a part of the story
Because they very much are in this game
And you know
Again this is not a one for one of the original Final Fantasy VII
What this is
Think of it more like this
And I can't think of a better comparison
Maybe you guys can
Final Fantasy VII is like Buffy the Vampire Slayer the movie
A nice two hour movie
Stands on its own
There's things people appreciate about it
Everybody loves that sequence with Pee Wee Herman as the vampire
There's Buffy the Vampire Slayer the movie
Then years later
There's Buffy the Vampire Slayer the TV show
It goes on for seven seasons
You know what it's the same character
And some of the themes they explore are the exact same thing
But it's very very different
That is Final Fantasy VII Remake
I don't know what do you guys think
Is that a fair comparison?
Anyone?
I haven't watched the Buffy the Vampire Slayer movie
Now you spoil it for me
You need to fix that
I can see that
I can see that except
No cause
I don't know
Maybe not directly that
Because yeah the plot of the movie doesn't really go over to the TV show
But I couldn't really think of a movie
The only other thing I can think of is that The Shining was a movie
And then they had the mini series
With Rebecca De Mornay and some other guy
What about more like V?
Oh that's a good one
We had V the mini series
And then it tried to flesh it out
I'm gonna tell you the TV series kind of jumped the shark a bit later
But I can kind of see what the TV series was trying to do
Oh MASH
Good one Pod Culture
I don't know if as many people know about
I hate to say it but know about MASH
Let's be real
The 20 year olds may not
May not have familiarity with MASH
Like those of us in our 40's
When the reruns were on all day long
But MASH is a good
If you know MASH that's an excellent example actually
So anyway
I think you all kind of get what I'm saying
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
Game Spots Review had the best line
For returning fans this isn't the Final Fantasy 7 your mind remembers
It's the one your heart always knew it to be
Tigerclaw says
Is the story in the Final Fantasy 7 remake
Verbatim from the original
All the same story beats and stuff that made the original impactful
No
And I'll leave it at that
So
Tigerclaw says
Remakes often do things different from the original
Stuff like origins of characters being different
The fate of certain characters being different
It's how they differentiate from the original
And I will say
And again I don't want to spoil
Because I want to be very
You know very aware that maybe not everybody
Some of you probably ordered from Amazon
Haven't got the game yet
But if you've played the demo
Which is available out there for everybody
You'll notice that the end of the demo
Is something very very explicit
That was only
Implied in the original game
And wasn't necessarily
Explicitly stated
The way it was very clearly done
At the end of the demo
For those that have played it you'll know exactly what I'm talking about
For those that haven't, well maybe that will make you interested
I don't know
But I kind of think playing that demo will give you a good sense
Of the types of changes they can make to the game
For one it will give you a feeling of the combat
Which the combat is
Very different and not everybody's going to love it
Again
I know a lot of people are like
Oh there's a classic mode
It's really nothing like the original battle system
I'm sorry to say
I don't know I kind of think it's fun
I like the new battle system
I'm playing it on easy, granted
Because I really wanted to focus on the story
And I kind of felt okay I'll do one play through on easy
And in the back of my mind I'm going
This game's going to come out on Playstation 5
Oh that was the other reason I went digital
At the end of the day
I went digital because my thought was
If Playstation 5 will play Playstation 4 games
Then hypothetically
Fingers crossed, toes crossed
We don't know this for sure
But I'm hoping Sony does the right thing
And that means your digital library on Playstation 4
Will instantly unlock on Playstation 5
Probably
That's my hope anyway
I hope Sony gets that right
So my thought is
I'm going to play through it on easy now
And if I have to replay it on Playstation 5
I'll play it on either normal or hard then
So that's kind of my other thought
Process that went to that
But I think the battle mode is
Kind of fun
It's like an improved version of 15
To me
And I know that might make a lot of people wince
Because I know 15's battle system wasn't popular
But that's why I say improved version of 15
To me
I feel like there's more point to some of the buttons that you're mashing
And it doesn't have all that crazy teleporting stuff
That is weird
That is not there
But I really like how when you do pause the battle to use fire
To use magic
It's really cool how everything moves in bullet time slow motion
And that just adds to the flair
This game has
This game has so much flair
And I talked about this with the demo
And there was a part of me that was like
I don't know how they can keep that going
Throughout the game
And there are some slower parts
Like there are some side quests that you do
That maybe don't have quite the flair
That the opening of the game does
It definitely fills in some of the back story
It makes, again, characters that were
Throwaway side characters in the original game
Have full on
Plot devices
In this game
And so forth, so there's that
But I would say maybe the game
Didn't have quite that intense flair
Moving through those side quests
And so forth, but I'm pretty impressed
When you're going through the main story
There's an energy that this game
Just doesn't stop
And I'll tell you
This shouldn't be a spoiler because this is a very well known
Sequence in the original game
The motorcycle sequence
It is reimagined and it's in this game
And it's another one of those
They do something kind of different to it
Where it's like, holy shit
This doesn't fucking stop
It's awesome
And again, if you've played it, you know what I'm talking about
If you haven't
Maybe in a few more months I'll feel a little
More at ease talking about some of these spoilers
Openly, but yeah
It's got a certain energy level that doesn't stop
And the graphics and the
Sound and music
They just, like Loki said
His wife thought it was a movie
Right? I mean, it just
With the camera tricks that it plays
It just feels like you're really playing a movie
It's fantastic
So
Fifth Dream Today in chat says
Biggs is Charlie Sheen
Circa 1986
Okay, but Charlie Sheen never
Had a voice as silky smooth
As Gideon Emery, who really adds
Everything to that character
It's so weird hearing him
Without a British
Accent
And I read a review on the game that said they
Couldn't unhear Balthier
And I'm like, I don't
If I really try to make myself hear that, I will
But, or Orang in Final Fantasy 14
Uh-uh, uh-uh
You know what's always for me?
It's Dragon Age 2
Of course
I always hear Fenris
And if you really want to hear that, you will
But I'm able to kind of let Biggs be
His own character, so it's pretty cool
He's cute
Yeah, and you know
Barret Jesse
Barret in the demo
Definitely has that
Same kind of hard edge
Hard ass Barret, but I think once you get past
The demo sequence
You start to see Barret's softer side
About why, I mean, especially when his daughter
Is introduced for the first time, which again, that was in the original game
And there, obviously
That element that Barret has
A daughter, is still in this remake
And you know, you start to see kind of like
More of the why is he doing what he's doing
And so forth, I think they really kind of start to
Develop him a lot
Better than just like
The Mr. T clone he was in the
Original game, they really kind of like
Flesh him out a lot more
And especially some of the support, like
I will admit, I was never really on
The Tifa bandwagon in the original game
But I really
Like her in this
I really, really like what they have done with her character
Because she's
She's a strong, bad ass
Fucking woman
And she's great in this game
And then they really fleshed out
Jesse, Biggs, and Wedge to be
Their own characters
Jesse's a little
I don't know, I have mixed feelings on Jesse
But I think she means well
I just don't like boob armor
Yeah, yeah
But yeah
I just like
I could go on and on and probably talk for three hours
About just this game, but I'm really enjoying it
And I think this game is
Absolutely going to come up
When we talk about end of the year lists
The one other thing I wanted to say about it
Is that everybody's talking about
What's going to be Final Fantasy 7 Remake
Episode 2, or what's going to
What's going to happen there
There's a weird part of me
That wonders if there's necessarily
Going to be one
I feel like they're going to do it just to
Kind of cash in on it and to get the money for it
But a game like that's going to take a long time to develop
And if this game truly stands
On its own, which I fully
Believe it will
Will they need to do a second game?
Well, I think it will take less time
Because now that they have the engine
It's more just
Creating the assets for it
All the recordings and everything
Whereas a lot of the time
From the initial development of this game
Was developing the engine
It would run and all that
So now that they have the tech in place
I think making more content for it is not going to be that difficult
You mean it's not just running in 15's engine?
Because I think it's running in 15's engine
I think it's different in 15
One other thing too
Because I like to spoil things for myself
Before other people do it
There's going to be another
Ok, so that tells me
They left the door open for more
At the point where it ends there must be more
Because that's only scratching the surface of the story
Ok, interesting
Alright, well we'll see what happens
And maybe it is going to be something where
Final Fantasy 13 had 13-2
Lightning Returns
What are they going to call it? Final Fantasy 7 Remake 2
I guess it will have to be the name of it
I don't know what they're going to call it
This will be very interesting
Chapter 2 Part 2
Chapter 2 is probably a better name for it
But we'll see
Except aren't all the in-game things chapters themselves
So maybe it would be
We have volume 1 because then you have your chapters
Of your one book
And you have volume 2 which is
Tigerclaw in chat says
Rob, now that you've played the remake
How would you rate it?
Is it better than the original?
I'm not fully comfortable answering that question
Until I actually beat the game so I can have
Had the full experience of both games
But as it stands now
I'm going to find it very
Difficult to compare the two
Because I think the Final Fantasy 7
Original game was
An amazing game for
Its time
But now this remake is showing us
There's so much more
There's going to be all these people that complain that
Final Fantasy 7 was just really a mediocre
Game and didn't really stand the test of time
Here's everything this game
Could have been
Is almost I feel like the game I'm
Playing now or here if I could go back
And do it over here's what I do
Differently I almost feel like
Is the game I'm playing now and so it's
It's almost like apples to oranges
A little bit or maybe not like apples to oranges
But like apples to applesauce
Like I don't
It's just I don't know if I'm ever going to be comfortable
Answering that question because Final Fantasy 7
Is great for its time
And it's even a game
That I would recommend as an RPG classic
Today but the remake is just
Different I don't know if I would say play
This or that I would say play this
And that can we rewind
To 20 year old Jamie for a moment
Please who did not own
A Playstation yet owned a copy of Final
Fantasy 7
Playing it on her roommate's Playstation
And you know
The whole Knights of the Round quadramagic
Blah blah blah making a sandwich you know
But I had
Three and a quarter discs and I had
A box full of them that was nothing but
Vincent fan art
Because reasons
I played I've beaten that
Game so many times I still
Have a working save file
Where Aerith gets you know
Skewered which is beautiful
And then it goes right into the Jenova fight which is one of my
Favorite pieces of music in the game too
And you know
It's
This was like my thing
This was one of my
It's been a while I go through
Phrases where I'll get something that's like my huge ass
Fandom this was my Mass Effect
Back then
And I am super excited
To play this one or to
You know have me and Dan play it together
You know do our take turn things whenever we do
But
I think I'm going to love this
As much as I love the original because
I love the characters so much I love the story
So much and for me
I
I'm looking forward to drawing my own comparisons
But I don't think I think they're each going to
Stand alone as their own just from the impression I've been
Getting from everybody agree and I think
I think also at a very important point about
This remake there's a lot that
Could have gone wrong with this remake
They could have easily fucked this game
Up easily
They didn't and I think that deserves
Applause
At least the parts that I've played they didn't
There's very there's even even if they completely
Decide to take the story in a 180 or whatever
There's very little that's going to make me
Change my mind on that I think they
There's a lot that could have gone wrong and it really does
Seem like it didn't and they've done a very good job
And it's interesting because now it has a lot of people
Talking about what about Final Fantasy 8
Are they going to do a remake of Final Fantasy 8
And there's a part of me that's like
No we don't need to go back and remake
All the old Playstation games
Like make a Final Fantasy 16
Already but there's also
A part of me that's like you know what
And I've taken a lot of shit on the show for this opinion
But it's my opinion dammit
Final Fantasy 8 is my least favorite
Final Fantasy game save the original
Version of Final Fantasy 14 which was
Which was hot garbage
Final Fantasy 8 is my least
It's my least
See I disagree but that's okay everybody's got their own rankings
Final Fantasy 8 is my least favorite and it's because
It's not because of the story so for those of you
That want to fight me on the story it's not
That's not the reason I find Final Fantasy 8
Unplayable because of
The junction draw
And that whole battle system
How the monsters level up with you
Which was the worst part of Final Fantasy 2
And just everything in that battle mechanics
Everything in that system sucks
And I hate it and I can't
Play the game because of it but now
I'm thinking well wait a minute
If they go back and do Final Fantasy 8
Then they get to keep what's good
The story and they get to redo
What's not good the battle system
So from that perspective
Bring it on you know what
This Final Fantasy 8 hater says
I would like to see that actually
Yes remake 8 do it
Because maybe that's actually gonna help
In a lot of ways with some of my own
Issues about Final Fantasy 8 so
Anyway and yes I
Realize so many people
Have their opinions on Final Fantasy 8
And that's fine
S2100 Matt in chat says
This is a perfect example of
People will forget the endless delay
If the game is done well
Poorly done delayed games become the butt
Of jokes forever
Kudos to that remark and this game
Again with all the
Flare and the strong art direction
In this game and just how this
Game dances as you play it
You see where five years worth of
Work went into this game
You see it
This game clearly took a long time to make
Anyway again I can talk for three
Hours about the Final Fantasy 7 remake but I should probably
Move on with other headlines
Other games I've played this week I've continued on Final Fantasy 14
My Dancer hit level 80
And I did play more Nier Automata
Until the 7 remake came out
And I actually got as far as
I got past that amusement park
Level and I got to do the boss at the end of the
Amusement park again I'm trying to not
Super spoil although that game's been out a little bit
Longer but that was a real
For me that was a really hard boss
At the end of that so
That game is very challenging
But again I talked highly about
That game last week I love the kind of like
Hybrid shooter slash action
Game that Nier gives
Y'all were right on Nier
I said it on Twitter I'll say it again
I missed out so I
Should go back and I will
Go back and finish Nier once I'm done
With Final Fantasy 7 remake
And then now somebody's saying but Persona
Rob you got to finish Persona 2
Yeah that's another one of those games where I feel like
Yeah I really need to revisit
That because that's another one of those games where like
I feel like you all
Are telling me this and I've been resisting
Well I've been resisting I just haven't had the time to play it
And I'll probably end up
Falling in love with that one too so we'll see
So alright
Let's move on we have a lot of gaming news
We want to cover tonight and get to that
So let's start off with
Lowkey with some gaming news
Alright so let's talk
A little bit about the
Side Xbox
Event that they did well not event
But like they had their little
Stuff that they show off the new
Games coming out so there's actually some pretty
Cool interesting things here
So one of them of course
Is a game called
Grounded which is a survival
Horror game or not make not
Survival game but imagine
Any survival game set in the universe of
Honey I Shrunk the Kids so basically
You're shrunk down to the size of
Tiny little
I guess microscopic
Characters and then of course
Bugs and plants and everything are
Giant and you're kind of like in a backyard
Or something it's sim ant
I love that game
But it's but the answer
Are much you know the
Insects are much bigger than you are so
I'm not sure what your scale
Is similar to like you know Honey I Shrunk
Kids or something like that
So they have that what I thought was interesting
Because you know there's people there deathly afraid
Of spiders so they have an arachnophobia
Setting that you can put on
So that you don't encounter spiders
Which I thought was interesting
So they showed off that
They also
Were talking about a
Game called Forza Street which is
Headed to Android and iOS
And
So that's kind of interesting
Because they couldn't just let Mario Kart
Be
Somebody at Microsoft was like how do we get a piece
Of that
No I'm all about it I'm for it
And then they talked a little bit about
Of course
Minecraft Dungeons is going to be releasing
At the end of May on the 26th
Journey to the Savage Planet
Is getting
An expansion called Hot Garbage
Which I thought was hilarious
And that's coming out
This week on the 15th
Then of course they talked a little bit about
Gears Tactics
Some of the new characters in that
Talked a little bit about
Hotline Miami Collection
Which is going to be coming out on
Xbox One at some point
Atomic Crops
That's coming out on
May 28th
And then they were talking a little bit about
Sea of Thieves is getting another update
On April 22nd called the Ships of Fortune
Which has an expanded
Reputation system
They have overhauled the competitive mode
And new cosmetics
As well as cats
That's of course important
That's the most important thing
Yes
And then of course a little bit about Games Pass
Journey to the Savage Planet
Football Manager 2020
We're going to be coming to Games Pass
For Xbox One and PC
Last week and then Mistover
And Stranger Things 3 the game
Are coming to PC Game Pass
Sometime in the future as well as the Human
Fall Flat expansion
Thermal
Evolstia Chronicles
And Yakuza Kiwami are going to be
Available on both platforms
As well soon
And then they touched on
Xbox Series X
Seeing the games can be stored on an external
Hard drive
They can be moved to internal memory
Or the official
Expansion drives in order to play them
I think this is kind of similar to what they were
Talking about with even the PlayStation 5
Saying that those drives
Have to be of a certain spec
In order to be able to run them efficiently
To be able to load everything
How you're supposed to so I think that's probably
Going to be similar with the Xbox
Where you need a fast enough drive to run
I wonder if it's like
It's an archival storage
Like a workplace or something
Where emails that are more than
Six months old go to
An archive and they take a
Lot longer to load because basically
You're going back retrieving it and bringing it over
To the current one so maybe that's kind of
Like what this is
It allows you to have a place to store the game
So you don't have to download it again if you're worried about
Bandwidth issues or things like that but it basically
Has to bring it over and copy
It back onto the drive so you
Can play it from the super fast
D drive maybe that's kind of what it sounds like
Like it's literally a localized
Backup storage type of thing
And then of course they were also
Saying that several countries
In western Europe
Project xCloud as well
And Dragon Age Inquisition
Unravel 2 and Sims 4
Are now playable through that service
Yeah I still
Want to check out xCloud so hopefully I'll get to it
At some point but Xbox Game Pass is
Continuing to be a great feature
I'm really happy to see what Microsoft's
Been doing with that I've been getting a lot of
My value out of that
During this quarantine period so
Yeah I kind of want to see
What's on the PC one because
That sounded interesting
Yeah and I did do the
Preload for Minecraft which is so weird
Preload but that's what it is for
Minecraft Dungeons because that gets like
It's Minecraft but it's Diablo and I like
Both of those things especially Diablo
So I'm really curious about that game
Yeah I'll probably pick that up as well
I do want to play that so
We'll have to play together then
Hey there's a Minecraft we'll play together for sure
Absolutely
Heck yeah
Good job by Microsoft this week on like a little bit
Of an update during this weird time
They were all, like Major Nelson was in his house
Phil Spencer was in his house
Everybody was kind of at home
Kind of looked like that episode of Saturday Night Live
If you saw that this week
This is very strange, this is different
Well I watch a lot of clips of
Late shows
And so everybody's been kind of doing that
Kind of weird
As well
Hopefully they kind of expand out
Just making fun of the usual
Stuff that we have to deal with
I don't know
It was okay
The weird one for me is that guy on
CNN who actually
Has COVID
Who's still working
Because it kind of goes
And he's doing it from his basement and everything
So it's not like he's putting anybody else at risk
But you're not supposed to go to work when you're sick
And you're going to work
I mean yes you're working out of your basement
But rest dude I don't know
That's the only one that's a little weird to me
Because it kind of goes against the message of
You're not supposed to work when you're sick
And I get that he's in his own house
And he's not putting anybody else at risk
And maybe it's what he wants to do
I think he shouldn't but okay
So anyway
Moving on
Let's talk a little bit about this story again
And you might think Rob haven't you talked about this before
And yes this topic has come up on the show before
Especially in this current situation
It has to do with
Coronavirus slash COVID-19
And the World of Warcraft pandemic experience
Why are we talking about it again?
Because it hit the mainstream press again this week
And it's actually out of the Washington Post
So it's a pretty big
Mainstream media coverage about what's going on here
And it was talking a little bit about
And it was actually written
I think the person that wrote the article
For the Washington Post
Is like somebody who
I don't think they're a doctor
But they know a lot about the technological
Ends of things and so forth
And have a lot of insight to what
Is true in that scenario
And how that kind of plays out
With what's going on with COVID-19
And so a lot of the Washington Post article
Kind of talked about the Corrupted Blood incident
Which I think a lot of you are familiar with
At this point, long story short
There was a raid boss
Who would poison you
But people figured out how to basically
Take that poison from the boss fight
And take it into the real world
So to speak, not the real world
But you know what I mean like the towns and so forth
And Warcraft so that that poison would
Spread throughout the towns and so forth
And it killed NPCs too
It did, it would kill NPCs, it would play
Regular PCs of a different level and so forth
Ironforge and Orgrimmar
They were overrun within hours
NPCs would get it
And then pass it on to other players and so forth
So kind of interesting
All the parallels there
And there was even a paper that the article refers to
That was published in 2007 that talks about
Their findings and so forth
But what I find is interesting about this
Is the kind of summaries
That this whole thing makes
And so they reached out for some
Comment about that
Article in the current research
About COVID-19
So the doctor that did this
Let's see, it was Nina Fefferman
Who played World of Warcraft at the time of the incident
Has some comments about that
On the current COVID-19 situation
Saying
What I do is I study all the aspects
Of infectious disease outbreaks
We really saw the full gamut of behaviors
We see in the real world reflected in the
Player characters during Corrupted Blood
There are games where you are encouraged
To behave in a way that you would never behave
Offline
You really have to know the game
Play it and understand the culture
So you can make these kind of determinations
That yeah, this is a pretty good proxy
And then
This actually was a quote
From the other doctor that was a colleague
Of Nina Fefferman's
critic Lofgren who said
Oh, I'm sorry, no, this was
Sorry, I'm doing this on the fly here
There's two doctors, they're quoting back and forth
But Nina Fefferman said this and I thought this was a great quote here
It's not just that
People were role playing
People were being themselves
And I thought that was a very
Kind of like harrowing
Quote about the whole situation
Is that in World of Warcraft
Although there are role playing
Servers and so forth
People can go role play as another character
The reason why this disease
Was spreading and so forth
Was not the result of somebody role playing
Or wanting to do something different
They were doing what they wanted to do
And I think they're drawing some
Parallels in this situation
In that situation
To what's going on in the COVID-19 situation
Where we all know
We've seen it in the news
How some people are not respecting what's going on
With social distancing right now
Meaning that they are above this virus
Which does not discriminate
Against people based on
Whatever factor you can think of
And especially today
Being a day of religious notoriety for some
You've all seen the news
About how some people
Don't care
They believe it's not going to affect them
And we'll see how that plays out I suppose
But it's just very interesting
In those comparisons
That people were not role playing
They were just being themselves
Dicks
What's that?
They were being dicks
And people in the real world can be dicks
We heard about
There was the guy in New Jersey
Who they had to arrest
Because he was going out well knowing he had the virus
And purposely infecting other people
Or the people that are recording TikTok videos
Of themselves coughing on all the produce
To the supermarket going I've got COVID
And even though they're lying about it
Fuck them
They've actually arrested
Quite a number of people for doing that
As well as those pastors
Who are like we're going to hold services
Fuck you
Actually the real heroes have been the landlord
That changed locks on one of those churches here in Sacramento
As much as landlords
Have been taking a beating on a lot of other things
That is landlord done well
In that circumstance
Azet in chat says
There's going to be a spike in about a week
Gosh I hope not
But you're probably right
Tigerclaw says
Another excellent example
And that happens in MMOs a lot
People will buy up the things they know
Are going to be in demand for the next patch
This just happened in Final Fantasy 14
Which is a game I play a lot of Materia
Because these relic weapons just came out
And they have all these materia slots
So people were buying up the materia for cheap
Then the patch drops and they're reselling it high
That's what people do in the real world too
You all heard the stories about the people
Soaking up the sanitizer
And the toilet paper
I know you all saw that one guy who had the warehouse
Or the politicians
Selling their stocks
Yes that too
It's interesting and I thought
It was worthy bringing up again
Even though we've talked about the pandemic
Especially hearing that from a doctor
That people were behaving
In this game just the way they would in real life
And seeing these types of comparisons
Like you would think oh no people wouldn't troll people like that
And then it's like
Fuck but they are though
They are
And so yeah there's a lot you can learn
From what happened in World of Warcraft
So
SSJ100Matt says if you don't believe in this virus
Or think it's a joke come to New York City
It's not great and it's sad
And just
Sorry I almost get choked up just thinking about it
I was just there in New York City
And obviously you know
I was there six months ago is nothing compared to
Being there right now and living amongst it
But just know I am
Thinking of y'all and I love that city
And I love the people and just
You know but that
That is as they say just the first place
You're gonna see this type of thing hit
Other cities and especially in these places
Where people can't seem to follow the goddamn rules
And I'm just very
Thankful whereas
It was extraordinarily frustrating
Maybe to be the first date
Where they said nope shut it down
No restaurants no bars and so forth
Maybe it was a little fresh but now in retrospect
I think most people in California
And the San Francisco Bay Area
And the greater San Francisco Bay Area
Are very thankful for that right about now
I think we're all very thankful for that
So anyway I don't want to speak out of turn
But anyway
Alright
So my thoughts
Really go out to you guys in New York City
And just know that I love you
And keep that distance
But hold through
We're all in it together
And we'll all
Hopefully get through this
Stay the fuck home
I am really happy that California
Sent ventilators there
Because they saw the need
Was lessening here at least for right now
And they sent that and that is great
I'm so proud of my state for doing that
Well Rob we are a nation state
We are a nation state according to our governor
That was a very
Anyway I don't want to get political
That was a very interesting power play
And although I am
I know this is a weird thing to say
But you guys know my mom passed a few years ago
And in many ways
I'm so thankful she didn't have to see this
Because she was such a worrier
This situation would have been
So terrible for her mental health
That like
I'm just thankful she
Didn't have to go through this
But the reason why I bring it up is that she
She loved Gavin Newsom
And that would be the one thing
She would be up and watching his
Press conferences every single day
I tell you that
Political fangirling?
She was
She said she was going to write him in
On the presidential ballot one year
I don't know if she actually did it
I love your mom
I miss her everyday
Let's go further down that
Let's change the topic quickly
And talk about a different story
DarkSakura, more gaming news
So in other news
We are getting more information about
The Playstation 5 in the form of
It's new controller
DualShock? Screw that
We have the DualSense
And I'm looking at this thing
Holding my hands up
At scale using distance
And everything
As people are
Saying it might
It makes me think of a Saturn controller
A little bit of a Saturn
Almost like the
Saturn dual analog
You know
And it's not quite a boomerang
I'm just saying
I'm so glad you're making
Those comparisons
And keeping it old school
Because Twitter instantly lit up with
Oh it's Microsoft
I'm looking for Microsoft
It's Microsoft's controller
And I'm going like what?
What?
The D-pad and the analog aren't even in the same fucking place
And if anything
It's shaped more like a Nintendo Switch Pro controller
I do not see the Microsoft comparison
Whatsoever
And to be honest
I really would
I'm looking at the back of it as well
At the curving on it
It actually seems like it would be quite comfortable to hold
Yeah
I can see where my fingers would fit
Holding the back behind it
I can see where my thumbs would fit
It looks like it could be a pretty good controller
If this is the design they stick with
But at any rate
And I honestly
I think it's about damn time
That they went to a different design
Although again though with the DualShock
If it ain't broke don't fix it
The DualShock was a pretty good controller
Although I have to say
It's not that different
All these are considered
Well and you know the problem I have with my wrist
I can actually though hold
My shift joy cons
In their little
Cradle without a lot of pain
So
But going back
I think the thing that's weirding people out about the controller
Is the bra
And if you don't know what I'm talking about
Look at that black shape
The odd black against white
The little
It's more of a tank top
But those little
Those little analog controllers are the boobies
But it's a bra
But anyway
Whatever Rorshark shape
You see in that controller
I think that's like the white against black
Well we all know you love boobs Rob
I do but that's the weird
Conflicting thing for some people
But I also say
Since the PlayStation 2 era
And probably before that Dreamcast
When has there ever been
Just one first party color
You know there's gonna be other
Colors so if the white on black bugs you that bad
Just there'll be others
Anyway sorry Darkshark I don't mean to interrupt
But I had to
At any rate
It's called the DualSense
Not DualShock 5
It was announced this past Tuesday
It has
Some different features like haptic feedback
Adaptive triggers
And a built in microphone
Which is interesting cause I mean
Gosh you know reading about the
Built in microphone kind of makes me think
Back to the old Famicom controllers
I thought pole voice from Zelda
Pole voice exactly
So
At any rate
It also is getting rid of the share
Button from the DualShock 4
Supposed to be replacing it with something
Different
And the good thing about haptic feedback
As opposed to just having like rumble
Especially you know
Think of it in terms of like
Say
Using your iPhone or you know
My Apple Watch for example how the feedback
Is a little bit different like for example
Excuse me when I do my breathe app
I get a different you know
Sensation for doing my breathing
And I think it's gonna be great we're gonna be able
To get all kinds of different levels
Of sensation from that
You also have the adaptive triggers and the
L2 and sorry
R2 buttons so you get tension
Like you know the example
From Nishino
Who is a senior vice president of
Platform planning and management at
Sony Interactive Entertainment
He's saying that you can feel
The tension of your actions like when drawing
A bow to shoot an arrow
So what they're replacing
That share button with is a create button
So
They don't have much in the way of information
About that but they said it'll come out
They want to create
Epic gameplay content that's a direct
Quote those three words
So then
As far as that
Microphone
They're doing it so that you can chat with your friends
Without a headset for jumping into
Quick conversation
But they're saying that if
You're gonna have like long term
Chat then you wanna use a headset
You know
It does still have that
Light bar but it's now
Hugging around
The left and right sides of
The touch pad
And the buttons
Are now monochrome instead of
Multicolored it's using like this clear buttons
With the grey icons
On top of it and it does have
A microphone mute button from the appearance
Of it so
And actually yeah there's an update
Very recently that says that the
Dual sense controller will have a built
In 3.5 millimeter headphone jack
Oh wow
So it's still gonna have that
They confirmed that on Twitter
That's my favorite part of the tool stock
Yeah that's kinda nice
That they're putting that technology right in there cool
And you know
The other thing too is that
I think it's going to
Do its
Charging
I think with a USB
Yeah dual sense charges with the USB C
With the port located on the top of the controller
Cool
There you go
Yeah that's great
Some comments from chat yeah Tigerclaw says
I bet the built in microphone will be used
So that when you plug in a regular headphone
You can just voice chat with the controller itself
Yeah Sony actually confirming that's pretty much
What it's for it's kinda interesting
I'm sure there's gonna be a lot of tin foilers that
Don't want their controller always listening
To them but I guess there is a mute button
On it and I guess you can always put tape
Over it if you don't like it I don't know
I want pew pew mode where you can just say pew pew pew
And have it shoot
You never know you never know
Let's see YYR says
Haptic feedback ugh why do they have to put that nonsense
In everything I don't know I kinda
I love haptic feedback I dig it in the phone
Although sometimes they overdo it
Some games and some things
Really overdo it on that
But I kinda dig like the way they use it
On the phone and I'm excited to see how that
Translates to cause obviously
On the trigger buttons that's gonna be very different
Than the phone right that's gonna be
A different kind of feeling so I'm kinda
I'll give it a shot sounds interesting
Well there's the big thing about
Haptic feedback
That I think is absolutely beautiful
Especially as we're dealing more with accessibility
These days like
I was reading a post from
Sturlok on Twitter not long ago
About being able to play
Animal Crossing without being sighted
And a lot of that comes in
With you know the sound effects
Like the sound design in Animal Crossing is tremendous
But with haptic feedback
You know you have a better idea
For you know say
You know
Say that you are getting
Footsteps
Near you
You know how sometimes depending on the floor you can feel them
Or someone breathing
And you might get just like a little
Little subtle rumble
When someone's breathing in the room with you
You know
Or you know you're
Say climbing like a rope in your game
And you get the feeling of the tension
Of the rope like have you ever been on
A rope when it's about to snap?
Or pulled something that's about to snap?
You kinda get that tension
And imagine having
Feedback when you're playing
A game that's just you know and for those of us
Who have I'd say
Full access to our senses
You know
Think about the immersion that you're
Gonna get with something like that
But I'm more thinking in terms of our
Friends who need more accessibility
I think it'll be great for them
And YYR is conceding that point in chat
Saying see I hate haptic feedback on my phone
First thing I did was turn it off but yeah I get that
It does make some things more accessible
And that is very good
And Mich in chat says
I usually turn haptic off because it messes
With the nerves in my hands
So yeah it just kinda might depend on you
And your body if this is something that is
Gonna work for you or not work
For you I also wanted to address this point
Cause I thought this was a when we talk about
That create button YYR says
If YouTubers are creators
What does that make the people actually
Creating games?
Artists in my opinion
But that's my
Answer maybe yours is different
I think this is our difference between
A professional like a patissier
And a home cook home baker
Or a pastry chef
Well that's what a patissier is
Yes I know I know for those
That may not know yes
Anyhow
Alright any other comments on the dual sense
Controller
It purred
Oh and then I will say this I think Loki
Had a story on this probably about two months
Ago where there was like a patent
Or something that had been filed on this
We kinda knew this haptic thing was coming
So you know for those that
Don't always like us covering the
Rumors and the unverified
Sometimes where there is smoke there is
Fire so we knew some of these things a couple months
Ago or at least we had a
I don't know if it was a patent
But they were
Just some of the features
That were gonna come to the controller
They just didn't show us what the controller looked like yet
I felt like there was some type of tech specifications
Whatever I like I know we talked about the
Haptic thing a couple months ago so it's kinda interesting
So anyway alright let's move on to the next story
Loki
Alright so
This is kinda cool so everybody is doing their part
To try to help
In the 2019 situation
You have folding at home
Allowing you to contribute in that sense
To try to find a
Cure
Well now Borderlands 3 is kinda jumping in on that
As well they have a thing called Borderlands
Science
A game that you can play within
Borderlands 3 through
In the Infirmary
In Sanctuary 3 which is the spaceship
In the game so
What it allows you to do is actually
Kind of like a
Block matching game
And apparently the puzzle
Game the way it works
It's basically
Allowing you to
Correct millions of small computer errors
That arise as scientists try to map
Microbiomes of the human gut
Apparently doing this will allow
You to allow them to
Better understand
Or have a better understanding of the human body
Which in turn benefits research and the conditions
Like obesity, diabetes and even depression
How does that
How does that work? Is that you
Actually playing the game is doing that?
Or is it that the game
Is so low
Doesn't tax so many
Resources on your system that it actually
Uses some other resources in the background
To do that other part
So what I think it is
Is it's basically
The computer does the matching
And then anything that it can't
Figure out it's allowing humans
To kind of look at
To try to figure stuff out
The game itself
It's kind of interesting looking
It's
It does look like
Kind of like a block matching game
I'm just trying to see
Like actually
How you match stuff together
I mean
It's interesting
S2100Matt in chat says
Oh how nice of Gearbox to come out with this feature
After hosting their employees on those
Performance bonuses
Yeah that's quite the
Retort although to be fair
It was probably those employees who actually made
This feature in the game so
You know
The other issue needs to be addressed
A little more at the top of the food chain
I believe so
Anyhow
That story aside
This is
I love these kind of like gamers doing good
Kind of like harnessing the power of
Games to do these other
Things is pretty neat
Yeah it's interesting
And it is
It's a little bit I mean it is still like
A match three type
But it's a little bit different
Arrows that you have
To basically insert at the bottom
Of your row to kind of move those rows up
To match three
And then it breaks them apart
So it's a little different but
It's interesting
And I guess with that you also get
weapons and stuff out of that
You earn the in game currencies
Alright
Well we'll have to check that out
I'll have to check it out I don't know
I don't know Borderlands 3 yet
Yeah I haven't played Borderlands 3 in a while
It's been on sale a lot
I'll have to look into it
Especially now it's off the Epic store
And it's available in more places so we'll see
Alright
Well anyhow moving on for now
Let's talk about Final Fantasy 14
A game I do play a lot of
And COVID-19 has had an impact
On Final Fantasy 14's development
Final Fantasy 14 has been on a pretty
Almost like clockwork it's release schedule
It's like they go X many a week
There's a patch then there's another patch
And then there's the expansion like everything is almost like clockwork
Which actually some people kind of criticize
14 about is that it's
Patch cycle almost gets too predictable
Like it's going to be a dungeon here and a raid here
And they don't tend to break that predictability
A lot well
The situation of what's going on in the real world
Is causing some things to get pushed back
Game director producer Naoki
Oshida put a
Update to the community this week about what's
Going on saying we are terribly sorry
For the disappointment this may cause our players
As we know you look forward to new patches
However it's also important to prioritize the physical
And mental health of our development team
Without whom we would never be able to release the
Quality updates and features you expect from Final Fantasy 14
So we ask under your
Ask for your understanding as we adjust our
Schedule in accordance with the situation
So basically talking about that this most
Recent patch most of the
Development was done for the fight because they just
Released a 5-2-5 patch
That was pretty much done right before they released
Or right before all this you know work at home
And all that kind of disrupted in Japan
So now this is going
To push some things back so they're
Basically saying 5-3 was going
To come out in June
It probably is going to miss that date
Due to the situation what's
Going on so you know
And he's got graphic designing
Teams in Asia, North America,
Europe and all over
So basically the game is going to
Have its content delayed for a month or two
And really quite an explicit
Apology there from Yoshida
To as somebody who's been playing Final Fantasy 14
Ever since the
Realm Reborn alpha
Let me say it's okay
We completely understand
Like it's really fine
Like do what the team
Has to do to
Take care of themselves and so forth
And yeah it's
If things slip a month or two it's okay
It's sad that
Fan fest may or may not happen in November
I mean I know that's a ways out we'll see
Where the state of the world is at that point
But it's
Really okay I understand there's other
Priorities right now and there's
Plenty of things to do in Final Fantasy 14
And you know what if I get burned out on it
I've got like a backlog a mile high
Of other games I need to be catching upon anyway
So it's fine so anyhow
I thought that was a very nice letter for them to write
They really don't owe us that
I thought it was very nice that they did
But they didn't have to
Alright let's move on Dark Soccer are you back?
Okay I know she went ahead
That's okay would you like to go ahead and do the next story
Or want me to come back to you
I can do the next story
Anyway
You know we've kind of
Gotten off especially with all the
COVID news and everything
About the protests in Hong Kong
And the free Hong Kong protests
So
Of all places for the protests
To find a new home in
It's an animal crossing
So since people
Can't go to the street
Protesting in force
Is not physically safe
People are going into
An unregulated
Area to do so
And that is animal crossing
So they are putting up
You know signs
You can do your patterns
And you can actually do nice big patterns
That you can lay out
Like as big mats on the ground
Like people normally do pads
Some people have signs
In their houses
Their characters are wearing
Gas masks and privacy masks
And doctors masks
And whatever things that can
Hide their face
As a version
Of what they're going to be doing in real life
And putting the information out there
And reposting it to Twitter
Or wherever they need to
Having pictures
Of
You know of people
They've lost in the struggle
People who are important to
The protest
And since you know
They're wanting to
And actually this is a quote
That one of the students involved in this
Was saying that animal crossing is a good way
For us to remind people
Not to forget what happened in the past
Eight months
Not everyone is open to political stuff
Animal crossing is a good way to promote our mission
To those who are politically apathetic
So
Keep going
You know do it where you can
I think it's beautiful
Now I believe there was
A follow up or something
Animal crossing I believe has been banned
And I think
This stuff might
Have something to do with it
Obviously they're neither confirming nor denying
But one can draw a pretty substantial
Conclusion from what
History has shown us in this situation
So yeah
Questbuster says just a week or so ago
There was news about how animal crossing had a big
Launch in China and people started using it
To recreate scenes including COVID
Checkpoints and now just recently
Animal crossing was pulled
I hope all these people have physical copies
Yeah well it's
Isn't that interesting because
You can't really pull it now that it's out there
I mean you can stop it from being sold again
But as you all know that just drives
Demand the product up even higher
Take your system offline
So it can't pull a
PT
I realize China is a very different society
And they have different ways of doing things
But I still feel like
Once it's out there
People are going to find a way
They will
Well let's move on we have a few more stories for you guys
Before we get to the classic game of the week
Loki
Let's see so
Let's talk a little bit about
Stadia
So Stadia of course you may know
Or are going to be hearing
That Stadia Pro has gone free
For two months so I'm assuming that
With the whole everybody having to be home
The whole COVID-19 stuff
So they said
Google basically said in their blog
Hey video games can be a valuable way to socialize
With friends and family when you're stuck at home
So we're giving gamers in 14 countries
Free access to Stadia for two months
That's from Phil Harrison
And so basically with that
You can access
Stadia Pro
You don't necessarily
Need a Stadia controller or
Chromecast
But you can
Use your controllers and stuff like that
You do need a Gmail account
To be able to participate in that
And then of course it comes with some free games as well
And they have
Of course
Destiny and Grit and stuff like that
So is this something
That you're going to jump back in
Since you've already got your free one
You know what's funny I wrote some tweets
About it because I was like I can't figure out how to
Reactivate this because
I was on Pro thanks to the friend code
Thing because Bobby had given me
His friend code and so I had it for three months
And then I remembered to cancel it before the 90 days
Ran out so that I
Didn't get charged for another month because
As much as I thought it was fine
I never really intended to buy
Any more games on the service
I was really just playing the free ones
That came with Pro
So I didn't really
See the need to keep it and keep
Paying $10 a month for games that
I kind of felt like there was more on
Something like Xbox Game Pass I wanted to play
But I was like alright well if they're giving it away
Free for another two months maybe I'll go back and try it again
Because I don't dislike Stadia
I think from a tech perspective
It's actually pretty impressive and I talked about this
When I talked about playing the Stadia
Before
It's like interacting with a YouTube
Live
And it works pretty darn well and so I think it is
A piece of technology worth checking out
My only concern is
Again I haven't gone in there so I don't know how this one
Is set up but is
This the gotcha gym membership
Thing where they get you to sign up for
So many days free and then oh your
Credit card is on file which with
Google it probably is already
On file if you've ever bought anything
Through Google they have your credit card
Info already if you forget to
Cancel are you going to get charged at the end of the 60 days
Again I don't know how
This one is set up so I don't want to accuse Google
Of doing something they're not doing
Yes so here's what the way it's
Says
You're cutting out a little bit Loki
It says what?
Sorry so it says anybody that
Signs up for Google Stadia
Will get access to all the games
It says if you're
Already a Stadia Pro member you won't be charged
Next two months
After that Stadia Pro is $9.99
A month but you can opt out of your subscription
Anytime so yes it is
The hey sign up
Now for free but remember to cancel
It before those two months are up otherwise
We're going to charge you $9.99
I
If I'm understanding this that
Way then I actually
Think this is an incredibly
Shitty thing that Google did
Because they're using this
Situation to get
People on their product
If I'm understanding it
That way that you
You have to cancel yourself
After 60 days
Or gotcha you're going to renew
At $9.99 a month
Then I kind of think
That's really shitty
Of Google to use this situation
It is what they're doing
So
The best business as usual
For a lot of subscription
It is
With that being said
All I'll say is
The technology is
Worth it but please
If you do decide to do it
Immediately set yourself a calendar
Reminder at 55 days out
To
Decide if you really want it or not
I will say this
Unlike a lot of gyms and that stuff
When it comes to gyms you have to call somebody
Or cable you have to call somebody
And they're going to try to talk you into staying
I will give Google credit with this
Canceling you just do it online
You click a button done
So I will say that you don't have to interact with anybody
You're not going to get pressured into staying or anything like that
But
Just be warned
Ain't nothing really free
In this world I guess
Alright
Make your own decision on if that's for you
Again from the technology perspective
I think it is worth checking out
But please set yourself a calendar reminder at 55 days
To evaluate if you really
Want it
YYR in chat says
Don't be evil slash strike through
That part
Alright
Moving on to how
Business is being affected on
Different sides of the ocean
The ESRB apparently
Still going amongst what's going on
With the coronavirus and COVID
Is that there is no delay right now
In assigning game ratings
At least that's what they're saying
I imagine most of that is still working from home
From what I recall of the ESRB
I don't think they're actually playing
A lot of the games
You kind of have to fill out a packet
And they kind of assign the rating based on the packet
And it's assumed that you did that in good faith
Because if they find out you didn't do that in good faith
Such as what happened with things like Oblivion
And Grand Theft Auto 4
With the hot coffee mod and all that stuff
That's when things get dicey with the ESRB
But they are still going
They are still doing ratings and so forth
Whereas the CERO
Or is it pronounced CERO
They are temporarily closed in Japan
Due to what's going on in that situation
So there are no ratings currently
Being assigned right there
That could cause a little bit of a backlog
It may impact some of the game releases
I don't know what's going to come of that there
But that is a little bit of a difference
Of what's going on over there in that situation
I don't know if they're actually playing the games
Or what happened in that scenario
Alright, well let's go back to a simpler time
Dang it, we're going to go back to when
The games weren't rated at all
Actually I'm not sure the selection is from that period of time
But we're still going to go back in time
At least ten years
And visit a classic game
Every week on this show Dark Sakura steps into the gaming vault
And says, hey, brats
Instead of playing these modern newfangled remakes
Why don't you go back and play the demakes of yesteryear
Dark Sakura
This was top notch when it came out
It was, this is much more than 8-bit
A title from the CD and DVD era
Dark Sakura, what is the classic game of the week?
This classic game is Project Justice
Which, like how have I not done this yet?
I mean, I actually had to go check multiple
Things to see if I, you know, had even remotely done it
So, as it was called in Japan
It was Moro Justice Gakuen
Which basically burned Justice Academy
The, you know, the previous before was
She Needs Justice Gakuen
Which is private, Justice Academy
So, it is a 3D fighting game
That came out released from Capcom
It's a sequel to Rival Schools and United by Fate
And, which was, you know, first released as an arcade game
In 2000 and ported to the Dreamcast in 2001
And fortunate enough to have been able to play
The arcade machine
Because they had it at SVGL
I do
I remember whenever we weren't doing that
TBR tournament that was inside there
Because I was doing Perfect Attack at that one
I was over there playing Project Justice
That was the one where Jessica and I
Switched out in platform shoes
Remember we said we were gonna, we did
A Perfect Attack wearing platforms
Which was pretty fun
I do remember that and I'm stepping away for just a moment, sorry
Okay, so at any rate
Project Justice is to this day
Probably one of my favorite fighting games
As far as I love the Rival Schools
This one is totally, totally, you know, for me
Just really goes there with it
So, it is still a team fighter
But you have teams of three instead of two
So you get extra team up attacks
That you can use
But another one called a party up
So that you would initiate by pressing any three attack buttons together
And it is a three person attack
That relates to whatever the school
Where that character comes from
You also have an additional
You know, your additional partner
Will also let you cancel an opponent's team up special
By putting in a team up of their own
So you have like a different short fighting sequence
Between one character from one team
And whoever gets the first hit in
Will, you know, be the winner of that one
And then it swimmers back to the main fight
So you have a bigger meeting
Also twelve that's five levels
Instead of nine from Rival Schools
The party up attack uses all five levels
Team up to two
Any attempts to cancel
Cost one level
Also carrying over from the first game
Project Justice from Dreamcast in Japan
Has a character creation mode that allows you to create your own team fighter
It can be used in all the modes except for single player
But its package is a board game
Which you do during an inter-school festival
Instead of the dating of the first Rival Schools
You also
And actually I have the Japanese version
So I got to do this, it was pretty fun
And you can also get sub characters
That you can unlock through this mode
You still have your players that are in the game
And a few things that have changed
So you've got
Like extra, you know, some of the other characters
When you have new people to be hinted at
Like in the Rival Schools revolution
Or I should say, Phoenix Justice
Right now I forgot what it was called
The Evolution Justice
Which I need to put back
Basically, things have gone back to normal in this
And then there's a group called Reverse Society
That comes back in so they have to fight again
We have a new character, Kuro Kirishima
And Momo
I always miss a person
Karui Zawa
Who is like this pretty violent player person
You also have the leader of the Gedo Gang, Daigo
Who was peripherally a character in the first game
Being mind controlled, so you have mind control
And then you also have a Batsu doppelganger called Vatsu
So trying to pin it all on Batsu
So you've got all kinds of different stuff
You have
You even have
They even go all out with your swimmer character
And you can play as the school president and everything
It's pretty fun
But again, one of my absolute favorite fighting games out there
There are people who didn't like it
And those people are wrong
Famitsu gave it a 33 out of 40
A lot of people, it got kind of an average review
Higher end of average
But you know what?
The game is fun
That's the important thing about it
It's got that goofiness
It was friends of mine who did the localization on the first tribal schools
And I think that we had just that same heart that went into the original localization
They kept a lot of the Japanese dialogue
The translation is like
It's so funny if you listen to what people say in the game
And you know enough to follow the conversation
Like, oh, I see what they went there with in this localization
That's fully not what they said
It's always fun
It's fun
I cannot state enough how beautiful this game is
And we need to make it trend rivals schools 3
Make it happen
We need to make it happen
We need like
I'm trying to think where they could go
Because we had Chirich Justice Gakuen
And then had Moro Justice Gakuen
What can they do that's even more than that?
Like maybe hot-blooded Justice Gakuen
We already have burning
We do
But anyway
The game is great
If you haven't played it, sucks to be you, go get it
Somehow
There it is, the classic game of the week
Project Justice
Which DarkSakura is amazed that she never picked before
But there's always more hidden gems to be found
Like how could I have not
Questbuster in chat over twitch.tv slash vog network says
I love the days when Capcom could afford to be occasionally crazy with their ideas
Hugs copy of Pocket Fighter
I mean
There's
I wish that we would get
A 2D Capcom collection
So that we can have things like
CyberBots and Red Earth
I have two copies of CyberBots
I have the limited edition and the regular one
But
I would love to have
The not released in America
Fighting game pack
Oh yeah
There was just recently that Kunio-kun collection
With all these NES games
That were never released here
And then of course
Secret of Mana 3
Or Trials of Mana if you will
Finally broke that barrier
And the remake
Or remaster whatever you want to call it
Is on its way out pretty soon too
So it's almost like all these old things that never came out
Are finally new again
Is Nintendo listening?
Mother 3? Hello?
You know I actually bought
A repro cart that had been translated
Just to sit down and play it
Mother 3
If you want to borrow it you're welcome to
Did you see the Animal Crossing level?
That opted all the
Stuff from the Mother series
It looked really cool
It was really well done
Google it
It'll be out there somewhere
Did you hear what I read from Orange Wright?
The Not Street Fighter Anniversary collection
Oh yeah for sure
I'd love to see something like that
Just before we went on air tonight
I don't think it's coming up later in the show
Capcom I think said
They're looking at a rumor is
I think it's a rumor that's why I didn't really put it there
That Resident Evil 4 remake is coming up next
Even though
Who would surprise no one?
That one is so good I don't know if they should remake it
Whatever they're going to
Because the other two have done very well in sales
But there is a part of me that's like
Why don't you explore some other things
Some other games that you have
Well Dan and I were talking about this earlier
And if they're going to redo one
You know what?
I want Code Veronica
That's what a lot of people are saying
It's funny you say that because that actually is like
What comes the next breath
What a lot of people are saying when people are talking about
The Resident Evil 4
Code Veronica next
Yeah Thar66 in our chat right there
I would have preferred Code Veronica
Yeah a lot a lot of people out there saying that
So we'll see we'll see what happens from Capcom
Because I don't believe they've officially announced anything yet
Alright well there you go
Code Veronica though was to me pinnacle
So just saying
There it is the classic game of the week
Let's do some rapid fire news
Loki we'll start with you
So the updates for No Man's Sky
Just keep on coming
We've got pretty cool stuff
In the giant mechs
You get to pilot so the exomech
Is part of
Update 2.4
And allows you to pilot these mechs
And of course they are immune to planetary
Hazard and they
Have a pretty awesome cockpit as well
And look pretty awesome in fact I
Decided to make the picture of the mech
That they posted on Twitter
My background for my work here
Looks pretty awesome it's almost like a little bit
No Man's Sky-ish but of course much slower
Not as fast
But
I really do need to go play this game
Maybe I'll install it on my hard dress
But yeah so
Check it out it's free if you own the game
Yet another thing to go check out
Exactly
Well if you're looking for some
More pre-games to play during
This whole COVID-19
Situation then
You'll be lucky to know that
Just Cause 4 is going to be
Among the free games that are on
This coming week on the Epic Games
Store and that's pretty awesome because I
Did skip this game which I think I did
And maybe I have it in my catalog
I don't remember
And so
Yeah it'll be nice
To have this and actually be able to
Now I'm second guessing
Myself maybe I did buy this on PlayStation
4 and I just completely forgot about it
Maybe the first time that I've gotten the game
And completely forgotten about it
But anyways along with that
There's going to be some other games
Including a visual novel
Of Aurelia
That's also going to be coming
Free as well and then if you act now
Sherlock Holmes Crime and Punishments
And Close to the Sun are free
But those are only going to be free
Until Tuesday when these
New games will come up and we'll be free then
I get those annoying
Little messages in the system tray that remind me
To download those free games so that's
Kind of nice I guess
Yes so definitely do that
Just because I should
Probably convince my son to download it
Because he'd have fun playing that game
Alright well let's
Move on to some other stories
This one has to do with Discord and a new
Beta feature that's happening in Discord
Called the Background Noise Reducer
You may have seen this in your own Discord
It just showed up there for me in the bottom left
So it is a noise suppression
Beta feature
It's only on the desktop version of the app though not the mobile version
And it is supposed to reduce
And remove background sounds so voice
And video chat folks only hear you
Speaking and you shouldn't hear that clack clack
Clack clack of a keyboard or the
Kids in the background or the pots and pans
Clanging or whatever it is going on
The technology is from a company called
Crisp and it is running locally
It is not sharing data with anybody else
Development is still early on and they are
Working on a phone version of it
So that's cool
A lot of other meeting software could use something like that
That's for sure
I'm really excited about this other feature here
That Twitch is looking at doing or is actually
Rolled out to partners
It's called Prime Watch Parties
So it's kind of like that Netflix Party idea
Except you're kind of leveraging Twitch
And you have to have
A Twitch Prime or excuse me
A Amazon Prime to really like
If you don't have an Amazon Prime subscription
You don't see the webcam or whatever of the person watching
But if you have both
You get the webcam of the person watching in the corner
And then you actually get like the
Amazon Prime show whatever they're watching
Timed up to where they're at
In the main screen so you actually get both at the same time
So it's kind of like an interactive watch party
They've actually been kind of
Playing with this feature since October last year
But now all partners have available
Have the access to be able to use this
I was looking at one earlier today
And my instant reaction was like
I want to do this at VOG
I want to get some of the
Star Trek, Starboard power coupling people together
And watch episodes of Star Trek
Wouldn't that be great?
Except it's not out for affiliates yet
And I'm not sure
It's a little weird because you have to link
Your Amazon Prime account
To your Twitch
And since VOG Network
This account isn't really a person
I'm not sure we're going to be able to really do that
So it might just have to be something on my personal channel
But it's still something that I'm really interested in doing
Because I think that's really fun
And especially in this day and age
That's the type of stuff we could really use
So yeah
I think it's a really cool idea
It kind of takes that Netflix party
To the next level
Because Netflix
That used to be a thing on Xbox 360
Then they kind of shot it down
And then there's an unofficial
Google Chrome add-on
That kind of does the same thing
That hasn't been shut down yet
So I don't know
S2100matt in chat says
First name VOG, last name Network
Middle name Smush
You never know
I don't want to break the rules
We're professionals here most of the time
So I mean if I can just use
My personal account on VOG's thing
Then I would do it but I don't want to break the rules
So as long as everything is
By the rules then we'll figure out a way
But if I have to do it on my personal channel then I will
DarkSakura, how about you?
Well
We have an update
About Adi
Everybody's Animal Crossing
Grandmother
The one who logged 3500
Hours playing
On New Leaf
Well the internet got together
All of her fans out there
And had
A crowd funding
To buy her
The limited edition Animal Crossing
Switch
Which I watched the unboxing
It was adorable
She's like I don't know how to do the button
You know
I want to say
Is this her grandson helping her
Create her character and everything
But we need to see
If Adi actually gets Adi
In her town which would be great
As we know
Nintendo of America
So
We'll see
I just think it's an absolutely sweet
She just looked tickled to bits
And really amused by the whole thing
And then
In other news
Regarding Streets of Rage 4
It is coming quote soon
With classic characters
And with soundtracks
There was a tweet
By Lizardcube
That confirmed the existence
Of classic characters and the original soundtracks
And also
Bringing back returning
Characters like Max Gate
And Dr. Zahn
Are playable in their 16-bit forms
With a price of $24.99
Confirmed
But it does not confirm the April 23
Release date
And only that it is coming out soon
However there was an Australian
Nintendo eShop
Listing
That stated that it would have
A storefront release on April 23
With a price of around $38
Australian dollars
Which is roughly $25 US
Listing says 12 unique
Stages and the ability to unlock
And play as classic characters
An option to switch out the new
Soundtrack with the
Original Streets of Rage games
And so
Hey there we go
Alright sounds
Good I'm excited to hear that new
Soundtrack that sweet new Yuzo Koshiro
Music very excited
I love Yuzo Koshiro's music
Let's travel around the world and check out the release
Dates for this week although I have a feeling
There might not be a lot but we'll check
In anyway and
Check out the releases so
Let's start with the US
Alright
Not much
Ace Engineers coming out
Vampire
Masquerade
New York on Xbox One
And
Pretty much it
I was just gonna see
If there's any other digital games
Since this list doesn't have a lot of digital games
So I'm gonna read some of the weird named titles
That are on this list like for example
We've got a game
Called Save
Your Nuts on Xbox One and
Switch. The Double Dragon
Collection looks like it's coming out on
PlayStation 4 and Switch so we have Double Dragon
On PS4 and
Double Dragon 3 on PS4
Double Dragon 2 on PS4 and
Switch and River City Ransom
Coming to PlayStation 4 as well this week
Lots of like digital games coming out this week
So yeah where is there may not be a lot of
Games coming out
There's definitely
Games you can check out like Super Forklift
3000 on PC
Alright nice
Alright let's travel over to Japan
And check out the release dates in Japan this week
Although I'm not seeing an awful lot
Happening let's see
On the 17th on the Nintendo Switch
There's a Guacamelee
Collection coming out that's I think the
Only thing I really see there
Looking on the PlayStation 4
Do we have anything different there? No that's
That's it it's a very quiet
Week in Japan this week but
Considering everything that's going on I'm kinda not surprised
How about the UK Dark Soccer
Crickets chirp chirp
Nothing until the 22nd
Yeah with all that's going on I'm not too
Surprised about that alright
We're gonna do things a little bit out of order because
I know Dark Soccer has to cut out soon here
So I'm gonna shake up what you see on the
Sidebar a little bit so Dark Soccer do you wanna take your
Next story here which is actually at the bottom
Of the list there for those watching
On Twitch for those on the podcast feed you have no idea what I'm talking about
We actually show the upcoming headlines
So we're gonna do this one down here at the bottom
Before Dark Soccer says goodnight
This one's a doozy so
It is a very very
Write up by
CNET and I'm more than happy
To share this with people but I'm gonna give you the
Cliff notes on it just because it is
Absolutely worth mentioning
So they're talking
About the upcoming
Systems in the climate crisis
That our next generation
Consoles could be worse for the
Environment
And
There's actually a
Game studio called Wildworks where
Their CEO Clark Stacey
Is quoted saying I don't think it
Occurred to many people in the games industry to ask
What sort of climate impact came directly
From making and playing
Games
But they're looking at
Things like the
Output of these
Systems and what they're releasing
In just carbon dioxide
For example the PS4
Said that
Basically if you have
100 million PlayStation 4 units sold
Since 2013
Generated approximately
9.8 million tons of carbon dioxide
Which would put it at
108th place for
Emissions in 2016
It would outrank Costa Rica
It would outrank the entire country
And then
In energy usage that number
Would double
And then
Xbox one
They have a slightly
Smaller
But a single
Xbox unit emits
1.23 tons of carbon dioxide
Over an eight year life cycle
And so
It is a lot more friendly
Than say the PS4 for its release
But it would still be 0.76 tons
And
If you were using a less conservative
Estimate
That
The general output from these systems
Would be something along the lines
Of taking between 40 and 95
Million flights from New York
To Los Angeles
So
Pretty intense
So the video games industry
Please Sony
And Microsoft
Have been challenged
To do
To do better
And so
Actually
For
The average PCs
And current generation of consoles
They account for 2.4%
Of residential electricity expenditures
In the US
And have a carbon emission release
Of 24 million tons
Which is about the same as Sri Lanka
In 2017
So a whole country
The devices associated with it
Like the TVs
Were responsible for 66%
Of home energy use
From gaming in 2016
So going back to what I was saying
The Microsoft and Sony
Have been
Definitely challenged
There was a
A conference
I'm trying to get the name again
Because like I said this is a big article
But they were challenged
By
In the UN's Playing for Planet
Alliance to create
825,000
Carbon neutral
Xbox One X consoles
Which would be under 2%
Of all consoles made
But every little bit helps
But they're trying
They're also wanting to
Make them
More carbon neutral by buying
High quality carbon offsets
Sony announced on March 18th
Mark Cerny who's the lead systems architect
On the PS5
Did not make
A single mention
Of energy draw or the environmental
Impact
The only thing we have about this
Comes from Jim Ryan
The present CEO of Sony
Interactive Entertainment
Who said that they would be able to
Suspend gameplay with much
Lower power consumption
And that if 1 million users
Enable this feature it would save the equivalent
To average electricity use
Of 1,000 US homes
And
Nintendo however
They
I mean Switch uses a
Bunch less energy than the other systems
Lower processing power
And graphic fidelity for one thing
Results
In less energy
Consumption
They're focused on
Better games
Even if they don't have that
Hardware
The size of those things
They practically run off a rechargeable battery
So it's kind of inherently built in
And even a solid three hours
Of playing using the handheld mode
It does not get hot
And that's kind of one thing
I was curious about is that
I don't know if it's going to be realistic to say
Oh we shouldn't have Playstation 5
Or Xbox Series X
Maybe there's better things they could do in the manufacturing
Process like you kind of brought up there with some of the
Carbon free consoles
But I wonder if there aren't maybe small measures
We can take on the consumer side
And you kind of brought one up there that maybe
There's a thing you can enable there to use
The lower power consumption in the background
Maybe our consoles don't
Necessarily have to be always on
I know it's very convenient to have
The patch downloads and things like that
I know my Xbox One started making weird noises
So I kind of like
I unplug it completely when I'm not using it
And then I'll plug it in
An hour before I plan on using it
To do any patch downloads and things like that
But maybe that's a thing
I don't know
I'm not saying everybody has to do it my way
But maybe there's things consumers can do
To cut back on some of that energy usage
There's a little bit more
There is
Clark Stacey again, the head of WildWorks
Has
Called out a few different things
For example, I'm going a little bit more
Into cloud
Networking for data
Saves for games for all that
Type of thing
And the fact that the data centers require a huge amount
Of energy pooling systems
That make it run 24 hours a day
Forever
And actually this is a different quote by Adele Tousie
Who's a data engineer at Monash University
A typical cloud data center consumes as much energy
As 25,000 households
And Clark Stacey
Who I mentioned earlier goes on to say
That Google and Apple are leading the way
Basically saying that since the data centers
Are 100% powered by renewable energy
Then
This actually requires
The companies that use renewable energy
To invest in renewable energy
For the open market
Ubisoft
Has gone 99%
Which has
Basically
Had them to release
Far less
Carbon dioxide
Into the atmosphere
But the thing is
That a lot of these other groups
Are using
Cloud-based services
Or even their own
I'm trying to think of
Just general
Operations
If they could
Lower that impact
That's how data centers
Make up
They actually could make up
Approximately 60% of all energy uses
In communication by 2025
So
We really need to be pushing them
Into
Using
Cleaner energy
Into
Finding renewable resources
And this has to start top down
But the thing is
They're not really having
The ability
For
Climate change
Based on
Their current operation status
They're not really having too much
Of an incentive
Other than
The public
Poking back at them
But
If they
We also need companies
Take to
EA
They haven't put any
Type of
Report on their emissions
Or their energy usage
And
Microsoft when their spokespeople did
Submit a disability
Sony and Nintendo did not
Respond to a request for comment
But
And of course we have all of our
Handhelds too
And some of the big companies
Are innovating and jumping the gun
On getting the
Emissions reduced
And making things with more
Renewable
I think now a lot of
Computers and
Handheld devices
Made from recycled material
So that's good but we need
To hold people's assets to the
Fire
And I think awareness
Is probably a big component of this
And one thing that we probably need
Our gaming media, our gaming press
To do is now that we know
Where these things are coming from
Cloud gaming is the future but at what
Cost as you point out there
We need our people that have access
To be able to interview these folks
To ask these questions. This doesn't have to be done in a
Punitive or a negative way but
This cloud gaming sounds great but
What are you doing to ensure that there's
No harm to the planet from it or what are you doing
To get back on these. We need these people
To ask those because unfortunately
We could say here on our little podcast
And say those types of things and think about
The things that we could do maybe a little more
Directly but we're not gonna
Realistically be able to really affect the change
The way that people that have more direct access
Have the ability to do that
If that makes sense. Like I was saying it has to start top down
You know but
You know we can also
I'm sorry but I'm really surprised on Microsoft
Side of things especially I know Bill Gates
Doesn't run it anymore and in fact Bill Gates isn't even
Involved with the board anymore but I'm just
Surprised with him kind of being the legacy
Of Microsoft and everything. Him and his
Foundations on the planet. I'm really surprised
They're not at the forefront of this
Which they ought to be
Microsoft has really been
I mean they're late to the game in terms of
Environmental viability
Other companies have really
Been doing a lot better than them
I mean I think
That will and here was what the exam
Say and
This actually brings our current pandemic
Into things. Look at how
Much these places
Around us have cleaned up
Without
The level of energy
And material and
Being put out
If we can get companies
To do you know
To what's the lack of a
Better description to
To have that same kind of
Control to keep things isolated
To you know using
This renewable resource keep them
Using recycled materials
To you know put pressure on
The government for example
To find cleaner ways
Of shipping
You know games and all of that we can
Really really make
Such a big impact. You know piggybacking
On that a little bit this is this is the hottest of
Hot takes but some would say
That you know and I don't know if it's right
Or wrong take it or leave it but some would say that
The pandemic and what's happening
Is in this I guess
This depends on what you believe in in science over this is
This is earth's response
To the humans living on it not
Responding to climate
Change. You know I mean when you see that
Direct impact that you know
The pandemic kind of isolating people in their homes
Or this having on the climate you know
Some would say that is the earth healing
Itself. At least it's not
The happening yeah right
So anyway I know that's I know that
Is the hottest of takes but it is it's one of those
Things that makes you go hmm
Yeah and you know what and there's
Also this thing going on oh
This is you know
I don't think it's people that
Are the virus I think that
Is people's decisions
We all have to be
Able to
And now I'm going to be getting into a bit more broad
Outside of video games but we all have to look
At what our personal impact is
And we have to make good on it
You know and I'm not talking about
Oh straight
Fuck that that whole thing was ableist as fuck
But I mean we have to
Look at the companies that we are
Shopping from and what they are doing
And the fact that our money is supporting their bullshit
You know
We have to we have to find this
We have
People accountable and we have to
You know and speaking
Of top down in this country
We have to fucking start with top down
Alright
So things don't shape up
Yeah you guys are both cutting in and out
I thought it was maybe just my wi-fi
And to my phone
Okay oh boy alright
So what I said is I said if
Things don't start shaping up
We're going to have to start bombing makeup
I think he's making a Final Fantasy 7
Remake joke
Oh yeah let's go hit Shinra
And run the balls
I definitely want to read this comment
Sorry no Bobby
It's not the new noise cancelling
Because I specifically said before the show
Don't turn that on until we have a chance to play with it
It's not the new noise cancelling
I didn't even know it existed so I didn't touch it
Yeah
VG Realness in Chat says
I feel like some gaming press is afraid to ask the hard
Questions for fear of not getting early releases
A big basket of bullshit in this industry
I mean it's not even about this climate
Change thing which I mean is certainly something
But I mean it's a whole thing
Where it's like we've known for
Some time that you know outlets who
Don't ask the hard questions get
They get their hands slapped
And you know unfortunately
As Darkstalk was talking about some things are from the top
Down and when you see the same type
Of thing happening at the highest of offices
In North America
Or excuse me in the United States
I don't know what to say
Anyway
I also want to respond to pod culture
To Brad
Digital only is pretty damn clean
But going back to the thing
In that CNET article I was going off of
Bear in mind that
It takes energy for the downloads
It takes energy to host
The digital copies
We're getting back into the cloud services
And those cloud services use a ton of energy
Unless they are doing a lot more to offset it
So even though it might be less physical waste
Which certainly would be a thing
Again there might still be a trade off
For that so anyway
And some folks in chat just kind of like breaking news
Folks in chat are saying playstation network
Is apparently down right now
So I wonder if there isn't a whole thing going on with the internet
And I thought maybe it was just me
Because for those that don't know
How things are wired
I actually have two accounts
On discord so I have one account
That strictly is on the wired
Connection and it also feeds in
My microphone and the mixing board
And so it kind of mixes everything with them on discord
And then the way I listen to them
So that you don't hear the feedback
Is I am in on my own personal account
On this wifi on my phone
That's why I've been wearing headphones
Ever since we started doing the
Social distance episodes of OLR
So I thought maybe my wifi was cutting in
And out so I was just kind of
Because I was watching the meters and they didn't seem to be dropping
But apparently it's a weird internet issue going on
So I don't know what's up
So sorry guys but we're doing our best
Wish we could all be in the same room but it is what it is
And as I said I was going to put
Because like I said there's a bunch more
In this article
So I posted it on
My own account
So
If you want to read up on it
And look at what you can do
Then
I'd say give it a look over
See what needs to be
Done who needs to be talked to
And hold their asses to the fire
Alright
I have spoken
Alright well on that note Dark Soccer I know you need to take off
So any final thoughts
Or last thoughts for our listeners tonight before you take off
Send me chocolate
Like legit
No one guessed my fucking favorite chocolate by the way
So it's
Vosages
It's the stout chocolate
I require many bars of this
Sent to my house, message me for details
And that is very true
Because every time I go to Chicago where they have a lot of it
That's what I bring back Dark Soccer
When she's doing the kitty sitting
I can find by the way
The bars at the nugget
But I cannot get those delicious truffles
Yeah those are harder to find
Alright
And I love you for it, love love love heart heart heart
Alright take care Dark Soccer
And we'll see you next week
Be well, be safe
You stupid people stay in your house
Alright
Let's move on to our mail bag
Participate at orangetontrader.com
It's the place where you can send us an email every week
We got one quick email tonight
This is from Robert M
Who emailed us to say
I haven't heard it discussed but after four years
WayForward released their formerly Humble Bundle
Subscription exclusive
Cat Girl Without Salad
On the Switch
Appropriately on April 1st
They will be getting repeated over multiple plays
At the few levels
Might not be worth the $9 for everybody
But a fun distraction between New Horizons sessions
$9 is really really low price though
And thank you for the email
Appreciate that
And just based on the title
It sounds like something I want to check out
The problem is
And for me this is a big problem with the Switch overall
It's great that they have a lot of games
But their eShop doesn't handle that avalanche of games
Very well
It's not like
Steam
Even Steam is starting to buckle under the weight
It's not very easy to explore and find things
Because I had no idea about this game
Until you send an email
So I think the best thing you can do
When you have a little indie game
That you like like this
Help spread the word
And I say it at the end of every Orange Launch Radio
Because it's true for us as an indie podcast
We're never going to get the types of views
That IGN Podcast
GameSpot Podcast
Or employees that formerly worked for those organizations
Having their own podcast
We're not going to have those types of numbers
Because we don't have that
So the best thing you can do for us
Is help us spread the word
And the same thing is true of these indie Switch titles
Because even though they're on the Switch
They don't have Nintendo's name on them
So spread the word
That's why I like to do that for YYR
We have a small audience here at Orange Launch Radio
But I like to pimp YYR's games
They're pretty good and I think people should see them
Especially, especially super multitasking
It blows my mind that that game has not gone viral
But you know, you gotta spread the word
Tell people about the products you love
So I will say this Robert M
You are doing the right thing
When it comes to how to spread the word
For finding those games on the marketplace
And I will check that out, Catgirl Without Salad
Spreading the word by streaming games
Is a big one as well
Do you want to rob Robert's super hot take, Loki?
Do you want a really unpopular super hot take
About streaming games?
Yeah
I think, and this is my opinion
And I'm speaking of no other streamer
Or no other watcher other than myself
I think it is a bad idea to stream Final Fantasy 7 Remake right now
Because I don't think narrative video games like that
Make for very good streams
Because if you drop in and out
You're either gonna be spoiling yourself on the story
For the game you hope to be playing
Or you're gonna be dropping in on something
Where you didn't see the whole few hours
Leading up to this particular point
And I just, there's a reason why I kind of stop streaming those types of games
Because I'm not sure it's always like
It's not really what I enjoy either
I don't necessarily like all the personalities
That I do see streaming some of these games
Kind of like doing their own voice acting
Doing their own voice acting
Or doing their own thing on top of this
Like I just don't think narrative games like that
Make for very good streams
On the flip side, I think Animal Crossing
And those more like evergreen games
That are meant for user created content
I think they're great games to stream
And I think that's why games like
Minecraft and like a lot of things
That are very like user, Stardew Valley
I think that's why those games have tended
To do very well on Twitch in the past
Because I think those streams are better
They also do a lot of creative things
Oddly enough so like
My kids watch a ton of Minecraft streams
And Roblox stuff and all that
I've started to watch more of those now
And it's because it's not necessarily
That it's just, it's vanilla playing Minecraft
They do interesting things with it
Like for example, one I watched the other day
It was two players trying to speedrun Minecraft
While they have a terminator after them
And the terminator is basically
A AI bot that just hunts them down
And while they're playing it
And that made it interesting
They have a person
One person trying to speedrun the game
And beat it, the other one has a compass
That points to where the other person is
And they're trying to stop them
From beating the game
And so those are fun
Or like some of the
Ultimate hardcore stuff that they do
Or like
Deathmatch stuff are pretty fun
They can mix it up
And of course my hot take
Is getting a lot of comments in chat
See what happens when you don't send emails
That's gonna happen now
You're gonna get a Rob Roberts really super hot take
Maybe it'll be on Drag Race, maybe not
So some comments here
That it's generating here
Bobby Blackwell says I only stream narrative games
If they were on MS-DOS in the 90s
And again, I'm not calling any single person out
And myself, I was streaming
Ni No Kuni 2 when it first came out
And then I kind of realized by the time I got to
Part 4 or 5
If you didn't see Part 1
Why would you come watch Parts 4 and 5
And that's why
When I see the tweets that are like
Come watch my Nier
Nier Automata was when I was looking for videos
Because I love the soundtracks
And I would see these videos that come up on the side
Watch my Nier Automata Part 23 playthrough
And I'm like girl
If I didn't watch Part 1
I ain't gonna watch Part 23
But if all your streaming is Part 1
I think that's different
And that's what kind of Bobby gets
So when you're doing the MS-DOS game in the 90s
I feel like you usually do that first
And then that's usually it
And that's kind of where it gets
Those first couple hours types of things
Yeah, if I streamed Final Fantasy 7 Remake
It would just be the beginning of the game
Exactly, that's different
That's a good little sample of the game
And then you're not getting too far into it
But I'm not gonna
And this is any streamer I'm following
And I love you guys, I love the community and so forth
But if you're streaming Final Fantasy 7 Remake right now
I'm not gonna visit your channel
Because you might be further along than I am
And I don't wanna be spoiled
It's just as simple as that
VGRealness says say their names
Everybody
Everybody is guilty, I've been guilty of it
You've been guilty of it
I'm calling out the planet
Let's see
I'm dragging everybody today
Says SSG100Matt
Questbuster says
I'll watch some classic game streams
Where no one says a thing
But because I love the gamer I'm really curious about retro
I'll stick with it
Again, different strokes for different folks
Again, I'm not saying you shouldn't watch these streams
You should actually, because I don't want to
So somebody should be
Supporting these streams
But I just think
It isn't the most compelling content
To be streaming narrative games
Part 23
That's all I'm gonna say
Alright
BobbyBlackWolf
I'm laughing because of the comments in chat
BobbyBlackWolf says Rob's being affected by Mako
I keep wanting to say Mako, but now we've learned it's Mako
Rob's being affected by the Mako
The planet is crying out in pain and he's mad
Yeah, I'm mad
Alright, let's move on
Loki, quick, change the subject before I get another
hot take out there that gets me in trouble
So we should stream this too
Because it's going to be pretty fun
No, I don't want to get cancelled
So the
LEGO Super Mario sets
They're going to be launching
August
They of course announced this
A few weeks ago
So now we have
Some pricing and what exactly
So I don't think it's
Necessarily too expensive
But the
Starter set, a $60 adventure
With Mario's starter course
Yeah, $60
If you pre-order it, you also get
A little
It's called Super Mushroom
And Monty Mole
So it's like a little collector's thing that you can
Get as well to add some more stuff
To that
I'm not sure if you'll be able to
I think they've stopped taking pre-orders
Because it's already been so popular
So there's that
And then they showed off some new sets
Piranha Plant
It looks like a little seesaw thing
With two piranha plants on it
And that's $30
And then of course the Bowser's Castle
Boss Battle expansion
Which is $100
When you're talking about Lego prices
That's not too bad
Not a lot of pieces though
But then again
The Mario's
The character itself
Is very sophisticated with these
A voice
And everything like that
So I can understand how that might be a bit more expensive
The Bowser's Castle thing looks pretty awesome though
I gotta say
Yeah, those Legos
As expensive as they are, what else is new with Lego?
They look so cool
Honestly
Sign me up
Uncle Sam's sending me $2400
Why not blow it on Legos?
I'm sorry
I should but
You know there's lots of people thinking it
Like
What dumb shit
Am I gonna spend that
And I shouldn't make a lie because a lot of people really need that
For very serious things
But there are a lot of other people that are like
I should spend that money on Legos
Why not?
Anyway
Pixel pockets in chat says
I want the Bowser set
Let's see
They're talking about the ability to post gifts in the chat
And I'm like yes I'm all for that
You should be able to post gifts
But Loki are you gonna buy the Legos and do some building?
Probably
Same
Big same
Let's move on and talk about
What's going on in the chat
Just wanted to know whether Blizzcon 2020 will be feasible
They have a lot of their own employees
In fact I think all their employees are working at home right now
At Blizzard
I mean certainly there's a whole side of event planning there
So those folks are still
Event planning
Because
They would rather
Plan something and have to cancel it
Than not have planned it at all
And find out
Miraculously we have a cure by the summer
I know
That's probably not realistic and I shouldn't even say that
But you know you always cross your fingers and your toes
Maybe something will come through
But anyhow Blizzard does acknowledge
That it could be several months before they know
If they're going to be forced to cancel Blizzcon or not
And that's the case with everything in the fall right now
Like early on in this process
It was definitely like
DragonCon, Blizzcon
FanFest, all those things that happen in the fall
We'll be fine, this will be over by the fall
And now the longer that this goes on
They talk more about the curve
The potential second waves
And we don't necessarily have all the answers
We don't really know
Is it going to be safe for all those nerds
Who don't always take a shower
To be crammed together
In the Anaheim Convention Center
That might not be a good idea actually
So
We don't know yet
We just don't know and neither does Blizzard
And so we'll have more information on that
In the coming months
But there is going to come a point
Where there is a go or no go
Like there is going to come a point where
They have to make their decision
So we'll see what's talking
Do you think they would try to do like a digital only event
And money?
I'm sure Blizzard would do a digital only event
Would they charge money for it?
That's a very good question
Because Blizzcon
Well, but Blizzcon is also all of their
Championship games
And if they can't really do that
I guess they could just do it via distance
I'm not sure
Like Hearthstone you could probably do that way
But I'm not sure you could do things like
Heroes of the Storm or Mythic Dungeon
That's like 5 people or Overwatch
I'm not sure you could do all those as easy
So I wouldn't rule it out
But yeah
It's not necessarily
Going to happen either
Sia Tabiri in chat says
I hope more comedians start doing Zoom shows
This is a big thing in the
Drag community actually too
There's a lot of drag kings
I know a lot of drag kings locally
That
Are doing their own shows on Instagram
And actually
I don't want to say who it is
But I actually follow a drag queen
On social media
And I actually chatted with them
And it's one of the Rugerolls
So you know who they are
That wants to start doing a Twitch stream
And so I was giving them
Like I was talking to them about
Oh well good news so do I
And I was telling them about how to download OBS
And all that stuff so we'll see if they actually do it
Because I think a lot of people really like
The Twitch bits system
As being able to donate and tip
And some of that stuff on demand
So a lot of drag queens are looking at Twitch
As the ability to do that
And so you know put any artist
You might kind of roll your eyes
Oh there's Rob talking about drag queens again
But where that goes comedians
And other types of artists
Really follow especially the longer
That this goes on
That's for sure
Yeah VGRealnessInChat says
That must be really hard without audience feedback
Or immediate feedback I should say
It is weird watching
Like even some of the late
The late night shows?
Yeah watching the audience
Normally laughing and stuff like that
Having their jokes without any of that
It's a little weird
I did watch some of the Saturday Night Live
And it was weird
Yeah I mean I appreciate that they did it
And they tried it but it was a little weird
But again for Twitch's benefit
When it comes to those types of performances
They have the chat room
So they are getting that stuff
I mean it might not be the actual audio laughter
But they do get their ha ha ha's
And their lol's and their emote icon spams
In real time and at least it shows them
Oh somebody's out there I'm not just talking to myself
And that goes a long way
Anybody that's done streaming before knows
Even though you still need to stream
Even when nobody's watching
And you need to act like the world's watching
It does sure feel a lot better
And rewarding when even one person
Is there saying hi
Oh lol or you know even this littlest thing
Will kind of like give you that motivation
To keep going for a long time
So anyway
Let's move on
So we already talked about the climate story
DarkSakura did that before she left
So let's go to Loki with our next story
Yeah so this is kind of cool
So you've been seeing a lot of company
Loki you're cutting out so bad
I don't know if there's even anything we can do about it
What I'm going to try to do
I'm going to reestablish your connection here
Can you just hang up on the channel
And come right back to reestablish your connection
Literally turn it off and then on again
It's the first thing I want to try
See if that helps
Because I don't know about you guys but it's very bad
Okay try again Loki
Alright
How's that? So far so good
Cool
Yeah I think there's just internet issues
And there's mosquitoes in the house
Okay
So anyways
So you have different companies actually stepping up
To build
Ventilators and one of those now is actually
A PC company of course
Main Gear
Who does a lot of different cases and whatnot
And so they're actually building
A ventilator called the Liv
And it's basically
It looks like it's built out of one of their old cases
But
It's a complex
Oxygen delivery system
With a touch screen interface
And they say it can supply
Oxygen in 1.5 seconds
So pretty awesome that they're
Going to be manufacturing that
They said
It can be manufactured at a scale
At a quarter of the price of traditional
Ventilators
Though it's pending FDA approval
But looks neat
I hope those sorts of things
Like FDA approval don't take so
Long that by the time they're able to do it
It doesn't matter anymore you know
Yeah I think a lot of that stuff is kind of relaxed a little bit
Because of the pandemic situation
But
I have a feeling that
The process will be a little bit quicker
And not to get like political
Or too off topic but I kind of think
These guys are getting ahead of the curve
Because I think what's going to happen
Is I think they are going to
I think they are going to invoke
That defense act or whatever it's called
And they're going to force more companies
To be creating things like tests
And ventilators and things to help
I'm kind of surprised it hasn't already happened
But I think they're going to force a lot more companies
To make these things in mass
So that we can have the appropriate level
Of response I really think that's
How this ends
Or not how it ends but how
We have a path to normalcy
I'll put it that way
But we'll see again I'm not a politician
That's just my tinfoil hat talking
But to bring it back to games
As you're seeing in this particular story
Game makers are not necessarily
Immune from that type of order
Right? So
I just ordered PC parts actually
Because my computer has been doing this weird
Like locking up thing lately
And I was like you know what I just want to buy new parts anyway
I actually got a new graphics card and I'm surprised
A. I was able to find one
And B. it got here as fast as it did
Because I was quoted the end of the month
For the card to get here and it showed up yesterday
So I was like alright I'll take it
But
I have a new graphics card for my games I'm really excited
Alright
That's cool? Yeah
Alright let's move on
Last story here before we get to
I think we are going to try to take calls tonight
Because somebody told me they wanted to call in
And I really wanted to hear from this person
So I was like alright not that I don't
I was like okay alright you know what I need to try to get
The discord call thing working again
So we're going to try to do it tonight
And video we need to do video too
Yeah we need to get video running again
I didn't think this would be for that long
So I wasn't going to force that issue
But here we are
So yeah that'll probably be a thing that comes
Just don't rush me
Alright if you want to call into the show
Join the green room
We'll get some folks here on the show
So get in the green room just like always
We're hiding in a different channel but go to the green room
And I'll still put you in the place you need to be
Alright
For now let's talk about a 35 year old bug
That's been patched
Or at least that's the way it's being reported
Although I'm not so sure I draw the same conclusion
However
An admin and a writer at the cutting room floor website
Which is a really cool website by the way
But the admin Gold S has released a patch
For Super Mario Brothers
Yes the 35 year old game on the Nintendo Entertainment System
That will change Lakitu's behavior
In saying in a quote
The spiny eggs are thrown by Lakitu
In a simple way
With no horizontal movement whatsoever
However
This is not the intended behavior
And is actually the result of a bug
The eggs are supposed to be thrown out
Relative to the player's speed
Lakitu's speed, the player's position
And a pseudo random value
As well as bounce off any blocks
Or walls that they hit on the way down
So how the heck did he find that this was a bug
He's just kind of assuming this was a bug
Right
But apparently when looking at the code
It was kind of one of those things where it's like
The code is in here but it wasn't really calling on it
Da da da da da
So that's where this patch came from
I'm really oversimplifying but I gotta try and keep this short
But
One could also argue
How many times has this game been re-released
At this point
We had the Wii version
We had the Super Mario All-Stars
We had the Game Boy Advance
We had the Game Boy Color
This game has come out again a fucking lot of times
And did they ever change it?
No
So was it truly a bug
Or was it one of those things where it's like
We just accepted that this is the way it is
And so we're not going to change it
I think that maybe they just didn't want to fix it
Because that's how it's always played
And it would be weird if we changed something
But it is interesting
And Dr. Suya says I just thought this was neat
Oh no, don't get me wrong, it is neat
And I'm not saying anything bad
Or mean against the person that found it
I do think it's neat, I do think it's cool
And it is just an interesting
It is an interesting relic of
We can't really patch the old games
So
Even though I'm saying maybe it just
It just kind of became accepted as the norm
It's interesting to think
Because Nintendo could not fix it
Did that just become embraced as the norm
Lakitu's behavior and that's why it was never
Fixed in a later release
That might really be the reason
We'll never know
But if Super Mario Brothers were released today
They could fix it
I mean that's what they do with Animal Crossing
So Nintendo can fix things
They can patch things, they do it all the time now
So it's just interesting
YYR in chat says do we know for a fact
That this was never changed in later versions
They did make at least some changes
In later versions
Specifically
Like All Stars
I'm sorry, specifically Lakitu's behavior
No, is not
Different
There's a great little side by side comparison
If you want to look at news stories on this
I was looking at an article at RetroRGB.com
That had this article
I think this was actually linked in our Discord
Because I know I stole a lot of stories from our Discord tonight
So thank you all to the Discord community
Over at vognetwork.com
Where I do borrow stories
Especially on news weeks
Where everybody's in quarantine
So the companies aren't always putting out news
At the same length
But anyway, I'm looking at this
And there's a nice little gif or a video here on the page
That actually shows the before and after behavior
And you definitely see in the after
You see how the eggs have more of an arc
More of a curvature
To the way they're thrown
Whereas in the normal game they just kind of go
They kind of just plop down
And you kind of outrun them in the normal game
Whereas with the arcing
It makes it a lot harder. You have to actually dodge them quite a bit
It does, it does. It's interesting
It's interesting
SSJ100Matt in chat says, Miyamoto is willing to fix it
But you have to put in a support ticket and he has to be billed
At his regular rate from 1985
I don't know about that
I don't know
I wonder how often
He gets in there and programs things anymore
I don't know. Alright
Let's get to some calls
I see a couple folks in the green room
So let's try this out and we'll see how it goes
Hello, you're on Orange Sounds Radio. Who's this?
Hello, it's Delvin from VG Realness
What a surprise to hear from you
Hi Delvin
Don't act like it's a surprise
I just missed hearing from you
I missed talking to you
And I just, I missed the world
The way it used to be, but how are you?
I'm doing great
I've been enjoying
The hell out of Final Fantasy 7
Which is what I'm here for
To talk about
Okay, before I let you talk about that, can I just say
Because I had to say
You came out here to visit and you were on an episode of OLR
Like a year and a half ago, right?
And I keep saying, I'm gonna go to Toronto
I'm gonna return the favor, I'm gonna go to Toronto
Last year I couldn't go
Because I ended up changing jobs
Right in the midst of that
And so I didn't have any time off, I couldn't do it
So this year I was all gung-ho about going
And then, womp womp, pandemic
Toronto Pride gets cancelled
And now the gag is
You're not even gonna be in Toronto much longer, right?
Well, who knows at this point
I guess that's true
Anyway, so I just
Yeah, it's just one of those running jokes
I'll go visit Delbert and return eventually
But anyway
In the meantime, you've been playing Final Fantasy 7
Yes, I have been playing it
And let me just preface this by saying
I had to take a phone call
Right at the moment when you started talking about it
So if I'm repeating anything that you said earlier, I apologize
Repeat away
I've been enjoying the game a lot
And I have a different perspective
On the game that I don't know that
Many people do
Is that I didn't play the original
Not by
A choice
I tried to play the first one
And I had a little brother
And anyone who has a little brother
May have also experienced this issue
They like to delete save files
Off from your games
It doesn't matter what it is
It could be a game that they don't even play
They would just go and delete your save file
I don't know why
But he did this multiple times
When I had it on PlayStation
And then I said, okay fine, forget it
I'm gonna play it on PC
So then I started it on PC
Way back when it was
98 or whenever
Yep
And then my computer crashed
So I lost the save file again
So I said, you know what?
This is just not meant to be
And I just never played it
Because I was like
I can't play disc one anymore
God is sending a message
Message received
Yes, message received
I'm not to play this game
So I left it alone
So anyway, here I am now playing this game
And it's really good
And the battles
Are really seamless
Honestly
This game feels like
This is maybe how they wanted
Final Fantasy 15 to feel
And what they were
Going for but didn't quite hit the
Mark because they ran out of time
But the battle
System just feels very fluid
And I mean in 15, yes it was
But this is just like perfected
At this point
So totally really good
But what really has me
Irritated is
The fans
Of Final Fantasy
And the haters
Get her Jade
I don't know
Where this hatred
And vitriol is coming from
For some people
Some of the comments I'm seeing online
Is that, oh you're paying $60
To replay something in better
Graphics just to pay another
$60 for some quote unquote
DLC when and
If it arrives. So some people
Are even going as far to say
Oh well Square's not even going to finish
The game. They're only going to release
One and maybe two and then not even
Release the completed
Product. And
I don't even understand where
That comment comes from. Why they
Would leave that money
On the table to not finish it
A fundamental misunderstanding
That this is not the same product
Anymore. That's
The other thing
Again I haven't played the original
So I don't know but just going on
Comments and things from
People who have played the game such as yourself
And other friends
This is not disc
One as it was
In its original game
Which is what a lot of people
Are making the comparison. A lot of people are saying
Oh it's just disc one in
Better graphics and
That's not what really is being put here
And then there's gamers who have
This purest attitude
Towards the game and saying
They don't want to buy the game until
It's completed
Because they feel it's incomplete or it's not long enough
And my argument
Towards that is
A lot of people are saying
Okay the game is only 30 to 40 hours
It's not long enough so it's not justifiable
To have the $60 price tag
$80 if you live in Canada
But whatever
And the way games
Are going today
Games are generally 30 to 40 hours
Long and
You know for those
Diehard RPG fans which I am
A diehard RPG person as well
We have to really think
And consider what was a 100 hour
RPG game back in the day
Was it really
100 hours worth of story
Or
Was at least a minimum
Of 40% of that time
So 40 hours of that gameplay
Grinding
Replaying dungeons
Over and over killing things
Over and over and over and over
To make the game feel like it's
100 hours
I mean
Don't get me wrong there are some games that
I truly enjoy that
But I don't want the game to be
100 hours
Quote unquote
Just and then
Making me have to grind
To make the game artificially feel
Longer just so RPG purists
Can be like oh yeah I can
Buy this game now because it's 60
It's 100 hours
And I don't know about your impression of what you've played so far
But for me like when you are in that main
Story this game has you
By the balls and does not let go
Like you are like it is intense
Maybe when you're doing side quests
And stuff you get a little bit of a cool down period
But like god you need it
Like
Let me have a nap for a minute
There's a lot going on
Like I mean I'm not like
Super like
Pro at like you know games and there were
Some battles where I like I died
Are you playing on normal or easy?
I'm playing on normal
Oh okay well that's to be expected
Yeah there were some battles I
I died and
It also goes against
That old school RPG mentality
Like I really think to get through
Normal mode even you have to
Use potions and high potions
Whereas like in the old Final Fantasy games
We would stockpile that shit
Like I got 99 potions in my inventory
I might need them I might need them
No you are never going to use those potions
Because you never do
The remake
So my number one advice to you
Delvin on those
Use the fucking potions
Oh honey
Honey
She is buying the potions
She is hitting the vendors
When they're on sale
Oh this merchant has it on sale
I'm buying them
I'm buying all of them
Trust and believe
All of them
But yeah it's crazy
I don't know where this attitude
Is coming from from people about this game
They want it to be a hundred hour
Experience
They don't feel like it's long enough
And I just really wish that people would put that thought
Out of their minds
This not being a complete game
You know and by that same
Thought you know
Do we look at movie trilogies as incomplete
You know like the Avengers
Whole movie saga
Do we just
We know more of it's coming
So I'm not going to go and watch
Captain America
Because I know it's not a complete movie
It's going to continue
That's just a bad attitude
You used the same argument I used on somebody on Twitter this week
Which is somebody I like a lot
So I don't want to make it sound like I'm fighting him
Or I'm cutting him down
But somebody whose opinion I value
Replied to one of my tweets and said
Well I don't really want to play the Final Fantasy 7 remake
Until the whole thing is available
And I just replied and I said
You know you got to do what's best for you
I said but I hope by that logic
You didn't watch any of the Harry Potter movies
Until all eight of them were out
Well I mean yeah
I don't know it just doesn't make sense to me
Some of these comments
That are being made that I'm seeing on Facebook
And social media
It's just unfounded
And what I will also say
One last thing
Is that
What Square is doing here
I would really like to see them
Go back and give this kind of refresh
On some of the other games
Because this is
And I don't like that they even call it a remake
Because it's not
What we have instilled in our head as a remake
This is not a remake
This is a complete retelling of a game
So to speak
Ooh I like that
I'm going to steal that one too
Retelling, reinvention, reimagining
For gamers to expect
You know
A developer to make
Such a game
That was originally 3 disc
100 hours and still release that
For you know 60 dollars
I still think it's a little bit
Unrealistic in today's world
And the reason I say
That is because
A developer can make a game
That is like
A single player game not talking about like the destinies
And the whatevers that are like
Constant ongoing games
Like a single player experience game
You have to think about
The amount of hours that would go into developing a game
To make a game that's say
100 hours worth of content
Not everybody is going to play that
Let's be real, how many of us
Have single player games that we've bought
And are sitting on our shelves incomplete
So we want developers
To put all this effort into
Making these games
So long that nobody finishes them
And they don't make
The money from
I just want to know it's there
I just want to know that the next time
There's a pandemic
I'll have entertainment
I just want that peace of mind
But no, I just think it doesn't make sense
So I think this is a good approach
Honestly, it may seem
Like price gouging
Like square trying to take our money
But really it's not, they're really giving us a completely
Different experience, the game is amazing
It's gorgeous
So to any haters out there I say
Put that thought out of your head
Go enjoy the game
I do want to say this
It's okay to not like the game
I want to make that clear
I don't want to say, oh my god something's wrong with you
Well I don't want to say
Oh there's something wrong with you
If you dislike the Final Fantasy 7 remake
Maybe it's just not your type of game
Maybe the battle system
There might be
But my point is
Know what it is you don't like
About the game
Don't assume you know
What you don't like about the game
Therein is the difference
Yes, I totally agree
So I just want to make that clear
Because I don't want somebody to feel like
Oh my god, is Rob going to drag me
If I don't like Final Fantasy 7 remake
No, as long as you know what it is
You don't like
Alright
Every time I see this whole like
Well I don't like it because it's only 10% of the original game
I'm just like, then you clearly haven't played it
No
And you're just making a
Flip in statement
You didn't even bother to look at the demo
You're making a snap judgment based off what everybody else on Twitter said
Your opinion is wrong
Sorry
This has actually inspired me now
I just actually downloaded Final Fantasy 7
On my Switch, the original
I'm dying to see
What's changed
I want to see how the first few hours of the game
Played out versus this
Just to see how different it is
Ok, so like when I was
Doing chapter 3
And again I got to keep things very vague
Because I don't want to spoil for those that haven't even touched the game yet
But when I was doing chapter 3
I was like, I swear
This sequence was like
5 minutes in the original game
Like you go to this area, you talk to somebody
And then you're on to the next area
You're not spending the type of time
So I had to go back
I actually looked at a playthrough
Somebody had one of those
5 hour plays
Maybe that's how I got on the part 23 and all that stuff
But somebody had a Final Fantasy 7
Playthrough and the whole
Midgar section was 5 hours
And I was watching it and I caught myself watching it
And I was like, this, ok
Some of these things
Were definitely not the same
I probably should have
Considered just watching on YouTube
Instead of downloading a game
But whatever
It's not like, like the question that came up earlier
You know, is Final Fantasy
Remake then better than the original?
I don't, like better is a very
Relative term, like the original
Is good for its own reasons
It's not the same game anymore
That's the reality
Yeah, that's like saying, is Final Fantasy 7
Better than Super Mario Brothers?
I
That depends on a lot of factors
Absolutely
Alright Delvin, I so appreciate your opinion
Are you producing any content these days?
Are you still streaming or what?
You got something to plug here?
I only stream like very
Very rarely
Every now and then on my Twitch channel
Twitch.tv slash VG Realness
Go ahead, throw a follow
And turn your notifications on so you know when I'm
Streaming, but it's
Here and there, but I'm probably gonna be
Doing it a little bit more now as we are in quarantine
But I need to finish FF7
First, because as we just talked about
It's not that interesting to watch
Well not that it's not interesting, it's just
Not good content
But I will say this, I
Downloaded and played Dotless because of you
Because you were streaming it one night and I was like
Oh I need to check out this game and then I tried playing it and I was terrible at it
Hey, it's free
It is free, so hey, I didn't lose any money
So
Alright, Delvin, thank you so much
It was so great to have you on the show
Thanks for having me
Take care my friend, bye bye
There was another person in the green room
But they disappeared, so I guess they changed their mind
But I'll give it another minute to see if anybody comes back
In the meantime, do we have any last minute
Stories, Loki?
Yes we do, so apparently
You may remember the whole
Atari VCS console
Well, we talked a little bit
Back in October about how
This company, Tin Giant
Had resigned
From project development
Because they were saying that they were
Citing six months worth of
Unpaid invoice as well now
Tin Giant, the head of
That company, Rob White, has
Formally filed a suit
In Colorado Federal Court
Claimed to breach a contract to the tune
Of $261,000
Because of unpaid
Contracts
So
It'll be interesting to see what happens here
I don't know
I didn't ever hear anything positive coming out
Of this Atari console, and I don't even know
When it's supposed to be coming out
The most recent release date apparently
Of the console was March 2020
And we haven't heard anything new yet
Well, I'll cut them a little slack
Because I'm sure the pandemic situation screwed everything up
Let's be real
The buzz for that Atari system
Wasn't there
Let's not mince words
The buzz for that Atari system just ain't fucking there
It's a very different story
Than say Intellivision last week
Obviously Bobby had Tommy
On his show and it was a great interview
I hope you guys all got to check that out
And he's working hard
To build buzz
He even stopped by our little tiny
Tent in the slums
Here of podcasting
To talk about Intellivision
Bobby's talking about that Atari system
Yeah, in fact
According to the lawsuit
Tim Giant actually
They basically said that
In fact it was Atari's own mismanagement
Of the console project that was the cause
Of the reason
Or reason for delayed launch
So
I want to mention this
In chat over at twitch.tv slash vog network
Because Pod Culture was the person that was trying to get through
On Discord and had some
So Pod Culture says
Just a quick anecdote about sending Christina
My OG Switch
So she could play Animal Crossing
New Horizons
While locked down
You know you're actually not the first person I've heard doing that
Because I guess the Switches are so hard to come by
I've heard of like people mailing their relatives
Because some people have a second Switch
Lying around because they might have bought the Switch Lite
Or they might have bought that Animal Crossing Switch
Or what have you
So for whatever reason they upgraded
You're actually not the first I've heard of somebody doing that
I only have one Switch
So I don't have one to mail out
But I have definitely heard of that
So that is a very interesting side effect
Of not many Switches being available
Either
So anyway
Just wanted to get that comment out there
Since he couldn't make the call work
Any other last minute stories Logie?
It says apparently
That Xbox has committed to
A digital only press conference
For E3 2021
That seems like a
Long way out to me
I do remember seeing that
I was going to bundle that with the inside Xbox thing
Yeah they basically said
They've made the decision to transition
All external and internal events
To digital first experience through
July 2021
That seems like a long way out
To say you're going to do digital
But okay if it's digital first
Then I can sort of
Just going more the Nintendo route
And keeping things with the direct and so forth
It'll be interesting
Yeah so we'll see
Alright
Alright well if that's it for last minute stories
I think we'll go ahead and wrap up tonight's show
We've been going for a little while tonight
It's a little longer than our last few shows
So we have a lot to talk about tonight
But I hope everyone enjoyed the show
And I want to say thank you so much for tuning in tonight
Whether it was live here at Twitch TV
Thank you so much for being here
Whether it was on iTunes or Google Podcast
Or Spotify don't forget we're there now
Or wherever it is you listen to podcasts
Help us spread the word, tell a friend or two about the show
Because we only get folks here
Listening if they know about the show
So we are the show where every gamer has a voice
But you've got to help us recruit those voices to get here
Auto host on Twitch
Those go a long long way
More than I could ever really tell you
So please those are all fantastic as well
Really appreciate those hosts
So I think that's all I have
On that side of things
So let's wrap up with our final thoughts
Loki, have a great week
We'll see you again next week
Stay safe and let's hope we get some good news
On the curve and maybe things start to go downhill
As far as, you know what I mean
Like down the hill
Not like things going downhill
But things going down the hill on the COVID situation this week
And maybe some good news to report next week
But any last thoughts for our listeners tonight?
No that's it
Hopefully we'll play some more games this week
I would like to start working on my game
I just haven't been able to work that out
I've been switching up my grocery shopping days
And so it's
It takes a long time to grocery shop
You just have to go to three different stores
To get everything
But we were like super stocked up
So hopefully next week it'll be a little lighter
Yeah that's good
And my final thought is
We do a lot of grocery shopping too
But I really like food delivery
And supporting local restaurants
But it's so expensive
Like if we could find any way to cut the cost down
That'd be great but you know
We gotta pay the drivers
We gotta pay the restaurants and so forth
So I guess maybe I need to do a little more takeout
But it's hard because you want to help everybody
But at the end of the day
I had an amazing Thai meal from downtown
On Friday it was so good
So
I definitely know as soon as this whole thing is over
I'm going back to eating out
Because it's so good
Alright anyway
That's it
We're going to wrap up for this week
We'll be back in seven days to do it again
Happy gaming whether it's Animal Crossing
Final Fantasy 7 Remake
Persona
Whatever it is you're into this week
We hope you're having a great time doing it
Have fun, stay safe, stay indoors
Keep your distance
And we'll be back in seven days to talk all over again
Thank you so much everybody
Have a wonderful night
See you next week
Thanks for watching!