This week the headlines continue to have an unsurprising theme and I spent all my creativity
in the bump the live listeners just cringed over. I hope you're safe and have a supply
of healthy foods and fun games to play in these times. We've always been remote from
you so please continue to enjoy the show where every gamer has a voice. Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice it is Orange Lounge Radio live tonight with episode number 814 for this
April the 15th excuse me April the 5th not 15th getting ahead of myself of 2020. My name is Rob
Roberts joining you here live of course with everything that's going on in the world we are
still doing the social distance thing so it's just me in the studio tonight usually my co-host
would be here live in studio with me instead I'm joined by Captain Pikachu and via discord we have
welcome back tonight please DarkSakura or Jamie Summers. Hello. Hi I hear that you're doing a lot
better? Yeah I'm doing better enough that they deem I can work tomorrow morning if I can ever get
the stuff I need from my work computer set up here at the house but yeah my I had a chest
x-ray and it came out clear they should have given me the chest x-ray three weeks ago but you know
it is what it is so she thinks that the breathing problems I have left over just inflammation from
having had pneumonia. Wow so but you never did find out if it was the big one or not just because
the testing shortage right? Exactly and I probably won't get to find out until they have the antigen
test ready. Well whatever way you slice it I'm really glad to hear you're feeling a lot better
because I know that was kind of you know if you go back and listen to that show it was about three
weeks ago or so when you were first calling in and you were you were feeling sick you you really
didn't sound good so I'm really glad to hear you're you're doing a lot better really really
happy to hear it and I know a lot of folks over in our twitch chat are cheering you on as well
because of course we do tape live every Sunday night at six o'clock pacific nine o'clock eastern
at the voice of geeks network twitch.tv slash vog network right after of course the Bobby
Blackwolf show. Also joining me in studio though I want to talk about Bobby's show tonight actually
with who else is also joining me excuse me on discord not in studio we'll usually be in studio
but not tonight say hello to tech master Loki our virtual studio say hello to Loki.
I was gonna say I'm not there. Yeah in spirit or I've been in quarantine for three weeks now
where Pikachu is just starting to look like Loki I don't know what it is maybe I don't know how
are you doing Loki? It's the jaundice it must be the jaundice. Clearly how are you doing? I'm fine.
So Bobby's show tonight he had a really big night because he had Tommy Tallarico on tonight who is
the CEO of Intellivision and I don't did you hear the whole interview Loki? No I like how like the
last five minutes. Oh bummer you should have heard the whole thing because there was a point where
Bobby actually brought up some of the things we had talked about on OLR before so and I won't
repeat everything because I know Bobby's want to get that interview out there but Tommy actually
addresses some of those things about the whole like remember the the no 3d games thing although
that's not really what it is he kind of clarifies that quite a bit and then he talks about the whole
average score thing which I guess people interpreted to be a 70 score a metacritic
but it's actually like an internal type of rating like think Nintendo CL quality type of thing
but anyway it was it was a good interview Bobby and Tommy had a lot of conversation and Tommy's
great he's a great salesman pitching his product and makes a lot of good cases for the Amico and
I can say I put down the deposit on one Thursday so I'm excited to check it out. I looked at it but
I don't know I don't know if I'm gonna do that. All right well it's I can also understand who's
one of those things where you got to get your hands on the games that the games are the important
part and I thought it was interesting how he kind of said like he actually said this may not
really be or this is what I heard anyway sorry I don't want to I don't want to misattribute a quote
or anything but kind of the message I was hearing was you know if you're like a hardcore gamer this
may not really be the thing for you like that's not the thing that we're designing it for so
that's the message I heard anyway so I thought that was interesting that you know he did have
that kind of like realistic approach like he definitely knows the audience he's going for and
I think it's I think it's very interesting he makes a good case when he kind of says
your your best memories in gaming are usually when you're together in the same room you know you
think back to days of like you know playing Mario Kart or things that you would play like in the
same room those are your great gaming memories and he wants to be able to bring those back and
when was the last time you were able to play a game with your family members your parents your
you know extended family members probably Wii Sports or something like that so I thought I
thought he made some really good arguments for the direction the console is going I thought it
was really good so so props to him and also I I have no idea if Tommy's still watching you
probably turned it off by now but uh kind of an interesting little aside about Tommy and
video games live specifically uh video games live and not everybody maybe necessarily knows
I think I might have mentioned it once before on the show but video games live is actually where I
met my husband Alan for the first time we knew each other online like on a blogging site years
and years ago but it was actually due to video games live that we met face to face for the first
time there was a chance meeting we didn't know that the other was going to be there it was one
of those type of oh you're oh you're that and it kind of like things proceeded from there as they
say so I do I do have Tommy to thank for that for creating video games live because if I hadn't had
that chance meeting who knows what would happen so um pretty cool anyhow let's get into uh and I
will just say tune into Bobby's show for the rest of it it was it was a good interview and I know
he's putting that up on youtube as well as his podcast feed usually um the video content here
at vog network we kind of see that as something extra because we've been doing these podcasts for
a long time 15 years 18 years uh we've been doing podcasting a long time so the audio podcast they're
out there free as they have always been but when we made the move to twitch we thought you know
video is something extra so we're gonna put that uh with the subscribe subscription thing and most
of you have a twitch prime uh account anyway so you get one free subscription uh excuse me amazon
prime um account so you get a free twitch prime subscription every month so if you consider using
that at vog network you get access to the whole video library but because uh this is such a big
thing and and there's really important news uh and things to be seen tommy did really show off
that controller and kind of it was showing it from all angles and stuff so there is kind of a
video component to that so he's gonna put that on youtube for free so that way it's not gated
because uh we don't want to be we don't want to be absolute uh jerks here at vog network and we don't
want to put the good stuff behind the paywall we're not we're not the la times putting all the
good stuff behind the paywall anyway let's move into tonight's kickoff topic something else a
little different going on in the gaming world um obviously with all the news around us we've got
things that are being cancelled moved shifted and all that stuff left and right and uh loki
e3 kind of or lack thereof providing some uh different moving and shaking this week right
loki right i mean so it's kind of expected that a lot of stuff around e3 well e3 already being
cancelled um is being postponed or cancelled as well so to go along with e3 as um we've had in
the past few years uh bethesda won't be doing their digital event around june um so they're
working on some alternate plans as well um to go along with that though we've got ign announcing
that they're going to be doing their own digital event called the summer of gaming uh it's supposed
to be a collaboration between several different companies 2k square enix sega bandai namco amazon
google stadia twitter developer digital thq nordic and more companies and you know they're
basically going to have some sort of event that's gonna be kind of i guess showing off some games
maybe some of the footage that we would have gotten during e3 but aren't getting um no deadline
or no exact date on when that's gonna happen but i'm assuming sometime during the summer
and last but not least we've got esa talking about their plans for e3 2021 with the date being set
already from 15th through the 17th june 20 of 21 and they said it's going to be their reimagined
version of e3 whatever that's supposed to mean so i don't know but it is it is interesting they're
using the word reimagine so that's where they're kind of setting the expectations is that this is
going to be a different show when it comes back in 2021 so the cancellation you know certainly
i i think covid and and the the global crisis we have going on there i think that was going to get
e3 eventually one way or the other but um i think it definitely goes to show that some some of this
other thought about how to reinvent a show um may have come into play with that you know again i
think the pandemic would have claimed the show eventually um but it is you know a lot of people
when they pulled the plug it did seem still kind of early on um so it's just kind of interesting
that they definitely are looking at what is the show going to look like in the future um right
and then i was going to say also to kind of clarify i dig it i did find the information
about the ign event that's supposed to take place in june as well yeah and it's it doesn't
it strike you as very i don't it's it's oddly opportunistic of ign isn't it i mean i'm not
that i'm saying like they're doing anything wrong i mean it's a it's a smart business move but it
is interesting that ign is jumping on that before the esa because wasn't the esa supposed to announce
a digital event or wasn't the esa supposed to be doing their own thing i thought i don't remember
if that's i thought that was a thing or not well they kind of um it was like they said look forward
to this but they never like confirmed it's happening here it's this time it's just kind of
one of those we're figuring it out as we go along type of things right and i guess you know it could
be that they're just trying to get you know more traffic to their i mean obviously they're trying
to get more traffic to their site because they make a lot of money from these collaborations
with different companies for advertising um i mean i'm sure it's just all kind of a lot of um patty
in the back and stuff like that but i don't know we'll see how the coverage is i mean i don't really
it's been so long since i've been to ign i went there today i'm like wow their sites really
changed because it's been like months if not years since i've been to ign well but i mean
even though i say it's a little opportunistic i mean it's smart because you know clearly if they
were able to sign on the dotted line to get all these companies to commit to doing these types of
reveals um at an ign event then clearly the esa had not thought to sign them all already which is
a severe lapse in judgment on their part uh yet another in a string of bad decisions by the esa
sorry but i'm calling it like it is um so ign was able to step in there smartly and get all
those uh people to sign off and now essentially they are taking the hat of being the uh digital
e3 even though they can't call it that but that is essentially what they're doing and now ign can
basically cock block everyone else and you know they have the exclusive video will be you know
going to their site to see all that stuff although we all know that shit will get ripped and put on
youtube and what have you but you know essentially ign is going to make their site the place to go
to see all of that which you know hey digital journalism kind of needs a lot of help and that
stuff right now so again i'm not like shaming or saying it's a bad thing on ign it's it's
fucking smart but it's interesting that they were able to do it is what i'm really saying
so yeah i mean i it's not surprising that they would take the opportunity to do that but
we'll see how the coverage is i really don't care i like my information and i feel that with all
these announcements that things are getting postponed and canceled that we're not going to
hear a lot until at least you know uh gamescom and so i don't know it'd be nice to hear something
during june i mean nintendo wasn't listed as one of the companies participating obviously because
they have their own thing that they're doing so it'll be interesting to see i thought a lot of
these companies were going to be doing kind of that like you know kind of the treehouse life type
of um coverage where they're just going to stream some information or gameplay for a few days um
i don't know well i guess we'll have to wait and see what happens well yeah and it was also
interesting because um you know a lot of folks were saying the e3 and i guess maybe i'm one of
these folks e3 was kind of all digestible online anyway like you know many of us would sit here and
watch the digital press conferences online uh we would be watching the videos as they're released
online it's almost like you know you could get more out of the show sitting here watching it
online than you actually could um at the la convention center which is you know what what
broke me on e3 and why i stopped going was when i had to fight my way to get in to see this uh
demo of a new assassins creed game that was just on youtube later that night you know it was kind
of like well if i can just consume all this stuff online anyway then what am i what am i spending
all the money to come to la for well the parties were always pretty good but you know realistically
i can't spend that kind of money and time just to party you know i can party here at home
so this is you know kind of kind of interesting how this may be pushing e3 to where it was at
anyway so i'm at least encouraged to hear the e3 uh and the esa kind of gets the memo
because sometimes i worry about that and that they are going to reimagine it for 2021 i'm just
so curious what that would look like and to be quite honest i'm not sure i have the answer
um maybe it is somewhere in that hole you know we like to party we like to get together um the
people that i know that still like to go to e3 are like well i like to see all my industry people
it's the one time of year i get to see all those people so maybe e3 turns into something a little
more like twitch con but it's not twitch it's the whole industry kind of thing it's kind of that's
kind of where i see e3 kind of going not just twitch con but everything else gone i don't know
we'll see uh we'll see what develops uh in the coming weeks and months ahead uh june all things
considered is not that far off it's only what about seven eight weeks off i guess it depends
what part of june they're going to be doing so we'll see and then of course you know the the
world situation we're facing is also rapidly developing we don't necessarily know what that's
going to look like in in three or four weeks or even by the time june gets here i mean obviously
our fingers and toes are all crossed that we get on the other side of this you know thing within
the next month but i think you know we're kind of mentally preparing some of us for the fact that it
could go on excuse me a little bit longer uh and the reason why i say that is because you know
we're looking to games com maybe to deliver some of the news a little later in the summer but
maybe there won't be a games com either don't know i mean just because this thing is over
does that mean we can suddenly have conventions with thousands of people again that may not
necessarily be the best idea i don't know i'm gonna leave it to health experts and scientists
and listen to what they have to say on the whole thing so anyhow um let's move on from e3 and talk
a little bit about closer to home how was your gaming week and the types of video games that
you've been playing this week i bet i don't have to guess very much what game dark soccer has been
spending the most of her time on what are you up to i've been playing doom kidding cool that'll be
good somebody finally played doom on the cast great playing animal crossing um and i got dan
playing now too so dan lives on koholint island and uh i just i i visited a friend in australia
right before the show so i have a couple of the southern hemisphere seasonal fish right now and
well just a ribbon eel and a couple of the bugs um but the funniest thing is like when you catch the
red dragonfly it says i didn't even have to roll initiative nice and that one's my favorite um
and then um i started playing pocket camp again once i realized that there's like a code for stuff
that they're gonna keep doing codes like this if you're playing both games so i started playing
that again um and that's really about i did play a little pokemon go when i had to go to the doctor
um and i'm disappointed because um i live just far away enough from the the gym that i can't
hit it but i can hit the pokey stop in my neighbor's backyard and what i mean in my
neighbor's backyard is it's actually at this uh this uh walking path or bike path that cuts into
my neighborhood and there's a sign there and um and sometimes if my gps is being wonky i can hit
it from the corner of my backyard um but now i can just sit in my bathroom and hit the pokey stop
yeah they also doubled the distance of the gym thing so you can actually hit a gym
from twice as far away as you used to be able to um which i know i did finish a gym battle oh nice
yeah yeah sadly i'm just out of range of the closest gym to the house now but there's a second
gym in the neighborhood i got a new um portal for ingress approved in uh opr or excuse me
niantic wayfare and it made a new gym in the neighborhood on my walking so now i have two
gyms on my walk path so it's great you should do my mailbox in my neighborhood uh i is it like
painted or something special yeah oh okay it's like a well not painted but it's a it's a mailbox
it's got mail on it i'll take a look if it's just a generic mailbox those usually don't meet
criteria i probably won't go through okay yeah all right so if that's it for your gaming week
then we will go to loki all right so i did play a ton of stuff uh this week so one of the things
i did is i'm like i said i mentioned i was replacing my laptop because my old one's kind of
dying so i got a nicer laptop um that it's got like an rtx 2070 in it and you know 32 gigs of ram and
you know a nice i7 processor so i was um loading up vr games so i played a little bit of half-life
alex and that's really immersive and fun so i really enjoyed that and then i finally got
around to playing beat saber a bit so um not uh it's still you know getting used to that because
it's quite hard to play it on normal and stuff so um it was pretty fun and then of course the
big thing i did this week was convert over my uh ddr cabinet to run step mania so now i have
a set medium machine with like 2 000 songs loaded in there so i did actually play some ddr this week
and stuff can you go back to the old way if you want or is that a permanent change um it's not
a permanent change this requires you know unhooking some things and plugging stuff back in
um so yeah i could go back if i want um so it's definitely not permanent i wanted to get it like
so that i could switch between the two but i that would require some more uh hardware and wiring
stuff up but it's got everything going i mean uh the lights work and everything i bought a while
ago a lighting board for it so that i could uh use set me to control the lights um but it looks nice
um i did find out though that the tv that they replaced in there so there's an lcd tv in there
um and apparently the remote doesn't work for it so i had to disassemble the front flex or the
front like a glass that was on there in order to actually get to the uh the tv to change the
settings on it which is kind of funny in order to get it to work with um how i have the computer set
up but yeah it's been pretty cool and um i'm just trying to get everything organized right now
because it's um there's a lot of songs in there and i need to organize it so i can get it down
to a more manageable level because i just kind of dumped everything on there and there's a lot of
duplicates and stuff too so uh that's what i've really been working on so can i ask you to expand
on half-life alex a little more because you kind of mentioned that one really quick but you know
since i i think many of us don't really have vr setups what makes half-life alex kind of like
different than a traditional first-person shooter because i guess most people are probably thinking
oh it's just a first-person shooter but you're in vr like what like what do they do that makes it
like you can't do this on a monitor this is a vr game it's very immersive so like the physics
in the game is really good so you can grab pretty much anything interact with pretty much all of
the objects in the game um you can use them in very creative ways so for example um and i i
don't remember what they're called but there's these creatures that have these giant like
tentacle things that hang from the ceiling and so if you get caught by one of them you can
basically get eaten so what you're supposed to do is you can throw things at them to have
them grab those and they can walk by or you can wear like you can find um you know stuff on the
ground to use to help you out as well like so for example there's construction helmets around so you
can put a hard hat on um my kids were saying put the button there's a bucket on the ground so
they're like put it on your head and yeah again once you put a bucket on your head if you really
wanted to um you can grab markers and draw on the windows and stuff um you can you know pick up
glass bottles and smash them you can i don't know you can grab like a explosive gas canisters and
throw them at something and then fire a gun at it plus then you get gravity gloves later on so you
can start grabbing you know things out of the air you can throw stuff up and catch it it's pretty
cool um and then it's just very immersive both sound and atmosphere um it's really great it looks
like the graphics look incredible like it's just a really great looking game um so i mean i i don't
know i got to play for about like an hour or so today and it was just really fun okay cool no
thanks i i was kind of curious a little more just because you know especially you know thanks to
quarantine like you know i have a couple friends that i probably could go to their place and check
it out you know play it but i i can't so i i kind of have to live vicariously through others right
now with all this uh quarantine going on but when this is over hopefully i'll get a chance to check
it out yeah definitely and then also i um i picked up boneworks as well which is supposed to be
another really immersive vr game so i'm going to be uh looking forward to play that as well
um and then even had fun with beat saber i like turning it up because you know i'm not too like
accurate with the um following the arrows so i like putting on the mode where there are no
arrows it just hit it in any direction whatsoever and then you just put it like you know expert
and just go crazy and it's that's a lot of fun so be sure to pick up autica too because that's a
really good music game as well all right i'll check that yep it's harmonix's uh game and it's
kind of like uh imagine if elite beat agents was a vr game it's easy simple simplest way i could put
it so all right cool all right well uh let's talk about my gaming week okay so last week i mentioned
i was going to check this game out and dark soccer this game is up your alley you really
have to check this game out okay this game this game is called demon's tilt with the uh headline
or with the subheading occult pinball action and it's basically yeah it's a it's it's basically
somebody took like their love of devil's crush and alien crush and like made a new crush table that's
basically what this is they made satan crush and that's what this game is basically uh it's okay
i'm getting it like right now it's like if heavy metal the movie was a pinball table which maybe
it was i don't know but it was i like there is so much going on in the game i couldn't tell you what
the fuck is happening but it's really pretty and it's one of the it's it's one of those pinball
games just like alien crush or devil crush where there's like you start on the middle table and
you can fall to the lower table or you go all the way up to the upper table like it's one of those
things there's the multi-levels like what was that like rollerball on the nes or something was like
the first game i remember doing something like that but it has those whole like different levels
um so i played it on xbox game pass but i believe it is on windows and mac if i'm not mistaken and
uh nintendo switch so dark sakura has no shortage yeah it's on steam but i think i'll probably get
it on switch that's pretty cool yeah so uh i i feel like this game's up your alley so i would
feel horrible if i didn't recommend it to you so i spent a good time some good time playing this game
and just watching all the pretty stuff and trying to get achievements and yeah it was pretty cool
so uh i look forward to your review next week dark sakura uh because you're the pinball queen
uh but i enjoyed it i enjoyed it and that was definitely my review will be i played animal
crossing was at some point you're gonna need a break from animal crossing at some point
anyway uh so i played that and uh i've been playing the usual stuff too i found sc14 orna
diablo uh but i played some other new well okay i play one other new game i play one old game too
so because you know i'm stuck at home i've definitely been making use out of my xbox game
pass i also played here's a jamie game sort of king of fighters 98 how random is that is on game
pass hell yeah so i was like i'm gonna play this why not oh i can put together my dream team of
kim kapwan and my and uh andy bogart all in the team and uh yeah there's uh you know it's it's
ba it's the neo geo game but it's when they did it for the xbox 360 because it's uh that
compatibility version but i thought it was like random and cool that that was on xbox game pass
so uh there was that but then the other game that i spent a bit of time playing uh was one of those
games where people have been telling me for like years you need to play this game and i don't know
why i resisted i guess maybe like watching the early trailers and stuff i was like i don't really
know if that's for me or i didn't like i had the first game on 360 and i don't really remember
playing a lot of it and now that i've played a good like 90 minutes or so of it i i fear i
may have made the same mistake that i made with the mass effect series the first time i played it
because and if you don't know what i'm talking about the first time i played mass effect
i thought i was like i don't get it but then i went back years later and played it and i was like
i am obsessed.com and i played the entire trilogy so what game was it that i finally played this
week near automata oh my god it's so fun it's like i i'm like oh it's so good like uh i played
through like that whole like intro level the only like frustrating thing was that you can't save in
that whole opening like you go through like an hour long opening and you can't freaking save
at all that was the only annoying thing but otherwise i i kind of didn't realize it's like
okay it's like an actiony kind of game like you're playing something like i don't know like maybe
like bayonetta i mean another platinum game i guess um but you're kind of playing a shooter game
at the same time it depends what difficulty level you're playing on if you play on bobby blackwolf
mode or easy mode then the shooter stuff i think is i i'm playing on normal but i believe i read
that on the easy mode the shooter stuff is kind of all done for you so you can just focus on button
mashing the um melee combat stuff but i'm playing on normal mode where you kind of have to do both
at once and it's it's really confusing at first but it's like really really fun so um yeah it's
and they just put it on game pass this past week so that's why i finally jumped in i was like oh
i should just play this already um hey rob yeah what if i can interject real quick demons till
just 13.99 on switch right now oh that's not bad that's not bad i mean i pay for xbox game pass
so it's free but not really free because i'm paying for xbox game pass so it's you know that
whole thing but if you have 20 on steam oh oh so it's a little cheaper on switch well that's good
cool um so yeah near i i definitely want to go back and play more so i can get further into the
game and tell you if there's like even more about it that i like um because now i feel like i kind
of hit like i feel like i played through all the prologue stuff and i was doing some of the stuff
around the ship and then i kind of like ran out of time um but i want to go back and do more and
see if like the later levels are as fun as that first one was um and i think finally like because
they have that raid in final fantasy 14 uh it has a really you know it's a really cool ambience and
the music in final fantasy 14 is incredible and like i didn't really realize they kind of lifted
stuff directly from the game i mean it's a little different but like the game's soundtrack is fucking
great like it's oh it's good so yeah uh my bad you all told me for a long time i needed to play it
finally got around to it you all were right what can i say finally played it so uh and i will be
playing more of it later on so it's near automata finally all these years later so playing the xbox
version which i guess is the i don't know if it's the definitive edition but it's like the most
recent one they put out so it has like all the extra stuff in it i think so playing that one uh
all right so there it is that's my gaming week so um don't really have a lot else to say here at the
top of the show i think we ought to just jump right into some gaming news so loki what's going
on in the gaming world this week all right so let's talk about rumors and speculation of course
um so there is the whole anniversary of mario coming up here pretty soon the 35 year anniversary
and the rumor is that nintendo is playing on remastering some of the 3d mario games to put
into a collection kind of like a new um mario all-stars type game so the thought is that there's
going to be remasters of the mario 64 the galaxy games uh sunshine that type of stuff as long as
um as well as there's going to be some information about super nintendo world and of course the
upcoming animated super mario movie that's being worked on um as well so apparently the thought
that the reveal is supposed to happen around e3 um but now it's gonna be rolled into maybe a
different trade show or maybe part of this digital event they're gonna do and usually you know i'm
i'm iffy on bringing up rumors here on the program it's obviously not the first time we've done it
but this is one of those rumors that's kind of coming from multiple places right like it's it's
not just like my uncle who works at nintendo told me this is happening like this is coming from
places that are right in historically and it's like several outlets are kind of cross-verifying
this information so it's it's a high pro on the plausibility scale it's pretty high right
um i think it's pretty reasonable that they would do something like this it seems like easy enough
to remaster some of these older games especially since they've kind of have remastered like some
of the galaxy games and stuff because they were running them on um the nvidia shield in china oh
that's right no you're right they did make those games on on the shield so so technically i mean
that's pretty i mean it's shield hardware is pretty similar to the nintendo switch already
so the work's been kind of already done um so i mean it's pretty plausible it's gonna happen in
more announcements regarding super nintendo world i mean that makes sense since they're already
working on it and we already know that the mario movie is coming it would be cool if we had a
trailer or something uh but i don't think i don't remember when that slated to come out that might
be 2021 or 2022 uh but yeah it'd be interesting to hear something about it i believe the mario
movie was supposed to be like holiday 2021 or something like that so you know maybe a trailer
or first look would make a lot of sense so we kind of get the idea like what does it look like is it
like a cartoon or is it like a and it's probably not it's probably gonna look like despicable me
that type of animation yeah oh i don't think i mean well not like you know what i mean like that
style of like pixar-ish type of art yeah it's not like the whole thing is gonna look like despicable
me but you know it's that same studio so it's that type of art yeah yeah um illumination is
like great stuff so i wouldn't be any surprise if it's gonna be great well and the mario uh world
was supposed to open in japan in time for the tokyo olympics and i don't know if they had
ended up ultimately pushing the opening back a little bit or if it was going to make it but we
saw some of those construction pictures out there it would have made a lot of sense that like early
june would have been a great time frame to get a first look at the mario park if it was going to
open soon for the tokyo olympics obviously the global pandemic has fucked up all of these
timelines so nothing is certain anymore but i mean it's it would seem like early june would
have been about the right time to hear more about the park and probably those sorts of things were
already in motion as far as getting the footage concept putting that stuff together before the
pandemic really hit so we could still still see some of that come out in june it just might be
the timetable of when this actually opens could really be up in the air
i suppose yeah i mean it'd be interesting to see uh i would like some more details of what's going
to be at the park because i'm very excited to go see that yeah i remember seeing some of the the
video shots that they had showing like those moving platforms and stuff um i mean it's looking
very much like their concept that they had in there so i'm very curious to see what kind of
rides and everything because i mean honestly once that stuff opens up especially over here in the
united states i'm down to go to go vacation there so we'll have to see uh sg100 matt with an
excellent point in chat saying theme parks are in big trouble so it's really up in the air yeah i
mean we don't know what it's going to look like on the other side of this you know we don't know
if theme parks are going to be able to reopen right away and i suppose just a lot of that
really depends on the science behind this thing you know can they test to see if people have it
really fast you know can they do more things to slow the spread down and so forth i mean a lot of
these factors are going to dictate if theme parks can open up really fast or not um because i i mean
again i am not a scientist or a doctor but i could see a situation where like small businesses open
up again and you can still kind of have small gatherings but they frown on the big stuff for a
few more months i mean again i have you that's just me you know being a fortune teller i have
no idea to listen to the people that are doctors and scientists and what they have to say but i
could just kind of see that that's like a logical progression that this sorts of thing is like
easier to track in smaller groups than it would be you know thousands of people at a theme park
type of thing so i don't know anyway um yeah and phoenix uh in chat is asking is it going to end
up being seasonal is another important question that's a hugely important question and you know
can we develop uh you know again the the rapid testing can we develop an immunity can we develop
a vaccine like we can do for the flu you know so much is dependent although all those things we
don't have an answer for yet but we know the world is working on it um and from a technical angle
you know that folding at home that we talked about a few weeks ago has never seen the type of action
that has been seen because everybody wants to help do something about all the bitcoin miners
are taking their resources and moving them more appropriately to be working on um this instead
maybe that's why cooking mama on the switch is it's actually where you know i'm just okay that's
that's a whole other thing i wasn't going to bring up because we don't know what the hell's going on
cooking mom on the switch but i'm sure you've seen some of the rumors going on out there so yeah
anyway but anyway uh so we just don't know there's still a lot of things that are going to find out
in the weeks and weeks and weeks ahead so uh we will see uh anyway going back to the
mario story for a minute uh what about these mario games that they're saying could be part
of the uh remaster i i think the mario sunshine and mario galaxy games really do seem like good
candidates to come back because especially mario sunshine i think was really under appreciated the
first time when it was out on the gamecube but i feel like it was one of those things like
a lot of people that played it still really loved it for its unique kind of water mechanic
and then you know bringing back mario 64 is kind of just like that sure thing you know especially
if they if they kind of up res it and make it look even better if they're gonna like truly remaster
it uh i think that has the potential to do very well because you know that's a lot of people's
all-time favorite mario game what do you think about specifically the games that they're choosing
loki or dark soccer well i don't think they've really announced yet what games they're gonna
choose i mean it's all kind of speculated right now um i don't know i it's been a while since i
played galaxy i would love to go back to play those because they were apparently really great
games which i had not you know wish i'd actually finished them i hear also that the rumor is
supposed to be that they're going to be announcing a new paper mario game and honestly i mean i
haven't been able to get into a lot of paper mario games but super paper mario that was on the wii
was fantastic and i love that yeah the wii one was really good how about how about super mario
rpg how about that although essentially i think that's kind of what paper mario is
it's kind of like well we can't make mario rpg anymore because that's the square enix thing but
hey anything is possible in this crazy world you never know i'm gonna cross my fingers i'm
personally looking for famicom grand prix f1 race i mean just saying it was only out on the
disk system and you know hey mario racing another car it isn't you know mario kart you never know
dreams really do come true sometimes you never know i'm rooting for mario is missing hell yeah
let's bring entertainment back all right anyway uh let's move on and talk about um you know this
this news is one of those like it's not surprising although it still kind of sucks but you kind of
saw it coming and that is that the last of us part two has been delayed again with no new release
date set we don't know when it's coming out it's like gaga's album it's been put on hold until
she's ready until we know when this whole thing is going to be behind us and so on so i'm sure
that news does disappoint people but i are y'all really surprised so yeah the game was going to be
coming out on may 29th but uh they did confirm via a tweet um sie has made the difficult decision to
delay the launch of the last of us part two and actually marvel's iron man vr until further notice
logistically the global crisis is preventing us from providing the launch experience our players
deserve currently there are no other delays to report but we'll keep you updated and i'm sure
a lot of people are wondering well why don't they just do a digital release and da da da da
and i think the reality is those day one sales are so important that i think they want to make
sure they're engaging not just digital but they are engaging the people that want to get retail
or physical or the people whose habits are more i want to go to target i want to go to game stop
i want to go to wherever it is that i get games um to to buy this game in a physical condition
because maybe i live in a part of the country where the internet isn't as strong so i can't
exactly download a 70 gigabyte game or whatever this thing chalks in as and so those day one and
those launch number figures are so important where it's like whereas sony could do an all digital
launch is it in their best business sense to really do that and i think the reality is no
it's not and that's why they're putting it on hold until they can really do a strong worldwide launch
i mean kind of look what's happening at the final fantasy 7 remake fantasy 7 remake kind of came in
like it went gold at a really weird time where it was like okay they've hit the ground running on
getting the distribution going and then the pandemic happens because you know these things
don't just ship from the factory the night before this is a a couple months long process to get from
the gold master of the game to what you see out there and now the final fantasy 7 remake thing is
kind of messy i suppose although certainly not square i feel weird saying messy because it's
certainly not square enix's fault or sony's fault or anybody's fault it's just well some copies got
there early and they don't give a shit anymore because of what's going on some copies are going
to be there late and i got my email from amazon saying mine is coming late and although i'm a
little bit like ah bummer i'm like you know what though i completely understand getting
things out like gloves masks groceries and things that people actually need right now
is more important than final fantasy 7 remake and if it i'm really that bent up about it
then i guess i could do digital so i'm not like you know that bent out of shape about it but
the final fantasy 7 if you were bent out of shape about it you need to evaluate your priorities
exactly exactly so i'm like you know whatever you know if i have to wait a couple more days
whatever uh it's i'll probably still be on house arrest through the month of april anyway so i'll
get a chance to play it uh plenty well in fact actually yes we all know we're going to be here
till at least may 3rd for uh it was was that the governor's thing was may 3rd or was that just the
bay area and where the bay area goes sacramento quickly follows regardless as a matter we know
we're going to be here till may so um you know if it's a couple days late whatever i'll still
have plenty of time to play it um i just don't think that sony wants to launch these games
and have it be as all over the place they want this to still be a gaming event and maybe
something when people aren't focusing on all these other more important things and can go back to oh
i'm just doing a game it's a fun silly thing and maybe it also may just be viewed in poor taste
right now to be doing a zombie related game i don't know i mean that that could certainly be
weighing to it as well i don't i don't think that's a big deal but it could be for some people i don't
know so um phoenix in chat says i'm curious about whether the delay is covid related or quality
related either way a good idea i really do think it's covid related as as its core and probably
because the quality can't really be finished like i don't know about you guys but like i'm working
from home right now and i and i'm very fortunate to be able to do that i'm very very fortunate and
very thankful that my position is something that can do that but it is a slower process
and that's nothing to do with you know i i still am a good little worker bee but it's that you know
sometimes the connection to the server is slower uh things working on a laptop is just not as fancy
as when i'm working on my dual monitor setup back at the office there's just things about it that
are inherently slower and the reason why i say that is that you've got all these sony employees
and so forth that are also working from home right now and so probably the quality process
is moving slower you know just and even just a little bit can kind of back up the whole system
if you know what i mean so there is that to be uh uh put in perspective um and phoenix and chat
also says rob what do you think about them charging full price for a quarter of a game
um it's not going to be a quarter of a game for i'm assuming that's about fall 97 remake
it's not a quarter of a game from what i understand and apparently a new trailer released
this week really shows that they are doing some things that should not have been part of the mid
gar story so they're clearly and i i've read one thing i hear there's other spoilers i'm trying to
keep myself pure on it i will probably get spoiled because people are dicks on twitter
but i'm gonna try to go in it as pure as i can um and i know i was super surprised by seeing that
i'm glad you uh cut out there all right so anyway yeah um so i i don't think it's really going to be
a quarter of the game like it's not and even if you play the demo again i i kind of use that as
my there's things in that demo that weren't in the original game so they're they're whatever
what i was trying to say as really surprised in that latest trailer that you know erith decided
to put on the impenetrable vest that's you know no blade can pierce through so i'm really really
curious to see how this is going to change this yes somebody gifted her a bulletproof vest for
no particular reason and we'll see how that changes thing i'm a time traveler for the future
here take this anyway and don't go to 2020 all right anyway uh so there those games have been
delayed so we will hear when they get rescheduled when sony is ready to unveil it i would anticipate
don't expect to hear a new date until people are back at work when people are back at work across
the country then you'll hear a new date but not before so moving on dark sakura
i forgot where i had myself muted so um you know we had talked about amazon's whole gaming deal
before and it looks like they've actually released some information about some titles that are going
to be coming out their first original big budget stuff coming out in may one of them is a sci-fi
third-person shooter called crucible um been in development for a while i mean the description
is pretty you know out there you know very vague um you it's survival and control fighting with
fellow competitors it doesn't really so it looks like it's a team versus game so you know kind of
maybe overwatch-ish from what it sounds like um or like you know fortnite something like that
and it's supposed to be uh released in uh in may and then another one in may is an mmo called new
world that has been described as a tolkanesque reimagining of 17th century british america
um so basically it's you know colonialism and fantasy i guess kind of weird um i don't know
that i'm too happy about that as a theme because i mean well we all know how great colonialism
worked for native populations so just saying kind of not very well of them to do that as a theme
let's see what they let's see where it goes like you know we don't we don't know what the story
really looks like yet it better be void of other humans for me to enjoy it yeah well if they're
going to bring in like magic and fire and things like that then clearly it's not set in a realistic
world anyway so which is probably for the best um well i mean as long as it i don't know i'm
uncomfortable with the with the concept of a game that requires overtaking you know an indigenous
population but that's me um anyway yeah there there's us oh another uh cloud-based uh gaming
service that amazon is developing called project tempo and working um on titles that twitch
broadcasters can play with viewers in real time so uh we'll see what that is i guess it's supposed
to compete with stadia oh that could be interesting i mean the cloud cloud yeah
so who knows all right well we'll we'll see i guess uh amazon will still uh bring uh pull back
the curtain on this a little bit uh in the next month uh in may they can stop being shitty with
the rest of their practices all right let's move on to uh a game i think we've all confessed that
we've been playing recently right logi um correct so pokemon go is making some changes to uh their
game to you know kind of address the having to stay at home and quarantined situations so of
course you know they've done this in other games like uh minecraft earth had a thing where you can
actually bring some of those adventures to yourself now they're going to be doing something similar
where you can take on raid battles um from the comfort of your own home with friends so that's
pretty cool they'll be able to raid it from home um no word exactly when that's supposed to go into
effect 100 but i'd imagine pretty soon so yeah that's got to be a huge change they're making to
the back end of it so that's uh it's kind of surprising they're going to go that far with it
so it's uh interesting for sure and you know um uh there are other games i i have not played
harry potter in quite some time so i couldn't tell you what's going on in that game um but i
have still been playing ingress a little bit and it's been interesting to see kind of the changes
they've been making there where um they really emphasize recharging which is something you can
do from your couch they bumped it up so you get like six times the ap or experience if you will
from like recharging that you used to get um so that's kind of interesting and then you're uh
streak badge for like there's like a badge for oh you hacked uh portals 60 days in a row or
whatever you can get all that from recharging now so it's interesting how they've kind of made that
the emphasis um lately but i've still been going out to ingress like once in a great while like
last saturday i went to a cemetery because there's a ton of portals there and it's a really easy place
to be socially distant from other people uh and just kind of you know messed around in ingress and
it's it was a nice little like take my mind off everything else for a little while type of thing
so oh yeah and as that brings up they brought a new uh uh double boost item as well that's right
i forgot about that they uh that is out as well so you can get some free ones in the shop right now
uh phoenix says are all the parks closed up there rob i know they closed them in oregon
um like city parks and like parks in the neighborhood no but i think like major one i
don't even think they've closed the river parks as far as i know because you know sacramento where
we're based is the river city as far as i know they haven't shut that stuff down yet i think
they've kind of said we're keeping our eye on it and everybody's been pretty well behaved so far so
we're not going to shut it down yet um but i think if you try to go to any state parks and certainly
like if i were to go to the coast uh that's closed down and i know they put out an advisory that said
don't go to south lake tahoe like the people up there were like don't come here stay home you
know so they're those types of more like touristy park things i think they are trying to discourage
people from going to so but um i do know even at the parks around here the play structures
they've put a bunch of caution tape around or they've like roped it off so that kids can't play
on them um because they don't want the surface you know um especially because most kids don't
exhibit systems symptoms yes i know there are certainly some very sad exceptions we've heard
about in the news most kids don't exhibit systems so they don't want them all over the play
structure kind of like spreading it from family to family that way which seems like a smart thing to
do so yeah or as that says in chat cootie factories pretty much so yeah i did see that they did
surround those because and from what i've seen too even just like going to the park just to kind of
walk around or whatever um there's like tons of kids still playing on the parks and stuff
so they they they wrap those all up now with caution tape so that it prevents people from
doing that yep and they did a similar thing in this neighborhood as well so not surprised
yeah well anyhow um just to my next story was kind of about the twitch gaming thing which i
didn't realize was going to be part of what dark soccer had already hit on but there's a little
extra detail in this to talk about those games that are being um developed for twitch because
right now most things as a viewer you're acting a little bit more passively like when somebody's
playing marbles on stream you're not really like in there playing the game with them and then
i also kind of have heard jackbox party pack using that example but i don't know i feel like
a jackbox party pack you kind of are in there playing the game with somebody else i mean maybe
the massively ones like you're just in the audience but i would say i know a lot of people
that are using jackbox party pack like i feel like that game is doing more business and more success
than anything else i know in gaming right now because a lot of like non-gamers are picking it
up and doing like zoom parties like my speaking oregon my cousins live up in oregon and um they
are doing they were doing a jackbox party pack thing on zoom the other night and i never i was
like you guys don't really play video games but that was the thing they were doing to keep in
touch with friends so uh that's uh you know obviously been a huge thing anyhow though um
amazon did mention in an interview with the new york times that they are developing games
that streamers and viewers will play together in real time which is interesting because twitch has
always taken a lot of shit about that lag although if you are which i actually don't
think is a big deal at all but then again we come from an era of shoutcast where there was
always a lag anyway so i'm used to it um but and i believe if you are a um partner you have and i
may be wrong and maybe bleeding some things with mixer but i believe you have access to like a very
fast uh bandwidth type of thing where the lag is lessened but if there's a new excuse me sorry
cough um i believe there's a new um um i lost my train of thought there's a new um technology
there yeah and bobby says in chat the lag is now only like three or four seconds oh affiliates get
low latency mode as well we actually have it turned on with vog oh i didn't even realize i
thought there was still a bit of the delay but even a three or four second delay you can't play
games on you can't live like an action game you play jackbox you can't really play like an action
game so hopefully uh you know with this cloud gaming and some of these other things that we're
hearing about that are you know because google stadia one thing that it does do very impressively
and when i've talked about google stadia i've mentioned it it does respond very well it is like
you're playing a youtube live so if they're kind of able to have some of that same technology when
it comes to playing with other people on twitch that could be very interesting um they are saying
games should be available throughout the summer it's not like this will be the first time that
twitch has had their own games uh twitch sings was a thing although obviously or is a thing
although obviously uh that's a little different because that's not something that viewers
play with the streamer all the time and so forth um so yeah they're saying they're going to keep
viewers engaged and interested enough to keep coming back and supposedly the thing that twitch
wants to have an edge over their competition mixer and youtube and so forth so we'll see where that
goes uh very interested to see what kind of games and so forth they come up with on that all right
let's move on dark sakura so um i i i'm going to go ahead and preface this story saying that it's
focusing a little bit too much on violent games when they're talking about addiction so i'm just
going to dive right into it um so there is a study published called computers in human behavior
that suggesting that playing violent video games in particular can impair anger detection and it
also will enhance a feeling of fighting abilities to make you overconfident in your response to how
you would uh think you could perform in a fight basically um and they're they're talking about
this bias that violent video games increases aggression and ultra social information processing
so they're going from that very flawed standpoint um but they're going a little bit more also into
pathological gaming but they're saying specifically that violent video games are leading to
pathological gaming which again is pretty flawed in general it's by uh thomas f denson who's a
psychology professor at the university of new south wales um where we've seen in other ways
that pathological gaming is like with any addiction it can be any kind of video game
um you know and it's it's defined as pathological gaming this is a quote occurs when people
prioritize playing violent video games he's saying violent i think it's others over facets other
facets of life even when doing so causes impairments relationships academic pursuits worker
mental health um but they did show a correlation and it's he did specify this as it's not perfectly
replicated but the general pattern shows that the violent video games in particular
um impair anger recognition and increase the self-perceived fighting ability and it also
is supposed he said it also lowers the perception of as and this is a quote again other men's
toughness um it was uh three experiments done with 868 participants are randomly assigned to
play either violent or non-violent games and then completing various assessments of social
cognition and threat perception so the first two they played the game for 15 minutes um on an xbox
360 connect i don't know what connect has to do with it because that's not really supported um
the third experiment um played internet browser games for five minutes and so with the non-violent
versus the violent the um the violent ones tended to be worse at recognizing an angry facial
expression and uh were less willing to back out of a hypothetical physical confrontation
um and i thought that they'd be able to take take whoever it was in a fight um i again the the the
experiment to me just sounds very flawed i went you know i wonder if they did the same thing
um you know with say watching a movie or something like that you know
again i think that this one went into the the research with a bias um and i'll go ahead and
just read this last quote from uh from the the paper this research extends to some other work
that we've done on why violent video games are so alluring in that study we found that people who
played a lot of violent video games also rated themselves as more of a good catch to members of
the opposite sex this is also running the gender binary which pisses me off and they also reported
a greater interest in sex um and it also says although those data record uh were correlational
they are consistent with our new findings that playing via video games may give people a boost in
confidence in both their mating and fighting abilities again flawed yeah well and it's the
fact that they used xbox 360 connect for one i can't think of what violent game unless it must
be one of those launch titles like the i i don't know there's got to be like some some stuff i'm
not thinking of in the moment like early but there wasn't a lot of like violent violent stuff on
xbox 360 connect and plus the huge flaw with that is that you're getting your physic if you're
playing connects you're getting your physicality up you're getting your heart rate up you're
getting your motion going versus an internet browser game where you're sitting there clicking
the mouse like that yeah why why aren't they considering the physical the heightened physical
senses that's i haven't read the whole study so i mean there could be possibly more in the study
but the the fact that this is number one focusing on a a gender binary you know which again is flawed
because that's not how people you know really work um there's also you know so many other factors to
consider like you were saying even just the physicality of using a connect game where what
happens if they're playing like a cutesy fighting game you know or say that they're watching a a
violent film or a scary film or say that they have them play a survival horror game you know
where where's the difference in there you know again flawed if we're gonna have this type of
research going then gamers with psychology degrees need to be on the freaking panel
or the fact that they're just being forced to play connect game might make them pretty angry
no that ain't me angry well no not if i was playing um dan central i'd be happy with that
because i missed that game but that game wasn't violent last i remembered maybe there maybe
there's a secret version i don't know about but yeah it's just someone's just really bad at it
i think i think you kind of hit your this sounds like it was a loaded thing and that's why you know
and again you know in full disclosure we're all saying we haven't really read it the finer details
but in reading this summary i think none of us want to because it just sounds like you you
really kind of misfired on a lot of different components of this like you go back to the
drawing board and start over number one you know get get some gamer experts on the panel get people
that you know no thing or two about games number two uh xbox 360 connect is not even a modern thing
anymore so modernize it up a little bit do some comparing with other forms of art i think you
made a good point when you said cutesy fighting games because you highlighted one it's the classic
game of the week well it wasn't a it was kind of a weird you know what i mean but it wasn't it wasn't
violent really you know all things are said and done you know there's some different controls here
that they're not even looking at that i think really kind of just like no this was ran to get
a certain result i don't know anyway um so bobby says fighter within fighter within is a oh god i do
remember that fighter within is a connect only fighting game that brings us motion fighting
where you'll be flailing your arms legs and doing other silly moves and hopes not only to beat up
your opponent but that the game will register what you're trying to accomplish by waving said
lips about so what about um they used a fighting game nobody's played crap now i can't think of the
of the name uh uh eternal champions with an activator well obviously well okay but just
looking at an activator makes me violent i'm just saying all right anyway so i think the study has
some problems an adventurous game as well too i don't know why they just didn't do that one that's
like a better option i know just play mortal combat 11 for god's sake if you want to test a
violent game use one of the most violent ones of all but you know it's it's more modern and it's
not you get you can sit there with a controller you're not getting your body and your heart rate
up and all that as well like i that that is the most flawed thing like and i'm no scientist or
it but i'm like even an idiot can tell you in one scenario you're also you're not really comparing
just this to this because the heart rate's going up the physicalness is going up it's it all this
other stuff is is is heightened and so you're not really like it's not you're supposed to have a
control because the control isolates the one thing you're trying to review and that's not
what's happening here at all so anyway just my thoughts on it anyway um let's move on
and talk about oh something else that might make you want to fight i don't know loki
all right well um yes so unfortunately we got news from um gearbox about some gearbox employees
about some um royalty checks that weren't going to be as high as they'd expected so
what i've been typical of gearbox employees is that they aren't paid as high as some of the
industry um employees in that same position but the way they offset it is they're paid i guess
a 60 40 royalty split between the company and the employees themselves so they get 40 percent of
that um what has happened or at least been revealed is that because of the fact the
development costs on borderline 3 despite the game being incredibly successful were high because you
know the game took long to develop and also the conversion from unreal 3 to unreal 4 it cost 95
million to develop the game and apparently over 100 million to develop the dlc for that and because
of that the resulting checks that they were supposed to receive which these are supposed
to be much higher than they were previously um aren't the case anymore so it seems that
with this happening they're still being underpaid in general across the board now i'm not sure that's
going to increase as time goes on i'm not sure the frequency is of these royalty checks but it
still sucks that they're in that position in the first place especially with um coming out of the
lawsuit that um they have as well for uh gearbox and everything with randy pitchford it was revealed
that he took a 12 million dollar bonus in 2016 um granted that would have been from the 60 percent
that the company gets not the 40 percent but in fact that he takes 12 million dollar bonus
when they're getting undercut kind of sucks hold up hold up that guy loki that guy point i'm
pointing at the poster in the studio that guy yes yes the guy that signed that poster maybe i'm just
gonna take that i think i'm gonna take this down for a little while i'm just gonna take it down
for a little while all right so anyways yeah so apparently yeah he took his bonus and of course
they're all getting underpaid um and then he had some kind words to tell his uh developers if they
were unhappy with it basically saying that hey if you're not happy with the royalty system you're
welcome to quit so um yeah that's unfortunate but um apparently they've been gearbox has been
looking to go public at some point so it'd be interesting to see how that plays in the things
but um it's not a good look and especially with a lot of controversy surrounding randy uh pitchford
even before the game came out uh it's just it's not not a good look for them no it's not a good
look when you're taking 12 million dollars and then telling everybody else to go without that's
that's really really not a good look so uh i think we're gonna retire randy from the studio
for a little while i think that would be the i think that would be the best idea uh esta
200 mountain chat says shame on gearbox for this then again they did promise these six figure
royalties in writing when they signed on if so then they have a case well and it's just it's
just tacky when the person at the top is getting the most money and the people on the bottom are
getting no i mean it would be one thing if it was like i'm taking the pay cut too or i am taking
some of this money as as you've seen some like like guy fieri with all the shit this he's taken
over the years hey at least he's kind of like taking some of his own money and trying to like
put that back into the frontline restaurant workers and all that stuff like it would be
a little bit of a different story if something like that was going on but unfortunately it does
not appear to be so anyhow all right well thank you for sharing with that us with uh thank you
for sharing that with us nonetheless um maybe do you think it would have made more if they hadn't
done that whole exclusive to epic thing like where where's the payola from that going i think
it's fine i mean because if anything that would have probably been less because i think they got
some sort of discounts for using a reel on their own platform um i just think that it you know it's
the cost of making the game but i still think they should take care of their employees as well
uh it just unfortunately they've had a lot of flops lately with you know both aliens,
clone and lorraine's and uh their looters i can't remember the other game that they had
so they had battleborn was their other their hero shooter that didn't really take off um
i just think yeah it kind of sucks that this is what happened but i'm hoping that maybe
with future success you know with the game that maybe they'll get paid better but i guess you know
you're in that position now where um you know maybe if opportunities arise you know in the
future or maybe they don't stay at the company very long but unfortunately i think a lot of
times in this industry that they don't really have the luxury of being able to choose going
choose to go to other companies because it seems like everybody is treating their employees poorly
in one way or the other well and right now things are kind of stuck you know like now is not the
time i think a lot of people want you know with everything that's going on in the world it's not
a great time i'm not saying you can't or you know so forth and um you know certainly in other
industry i'm talking about specifically about like gaming and tech types of things i think most
people are trying to like stay where they're at type of thing i don't think there's a lot of moving
and shaking going on in that regard so i mean yeah but after that who knows and i think there
are a lot of tech companies people are really happy to work for like i have some friends in
the industry and i i don't want to name it because i don't have permission to even though it's a good
thing it's just a tacky thing to do because i want my friends to be able to trust that i can
separate personal life from the show um but i have friends that work in gaming that absolutely love
where they're at and love their companies um and you know uh wouldn't think to you know but but i
i'm not hearing these types of stories about those companies either you know what i mean
true that that's awesome yeah definitely true and and i think you know different with even
leading up to the release of warlands 3 it was just always about randy pitchford doing weird
things whether it's leaving a jump drive in a strip club or something like it was like a jump
drive with like pornography on it and company you know personal company information it's just or you
know punching you know his what was it like getting into a fight with one of his colleagues or
just getting into a lawsuit it's just ridiculous all the stuff before the game came out all right
well let's move on and try to get to um some more hopeful news here before we get to the
classic game or pinball game of the month uh and that is a story about another humble bundle that's
out and i know you know humble bundle kind of became its own store so i think the news
the notoriety about different like charity bundles and humble bundles i think we haven't heard as much
of that uh in like uh the at the top of gaming like remember when these guys first started like
every bundle they did um would be a notable thing and that kind of died off a little bit when humble
kind of started you know becoming their own store in their own company and so forth but this one
is a pretty big one that's getting news headlines again and i think you'll understand why
it's the covet 19 humble bundle and it's it's a really pretty impressive bundle that they put
together there uh they're saying it is a thousand dollars worth of games and comics that they are
putting together for just thirty dollars or more but the 30 is the minimum to get everything
but if you want to contribute more you certainly can and all of the money is going to different
coronavirus outbreak organizations um and again you can kind of um mix and match how what charities
you want to support out of the four uh and so forth which um oh i don't have the names of the
charities right in front of me uh i'm loading that up right now let me mention some of the
games though that are in the bundle into the breach the witness super hot broken age undertale
psycho not psych psychonauts excuse me um and uh yeah so there's there's a lot of you know and
again these are indie titles that were probably big in the last like three four years but still
i mean this is a great collection of things you might have missed and it's pretty hard to say like
oh these games should have been better when it's going for a good cause because it's really about
the cause it's not about um you know all the games that you're getting so the charities are direct
relief international rescue committee doctors without borders and partners in health so um
i just when i donated i just split my money evenly between them all but some people might um you know
kind of mix and match a little bit um another one that's very interesting uh that's in there
music maker edm edition because that was uh another like utility file that i picked up and
i was interested in that one so and some of them are run it starting to run a little low if you
want zombotron uh they're down to less than 25 000 keys on that so um something to consider there
anyhow at least it's for a good cause and it's nice to see the gaming world come together
and uh sell their old games again for good causes so yeah i picked it up as well i just want to make
sure i didn't most of the keys i did have quite a few there's a lot of games that i own that i
didn't realize i was like oh yeah it's like you already have this i'm like i do yeah i had a few
of them like a win uh pac-man championship edition 2 is in there i was like oh uh i love i i already
have that game on switch and everything so i'm like oh i'll get that on sale and i was like oh
i guess i already had this on steam and i forgot but i still i bought it anyway just because i want
to support the cause you know and uh i i think uh there's there's enough stuff in there that'll
keep me busy uh the music maker thing too was kind of new for me so i was like oh i'll check
that out i want to i want to look at that so yeah really fun yeah for sure all right well let's take
a trip back down memory lane we're going to revisit some simpler times uh and dark soccer
likes to step into the gaming vault every week and pick a game that she thinks hey you guys should
check this out but in a yearly an annual twist once a month she does something a little different
and this time uh in the year 2020 she's highlighting classic pinball tables of i think
the late 80s and early 90s so uh dark and dark sakura what did you pick for the classic pinball
table of the month another one that i own um i picked black rose which is another of my favorite
awesome so black sorry the twitch uh twitch video coming in a moment here sorry guys i made a boo boo
on my end okay sorry go ahead and talk though we'll get the video up here shortly all right
well um black rose is a lady pirate themed game um it was designed by john trudeau and uh brian eddie
and it was produced by uh midway as bally and so um its slogan is this game is loaded and so uh
you use uh you know uh basically you're doing a pirate fight um so uh it uh actually had um
for uh the uk release there was supposed to be some x-rated artwork for the back glass
um but it was never produced and they also considered using black pinballs
as cannonballs but they abandoned that idea um so the game uh was manufactured in july of 1992
as i said by uh midway uh as a subsidiary of williams uh under bally um it uh it was using
the williams wpc electronics 2 um and uh there were 3746 units confirmed sold um and so as far
as its features it has three flippers three pop bumpers three ramps uh three bank stand-up targets
uh two or three multi-ball the left ramp is mechanically raised or lowered with a ramp um
to use the ball cannon lower playfield has below the playfield ball cannon a catapult type that
oscillates when it's load so basically what this is is that you have this one ramp in the center
and it moves side to side and you have to line it up where uh you want to basically shoot the
cannonball um and so you fire when you press the fire button on this lockdown bar um it has the
the broadside so it will kick the ball to the center of this rail um so we'll set it back to
the flippers that way um the art for the table was done by pat uh pat mcman who has done i mean quite
a decent bit of uh of various pinball art you know uh he did things like uh trying to think
of what people are seeing roller games um he did tales of the arabian knights uh he did baby pac-man
dirty harry dungeon dragons fish tales so he's done some big titles mr and mrs pac-man pinball
i'm gonna have to find that one day um i was just looking at other artwork that he did but now um
one of the things that i'm going to bring into this is a little bit of some crazy notoriety
about one of the designers john trudeau um basically he got busted for child porn
that's a yike yeah now let me tell you what else he designed that rob the machine bride of pinbot
creature from the black lagoon uh judge dread i actually we actually owned judge dread and
creature from the black lagoon he did congo um and he had started working for stern in uh 19
sorry in 2013 and he had some tables all set up but yeah he was arrested and charged for
a possession of child pornography he might have done some cool stuff but what an asshole
now here's a little bit more about it is that he actually was um uh that he did plead guilty
to those and they had also gotten him on um abuse of a criminal sexual abuse of a female family member
um so yeah garbage absolute garbage um so you know i want to point out there that um
the uh you know we can have fun with with our tables we can enjoy our fandom but we need to
also be aware that you know if you're gonna say oh i love this designer know about the people
your favorites are problematic so yeah he's done some great tables i mean creature is dan's favorite
um but again you know be aware of the people who uh be aware of the entertainment you consume
hello for sure no yes you're still good sorry i'm i'm working on some other projects while
you're talking i'm multitasking um back though to a little bit more information about black rose
um it was included as a license table for pinball arcade and um goodness i accidentally turned on the
stream when i didn't mean to there we go all right so sorry about that um it also was included in
williams pinball volume two for pinball fx3 um and included in williams pinball classics in 2001
that came out for pc so there you go now i will tell you this is seriously still one of my
favorite tables ever um it uh it you might you know if you go to like a trade show or something
and you see it out there um it is it's one that people tend to pass up because it seems kind of
generic blah blah blah whatever you know but it really is super fun that center cannonball ramp
is it probably just makes most of the fun in the game for me and you know you have like these
light up targets that say uh sink ship um so it really is just a lot of fun um and i mean as
people can see from the video up here it's fairly unique little table it's got enough in there i
think it'll keep bringing people back to playing it so um definitely wanna um make sure that all
of you out there give this table a shot because it's really a lot of fun don't pass it up if you
find one to play all right there it is your classic pinball table of the month black rose
and this is our maties yeah that's a fun table and you and it's in your collection at your house
right it is it is in right in between my world cup soccer and my doctor who all right very cool
all right um so dark soccer i believe my you're working from home again tomorrow so you have to
leave us a little soon tonight um so do you want to get into your rapid fire stories here real
quick before we uh say goodbye sure um forever entertainment um uh has said that the revenue
from panzer dragoon remake has exceeded the production costs so um by more than double so
yeah they made the money back good for them hooray and um in other news um a first person resident
evil 8 is in the works and should be out by next year at least that seems to be some speculation
they're thinking it might be switched but again i don't know i don't i they kind of lost me so
i only care about the early ones yeah i but i don't know if i want to see him remake resident
evil 4 because i heard resident evil 3 like they really kind of they they kind of changed it quite
a bit like they they didn't really stick to it well the big thing on there is with jill's design
i was reading is that they tried to make her like take out the sex appeal as much because honestly
who's gonna run around fighting zombies in a fucking mini skirt and tube pop yeah it's like
running away from dinosaurs in high heels yeah yeah so um but the thing is that you know and
this is actually the quote is that they didn't want her to be in something that would be
uncomfortable for her task um and i think that's great and it kind of makes me consider that maybe
this will be the next cosplay that i revisit because one of my very early ones uh for my
first anime expo actually was um jill valentine old school jill all right there you go looking
forward to seeing it all right well um dark sakura i know you're heading out but do you
have any last words for us before you uh make your way out tonight pray for me 5 a.m shift
hey i'm happy to hear you get to go back that's the most important thing so well the big thing
is going to be can i actually get back because apparently i can't get into any of my work sites
so we'll see if that happens right all right fingers crossed good luck all right fingers
and toes bye y'all all right bye thanks for joining us find words to you all right take care
great to hear from you tonight all right all right um let's move on with some other rapid
fire news uh loki you want to take your your stuff sure okay so i was unaware that they
were still even making um updates to this game but apparently rock smith uh 2014 remastered
has um ubisoft san francisco has basically said that they're done adding dlc to rock smith so
right now they have a library of 1570 songs and yeah apparently they're working on a new project
now um it's interesting that's been going on this long i like i said i was completely aware that
they were still supporting that game so yeah i knew they were supporting it a while i didn't
realize it was like still going on even in 2020 i thought the last time i really saw the dlc was
last year but that's still very impressive and it was remastered so i was not aware of that either
so yeah neat um yeah so that's unfortunate but i guess we'll have to see what's coming from
ubisoft san francisco and then of course this time of the month since we're being a brand new
month and everybody is at home it's time to figure out what are the brand new free games that you can
get from your subscription services so we have playstation plus which is going to be gracing us
with uncharted 4 and dirt rally 2.0 so those are going to be available very soon april 7th through
may 4th on the xbox side of the house we've got project cars 2 and nights of pen and paper
and then of course on the xbox 360 side we have fable anniversary and toy box turbos
all right i didn't i i had forgot they even made a fable anniversary edition but i want to probably
check that out i like those games they're fun yep all right uh moving on over to some other news uh
this one's about saints row the third uh i don't know what do you think about this loki apparently
a remaster could be coming the esrb had a listing for saints row the third remastered uh do out on
pc playstation 4 and xbox one you might remember originally these games are on pc playstation 3
and xbox 360 um but it's um i guess there was a nintendo switch port as well but it wasn't
very good uh that just came out last year but potentially these games could be remade and coming
out again on playstation 4 and xbox one although i would think why not start for playstation 5 and
the other one but maybe i don't know maybe it's not going to be that big of a remaster i don't
know what do you think um i thought that they i mean i guess i guess it was saints row 4 that
they had remastered um i mean i i guess it wouldn't be that much of a stretch since um
four wasn't that much of a stretch from three so i mean it's practically the same engine
so i wouldn't see how that would be a hard thing for them to um port in there yeah it's just kind
of killing time i guess until we get a new announcement for saints row oddly enough though
because i did end up buying the humble bundle the covet 19 one it did have agents of mayhem in there
i saw that it was probably never gonna buy that game but now you got it at least for a good time
yeah all right uh also in a quick rapid fire story our last one tonight uh cellar door games in a
tweet mentioned that they are working on rogue legacy 2 that's right they're confirming that
rogue legacy 2 is in development and they'll be releasing more info later this week in the coming
days and there's some screenshots there on their twitter account over at cellar door games and i
do want to thank all the folks on um our uh twitter uh and i'm sorry on our discord server for sending
us all these stories over on twitter and those sorts of things uh for inclusion this week yes
a lot of the things you guys posted in our discord over at vog network dot com slash discord uh we've
included on tonight's show so thank you very much for that all right let's move on and travel around
the world and check out some release dates and we're going to start in the us loki all right not
a whole lot this week so we've got of course disaster report for summer memories on pc
nintendo switch and playstation 4 and then of course final fantasy 7 remake is going to be
coming out on playstation 4 and that's it yeah and i imagine with everything else going on in
the world some of these uh things are you know in influx in limbo and all that good stuff so uh
trying to pull up the japanese release dates it's being very slow but i'm pretty sure that
final fantasy 7 remake is also a thing uh but on the nintendo switch you can look forward to
um let's see a uh i guess there's a whole bunch of animal crossing um like accessories that are
out this week but i don't see any actual new games on the switch this week probably because over on
the playstation 4 the final fantasy 7 remake is out and final fantasy 7 game or fun fantasy games
including 7 tend to do very well in japan uh the only other thing i see uh that is coming out in
japan this week is a tom clancy rainbow 6 siege deluxe edition uh that is getting a japanese
localized release this week otherwise enjoy that final fantasy 7 remake hell you can even get a
playstation 4 or a playstation 4 pro that's a special final fantasy 7 bundle so check that out
but that is your big release in japan this week how about europe not a lot coming out in europe
as well so we've got cooking mama cook star on nintendo switch and final fantasy 7 remake oddly
enough based on the release dates i have here unless that changes this is all we're getting
for the next few weeks uh with everything that's going on in the world i'm not completely surprised
to hear that to be honest so um it is what it is you notice we're hearing other things get shift
back and moved around and i think some of these retail sites that we use to get this information
are probably changing because the retail end of things is uh kind of closing down and changing so
yeah anyway uh i need to pull up the mailbag here you know what maybe we'll do things a little bit
out of order uh loki do you want to read the next story here while i pull up the mailbag
sure so this is kind of a continuation like we had last week where we're talking a little bit
about gamestop and there is a little bit we could talk about game as well but um talking a little
bit more about game exchange so you may remember game exchange is kind of an independent retailer
that is similar to a gamestop in certain regions of the united states well um last week we had
employees kind of speaking out saying that you know there's issues with you know the sort of
thinking that it could be deemed essential considering that gamestop is they're saying
they're essential so apparently though now instead of actually uh providing them with you know
instructions to close their stores they've been providing them with tips to keep safe instead so
like take a sip of warm water every 12 or 20 minutes this keeps your mouth moist and washes
away any viruses that enter your mouth into your stomach where your gastric juices will neutralize
it these are no these are like fucking bullshit facebook chain posts that like really bored
karens are spreading around that are quite harmful actually yes so basically a bunch of these types
of uh things you know try avoiding cold it's just doesn't make any sense um so yeah so they've been
given this kind of information via an email that was sent to staff on tuesday um and apparently
this is from their vice president of retail operations Mindy Kent it's just it's ridiculous
and they really need to close these stores down but based on what i'm hearing and there was
another video that came out this week about you know some of the gamestop stuff and of course
a lot of that is still like rumor until we get from like other sources but um basically saying
that gamestop legal is trying to find a way to find a loophole where they can stay as um
as trying to deem themselves essential and reopen their stores or they have reopened their stores
and are basically fighting the situation and i've read that there's several states that have
actually cracked down on them to the point where they've just sent in police to shut them down
yeah and i think it's logical we just flow into the next story here before you get to
the mailbag and talk about the game stops in massachusetts so all the game stops in
massachusetts have closed and uh it doesn't sound like it was something they really wanted to do
but here's what happened the inspection services department for the city of boston went to the
dorchester store and basically ordered them to close they didn't get a fine but they got issued
a nuisance order so yes gamestop got declared a public nuisance this week for their antics at
least in boston they did um so they actually followed up went back on wednesday to make sure
that it was closed and gamestop confirmed to a report in the boston globe they did close all
massachusetts stores on thursday um don't know if gamestop is shut down in any other states
although california where we're at they did all close they had to follow the governor's order
yeah remember i i said that there might be a possibility of getting posters well i don't
think that's going to happen they've already taken signage of the store that's closing nearby here
and i mean it makes sense i don't even know when they would be reopening in the first place
yeah so oh well yeah it's it's a bummer we lost out on that but completely understandable due to
everything else that's going on in the world for sure yeah so all right i think we can now uh take
a trip back up to the mailbag and i can read some of these emails that came in uh because we
actually got some emails this week thank you very much and if you want to send some emails
participate at orange lounge trader.com is the place to send those emails so let's go to our
first email tonight from sia tabiri who says hello everyone i often mean to write in but because i'm
usually in the chat room i tend to neglect the whole email thing well that's okay we love that
you're participating one way or another i know that licensed games are generally not accepted
well but are there any non-video game properties you would like to see adapted into a game if so
what genre would best fit it and what specific mechanics would you like to see in that game
the easiest thing that comes to mind for me is i want to see more game shows adapted like one
versus 100 on xbox 360. i think that's like my easy go-to answer because that was a real crime
what happened with that whole thing and that it's not around anymore so that's like my easy
go-to answer but let me continue on with sia tabiri's email and then i'll get loki's answer
personally i would love to see a telltale games type enhanced visual novel a la wolf among us
for the tv series version of the magicians or perhaps something more along the lines of
psychonauts where you delve into different magicians power sets to tell a more original
story within the universe i hope you're all doing well and that this question wasn't as dumb as i'm
starting to feel like it was take care no it's not a dumb question uh what type of uh license
i open this up to chad as well what do you guys think what's like a um like a licensed property
you want to see put into a game loki any thoughts yeah so a licensed property i'd love to see
would be a um a vr version of nailed it it's my head my my brain was going to nailed it as well
so i was thinking of a cooking mama crossover somehow except one that isn't farming for bitcoin
or or if we want to like really get rid of this aside from just vr let's just have the folks from
uh that created uh surgeon simulator to do nailed it just have a really crappy like control thing
where you have to move the hands and stuff i just want the commentary from nicole buyer because i
fucking love her speaking of nailed it by the way if i don't mention this tweet at some point during
the show i'm gonna get a nasty gram from shane because he tweeted me earlier this week apparently
in the first episode of the new season of nailed it they use music from mass effect and like it's
it's like it's music that was made for mass effect and it's on the mass effect soundtrack it's the
synthesis ending music of all things is in nailed it he even sent me the clip on my on my twitter
account uh and it's it's so it's just funny that you're seeing these uh video game things get used
in other places how do they even find that music to use i don't know it's just like a there's weird
probably some nerd on staff that decided that hey i'm gonna sneak this in there you know they
i'm sure they have the license it but i'm just gonna slide it in there for the few people that
will even get what it is uh phoenix 77 26 says how about trauma center like a game centered around
house md i like that one uh tiger claw says how about a video game adaptation of the rocky horror
picture show but call it the rocky horror video game show so believe it or not that's already
happened except it was um a game adaptation of the play the rocky horror show um and that is on
way back in the commodore 64 days uh and uh they did make a new one on cd rom when they did the i
think there was a revival i don't remember if they made it around the new york city broadway revival
or if it was around a british revival in like 2005 or something like that but spoiler alert
neither game can you mute loki loki go on mute classic zoom meeting uh but i guess here's
mechanical keyboard but spoiler alert neither rocky horror game was very good um but just
if you didn't know they actually did make those games and neither were very good
um speaking of uh i said newer phoenix newer uh speaking of um uh things that didn't translate
very well phoenix had suggested what would you think of a drag race game they did a dragopolis
do you remember that it was on cell phones and also not the best game in the world sorry to say
sorry i know some developers probably did their best on it but it was just too limited by the
mobile phone and it's just i think that game is not the reason why people watch drag race you
know people watch drag race for the horrible puns and the lip syncing and the fun challenges and
things like that and as much as i think sure a drag race game would be a great idea and i think
i've joked about it before in like a dream game or something have you ever played project runway on
the we and let's be real ruble's drag race is a spoof of like project runway and america's next
top model it started as a spoof but then it like became self-aware somewhere along the line um
but the point is project runaway on the we mama this is garbage it's the best way i could put it
it's not good uh so i don't know how a rupaul's drag race game would just like be good like it's
just it's just not going to be good um but i suppose you know i i linked in uh twitch chat
be linked because thankfully all of these characters oh yeah the Commodore 64 games are in
the archive so they have a rocky horror show thank you oh there you go tiger claw go check that out
maybe it'll be a classic game of the week sometime although again it's not very good
it's really not good all right uh oh and act deft are responding to the nailed it thing and
shane's tweet saying rob in mexico a lot of news shows use video game music a lot like no joke
it's almost a meme it's kind of funny i don't know why that's so funny anyway well thank you
see you tiberi for the email that was good uh moving on to another email from ronma tonight
who emailed us participate at orange lounge radio.com and you should too for next week
rama asks there hasn't been much in the way of talking about food so here's a question for you
all what is your favorite go-to comfort food mine is what some people call roman holiday or goulash
it's a mix of pasta sauce meat and cheese i can make a big batch of it and eat it all day and all
week and not be bored with it that's all for now till next time i'm sure a lot of people i'm
putting on i'm putting on quarantine wait because of all the stinking food i'm eating being trapped
at home and there's plenty of comfort food snacks in there but do you have a go-to comfort food
loki no but i have important information so you may remember that you know i was obsessed with
bond's uh honey butter chicken for a while and they of course closed down and i have not been
able to fill that void until recently when i decided to make wings and i found a honey
butter recipe that i used and that stuff is crack it is absolute crack i love it i will make as much
of that sauce as possible and i will literally now put it on anything and it is awesome so so
loki's answer is honey butter basically yes three tablespoons butter three tablespoons honey one
tablespoon of soy sauce and chopped garlic probably about two cloves or so mix that all
together simmer it in a pot or whatever and just like dip everything in it i did not expect loki
would be the one i'm getting cooking tips from on the show don't worry cooking loki will fix it
um let's see so my comfort food uh so we have this local chain and they're not paying me to
give an advertisement but i'm going to anyway and and loki mentions them all the time on the
show anyway because he brings their food in all the time but it's round table pizza i think they're
a west coast thing i don't think they have them on the east coast but they have them like arizona
and stuff right okay so they're pretty bomb pizza and like the pepperoni and olive specifically
takes me back to being a kid and like that used to be the pizza that my grandma would order when
i would go like stay with her for a weekend and things like like it would be it would always be
exciting times to go to grandma's house for the weekend because she would without fail
always order pepperoni and olive pizza from round table which is that's the one we just got so um
yeah i guess i gave him free ad but whatever it uh it's it is comfort food i know that's weird
because it's not really something you make in your kitchen but i still think comfort food kind of
evokes a certain memory um the other one and this would go back to grandma's house as well because
she always had a well-stocked cupboard of sour cream and onion pringles because i think they
were probably her favorite but they're definitely mine as well and uh i i probably ate or had ate
her out of house at home uh on those um sour cream and onion pringles and that would be
another comfort food and another company that didn't pay me to give them an ad but it is what
it is i mean that's the comfort food i like so um act dev says i do remember them uh round table
we used to have one in the city next to where i live i used to play in the arcade it had oh yeah
the the i always forget round table like i guess they technically still have arcades but they're
you know crappy crane games and things like that but back in the day they have the clubhouse once
now they have uh crappy a little bit larger of an arcade yeah but yeah it's still they
they still technically each have an arcade but they're like yeah they're crappy but that used
to be the place where without fail there was always an iron man iron stewart super off-road
game always that game was in every fucking round table i've ever been to
and um so that which that game was fucking great it's one of my all-time favorite arcade games we
don't talk about it enough on the show how fucking great that game is the first round table and see
because this is back pizza places used to be just like i don't know what it is nowadays where
everything's all bright and cheery but they used to be dingy and dark that's always like all of
these places even like like shakies do you forget am i am i that old that i'm the only one that
remembers shaky's pizza but going to shaky's pizza was going to like a fucking like like damp castle
with the gigantic doors it was something it was super dark but i remember like um
at the first round table i'd ever been to uh i think it's the first one um they used to play
pole position there because they used to have this arcade that was kind of just down these stairs and
not really like a basement but it was like down some stairs in a room um but yeah it was it was
always very dark i remember all of them being dark and even chuckie cheese was like that
actually you know what that might have to do with some of the things these uh kind of are
derivatives of because now that i didn't really think about this until you mentioned that but
now that i think about it like i remember going to a fancy um uh deep dish place in chicago uh it
was actually a misty because we were we didn't get to go because the weight was like forever but it
was very dark in there and it was all like candle lit type of thing and then i'm thinking have you
been to zelda's in downtown sac it's all candle lit it's all dark and candle lit there so i think
there's something about like pizza places be and i feel like chicago fire is a pretty dark place
too i don't know if it's only like chicago because zelda's is a really good deep dish place i don't
know if it's like a deep dish pizza thing or what but i feel like the dark pizza place thing like
goes back like it's not just chain restaurants that we remember growing up who knows but then
i also remember straw hat which was in a strip mall and it was very bright because the windows
were right there so they weren't all dark all right anyway there we go pizza discussion thank
you uh rama i hope we didn't let you down with that and rama i know about it because i know
you're from new york i know better that it get into the chicago versus new york pizza i'm not
going to do that i'm i'm a fat boy and i'm going to say there is room for both there is i love them
both so i'm not going to get into the chicago versus new york debate yes to both that is the
correct answer what i want to find out though is they have this new pizza place pizza bar place
that's opened up um that i haven't been to i keep driving by though it's called boston's pizza
and i'm curious to see what boston style pizza is interesting it's just i don't know it's the
new pizza place got chicken up do you remember though speaking since we've given chicago pizza
a highlight do you remember though there used to be that new york pizza place um it was over in
sowsack and it was i don't remember the name of it but they had a max it was the only max 2 machine
in town for the longest time and they had some fucking delicious pizza do you remember that place
it was no i don't remember no i know you went once it was in south sacramento
off fruit ridge or something and like that's that's quite a drive for like i think at the
time i was out in roseville or something that's quite a drive down there but it was
like the only place in town you can play max 2 for a little bit so anyway
uh i i don't think i ever went there act deft in chats no it wasn't godfather's it was it was
definitely it was in new york was giovanni's because there is a giovanni one here in sack
but it's not in south side but anyway i think it might have been that but anyway it was it
was definitely new york pizza um let's see uh act deft in chat says which style of pizza do you
prefer yes that is exactly exactly that the only i am not a fan of chicago style pizza
yeah i love i love them both like there's a time and a place for both i really do and i
understand i understand some people like poo poo on the chicago thing because you're eating
it with a knife and a fork so it's not but you know what i'm just i'm i'm not here to debate it
i'm just here to eat it if you want to fight me on chicago pizza i will eat that pizza before
you're done arguing and then you won't have a problem all right anyway let's move on all right
we got past the game exchange and game stop thing uh let's talk about this because this is uh an
another unfortunate kind of side effect of everything that's going on in the world and
that is that the national game museum is saying that they are in danger of closing because of
what's going on with the coronavirus i do want to point out this is the national video game museum
in the uk uh and you can follow them on twitter at nvmuk and they actually made a tweet saying
we need your help the uk's only museum dedicated to video game culture and education is threatened
with permanent closure by coronavirus despite 40 000 visitors in 2019 we have no safety net of
funding to ensure our new charity atlas a prolonged shutdown the uk is in danger of
losing this unique venue with nearly 100 playable exhibits school workshops and family events so
they're actually doing a crowdfunding page to try to i guess make up some of the stop gap that
they're losing because you know we're on a shutdown here in the us in most states
i think there are better than the yelp crowdfund idea that they oh yeah oh god that was horrible
that was horrible no this isn't this is a officially sanctioned by and on their official
twitter uh and nvmuk yeah if you guys didn't hear about that yelp man that's so shitty what they did
they were setting up uh crowdfunding things and the owners didn't even know about it all the time
it's just really shady anyway um anyway but this is official and is something you should look uh
be checking into especially if you are over in the uk but you can certainly help uh from anywhere so
um check that out over on their official twitter for more information nvmuk all right let's move
on loki what do you have for us before we get towards the end of the show here so this is
amazing uh but there's actually a new game coming from atari it's a pong rpg so it's pong quest and
it looks very cute it's got these qt graphics and you play like a pong paddle that's dressed up in
costumes and you fight other pong paddles as well so they have character customization and it's a
very tongue-in-cheek looking game it's being developed by uh uk design duo uh checkered inc
huh it's supposed to be coming out in consoles and pc this spring it's interesting to see all
the different ways they've reinvented pong over the years that's for sure yeah they have like
incorporate other atari games into it so they have like uh stuff in the trailer about centipede and
adventure so it's kind of cool very cool all right and one more story for you guys about you know
what what is sorry it has an autoplay video on the site uh what what are they doing on sports tv
when there's no sports um because we're not able to get together in sporting arenas and things like
that and of course as we've talked about over the last few weeks there seems to be this growing
trend into esports and espn took that up another notch this past weekend i must admit i didn't see
it maybe some of you in chat did and want to tell me about it but my understanding is that the nba
and 2k kind of came together to do an nba 2k tournament that was on espn and espn 2 and it
actually all started on friday and it's running through april 11th so we're in the middle of it
right now um it was uh on espn on friday with a half hour pre-show and then they ran it um
on espn for like an hour and a half and it went over to espn 2 uh and there are 16 nba players
competing including kevin durant uh donovan mitchell devin booker so there's lots of uh
nba celebrities competing in this the winner of the event will get 100 000 to give to a charity
supporting coronavirus relief specifically so that's going to be a win-win situation
um all together and uh is definitely an example of what you got to do on tv right now to um
fill in the time because we don't know when the nba or any of that stuff is coming back and it's
kind of like something i alluded to earlier in the show you know a lot of these sports events have
thousands of people that go to the arenas and they may not want those large gatherings for a little
while um maybe they'll allow and again i'm just fortune telling here listen to doctors as a
scientist maybe they'll allow smaller groups like 50 so that maybe they can get the the the people
there to record the game and play the game and maybe that'll be okay maybe they just play it
to empty stadiums but we don't know we we just don't know the future is kind of uncertain in
that way um so they're having to fill the time right now with what to do um sj100 matt says the
reviews i've read is that it's kind of boring i don't know if these reviewers are gamers but i
think people were expecting players to heavy trash talk each other and they're not doing that it's
kind of quiet between the players i have yet to see it so it's kind of what the early vibe seems
to say is that maybe it's not the side of the players we're used to seeing on the court because
it's a little more casual maybe because for charity they're toning it down i don't know
um act f says some soccer leagues are doing something similar and i think f1 racing is also
doing it and streaming it on twitch and bobby blackwolf says espn was showing the madden
championships today but it was a rerun from back in december and january so uh very interesting
to see the sports um folks having to really fill time i mean on the good side of things
there's no bars right now to gather to see these in anyway but i'm sure these tv companies are like
that's our bread and butter what are we going to do so it seems you know like definitely these um
online things are kind of filling in the gap a little bit so that you know people will still uh
be there to tune in and the flip side of that might be that tv ends up being the only way to
participate in these things for a little while so there might you know might be a little time
of weirdness but then it's going to kind of pay off double hopefully um well i don't know i'd
rather go back to the old way but you know what i mean uh for the folks that all are working and
making the tv they can um get back into that hopefully a little earlier than everything else
we'll see so all right nifty 805 says chicken wing sales are down yeah when there's no football
parties that's not necessarily true chicken wings are very hard to find really well but wingstop is
like that half their business comes from uh ball games and things like that i'm sure well true i'm
talking about like in stores because people keep uh oh yeah that's doing awesome i've had to go
like see recently when i go grocery shopping i have to go to three stores to get everything that
we need yeah uh which is not necessarily fun but it's been less crazy this week um i did end up i
found paper towels which is ridiculous um that was a random thing i found early on too is paper
towels and luckily we have plenty of toilet paper because alan like the week before we went on the
cruise alan bought some and then that was when all hell broke loose so anyway uh it is time for the
listener roundtable i'm sorry it's a typo there in the sidebar because i used an old template it's
listed around table via chat tonight we're not gonna be able to do discord so if you have any
questions for us in chat uh go ahead and put those in our chat room over twitch.tv slash vog network
if you have anything uh you'd like to ask us there uh pod culture and chat saying yeah even wonderfest
is up in the air now i am accepting the reality that dragon con could not happen i'm crossing my
fingers and toes that it does but i think there's just a lot of unanswered question marks still on
the whole thing uh again just because we can get back to some sense of normalcy are they going to
want 80 000 people to get together i don't know again i think it's just too early to say um i did
buy my flights this past week because here this is what i think will happen flights are really
cheap right now i don't know if you're aware but flights are really cheap right now so i wanted to
get in on the good deal because i have a feeling when they do say it's okay to fly again you're
gonna have all these business travelers snatching it up to catch up on lost work and the price of
those air tickets is gonna go way up because that backlog of people who haven't been able to travel
for a while are gonna suddenly want to do it so that's just you know i i don't know anything and
if airlines do close or whatever i feel like airline tickets may be a little harder to come
by for a bit so i wanted to lock that in now and the airline that i'm flying has a pretty generous
refund policy in this scenario you can imagine like they they change their policies specifically
for things bought in the month of april uh and and march so i feel okay about it that if if for
whatever reason the convention doesn't happen i could still use that money and just put it towards
2021 or go on a different trip when it's more appropriate too i don't know so we'll see again
it's too early to say but i i am mentally preparing myself to be disappointed because it would be very
disappointing but i yeah it i mean it is what it is we have to save lives so that's the most
important thing so uh anyhow uh dart tetsuya is wondering hey have any of you all seen king's
avatar on netflix it's a chinese drama but it's all about this online mmo thing a bunch of
different guilds playing together no i haven't heard of that is it um is it like a documentary
or is it just a scripted thing that's kind of interesting be curious about that so let's see
also um oh yeah some folks are talking about wrestlemania um because that's a sporting event
that's going on right now peso paca says wrestlemania was definitely odd how quiet it is
outside of hearing the narrators and wrestlers screaming and grunts yeah i bet that was really
weird and i guess they did that at their own facility they didn't do it um they didn't like
empty out a stadium or anything like that like they kind of did it in their own studio or
something i didn't watch it so i couldn't tell you but i'm sure a lot of you guys were watching
it and i'm sure i have plenty to say about it uh okay dark tetsuya says uh that was a scripted
drama so interesting all right nifty by the way in chat is linking to an article one thing there's
definitely no short of right now is chicken wings so i guess that's just at your local store loki i
don't know it probably was yeah we went to the store yesterday because we were starting to run
out of some things and oh but i don't want to i you can see how there's some people that just
don't care about like what's going on and being very careless so i'm just like oh meanwhile i'm
like i don't have any face masks but i have a scarf from those trips i've taken back east when
it's cold so i kind of like wrap the scarf around my face that's like all i could do
even though i wasn't coughing or anything but still you know just to
just out of an abundance of caution so anyway
all right well any last minute stories for us loki yes um so i wanted to talk about because
we didn't talk about i mean obviously this week april fool's day was and and i understand that
a lot of people think april fools is canceled yeah i'm one of them that's why i didn't slot it
so one company though that took it very seriously of course is mojang and mojang released a brand
new snapshot from minecraft that's absolutely incredible so it's called snapshot 20w14 infinity
and is the ultimate content update now what did they do to the game they added two billion worlds
into the game based on player input and um so what this does is actually you know in minecraft
there's another portal that'll take you to the nether so with this update if you take a book
in the game and you write whatever you want in the book that creates a new seed for a brand new
universe basically that you throw it into the portal walk through it and it'll take you to
one of these procedurally generated worlds based on your seed that you create so it's all sorts of
weird glitchy looking things that are out there plus there's several different uh worlds that they
made themselves kind of like easter eggs that you can work to as well or find amongst all of these
two billion worlds that are in there and at first like when i saw like the youtube videos i thought
oh this is just like people trying to play pranks but i saw more and more of them and actually
watched you know how it works and no it's a legit update that adds a ton of replayability
into the game and funny enough they added an advancement or achievement into the game
for visiting one billion of those worlds so you know visit one billion of them in order to get
that achievement but they have all sorts of weird stuff in there and brand new blocks that they
created specifically for this now this is aside from um the nether update which is supposed to
be coming as well to java but i mean i can't wait to check this out i downloaded this today to go
um play around in it but i haven't gotten a chance to play it yet because i need to reload all my uh
i had some scripts for using controllers in the java version and stuff like that because i have
a new pc now i got reload all that stuff and it sucks but yeah it's really crazy just some of the
stuff that generates in this game so right there's uh they have like skyblock stuff in there now
there's just a bunch of weird dimensions that this is created so um worth checking out if you
have the java version go download the beta client or the snapshot release and go jump into a billion
different worlds all right anything else uh that's it all right let me get this last question here
from s100 max i think this is a good one uh over in our chat question because i'm finding new ways
to entertain myself i challenged myself to 100 super mario world within a week on just pure
memory no online checking are there any games that you know so well you can pick it up and
beat without researching anything uh i might struggle a little bit especially in the water
levels but uh super metroid i'm pretty sure i could uh pecking crash my way through uh probably
final fantasy two and three which are really four and six of course on super nintendo i could
probably get through those again too but those those are actually kind of linear i don't think
it's that hard to pick those games up and um you know because everything is kind of like gated you
know like metroid can't get to this point unless you have this can't get to this point unless you
have this so um i don't know if either of those answers are as impressive but i feel like those
are two games i could definitely pick up uh loki what about you is there something you could like
pick up in full clear just from muscle memory um i don't know like it would have to i can't think
of an older game that i would have played so much of that i could do that oh uh akuma jp says i
think sftn symphony of the night i think um it would be yeah symphony of the night that's a good
one too i bet that's one jamie could do uh act f says i could also do shovel knight from memory oh
that's a pretty good one as well so nice bobby blackwolf says adventure for the 2600 so
that's another one that well no actually some some parts of that can be pretty tricky i think
so but there's some other ones i'd like to challenge myself with like the original metal
gear on nes i bet that would be a fun one to try again see if i can remember how to get through
some of those mazes and things like that all right anyway we're gonna wrap up for the night
thank you guys so much for uh tuning into orange launch radio or watching us live however you
decided to uh participate with the show tonight uh if you enjoyed what you heard here at orange
launch radio help us spread the word tell a friend or two about the show because we are
the show where every gamer has a voice but the voices have to be here to put on air
uh so help us spread the word we really appreciate it um uh auto hosting on twitch that goes a super
long way really appreciate that but otherwise just tell a friend or two where you might have heard
about this show uh and how to find it and that would be awesome a nice five-star review on a
podcasting site like itunes those go a long way as well uh and again just take care of yourself guys
uh take it seriously what doctors out there are saying um staying at home means you got to stay
at home like as much as you want to see your friends and you're probably uh really want to
hang out with them like i would love to yeah you know there was a part of me that was like
why don't i just have loki over it's just loki but then i thought well it's you're you know who
knows i may be sick and not really showing it and then you know i don't want to i don't want to give
that to loki so uh staying away from people means staying away from people and if we can work
together uh we will uh get rid of this thing a lot faster so please stay safe stay healthy
make good choices and all that good stuff um with that loki your final thought tonight
my final thought is i'm gonna play more uh try to play more games i've been trying to get to
where i can programming um i've worked so like this week i've got uh replacement parts coming
from my switch as well because my switch has been acting up um so i'm gonna fix the joy cons
manually and but i still have an issue with the stupid sd card we're like literally just holding
the switch and it keeps saying that the sd card is being disconnected so there's something weird
at that so i'm gonna take it apart and hopefully not break it good luck with that uh where i'm
actually getting some new computer parts as well because my main computer uh keeps freezing suddenly
like it doesn't happen all the time but i i was wondering if it's like an overheating thing or
something is it'll like freeze in the middle of a game i have to shut the system off bring it back
up but i don't know it's just it's just really annoying me so check your fans and make sure
they're not they are we give it we give it a big dusting we took the and it still did a freeze up
on me so i don't know what the hell's going on so um i was like well maybe it's an excuse to buy
some new computer parts i've been wanting a new video card anyway you know so we'll order them
and they'll get here when they get here because you know i know all that stuff is not essential
and it's fine new weeks shipping pretty fast are they saying all right we'll see we'll see um okay
akuma jp says stop downloading porn it's not it's not porn that's causing it's final fantasy 14
unless you consider fantasy 14 porn which you might i don't know um so my final thought is um
yay i i hope to get new computer parts soon as well and i will definitely be playing more near
automata this week and i'll talk more about it on next week's show so with that have a great week
everybody thinking of all you guys out there stay safe take care of yourself um reach out talk to
friends virtually uh if you need to say hi to somebody vog network.com discord we got a lot of
people on there they'll say hi to you um please don't hesitate to reach out and say hello i know
these times uh suck but there's got to be light at the end of the tunnel so keep focusing on that so
until then we'll see you in seven days and we'll do this all over again have a great night everybody
bye-bye you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of
olr studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific
9 p.m eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of
the staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you