[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We are live on September the 5th of 2010, a Sunday here with our Orange Lounge Radio Marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: We are almost, what, about seven hours in at this point now?
[SPEAKER_28]: We started at about 2.05, and it's now 8.50 on the West Coast here where we tape.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can listen live, of course, at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, and I imagine that's what most of you are doing, because the podcast, you'd have to be way, way, way into that now to get to this point.
[SPEAKER_28]: So...
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyhow, we were going to do some news here, and I was going to open the Skype line again here in just a moment, so we'll have that again open.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you want to give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not just yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to open it here in a moment.
[SPEAKER_28]: But we had another question, I guess, come in on Ask Orange Lounge or something that slipped through the cracks, and I thought it was a pretty good question, so I apologize to bother Alan mid-chew there, but do you remember what that question was all about?
[SPEAKER_28]: The extra question we got?
[SPEAKER_14]: Which game or system did you pass up on when it came out that you never bought that you now regret?
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought there was also a question, what system do you regret buying, too?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, well, let's do both.
[SPEAKER_28]: What system do you regret buying, and what thing do you wish you hadn't passed up, I guess that would be?
[SPEAKER_28]: Um...
[SPEAKER_28]: Saga Dreamcast Saga Dreamcast Saga Dreamcast
[SPEAKER_28]: So that would probably be my answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: I did get one when they were like $40.
[SPEAKER_28]: Remember when they cut the price down to like $40?
[SPEAKER_28]: Or at least GameStop was just trying to unload them or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because at that point you could do all the NES emulators on the Dreamcast and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: So that's when I finally got on the Dreamcast bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it was a little bit too late.
[SPEAKER_28]: And keep in mind, guys, the Skype line is not open yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: So if you're calling in, hold off.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll get to the calls a little later here in the program.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan?
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually was able to buy an original edition of Panzer Dragoon Saga for the Saturn, which came out well after the Saturn was dead.
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought it, took the bus after school to go to the mall, dropped the 70 or 80 bucks for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ended up selling it for a killing on eBay like two years later I never touched it so I bought it never played it and Panzer Dragoon Saga is one of the greatest RPGs especially for the Saturn and I sold it on eBay for like 200 something bucks and I needed the money but it's like why did I do that like I had I just walked into the store and bought it I never touched it you could play ours if you want
[SPEAKER_14]: The N64 I got for Ocarina of Time because at that age I was very elitist and snobby about CD-ROM versus card and how Nintendo was making the wrong decision.
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought an N64 just for Ocarina of Time and I never really played any other game aside from that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought a bunch of games for the N64 and never touched them.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that was probably a waste of money.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now you're talking the games you regret buying, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, those are my two for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you have any for the one that I had answered about the system or game you regret not buying?
[SPEAKER_14]: I really wish I could have checked out the TurboGrafx, but that was a bit out of my league at the time.
[SPEAKER_28]: My friend had one, and at the time, I thought it was kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_28]: I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_28]: The games I played on it were not that great.
[SPEAKER_28]: We played Splatterhouse, which was kind of cool, in the fact that it was Splatterhouse, and it was kind of like a horror movie type game.
[SPEAKER_28]: But otherwise, I didn't find the games on it to be that great.
[SPEAKER_28]: And to this day, I gotta admit, I know DarkSakura's got a lot of love for it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe it's because she's out of the room.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll dare to say this.
[SPEAKER_28]: I still kind of think the whole thing was kind of overrated.
[SPEAKER_28]: It wasn't that great of a system, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it was the only system that got the original Street Fighter, and it also got, you know, Castlevania X, the lost Castlevania game until recently.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that's cool, but, you know, how many of us actually played that?
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, sure, Jamie did, but she's, you know, cray-cray.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: In a good way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Aside from that, all the systems that were even a little bit relevant, I had at one point, I did get a Genesis.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got it years after everyone else, but I got it before the PlayStation 1 came out.
[SPEAKER_14]: The 32X and the Sega CD were all considered failures, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, don't really have much regrets there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have the original Lunar on a ROM.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can play it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_28]: For me, the system that I regret buying, like not, don't, or regret not buying, but the system I regret buying that I kind of wish I hadn't was a second DS.
[SPEAKER_28]: I had a DS Fat and then the original DS and then I bought a DS Lite and I don't think I really needed that Lite.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't handheld game at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: PSP Fat PSP Fat PSP Fat
[SPEAKER_28]: I did and I ended up getting a PSP 3000 as well but you know what I actually would play the PSP probably more than I did the DS just the certain games that were on it with Luminous and the Final Fantasy remakes and so forth I mean don't get me wrong the DS had its games too but I don't know also the PSP 1 I kind of wore it down and it didn't work as well anymore so it kind of justified for me the PSP 3000 even though that's probably not like the greatest reason to have one if that makes sense but yeah
[SPEAKER_14]: I know the idea of buying a movie on UMD is kind of ridiculous, but if you can get Kill Bill on UMD, it fries for like five bucks.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's got a better screen on it than your iPhone does, really.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: To watch a movie on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, we're talking about the system or console you regret most buying, and then the one you regret not buying.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't really have anything that I regret buying.
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess if I was going to pick one, it'd be the GameCom because it was awful.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't even regret the N-Gage because I had some good stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_18]: But as far as things I regret not buying... You know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_28]: Robert M. in chat gave the same answer almost at the same time.
[SPEAKER_28]: The GameCom.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is where you're at.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_18]: Bradley?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I regret probably not buying was I never got a Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear all the great stories about it, and I just never got around to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this might have been the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't have a job at the time, so I couldn't get it.
[SPEAKER_28]: The system was truly ahead of its time.
[SPEAKER_28]: If it had come out like two years later with DVD support, I honestly think it would have whooped the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: I really, truly think that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know I'm crazy, but I do.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think there's any systems that I regret buying because I think I like all my systems that I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: His story about Panzer Dragoon reminds me, I actually had to sell mine off because I had no money at the time and I really regret doing that and really didn't want to buy it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually did win an auction for it on eBay for like 200-something bucks, but the guy never shipped it, which was really annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: He kept saying he was going to ship it, but he didn't, and he gave him like a fake code or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But since I did it through PayPal, I was able to get the money back, at least for that, so I can see if I can find it again sometime.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game I regret buying was the sequel to Alex Kidd and Miracle World.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember what it was called, Alex Kidd 2 something.
[SPEAKER_03]: is just because it... I'll say what in Miracle World is a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It takes a while to get through it and it takes a while to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I played it again like a few years ago and I couldn't get through it because there's like some spikes and stuff in the last few levels that can be kind of hard to get past.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the second game is like, it's a really easy... Instead of having like...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's, it doesn't, it's not like the map like the first one has and, and the first one, first one is not exactly as linear, it's not linear.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because you can go, or it's not left to, just left to right is left to right and then you're up and down depending on the level.
[SPEAKER_03]: But on, in the second game, you only go left to right and it's actually a really easy game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I beat, I beat it the first, first, first day and it's like really disappointing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a bit, pretty much because of how great the first game was.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good answers, guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think we're going to do some quick news stories.
[SPEAKER_28]: We had a couple left over that we never got around to, and then we actually have some other discussion topics.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, DarkSakura, I don't know if you have the piece on the last one that we had left over that we didn't get to before dinner.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_18]: About Telltale.
[SPEAKER_18]: Basically, Telltale's doing a five-episode Back to the Future series, and it's going to have Marty McFly and Doc Brown.
[SPEAKER_18]: It has Christopher Lloyd voicing Doc Brown, which is great.
[SPEAKER_18]: and Hill Valley being 1985 and guidance from the screenwriter Bob Gale and the DeLorean so they're still working on getting the rest of it up but there's still a bit missing you know I guess what hoverboards and Huey Lewis in the news
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm looking forward to seeing what the actual game looks like.
[SPEAKER_28]: We've heard a lot of talk about the game and kind of ramping up to it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kind of excited to see what the damn thing actually looks like, but I'm sure it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have some trivia for you.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can kind of guess.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I tell you a secret?
[SPEAKER_28]: A lot of people are going to judge me for this, but I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have never seen Back to the Future 1 or 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can fix that.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I have seen Part 3.
[SPEAKER_28]: Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_28]: The Wild West one, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: I saw 1 and then I saw 3.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't see 2 for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_28]: I never saw 1 or 2.
[SPEAKER_18]: But Rob, here's some trivia for you.
[SPEAKER_18]: On the Back to the Future pinball table, you know that Michael J. Fox would not allow his likeness to be used, so they made a generic looking dude.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think I know that because you've brought it up on the show before.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually, true story.
[SPEAKER_28]: True story.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: One other story for you guys, and it has to do with the Connect Beta is going on right now, of course.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're starting to ship out and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Someone is trying to sell theirs on eBay.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're trying to get $1,200 for it, but it was quickly taken offline.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm assuming Microsoft sent a cease and desist to the kind folks at eBay.
[SPEAKER_28]: So probably Microsoft did not take kindly to the fact that the unit was being sold.
[SPEAKER_28]: The seller on eBay was Blue Room Project and there were no bids actually made on the system.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there it was.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's interesting about it though is that I would think that this, and the article kind of gets into this too, is that you would think these connects are going to be sending back quite a bit of data to Microsoft servers.
[SPEAKER_28]: So it could kind of figure out who's playing connect that shouldn't be, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Like if you get a connect early, aren't you kind of setting yourself up for trouble unless you never sign on to Xbox Live, which I guess you could do, but then how would you get the patches and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_28]: It just seems tricky, tricky.
[SPEAKER_28]: I wish Loki was here to explain a little more about how you could get around that but I'm just thinking, you know what, probably not a good idea to just buy these that you don't really have the rights because Microsoft can track what goes online and you're going to have to go online to get some of the patches and updates so it just doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was it for the news.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was all the news we had set to cover this show.
[SPEAKER_28]: So if you have more stories you want to talk about, we're actually going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now it is open, folks.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: So you can either call us and talk to us about a news story or really anything you've heard about tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or you can send us a tweet at twitter.com slash O-L-R.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can send us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_28]: And we'll read those again in a little bit if we're getting some tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I think DarkSakura had mentioned something about wanting to do the mailbag again, but I don't know if any letters have dropped in.
[SPEAKER_28]: But we're kind of monitoring all those pretty closely right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm actually going to kind of load up the tweets.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see how those are going.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, we are getting some calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome to Hour 7 of the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Doing good, and you?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm still awake, that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I'm really excited to hear that they are going to do a miniseries based on Back to the Future, which is hopefully going to be epic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now they're getting actual actors to do the voices from the movie and stuff, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would love to see Michael J. Fox to come on also, because that would be excellent.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, Telltale also got cited for because they announced a new poker game coming out this fall with different characters from different game series.
[SPEAKER_15]: Poker Night at the Inventory with Tycho from Penny Arcade, Strong Bad from Homestar Runner, Max from Sandman Max, and then the Heavy from Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: so that should be pretty interesting of a poker game when they get that all said and done yeah we to be fair it was brought up about six hours ago but yeah we did talk about it a little bit but um it sounds kind of interesting i'm not usually like a somebody that gets like super into the uh poker games but um i kind of like where this one's going it's an interesting hodgepodge of characters what do you kind of hope you get out of this poker game
[SPEAKER_15]: Just the wackiness.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because of Telltale and the way they're going to put this together, there's going to be some kind of epic fighting going on between characters and stuff, which is going to be absolutely great to see.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the over-slapstick humor that they usually do with some of their games.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_28]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: So what else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I've been playing a lot of WoW, as of course you should know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Of course, because I play a lot of WoW too.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fancy that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we all do.
[SPEAKER_28]: What are some of your WoW accomplishments recently?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, almost had the, uh, TOC 25, which I would have been very proud of.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, uh, you know, just a lot of different odds and ends, uh, ICC getting farther than that now in the 10 man.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, uh, the guild, um, you know, just, and hopefully I'm really going to be proud because I'm going to try to go for some of the other odds and ends like the fishing mounts and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: So awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, um,
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, anything else on your mind, buddy, before we let you go and take more calls?
[SPEAKER_28]: Nope, that's pretty much about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, you have a good night.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good luck with WoW.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: You too.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can give us a call.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was just ringing off the hook a minute ago, so I'm hoping more calls will come in.
[SPEAKER_28]: We are getting some tweets.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll get to those in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you doing over there, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you good?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I'm a little boozy.
[SPEAKER_28]: From the drinking?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm starting to get a little like, hey.
[SPEAKER_18]: Brandy hits me really fast.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome to the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is probably a question that's probably better answered by Loki, but since he took off a few hours ago, I'll ask you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of sort of toying around with the idea of...
[SPEAKER_05]: more or less recreating an arcade kit that I once saw going years back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you've ever seen this one particular model.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had Samurai Shodown 4 in it and basically the configuration was it came in two pieces.
[SPEAKER_05]: One section had the
[SPEAKER_05]: Joysticks and the buns and the coin slots and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe the second piece was basically the modern.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was like five or ten feet away.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was like a set of chains licking the two together.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_28]: You got to back up here.
[SPEAKER_28]: This was a special machine or a custom machine you're saying?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think I'm more or less recreating at least part of the custom machine for myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least the control, the part with the controls on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aside from the part with the controls like the joystick and all that, I was wondering, what kind of materials do you think I should be...
[SPEAKER_05]: using to build the cabinet itself, like, should I use, like, particle board and laminate, or...
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, this is definitely a Loki question because I don't know anything about this stuff, but I will tell you one somewhat cheap alternative that I've heard being used before is actually trying to find old arcade cabinets that, for whatever reason, the games inside them don't work anymore because the cabinets seem to make pretty good shells for these custom cabinets for whatever it is you're trying to build, a Samurai Shodown 4 case or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those are usually a really good place to start, at least from what I've heard, and I think that's what quite a few people have done.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, don't you guys have a custom cabinet?
[SPEAKER_18]: We just modified a pole position back in the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: And used it and put a... Dan built the layout and everything with the buttons and joysticks.
[SPEAKER_28]: Otherwise, as far as specific materials that work best, not really my realm of expertise because I've never built a cabinet, so I'm not going to profess to know that stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I'm sure there are some websites.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, Loki's a good resource when he's here.
[SPEAKER_28]: When he's not babysitting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ultimately, my goal is to, let's say, to use this as just an example.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was thinking of getting one of those $150 arcade sticks for the PS3 or 360, drop that into the cabinet, run the arcade stick flyers to my game system, and then try to have my...
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I know that Loki was also going to be working on a project about building arcade cabinets for like a hundred bucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, you know, I'm all about building on a budget.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thanks for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_28]: You too, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_28]: YouTube
[SPEAKER_28]: Legend of Zaku from your cell phone Oh wow, you guys are really pushing it this time, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_28]: We haven't done a show this long since DDR tournaments, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, apparently the biggest thing right now is Duke Nukem Forever basically coming back from the dead in a more spectacular way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never thought it would actually happen.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh yes, what do you think about all this news that has come out of Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_06]: All I know is that they better just stick to the schedule and get it out because the last thing we need is for other folks to just have this game be the butt of everyone's joke again.
[SPEAKER_28]: At the same time though, at this point, Zaku, what's another year?
[SPEAKER_28]: If they delay it to 2012, what's another year at this point?
[SPEAKER_06]: But the game is so close.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, people are already playing a demo of it and
[SPEAKER_06]: What I hear is like at polishing stages.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like.
[SPEAKER_28]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_28]: If they're showing it on the floor at Penny Arcade Expo, it's darn close to done.
[SPEAKER_28]: Showing it at Penny Arcade Expo, keep in mind, they bypassed E3 to make this announcement.
[SPEAKER_28]: If this has been in development since 2009, they could have announced this at E3, but they didn't.
[SPEAKER_28]: They went and took it directly to people like you and me at Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's like unzipping it and whipping it out on the table for everybody to admire.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Then again, this game actually appeals to the hardcore demographic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not necessarily something you would want, you know, average Joe gamer who pretty much doesn't have a clue as to what Duke Nukem is, unless they have been playing during the, you know, mid to late 90s.
[SPEAKER_28]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, the whole point is that, I guess, I kind of find it surprising that the first, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: The studio behind Borderlands and the guy who founded it pretty much has a connection to 3D Realms and the folks who ran it up until its demise.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never thought that guy's career is pretty much owed to Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, now I'm wondering, though, if they knew that they had this game, that Gearbox has had this game since 2009.
[SPEAKER_28]: When did Duke Nukem come out?
[SPEAKER_28]: Didn't it come out about a year ago?
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, all I know is that basically, when I read in the article, like a Taco article where they interviewed, you know, that guy, basically...
[SPEAKER_06]: After 3D Realms shut down, most of it was pretty much a two-bit operation running from people's apartments.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much a garage game up until a point where Gearbox took control of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty much coming together piecemeal.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's no way you would mount something unless you have a solid backing from a developer who's able to actually finish the job instead of putting it through development hell.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, you know, again, it's been shown now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something that is actually going to come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll, you know, see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And hopefully everything will make sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: And at least I could hear more one-liners out of this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much what OLR needs.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot more Duke Nukem one-liners out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: The soundboard is kind of saved for special occasions.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_28]: And real quick, a comment from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Derek H is asking, is the caller saying that 3D Realms was a garage development house?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just saying that after 3D Realms blew up because of Duke Nukem Forever's development, the folks from 3D Realms, in the transition to Gearbox, in between that time, started working on Duke Nukem Forever from their apartment.
[SPEAKER_06]: So some of it during that time with 3D Realms' demise, until it got handed over to Gearbox, was pretty much a two-bit operation.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know 3D Realms is pretty much a big name studio back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: They turned out a lot of PC titles that I'm pretty much fond of.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think it's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_28]: The only thing that's going to be sad is that since it's not just like Borderlands, you're not going to get quests in Duke Nukem as far as I know, so it won't be like, hey, you need to go up to the stripper and tipper.
[SPEAKER_28]: Although I guess you do have to press R to pee in the toilet.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the whole point of Duke Nukem is just pick up and play, kill people, max out on your... try to get all the power-ups and weapons and just go all out with
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the whole point, is that you're just killing, you're just shooting people, like Doom.
[SPEAKER_06]: But instead, you're just like, you know, you're killing a lot more aliens and monsters.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: And with a lot of one-liners.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, well, Zaku, we gotta let you go to get some more calls, but I hope you can get your hands on Duke Nukem soon, and see it's the real thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Later.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_28]: 877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, this is DJ Blaziken.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not much other than I've been listening to this whole marathon shindig since it started up and the whole music break thing is bringing me back to the old days, back from the really old episode that I started listening to you guys back on your old station.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I'm glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's kind of the idea behind it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, for those that are listening on the podcast, we can't do the copyrighted music that we were playing during our little breaks here for meals and potty and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yeah, we're playing a lot of the music.
[SPEAKER_28]: When Orange Launch Radio, back when we were a station on Live 365, we would play music from DDR and just a variety of the other music-based games and some of the Dance Mania CDs that inspired the music song list in DDR and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, which, of all things, okay, I've been a little bit on a Jersey Shore fanatic point, so I've been fist-pumping throughout the whole breaks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't think I've ever heard anyone say that about this program.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a first for everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, by the way, actually, just thinking of systems I regret not buying, systems I do regret buying, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Somehow, I regret not buying a Sega Dreamcast myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Outside of the second system, I regret not buying, because I had a kick-ass fighting game on it, was the N64.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, it had killer instinct, and the controller itself, the standard controller, was perfect for fighting games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to admit, I got used to Street Fighter on a Super Nintendo controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole fact that some of the punches and kicks were shoulder buttons totally didn't bother me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was able to get used to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you ever remember the Capcom controller that they came out for the Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, and I thought that was on the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_18]: They did it in Japan.
[SPEAKER_18]: The six button controller where you held part of it in your hand and you played with the top of your fingers.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was kind of uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, it sounds it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And on top of that, a game I regret not buying, but I've actually got to play, well, I now finally got to buy and own, is Full Calibur.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dreamcast good stuff I wish I had Goldeneye too cause god I mean occasionally my friend would bring it over to the daycare occasionally and he'd bring it over to N64 and we'd all just sit down four player multiplayer it was just epicness and even though I never owned it it was just like god I wish I could plop some money down on that and now that I think about it
[SPEAKER_09]: a game that I do regret buying wow it would have to be DDR Disney Channel Edition you must have been a real DDR completionist to get that yeah it's another DDR worthy of the whole old bumper from Step Squad saying this DDR sucks saying to Solo
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, Solo was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_28]: Solo was awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was some of the best music they had in DDR ever, especially Solo 2000.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think my arcade had the Solo 2000, but stupid idiots trade for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not even the second.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to back up real quick, because you were talking about the Dreamcast and missing out on that and everything, which was the same thing I said for the system that I kind of regret not buying.
[SPEAKER_28]: But then I also think about it, and it's like, you know, at that time in my life, there was no way I could have paid that type of money for that system.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, I was barely out of college, and I didn't really have a job.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, I sort of worked temp jobs in the summer and so forth.
[SPEAKER_28]: There was no way I would have been able to afford one.
[SPEAKER_28]: So...
[SPEAKER_28]: I regret not being able to afford it, I guess, but I couldn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess I can't say I don't regret not buying one because I was able to buy food and other things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, contrary to the whole gym casting, the babysitter my mom sent me to a bunch of times, he had a bunch of systems to play and six or seven arcade games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mortal Kombat 2, Asteroids, Snow Bros, and Defender I was like 6, 7, 10 Yeah, and Mortal Kombat 4 He had Final Doom on the Playstation I played that a lot
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, when one of his friends would come over, we'd link up the two playstations to play four-player Final Doom.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, once again, FPS Epicness, which, that's why I ended up buying, what was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I ended up buying Doom on Xbox Live and Soul Calibur Am I the only one that's like what's wrong with this picture?
[SPEAKER_28]: Why is the six year old being allowed to play Mortal Kombat 2 and Doom when he's with the Manny?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't get that But the cool thing was not only that did I play it in his house but on the occasions I'd go over to the mall and then my mom she was searching for me
[SPEAKER_09]: and so she knew I was in the arcade section of the mall at the time and this is the same mall that won't fix their ITG machine it's still down which sucks but at the time they had a Mortal Kombat 4 arcade machine and I would play that constantly because there was only one token to play and how old were you, 8?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was 10 and actually the first game I ever got actually the first game system I ever got was a Game Boy
[SPEAKER_09]: Game Boy Pocket.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first two games I got, one was a combo game cartridge, Mortal Kombat 1 and 2, and the other was Star Wars The Empire Strikes Back, which I loved the cantina song that would play whenever the characters were bringing up dialogue.
[SPEAKER_28]: And those games didn't screw you up as a kid?
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, you're fine now?
[SPEAKER_28]: You have a good sense of reality?
[SPEAKER_28]: You're stable mentally and all that good stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, my mom was like, it's too violent, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll make you go crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I bought GTA Liberty City Stories behind her back on Amazon for a PSP hacking point because it was used to get the hen to activate.
[SPEAKER_09]: but it ended up not working as well as I thought the hack would work.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I just had fun with that and she never knew about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you told your mom recently about all these things you were playing behind her back when you were growing up?
[SPEAKER_09]: She kind of figured out after a while what I was playing but she didn't care by the time I was... She was like, here's the good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't become that stupid Virginia Tech...
[SPEAKER_09]: Shooter, or the Von Maher Shooter, which you probably might have heard about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've heard about them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, I didn't go out and shoot at the high school.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't go out with a sniper rifle and shoot a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I felt like I wanted to deck someone in the face, I waited until I got home or got on the bus, started up GTA, and started beating up random civilians in games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my anchor management.
[SPEAKER_28]: I like what Hoofhearted says in chat, saying, My father didn't care that I played MK, but my mom got scared and said, You're going to live with your auntie in Bel-Air.
[SPEAKER_26]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Blaze, I've got to let you go so we can try and get some more calls and do more Marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: But thank you for the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: One last thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, basically the PSP in of itself is almost like a Super Nintendo controller in of itself with a screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just with an analog stick.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Alpha 3 Max plays fine and I go between that and Street Fighter 4 and I'm looking to get in the EVO tournament one day and beat Daigel Well good luck to you
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, peace out, and have a good rockin' show.
[SPEAKER_28]: We will, we'll try.
[SPEAKER_28]: Later!
[SPEAKER_28]: Thanks for being a part of the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was kind of a marathon phone call here on the Village Lounge Radio Marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ah, we can probably do one or two more, whatever, I got nothing else to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm trying to look in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_28]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com, which is still pretty full here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: What was the question?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, BetaCNCRA was asking, why is the show only on Sundays?
[SPEAKER_28]: Why can't it be on every day?
[SPEAKER_18]: We have this thing called lives.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, that and a job.
[SPEAKER_28]: And this show doesn't pay us anything.
[SPEAKER_28]: In fact, we actually pay to do this show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Although we don't pay very much anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't have to pay for a feed anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: The fine folks at All Games Radio help subsidize that.
[SPEAKER_18]: But wait until I can show you the bill for our mixing board.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, hello there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that Swede, who's been with you all this time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good morning to you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, gosh, when we started, it was probably, what, like midnight where you are?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was... What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: If I remember... No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like 11 o'clock or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, that's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: If I remember... We've been going for seven hours now.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_28]: Seven and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, do the math.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, oh, well, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, Mass Effect is kind of interesting, almost, in that sense that, well, finally, DLC for that game will show up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah, because that's right, Mass Effect 2, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Has it had a lot of download content come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: DLC that you actually want to buy, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because that backstory with the Shadow Broker is like, winner!
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I already have actually read the comic for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Mass Effect Redemption comic.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about... Which takes place actually around that, before Mass Effect, around that time when...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it takes place, like, before Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mass Effect movie would be kinda nice in some way, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, my problem though is that my Shepard is not male.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's female.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shepard is female.
[SPEAKER_04]: Point!
[SPEAKER_28]: Shepard can be whoever you want them to be.
[SPEAKER_28]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, completely not what you were asking, but I only play female characters in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_28]: because people treat you better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, so do I. Even though the ironic thing about that front is that, well, I didn't get to max level at... I didn't get to max level that soon, actually, because I, like... I didn't hit max level, but then I think I did at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I mostly played female characters, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what happens?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I roll a troll male and I hit max level.
[SPEAKER_28]: it's funny the characters you will get most invested in out of everything else I gotta read this comment from chat real quick DDR Dollar says in our chat room this caller reminds me of when I was younger and said the avatar from Ultima was female you know yeah when I played Ultima Quest for the Avatar on the NES usually like half of the different class types you could get were females and I think usually the one I would opt to play is like the druid I think or the shepherdess and both were female
[SPEAKER_28]: Unfortunately, I can't think of any system that I regret buying in some way.
[SPEAKER_04]: because I don't get any of my system buys, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I might regret is that I smashed two Game Boys in my time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really...
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them was play, and I actually know the two games that I did play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, first of it was that I smashed my original Game Boy while I was playing Kirby's Pinball Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other time was when I smashed my other Game Boy Pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: playing Wario Land for some strange reason.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those Nintendo pinball games were so freaking good, though.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, the Pokemon pinball was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: I used to play that on it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't think I would have broke a Game Boy over it, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but here's the other thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have... Oh, but here's the other thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was much younger at that time because I was like 12 or something when I...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we lost the connection there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hope we didn't lose the whole damn internet again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, it's still showing us connected and I see the chat room going there, so we're good.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, unfortunately, we lost Hockey Ripper, but Anger Management.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to talk about this, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's talk about your most angry video game moment that just made you like you wanted to break shit or something like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Angry video game moment.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, it looks like you're thinking of something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mike Tyson's punch out, the guy in the turban that span around and he had the little gem on his turban that sparkled when he was going to do his move.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tiger something, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Him, he brought me to tears.
[SPEAKER_28]: Did you actually cry over a video?
[SPEAKER_14]: I cried so much over that guy.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't beat him and it just, I cried.
[SPEAKER_28]: Would you actually do the whole like crying into your pillow thing where you like you throw the controller down and jump on your bed and go No, it was far more heart-wrenching.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you describe?
[SPEAKER_14]: I was utterly defeated as a person.
[SPEAKER_14]: My nine, ten year old self just had like these bitter tears of
[SPEAKER_28]: Several people in chat, thank you.
[SPEAKER_28]: GreatTiger was his name.
[SPEAKER_28]: You've clearly tried to block that from your mind.
[SPEAKER_28]: GreatTiger made you cry.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to make you a little t-shirt or something with this picture on it.
[SPEAKER_28]: GreatTiger made me cry.
[SPEAKER_14]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually got up to Mike Tyson in that game, and I never actually beat it because he was impossible.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yet I was like, this is...
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, this is just stupid how hard this is.
[SPEAKER_14]: So then I just stopped playing to Mike Tyson, but that one boss, I just cried.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think I've thrown controllers, like power outages have made me throw controllers, which is very frustrating.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can't think of any boss fights or anything that have really driven me to that, or cry.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't get a drop in WoW the other day.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not that bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll do the Huffy stomp.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll do the...
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you roll like a 95 and then someone else... That happened.
[SPEAKER_14]: That fucking shit happened to you last week.
[SPEAKER_28]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_28]: And you were like, no, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: And like you typed a chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're like, oh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm glad you won it.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I'm like, he's fucking sitting there fucking throwing a fit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like these probably like pillows are getting thrown in his place right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why do we even fucking do these raves?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hope that drop was worth it when I push you down the stairs next time I see you.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anger Management, DarkSakura any moment in gaming where you've just gotten so angry you wanted to break something?
[SPEAKER_18]: Playing Dan in X-Men vs. Street Fighter, I just wanted to take the controller and embed it firmly into his skull.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because see, Dan, back in the day, and he's still like this to a degree, but not nearly as bad as he used to be.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dan likes to gloat.
[SPEAKER_18]: And likes to be alpha male, you know, big junk.
[SPEAKER_26]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_18]: And back in the day, he had that problem even more.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so he would kick my ass soundly until I would play Cammy and Gambit.
[SPEAKER_18]: and he would just, ha ha, ha ha, you know, he was Nelson.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he would be really dickly about it and finally I'm like, I'm just gonna beat you with this controller.
[SPEAKER_28]: I beat Alan with my shoe last night.
[SPEAKER_18]: How was it, Alan?
[SPEAKER_28]: Was it hot?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let me tell you about this in a minute, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because we have a call.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, who uses a shoe?
[SPEAKER_28]: Caller, you're on the air.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_24]: I have been derailed.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys just derailed me with the talk about their shoe.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is the third time you've called in tonight, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, you must be tired of me calling all the damn time.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_24]: I have an interesting Xbox Live story, which in turn, I end up getting two months free service out of them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, how'd this work?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I always buy the cards to reload my subscription.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a rarity that I actually log in with my credit card, give them my information to re-up me for a month or two.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, the last time this happened, they started automatically debiting my card, and I'm like, no, don't do that.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I set it to make sure that it would not do that.
[SPEAKER_24]: So...
[SPEAKER_24]: I figured I'd go back to the cards and refill.
[SPEAKER_24]: They had that $1 special, so I'm like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to sign up for that.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I signed up for about two months of service, and then I went out and got another card.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I get an email from them saying that they were unable to bill my card because the card was invalid.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I shrug it off like, no big deal.
[SPEAKER_24]: You would think that they would see that in the system I automatically re-upped my account for another year.
[SPEAKER_24]: Every two, three weeks I would get an email about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then one week in July, I figured I'd jump on, buy or something on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_24]: I go in and it says that my account is back to silver.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I'm like, what the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_24]: I call them up.
[SPEAKER_24]: asking them why did they cancel my account.
[SPEAKER_24]: And they said, I did not pay for it.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I'm explaining to them, if you see in the system, I purchased a one-year card.
[SPEAKER_24]: So that makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_24]: So here I am screaming at the poor guy in India who in turn is like, the best thing I can do is get you a supervisor.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm like, yeah, put him on.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm explaining the whole situation.
[SPEAKER_24]: He's like, my hands are tied.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's nothing I can do.
[SPEAKER_24]: At that point, I just drop a nuclear bomb because I'm just beyond aggravated about all of this.
[SPEAKER_24]: And he goes, well, what we can do, we can have a manager call you back within 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here's my number.
[SPEAKER_24]: Call me back in 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_24]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_24]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I go online.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm misunderstanding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: They were set up to charge you automatically.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I canceled that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, you canceled that, but they tried to do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then you used prepaid cards.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what were they doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Were they adding it to the time in the past that you hadn't paid for where you were like, I don't want to use this or I'm still lost right now?
[SPEAKER_24]: What it was doing, the card was supposed to kick in after I paid for one month, which was in April.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: So my live was supposed to go from May 2010 to May, I guess, May 2011 or April 2011.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_24]: Manager never called me back, so I go on to the consumers, find contacts from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_24]: I sent an email to Steve Ballmer and somebody else in charge at Microsoft with Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Within two days, I get a call from the manager.
[SPEAKER_24]: I explain everything.
[SPEAKER_24]: He profusely apologizes and goes into the system.
[SPEAKER_24]: It seems that on the supervisor's end, they don't have access to billing.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, what's the point then?
[SPEAKER_28]: You'd think there ought to be somebody that can fix it, you know?
[SPEAKER_28]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, very.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm like, I'm yelling at the guy, log into your system and fix it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, we don't have access to that.
[SPEAKER_24]: How do you not have access to, you know?
[SPEAKER_28]: Goldanthro in our chatroom at chat.orangelandry.com says, it's because of shit like this that I'm just going to stick to prepaid cards now.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't blame him, but you know, damn it, a dollar for a month is a good deal and you can't beat that.
[SPEAKER_28]: That is a very good deal.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Ranma, anything else you want to say real quick?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because we're going to get back to Angry Games and beating with shoes and stuff in a minute.
[SPEAKER_24]: Long story short, the guy contacts me back, he cancelled my gold, sends me a new code, so now I'm good from July to like June of 2011.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I end up getting like two extra months out of the deal.
[SPEAKER_28]: Must be nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: So in the moral of the story is yelling at the supervisor fixes the trick every time.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: I used to work in a call center.
[SPEAKER_28]: Please don't.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't yell at them.
[SPEAKER_24]: If they can't help you, find me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll give you an email address of somebody that will take care of it for you.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, Ranma, I'm going to let you go for real.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good one, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_28]: I need more vodka.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, good luck.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, where were we?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh yes, Beating with Shoes.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Alan's like, I want to tell this story.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so Rob does not parallel park.
[SPEAKER_14]: He doesn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: In San Francisco, near where I live, parking is more precious than platinum or gold.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you see a space, especially if it's a rock star space right in front of where you're going, you park in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know, if you're used to parking lots and you can't parallel park, you just say fuck that and you keep going.
[SPEAKER_14]: So whenever Rob under extreme duress has to parallel park, I will basically tease the hell out of him for it because he usually will not try.
[SPEAKER_14]: And last night when we were going to his Rocky Horror performance, there were basically three blocks of parallel parking without cars.
[SPEAKER_14]: So he just had to like drive in and sort of scoot his car up to the edge.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I was like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you sure you can handle it?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's parallel parking.
[SPEAKER_14]: So he takes his shoe off and starts whapping me with it.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, no, it was, I said, you better be quieter, I'm gonna beat you in my shoe.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then I think I, like, hit the curb with parking.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, see, and that's the thing, then finally he stops the car and he's like, oh wait, how far away from the curb am I?
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm like, there's no one here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, my original making fun of you still stands, and then he took his shoe off and he hit me with it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, you deserved it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not one to advocate domestic violence, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yeah, he gives me stink eye for making fun of his parallel parking and then he stops the car and we're like five feet away from the curb.
[SPEAKER_14]: With no cars.
[SPEAKER_14]: He didn't have to wiggle wiggle in at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nope, not at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I agree with Brakeman in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck parallel parking.
[SPEAKER_28]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Misty says, fuck driving.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's your attitude, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, that's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_28]: What is it about driving that you're just not going to do it?
[SPEAKER_14]: The expense in, you know, car payment, gas insurance.
[SPEAKER_14]: Someone gets drunk and hits you, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's just, it's awful.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it's really nice, like, being able to go wherever you want, whenever you want.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, that's really, you don't have to rely on really anyone else.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have the internet at home.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't have to go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: What about food?
[SPEAKER_14]: Amazon will ship it to my house.
[SPEAKER_28]: What about if it's like, oh my god, I need some pink berry right now or I'm going to kill somebody.
[SPEAKER_14]: I went there.
[SPEAKER_17]: I heard.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they played ABBA.
[SPEAKER_17]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't it amazing?
[SPEAKER_14]: So good.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had the chocolate with the hazelnut crunch stuff on it and I wanted to die.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've been telling you.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I love the way that place is designed.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_28]: Very cute little place.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry, it's a derail.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Misty in chat says, it's a combo of the expense, the idiots on the road, and my failed attention span.
[SPEAKER_28]: Long drives can be tough.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sometimes I'm like, oh, I want to take a really long drive.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to go drive across country, or I'll drive, I'll do something crazy like go drive to Kansas and visit Shane because it's halfway across the country, or I'll drive up to Canada, like Vancouver or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then I'm like, oh, God.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: We drove to Poster, Washington.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's pretty much just as far.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think last year we did.
[SPEAKER_28]: Drive up there is great.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, Dan drove.
[SPEAKER_18]: I slept.
[SPEAKER_18]: He would stop me on the way back for snow.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love that that's your response.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that was me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I know one of them has, the shoulder button has like a magnet in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you hit it wrong, it'll detach the magnet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can't, if you, because it works with a magnet somehow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so if it's not attached in the right place, it won't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that, for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know the last week when I was playing Burnout Revenge, any time I was like screwing up a bunch, I would get a screaming going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just go, oh, fuck you, god damn it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's so funny how Nintendo, like, puts out this, like, very family-friendly system, you know, and it's like, oh, you know, oh, we have to use friend codes so that children don't hear naughty language and da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I remember back in the day in college playing Super Mario Kart in the dorms, and we would say the filthiest shit while playing that game.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, you know, talking about each other, our mothers, you know, sex stuff, and just all this stuff while playing, you know, Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_28]: It got ugly.
[SPEAKER_28]: Very ugly.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it's not my fault I whoop them all with Toad because he's the best.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those are cars you will drive.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go-karts, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Would you drive like a real go-kart?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm 6'5".
[SPEAKER_14]: Could I fit in one?
[SPEAKER_28]: When we go to Disneyland, will you ride Autotopia?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my god, then I could take a picture of you driving and be all like, hell froze over, lol.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're like, this isn't funny, I want to change the topic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see, Breakman in chat says, long drives are fine as long as your wife or girlfriend sleeps.
[SPEAKER_28]: Lol.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, my girlfriend just keeps telling me how bad of a driver I am.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bitch, I know I'm a bad driver.
[SPEAKER_28]: Close your eyes, you won't notice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, hey, the phone's ringing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why don't we answer it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Aseo again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, what's on your mind, Aseo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I was hoping to talk about Infamous 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you think of Infamous 2?
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell us a little bit about it for those that don't know what Infamous is all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I haven't actually played the game, so I don't really know a whole lot about the story, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: apparently some world ending thing or whatever disaster strikes and here appears by the name of Cole and he has electrical powers now what I want to talk about the second one is how are they going to integrate the ice abilities into the gameplay mechanics because from what I played on the
[SPEAKER_08]: What I played on the demo for the first one, everything just kind of melded together for the electrical abilities, so I'm just wondering how that would work.
[SPEAKER_28]: Unfortunately, it's not a series I'm on the up and up on.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki's kind of the expert about those, and he's not here, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is Infamous a series you've read up on at all, Alan, Jamie, anybody?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know much about this.
[SPEAKER_28]: I bought it, but I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_28]: At least somebody has used it.
[SPEAKER_18]: What series?
[SPEAKER_28]: Infamous.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, um, no.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're so informed here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, we don't have time to play everything.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: We can't play anything right now because Dan's playing the game that shan't be named.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: They've been playing that all night.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was thinking about playing Sims.
[SPEAKER_28]: As long as we have been doing this marathon, they have been playing the game we can't name.
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Once again, it shall not be named.
[SPEAKER_28]: Name it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's violent.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is there a reason why?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because it's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_28]: He's playing Imagine Single Lady.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't tell you what we were playing.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know nothing.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know nothing, you savages.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's been about an hour.
[SPEAKER_28]: You guys want to take a quick break here?
[SPEAKER_28]: Take a stretch?
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to get more water.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to take a potty stretch break.
[SPEAKER_28]: Come back.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got some more topics we got through Facebook.
[SPEAKER_28]: Twitter topics galore we still have to do.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, you have to do the theme.
[SPEAKER_28]: What theme?
[SPEAKER_18]: The Pala Pala Parapara thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I didn't have time to set it up.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've just put everything on shuffle.
[SPEAKER_28]: So maybe you'll get the... I know you like this song.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll do this song.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: You'll like this.
[SPEAKER_28]: And so we'll be back with more of the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon as we enter into hour eight in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll be back with more of the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon, your tweets, so forth and so on.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_28]: of our marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: We started at two and it's now ten.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, and it probably doesn't turn out that long on the podcast because we have been taking musical breaks, which some people might consider cheating, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: We gotta go to the bathroom at some point.
[SPEAKER_28]: We gotta eat.
[SPEAKER_28]: We gotta, you know, just get up and stretch.
[SPEAKER_28]: This room gets kind of stuffy too, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's just how it works.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you don't like it, too bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: The show's free, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_28]: Stop complaining about free things.
[SPEAKER_28]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: I should say though, if you want to support free things, you can always leave us a nice review on iTunes or tell a couple people about the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's what we always ask.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just tell some friends and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's all we want.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Chat's asking about chat FUs.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can we do some chat FUs?
[SPEAKER_18]: Are we going to read some of those?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go ahead and send them and I'll read them in about 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: Meanwhile, Twitter, we never got around to doing the tweets that were sent us in the last segment because I asked for some tweets and we got on tangents talking about Angry Games and the callers that we had and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I'm going to try to get to some tweets.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I don't have the Twitter music.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can't do tweets without the Twitter music.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_28]: I ruined everything.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have to stop the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_19]: No!
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_14]: When you were out getting pizza, I deleted all of the native OLR music files.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're gone.
[SPEAKER_28]: You jerk.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, I found it.
[SPEAKER_28]: We love our Twitter, O-L-R-E-D To KRA saying, how is the Final Fantasy XIV beta?
[SPEAKER_28]: Isn't it just a prettier FFXI?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's FFXI with different combat and this whole guild leps thing that makes no sense to me whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_28]: The biggest problem with Final Fantasy XI is that it doesn't handhold you at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: And like, I agree, some games overdo it with the handholding.
[SPEAKER_28]: But what was the most frustrating thing about Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_28]: The fact that it just plunks you in the middle of a town and was like, okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_18]: The people.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: So Final Fantasy XIV, the beta is really crowded.
[SPEAKER_28]: I couldn't figure out what to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: I couldn't figure out that there was a whole other map level I was supposed to go to and activate a switch.
[SPEAKER_28]: You would think the game would lead you through the first couple quests just to kind of give you a tutorial about how the game works, the interface, you know?
[SPEAKER_28]: maybe it's because it's a beta not all of that's built in yet but I just the beta left me feeling very frustrated and that's why I'm kind of laughing at all this like closed betas or the open beta stuff going on is I'm like guys it's not worth your time okay but hey it's a free game and at least you'll know if you can uh buy it when it comes out or not but I honestly think the game is going to tank I think it's going to tank bad especially for a Final Fantasy game like I think they're expecting it to do really well it's not going to do nearly the business 13 did
[SPEAKER_28]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Blaziken sent us several tweets.
[SPEAKER_28]: Usually I limit people to two tweets, but hey, it's the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_28]: So DJ Blaziken says, What's cuter than a cat playing Duck Hunt?
[SPEAKER_28]: Nothing!
[SPEAKER_28]: And sends us this tweet, or sorry, article via Twitter.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I actually did see this.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's a video on YouTube of a kitty who's actually playing Duck Hunt.
[SPEAKER_28]: And they start the game there.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then the kid, this is terrible radio, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_28]: And the cat, see the cat's like scratching the dog with her paws.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like attacking the ducks even though they fly off screen.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tell me that's not adorable.
[SPEAKER_28]: Cats are so damn cute.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Blaziken says, don't bother watching football this season.
[SPEAKER_28]: Madden 11 already picked all the winners.
[SPEAKER_28]: And linked us to a news story about how I guess all the winners are already, it's been determined because, you know, there's all the statistics in Madden and everything.
[SPEAKER_28]: The Ravens and Packers will be the conference winners.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I just, I, LOL Super Bowl spoilers.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think the football star that actually is on the cover of Madden has the Madden curse.
[SPEAKER_14]: So like if you're the guy who's on the box art, they have a horrible season after the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's like a thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't follow the ball.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've heard the same thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: They always get injured or something happens.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who was on the cover this year?
[SPEAKER_28]: I wasn't paying attention.
[SPEAKER_28]: Was it Brett Favre?
[SPEAKER_28]: People like him.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tiger Woods.
[SPEAKER_14]: David Beckham.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's football, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's David Beckham.
[SPEAKER_28]: It is.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Blaze can send us a story that we talked about in the very first hour of the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I'm just going to assume you didn't hear it about Microsoft raising the price of Xbox Live Gold.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll just pretend that I didn't get that tweet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Apparently Super Scribblenauts is there.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's an announcement about Super Scribblenauts or whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Red Entertainment is linking us to this story on Twitter at Mega64.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess they're excited because they're in the game.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're actually in the game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whoopty shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you know who I am?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I don't expect people to know who I am.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yay to them getting in a game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess now I won't be able to get away from it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll have to know who they are.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was... I don't know if I should say this because this is getting back to... I won't go into it any further.
[SPEAKER_28]: Allegedly.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: The word allegedly will always say it over and over again.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is an alleged story.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's all allegedly.
[SPEAKER_28]: Allegedly, it was a large man with glasses.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I think that's all of them, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_28]: I think in that video they were all large men with glasses, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't think that tells you anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, large men in IT and software development.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yay for Super Scribblenauts.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sony is going to be rolling out Arrival to iTunes, apparently.
[SPEAKER_28]: Didn't Loki bring this up earlier in the show?
[SPEAKER_28]: I think he did.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shout out!
[SPEAKER_28]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's see, moving on.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkTetsuya says, I know this is a more local question, but will the Golfland slash Dave and Buster meetup still happen sometime soon?
[SPEAKER_18]: They've been happening.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, well there wasn't one this past week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well no, because Dan and I were saving money and time for our anniversary.
[SPEAKER_18]: But they've been happening.
[SPEAKER_28]: History will repeat itself.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, it'll happen again, of course.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, Jeju Go on chat says, uh, how much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
[SPEAKER_28]: Possible, impromptu, listless?
[SPEAKER_28]: Question mark.
[SPEAKER_28]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_28]: We do need to do a listless at some point before the marathon's over.
[SPEAKER_18]: How about during the next break we write up stuff?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, we'll write that in a match game during the next break and then we'll have something to play for real, so that'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see, Amay Satsuma says, what kind of pre-order bonus do you want to see in Duke Nukem Forever?
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to see a Duke Nukem Forever urinal cake.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think that would be quite classy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't you think that would be very classy?
[SPEAKER_27]: I know, I think it's classy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anybody here in the studio, what kind of pre-order bonus do you want to see for Duke Nukem Forever?
[SPEAKER_28]: How about Duke Nukem Forever pasties for your stripper friends?
[SPEAKER_28]: That would be good, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_18]: I want the stripper pole.
[SPEAKER_28]: You want the stripper pole?
[SPEAKER_18]: I want the pole and a gun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, anything?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Other tweets at OLR.
[SPEAKER_28]: Breakman says on Twitter, What are the OLR drinking games?
[SPEAKER_28]: What are the rules?
[SPEAKER_28]: Can the chatters play together?
[SPEAKER_28]: I use any excuse.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, drink anytime one of us says um.
[SPEAKER_28]: You'll be floored in like a minute.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, uh, oopsie drink.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think there is a drinking game compiled on the Orange Lounge Radio wiki, which is orangeloungeradio.wikia.com.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to say there is a drinking game compiled there.
[SPEAKER_28]: And it combines some stuff with Under Sedation Live, if you listen to that show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm looking at Twitter and there's a tweet from Travis earlier six hours ago so that was during the main show actually heard something on OLR that made me angry and dislike the show and that is something that never happened before okay he's so theatrical I love Travis but just say what it is or I mean I don't know what else to say sorry Travis sorry we ruffled your feathers alright anyhow
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it for Twitter.
[SPEAKER_28]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to send us some tweets.
[SPEAKER_28]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now what?
[SPEAKER_28]: What are we talking about now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, chat FUs.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do we have chat FUs?
[SPEAKER_28]: Just about.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sufficient chat angst?
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you mean just about?
[SPEAKER_28]: Either you do or you don't.
[SPEAKER_18]: You do.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, let's get to the angsty music and we'll do some chat FUs right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: First one comes from Toygak.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to being East Coast.
[SPEAKER_18]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thanks for the amazing show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ranma, massive F you to Pepsi cult.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: Stop Drinkle holding Pepsi throwback even though it's in limited edition.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's still hard to find.
[SPEAKER_18]: Add to snatch the last 12 pack of throwback out of someone's cart.
[SPEAKER_18]: Step it up, Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, it's everywhere here, really.
[SPEAKER_18]: Weiland, F you to this ear infection and the hearing loss that's gone with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Owen, F you to that one guy.
[SPEAKER_18]: The one guy that did that stuff back then at that place.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkTetia, fuck having to wake up early to fly home tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_18]: Poor baby.
[SPEAKER_18]: Breakman, my F you.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to five day work weeks.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to faux holidays.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know in some places they work six days a week.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkCircuitry, F you to annoying little fucking kids who jump up on the 2P pad while you're playing a particularly difficult doubles chart in, insert dance game of choice here, thereby either ruining your score, distracting you, or causing you to fail out entirely, or fall out entirely.
[SPEAKER_18]: DDR Dollar, FU on two parts.
[SPEAKER_18]: One for someone on IRC who actually has my name.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm the fucking original, damn it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And two for the Call of Duty Black Ops developers who are trying to get people like me to play more multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Final Fantasy VII, FU to the bad effects.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hours later from eating extremely hot slash spicy food.
[SPEAKER_18]: Feeling like you're giving birth to lava blows.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Eat more crackers.
[SPEAKER_18]: They'll help.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ray Goldrush.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to this Japanese textbook for being confusing and hard to learn vocabulary and kanji in.
[SPEAKER_18]: Kawaisone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alpha Kananagram.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to me having to wait for next Tuesday for 360.
[SPEAKER_18]: Poor baby.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm officially out of topics.
[SPEAKER_28]: What is your favorite video game of all time?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well said TGL, bitches
[SPEAKER_28]: Guardian Legend Bradley, what is your favorite video game of all time?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hard for me to decide Go on It's too hard I love them all so much Alan?
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to try this one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Valkyrie Profile
[SPEAKER_14]: and Ty Maniac you can't pick two you're a cheater no okay fine you pick two Maniac Mansion okay why Valkyrie Profile because your mom I don't know don't give me that look like I don't need a reason bitch like there's gotta be something about the game that you like right the art the music the story the unmatched combat no RPG has ever really done what was the combat in Valkyrie Profile for those that don't know
[SPEAKER_14]: it was a weird hybrid of active time battle and real time it had really insane combos in it like Street Fighter why Maniac Mansion?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: I barely remember that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think you're right, though.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm almost positive there was.
[SPEAKER_28]: Did you actually play that through to completion?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is it true you can beat it with every combination of characters, or no, you can't do it with all of them?
[SPEAKER_14]: There are... I know that there are two or three characters that it's really preferred that you have at least one of them in there, but yeah, I think you can beat it with all, with any three.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wait, here you go, here you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Look at this, Blast in the Past.
This is a live-action movie.
Yeah, it was a live-action show.
A TV show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my gosh, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was almost like a drama, the way the credits make it look like, huh?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's see, let me see if I can go... Oh, it was created by Eugene Levy, really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, wait, there's a... I think it ran for like three episodes before they pulled the plug on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is like a scene out of Twin Peaks or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is creepy.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't like this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, this is upsetting.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's upsetting me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is it ruining your memory of the show?
[SPEAKER_28]: Or is it ruining your memory of the game?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is it making you like the game a little less?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it has nothing to do with the game, so... Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it said in the credits, based on the Lucasfilm game, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, save it for when you get home
[SPEAKER_18]: It was even mentioned during this show.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because Bob grabbed my copy and goes, Look!
[SPEAKER_28]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_28]: And yet I haven't bought Metroid Other M because I'm afraid it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've heard from people it's great.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've been hearing mixed things on it and I'm very worried.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I have to hook up my Wii to play it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't want to hook up the Wii.
[SPEAKER_18]: Solution.
[SPEAKER_18]: Netflix.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: or Gamefly or whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I was like, Netflix?
[SPEAKER_18]: You can get games through Netflix too.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I could do the Netfly, the Gamefly thing, but that would involve me again getting the motivation to hook up the Wii to my TV and that means, you know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, it takes 10 freaking minutes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not in my house.
[SPEAKER_14]: You've had a Gamefly account since like March that's been rotting since March.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't really ever use it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is it worth it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Should I play Metroid Other M if I'm such a stan for Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_18]: Chat, vote, why in?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Breakman says watch FNG Friday Night Gaming or F-ing Live.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's F-ing Live.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bobby's going to show Metroid Other M. Maybe I'll check that out.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_28]: I might.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley, time's up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you think of something?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'd probably go with Panzer Dragoon Saga.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a really epic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one game when the first time I saw the battle system, I got, whoa, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because it's such a different system and seeing that you're flying right next to the enemies that you're fighting, it's like, oh, this is really, really, really neat because you're flying around them in a circle and then you attack based on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then just a really cool storyline and lots of things to explore and neat things never played it sadly I think I've played all the other games that have been mentioned but I've never played that for some sick reason I'm just not cool yeah well it was only a limited edition and all that kind of stuff it's definitely worth a play I want to say that only 6,000 copies were printed in the US when it came out wow no wonder it's so expensive
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see some folks in chat about Metroid Other M. Yes, yes, yes, why, why?
[SPEAKER_28]: But then I got a private message that says it sucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: So maybe the people who think it sucks don't want to speak up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Frisbee says at least try it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, there's Miklatov saying no.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, we got last minute FU.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ranma says someone get Sky some caffeine stat.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Breakman says fuck caffeine, get him some more booze and a cot.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is there caffeine in that?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's real dark Pepsi.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can finish it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got the last one so you can have it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, what'd you have for you?
[SPEAKER_18]: From Marissa, F you to not seeing Rob and Jamie, heart, heart, heart, need to visit.
[SPEAKER_18]: From Marissa.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell her about Tron.
[SPEAKER_28]: She wasn't listening earlier.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're giving it to me?
[SPEAKER_28]: I am.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're a nice lady.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm gonna have more beer.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you want some Pepsi?
[SPEAKER_26]: Good, because I wasn't gonna give it to you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, we're planning on going to see Tron at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_28]: But then your mic cut out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hint, hint, hint to people who work at Disneyland, let us in.
[SPEAKER_18]: But no, we're planning on going to see Tron and go to the big Tron party and then go have ourselves digitized so we can live in Tron world and then go play the Tron level in Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then, then we might find a life.
[SPEAKER_18]: Play that music.
[SPEAKER_28]: What music?
[SPEAKER_28]: Didn't I give you the Tron music from... Oh, because I have it just right here sitting in front of me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fine, I'm going to email it to you.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just happen to have it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Right here, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's on the desktop.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have it saved just for circumstances like this when Jamie's going to shout randomly.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't make me break out the Vuvuzela.
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't you have that freaking... Whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just don't want this.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're almost nine hours into the broadcast and tensions are finally... That's right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tensions are finally flaring.
[SPEAKER_28]: I will vote you off this island.
[SPEAKER_28]: I will shove that Vuvuzela so far up your ass.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ah, stop!
[SPEAKER_18]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_18]: Fucker.
[SPEAKER_18]: There.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just got a text message from my friend Nathan.
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe it was a mistake to post about this on Facebook, because I think some of my real-life friends suddenly tune in.
[SPEAKER_28]: I post on my Facebook.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm on hour eight of my radio show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Please help.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, but Nathan sent me a text saying, if you run out of stuff to talk about, there is always the D&D campaign I ran with you as the sassy black lady.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's so funny?
[SPEAKER_28]: We had fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can just imagine you playing the sassy black lady.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, because I've heard you do impressions of people and I could totally see you doing the sassy black lady.
[SPEAKER_18]: You did pull off a good Jewish mother once.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_27]: Rob, why aren't you picking up your phone?
[SPEAKER_27]: You need to call your mother.
[SPEAKER_17]: See?
[SPEAKER_18]: He does it really well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you cast like, oh hell no, and it has like a one day cooldown where you use it on like an orc and you couldn't cast it again for another day?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, you know, no, it's just like, you know, all these freaking elves and dwarf people up in here, like, you know, we need some, we need to represent.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, good times.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Silent Nathan says he was the best noob player I've ever had.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, this is the time.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've told you about the ex, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: The one that just ruined everything.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, no matter where you take him, he'd ruin it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, for some reason, I invited him to play D&D with us, and he was also a noob at this whole thing, and man, he just ruined it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, you know, he'd be like, you know, you know, oh, I want to cast a spell.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, it's in the book.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to cast a spell in the book.
Um...
[SPEAKER_28]: He's like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to show my titties.
[SPEAKER_28]: How do I show my titties?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not lying.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was like that, allegedly.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was like this.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, Rob, I'm sending you something.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you need to read the email on the air.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why?
[SPEAKER_18]: I just sent it to you.
[SPEAKER_28]: to my personal email?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to roll a cleric, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's its name?
[SPEAKER_28]: He was a cleric!
[SPEAKER_28]: He was a priest in WoW, so he wanted to be a priest in whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Pull up the Satan's Game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Satan's Game?
[SPEAKER_18]: On YouTube.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dungeons and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_18]: Satan's Game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because you brought that up and it'll give us time for you to check your email.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've got like a million things I'm trying to do.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe you don't.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe 100,000.
[SPEAKER_28]: I told Nathan to call in and talk about D&D, but he doesn't want to.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_28]: Satan's Game?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Should be Dungeons & Dragons.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dungeons & Dragons, Satan's Game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't think that's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like it or not, are attracted in their weaker years Dungeons and Dragons
[SPEAKER_21]: Satan's Game.
[SPEAKER_21]: Your children, like it or not, are attracted in their weaker years to the occult, and a game like D&D fuels their imagination and makes them feel special while drawing them deeper and deeper into the bowels of El Diablo.
[SPEAKER_21]: This afternoon, the Dead Alewives Watchtower invites you to sit in on an actual gaming session.
[SPEAKER_21]: Observe the previously unobservable
[SPEAKER_21]: What's with the extra music?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go look it up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'll be right there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do the 8-bit theater one.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was right there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dungeons and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't want to hear the opening.
[SPEAKER_21]: As a hidden camera takes you to the inner sanctum of Dungeons and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_13]: Galstaff, you have entered the door to the north.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are now by yourself, standing in a dark room.
[SPEAKER_13]: The pungent stench of mildew emanates from the wet dungeon walls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where are they?
[SPEAKER_13]: They're right next to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I cast a spell!
[SPEAKER_11]: Where's the Mountain Dew?
[SPEAKER_13]: In the fridge, duh!
[SPEAKER_13]: I wanna cast a spell!
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, you can have a Mountain Dew, just go get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can cast any of these, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: On the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, any of the first level ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm gonna get a soda, anyone want one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Cram, I'm not in the room, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: What room?
[SPEAKER_13]: I wanna cast Magic Missile.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just wanna point out, this is exactly, this is true.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is all true.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's the funny thing about this video and why you people are laughing at it, because if you've ever been to play D&D, this is it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It really is like this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you a D&D player, Alan?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_28]: Never?
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you never played D&D?
[SPEAKER_14]: I bought the rulebook, the kit, when I was in 6th or 7th grade, but I just read it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I never actually had any friends to play with.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm getting a call.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm getting a call.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is Simon Nathan.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, Nathan!
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_18]: You got any Cheetos?
[SPEAKER_18]: You got any Mountain Dew?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll get back to the funny in a minute, but Nathan started this whole stupid D&D conversation in the first place, so you're a D&D nerd, right, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: and you still play D&D, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm the dungeon master.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're the dungeon master?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Right, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm the gatekeeper, you're the key master.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's the dungeon master and you're the cavalier.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, shush.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so you wanted to talk about me playing Dungeons & Dragons.
[SPEAKER_28]: So what was it like to have me as your player in Dungeons & Dragons?
[SPEAKER_09]: You do remember the orc panty seller, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Vaguely, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, I do actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys wanted to buy your fancy lingerie because all you dudes and women were playing women characters and they needed fancy lingerie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, it's important.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_18]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to hear more, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did Rob roll his charisma check?
[SPEAKER_09]: The normal go-down-kill rats in the basement.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had to fight undead chickens.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, I remember that quest.
[SPEAKER_28]: I actually distinctly remember.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was like one of the first... I think it was like the first or second night we ever played.
[SPEAKER_28]: We did the undead chickens in the basement.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I have to know, did Rob make his charisma rolls?
[SPEAKER_18]: Did he save or fail?
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, stop.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let the man talk, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_28]: No, that's Panda Lady's
[SPEAKER_08]: Sister is here visiting.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, say hello.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell what we said hello and send our love from OLR.
[SPEAKER_26]: What was I going to ask?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello and all that.
[SPEAKER_28]: What was I going to say about... Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: How was it having me in your game?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because Alan really likes to hear stories about how terrible my ex was.
[SPEAKER_28]: How was it having me in the game versus having my ex in the game, allegedly?
[SPEAKER_09]: It
[SPEAKER_09]: It took extra time.
[SPEAKER_09]: He slowed things down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your very first quest, you were in a basement with shelves, and he decided that he wanted to climb these shelves to get a better look at the surroundings of the basement.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can see that happening once, but he tried it at least three times, one of which he rolled a natural one and knocked over the shelf.
[SPEAKER_16]: Which is just like real life, allegedly.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: He was special.
[SPEAKER_28]: But he's not here anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's the important thing, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: He kept thinking that
[SPEAKER_09]: The cleric was a priest and he kept trying to cast his wow spells in D&D.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cast smite.
[SPEAKER_14]: Smite.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want the bubble.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll cast a bubble.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to cast a bubble.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nathan's laughing because he knows I'm telling the truth.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not exaggerating anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's exactly what happened.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sadly, I'm not playing D&D with you guys anymore because I travel to the Bay pretty much every weekend when you guys play.
[SPEAKER_28]: But what kind of adventures do you do in D&D now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, they're not too ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there was a big asshole who everyone kind of hates who's the big hero of the town.
[SPEAKER_09]: His name's Larbio.
[SPEAKER_09]: and he's modeled after Fabio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only more sexual harassment involved.
[SPEAKER_18]: Does his hair have its own saving throw?
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but he did have commercials for a fancy type of butter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't believe it's not butter light.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the thing about that was it glowed in the dark.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Your games totally rock.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: One of these days, Nathan, I'm going to have to drop in and make a cameo.
[SPEAKER_28]: If I could find my old character sheet, although to be honest, I think it's long gone.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think it's in that box of things that remind me of the X that got shredded when I left.
[SPEAKER_28]: So sadly, I don't know if I have it anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I'll have to make a cameo at some point in your game.
[SPEAKER_28]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every once in a while we've done some drunk D&D nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've done two of those so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Eddie has actually come to those.
[SPEAKER_09]: And one time we played the campaign module that the guys from Penny Arcade had made and was making fun of the Twilight movies.
[SPEAKER_28]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, you're more than welcome to stop by.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a perfect time because we don't do any big campaigns.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just something stupid and we get drunk and laugh.
[SPEAKER_28]: I will absolutely do that.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I'll cast Bubble.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I cast Bubble?
[SPEAKER_26]: No.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is not wild.
[SPEAKER_28]: and that's exactly how Nathan would have to respond to like trying to bite his tongue like you could sense he just wants to jump over the table and be like you're fucking ruining my fucking game you little shit like you just no you can't you can't you can't do that this is this is D&D you not wow it's not no no all right Nathan thank you so much for calling in and good luck with the D&D okay no problem you have a good time the rest of your hours oh we will take care buddy all right bye
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm gonna call him For this incarnation I'm gonna yell at him right now
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi Shane, how are you?
[SPEAKER_28]: It's Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're live on the radio, et cetera, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_28]: You playing WoW?
[SPEAKER_08]: You playing the beta?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, I wasn't playing the beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was fishing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have to ask you a question because this is really important, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have to answer it.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, you do.
[SPEAKER_28]: How did we meet?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't pay attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just words that come out of the radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, okay, if there's something that's interesting, I'll pick it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a phone number?
[SPEAKER_28]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Oh, see, I was going to dial 1-866.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I think I got the other two things right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was like, wait, that could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might get like...
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, a porn line or something Yeah, it's 877, just for the future Just so you know Alright, well, I'm calling you because you were telling me about a bunch of cool stuff you saw this past week So where were you?
[SPEAKER_28]: What was going on?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know what you can and can't say Where were you at?
[SPEAKER_28]: What were you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: What's cool?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was at the GameStop Managers Conference in Austin, but not San Antonio Is there... What's awesome in San Antonio?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyone?
[SPEAKER_28]: The Alamo Did you go to the Alamo?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not a tourist.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care about that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know what the Alamo is because I think people died there or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can you say tortilla?
[SPEAKER_28]: Tortilla.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is that Showgirls?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I think they played a clip of that at our conference because it was like she was in a phone booth and
[SPEAKER_08]: The stars at night shine big and bright
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't think it will if I end in rape or shooting
[SPEAKER_12]: The first time I went to, whoa, that's loud.
[SPEAKER_12]: The first time I went to a manager's conference in Texas, that was exactly the first thing I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I called Mystique.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was like, hey, I'm in Texas.
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen, I'll prove it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the people played along.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I'm sorry you didn't get to go to the conference this year, Dan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I haven't gone to a GameStop conference for a while.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm missing, I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I'm sorry I did too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, uh...
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so tell us, I don't know what you can or can't tell us about the conference, Shane, but tell us about your experience there at the conference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'll start off with some highs.
[SPEAKER_08]: The very first thing that we had to see, we were broken into groups, so we had to go to different vendors.
[SPEAKER_08]: The very first thing we saw in my group was a trailer of tons of different fatalities from the new Mortal Kombat game, and they were hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any that you remember?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Any that you remember?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one where a reptile threw up in somebody's mouth, like a whole bunch of acid.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think I saw a porn like that once, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one where Sector blew up somebody's torso into a few different pieces, and as the pieces were flying up into the air, he locked onto each individual piece and shot missiles at them, so it made them explode even more.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one where Skurkin cut right through the guy at the waistline and he didn't fall over or anything and then he cut the guy through the neck all the way through and then he kicked the torso so just the torso flew and then the head flew up and he took his little knife and sliced the head in half.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, oh, that's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is sounding like a Saw movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: What were the stage ones?
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you see any of those?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they didn't show any stage ones, but they did show in the new acid pit place, or old acid pit place, I guess you would call it, one of the background dudes that was hanging, like, you saw him get dipped into the acid, and he was, like, screaming and freaking out, and then they pulled him back up, and he wasn't on a skeleton, he was, like, this fleshy, dead...
[SPEAKER_18]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was it like the Mortal Kombat 2 acid pit?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I want this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if this has come out yet, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had tag team combo things like they do in the Marvel vs. Capcom games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you could be beating somebody up and then tag in another partner and they'll jump right in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was crazy cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_28]: So they stole that from Marvel vs. Capcom, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I don't know if any other games did it before, but probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, what else was cool there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that was the coolest thing I think I saw, which is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did get to play Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know how to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried to play it like WoW and that got me killed pretty quick and nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: I give up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand that I'm terrible at it and I won't buy it.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Diablo is awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: I like it better than StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to get my budget for StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not buying StarCraft either, but if they give me a WoW pet, maybe I'll get it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, what have you been doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because I know you were able to get into the Cata Beta as well.
[SPEAKER_28]: What have you been doing in the Cata Beta?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have played a Worgen up to 12 almost, and then a Goblin up to 4, because that's where the quest is currently broken and we can't proceed.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Worgen's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game doesn't feel like WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll say that right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does not feel like the same game we've been playing for so many years, just going through the Worgen and Goblin experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the Worgen's all depressing, and, oh, we've got to save our home from these attacks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God, we're going to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I was like, let me get some bling glasses and I got running over people with my car and it's the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love the Goblin area so, so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was laughing the entire time.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't know what to do at first.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was like,
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really close to this guy, why am I not throwing the barrel?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you have to get right up next to him.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, that was pretty funny and I laughed at that.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to do a spoiler for the Worgen questline, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it was a fun glitch that happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a part where you're fighting Sylvanas and the whole town is fighting Sylvanas and she knocks you back and she's about to shoot Gen Greymane, the leader of the Worgen people.
[SPEAKER_08]: with this poison arrow, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: But instead, his son jumps up front to take the arrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when I played, she was facing the opposite direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: So she shot, like, facing to the screen's left, and the prince was right behind her.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it still killed him.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like...
[SPEAKER_08]: That just ruins the mood.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't see that part.
[SPEAKER_28]: It just skipped over it, I think.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't read that at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's in the church.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I knew there was one there, but I didn't see anything on the screen telling me that something was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew it was going to happen, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really care about my worgen nearly as much as I care about the goblin now because the goblin is so funny like the music is all like I don't know whimsical when you play as a goblin in your radio that goes only to 11 but yeah I like it it's not wow what we're used to but it's neat to the evolution of the game
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, you haven't checked out any of the new areas yet?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because that's what I'm waiting to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want my stupid character to copy over so I can check out the new areas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still can't get my character to copy over.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm at Darkshore now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll get to see that area redone, but no character copying over.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's making me a little sad.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was having the same problem.
[SPEAKER_28]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, like a month ago, I wouldn't have ever said this, but I think I'm a huge Microsoft down boy now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: So your loyalty can be bought?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I pay you like $20, you'll wear like an Orange Lounge radio sticker to work?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll wear a sticker?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I wear stickers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Will you wear a shirt?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I can't wear a shirt that says Orange Lounge to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_08]: but I'll pretend and I'll still take the $20.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not going to cut it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll wear that sticker.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we're letting you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're useless to me without being able to promote.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, thank you Shane for being on.
[SPEAKER_28]: Appreciate the phone calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see, which would... Oh, I never played the rest of this Dungeons & Dragons thing, so should I finish this, even though the mood is gone?
[SPEAKER_17]: Or start it over.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: Dungeons & Dragons
[SPEAKER_21]: Satan's Game.
[SPEAKER_21]: Your children, like it or not, are attracted in their weaker years to the occult, and a game like D&D fuels their imagination and makes them feel special while drawing them deeper and deeper into the bowels of El Diablo.
[SPEAKER_21]: This afternoon, the Dead Alewives Watchtower invites you to sit in on an actual gaming session.
[SPEAKER_21]: Observe the previously unobservable as a hidden camera takes you to the inner sanctum of Dungeons & Dragons.
[SPEAKER_13]: Galstaff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have entered the door to the north.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are now by yourself, standing in a dark room.
[SPEAKER_13]: The pungent stench of mildew emanates from the wet dungeon walls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where are the Cheetos?
[SPEAKER_13]: They're right next to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I cast a spell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where's the Mountain Dew?
[SPEAKER_13]: In the fridge, duh.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to cast a spell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I have a
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, you can have them out and do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just go get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can cast any of these, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: On the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, any of the first level ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to get a soda.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyone want one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Cram, I'm not in the room, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: What room?
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to cast Magic Missile.
[SPEAKER_11]: The room where he's casting all these spells from.
[SPEAKER_13]: He hasn't cast anything yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am, though, if you'd listen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm casting Magic Missile.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why are you casting Magic Missile?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's nothing to attack here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm attacking the darkness!
[SPEAKER_13]: Fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: You attack the darkness.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's an elf in front of you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_13]: That's me, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: He's wearing a brown tunic, and he has gray hair and blue eyes.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have gray eyes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me see that sheet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it says I have blue, but I decided I wanted gray eyes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, you guys can talk to each other now if you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am Galstaff, Sorcerer of Light.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then how come you had to cast Magic Missile?
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are being attacked.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you're outside by the tavern.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool, I get drunk.
[SPEAKER_13]: There are seven ogres surrounding you.
[SPEAKER_10]: How could they surround us?
[SPEAKER_10]: I had Mordenkainen's magical watchdog cast.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are there any girls there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I totally did.
[SPEAKER_10]: You asked me if I wanted any equipment before this adventure, and I said no.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I need material components for all my spells, so I cast Mordenkainen's faithful watchdog.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you never actually cast it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Roll the dice to see if I'm getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you are.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are there any girls there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I completely said when you asked me.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: You didn't actually say that you were casting the spell.
[SPEAKER_13]: So now there's ogres, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ogres?
[SPEAKER_11]: Man, I got an ogre slaying knife.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's got a plus nine against ogres.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're not there.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, but if there's any girls there, I want to do them.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_21]: A frightening look into America's most frightening pastime.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember that it's not your children's fault that they're being drawn into a satanic world of nightmare.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's their gym teacher's fault for making them feel outcast when they couldn't do one single pull-up.
[SPEAKER_28]: All true.
[SPEAKER_28]: All of it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: 100% true.
[SPEAKER_28]: Including the pull-up.
[SPEAKER_28]: I actually, you know, funny enough, Nathan thinks that he popped my D&D cherry, but that's not true.
[SPEAKER_28]: I actually played in high school with some friends of mine.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hadn't played in years and years after that, but there was a little group of us in high school that used to play, and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: One of my friends was really into it.
[SPEAKER_28]: He would talk about the campaign at times that wasn't appropriate.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know, but you, me, and Ben will all start talking about WoW like, oh yeah, there was that raid yesterday and oh man, the fight and if we'd only done this differently and you can see Jim and Victoria looking at each other like how far away are we from the bar?
[SPEAKER_28]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what are we going to do as soon as we get back to your place?
[SPEAKER_28]: We gotta run the daily, that's why this marathon has to be over before 3am when the frickin' servers reset 4, 4am I'm kidding, I'm kidding, God We missed the daily yesterday, Friday?
[SPEAKER_14]: Two days ago Didn't kill us We didn't do a daily That's alright, we'll be okay So you owe me two frosts, I'm very upset
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I... Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, kids.
[SPEAKER_18]: I told Alan.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm like, Alan, you might want to mark yourself tentative for the raid Monday because I don't know if we're going to be able to run because you're going to be visiting me and, you know... We might go out for Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, we might go out because it's Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, I have the day off.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Alan's like...
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm just helping.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm just...
[SPEAKER_28]: You should be saying, oh, yes Come to dinner with me Let me get you outside the house at 8 o'clock Let's get ice cream tomorrow Let's go to Pinkberry Let's go to Pinkberry No, here's the thing, I'm going to tell Alan We will go to Pinkberry tomorrow, but we're only going to go to Pinkberry At 7.50 That's the only time we can go to Pinkberry
[SPEAKER_28]: Pinkberry's closed the rest of the day for inventory.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just playing along.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jvmon in chat says, I was going to play WoW with my boyfriend, but then he dumped me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Debbie Downer.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, but...
[SPEAKER_28]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: The couple that games together stays together.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or at least appreciates each other's nerddom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, I've dated guys in the past, you know, and I've talked about this in the past on the show, is that part of the difficulty of being gay sometimes is that most gay guys you meet are like, let's talk about fashion, let's talk about Madonna, or oh my god, Lady Gaga, you know, all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: And, you know, it's just like, I'm not, like, you know, I like Lady Gaga, I guess, but as far as, like, all that other stuff, like, I'm not, like, into that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just play classes with different armor classes so you don't have to roll against the same loot.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you will have a happy relationship.
[SPEAKER_14]: Clothy and a plate, you never have to roll on the same loot.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'll be together for years.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hold on, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, damn it, I just missed it.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's alright, I'll call him back.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll call him, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll call him.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because he's a WoW guildie, and so I'm sure he has some insight on this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_28]: I saw you were trying to call.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're not taking no days off.
[SPEAKER_15]: You and Alan take off, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_15]: you the best healer, Alan the best DPS.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to be in a lot of trouble for our guild.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, no, you're not taking tomorrow off.
[SPEAKER_15]: I understand it's a holiday.
[SPEAKER_15]: You schedule it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're going to show up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know that's part of the deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want my frost badges.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want my T10 pants.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't get my T10 pants unless you guys show up.
[SPEAKER_18]: They have to go get Pinkberry with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can get Pinkberry afterwards.
[SPEAKER_28]: It won't take that long.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, Pinkberry closes at 10 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't stop rating until 10, 30, 11 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's more important?
[SPEAKER_28]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's more important?
[SPEAKER_28]: Two Frost Badges or fucking original Pinkberry with watermelon and mango?
[SPEAKER_15]: Frost Badges because I could care less.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not playing Star Trek Online right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_28]: You're supposed to be supporting me in this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, Alan, come over.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can use my computer to raid.
[SPEAKER_18]: Screw you, lady.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, because I forgot that the little sale is going on and I have some cryptic points left to spend and it's cheap right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a sale, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are denying a woman a sale.
[SPEAKER_18]: For shame.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go raid with your party.
[SPEAKER_15]: Crossing very thin lines here.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's cool, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: You gotta take a day off.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just funny the way you just said it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't need a show.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alan, any comment?
[SPEAKER_14]: See, for those listening that have been considering playing WoW, this is what is waiting for you in the future.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is real.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is like an episode of, I don't know, Intervention and VH1 behind the guild right here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nah, I love both of you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all your fault, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: You got me addicted on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm a bad person.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_28]: Our phone's ringing.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess I should take another call, alright?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: I still love you guys regardless if you show up or not.
[SPEAKER_28]: No homo.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was the most unenthusiastic kissing noise I've ever heard in my life.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can't take it anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: What time is the raid tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I might be level 8 and I want to come.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hold on, folks.
[SPEAKER_28]: We do a show here called Orange Lounge Radio where we talk about gaming and gaming culture.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is not the Danger Squad updates and important bulletins.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can just see there in guild chat now, that bitch just said he ain't coming to raid with us tomorrow because he got a pink berry.
[SPEAKER_28]: That fat bitch.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, really?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, 8 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, okay, 10 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to go raid.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you guys raiding?
[SPEAKER_28]: They're doing ICC, the second half.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're trying to do progression, so if you're in greens and blues, I don't know if that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to be in tier 9, but you can still take me.
[SPEAKER_28]: We took somebody in greens and blues last week.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't see why we wouldn't do it again.
[SPEAKER_28]: You need to talk to Tim.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's his radio show calling?
[SPEAKER_28]: I can make a joke here, but I don't want to out what he does, so I better not.
[SPEAKER_28]: You have a good one, Shane.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_28]: He better be doing his daily every day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I spent my points.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now I'm logging out.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm a rear admiral, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_28]: A rear admiral.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anonymous123 in our chatroom says, When you hear WoW talk and you've never played, you wish you could understand.
[SPEAKER_28]: When you play or haven't played WoW and you understand WoW talk, you wish you didn't understand.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is a good question.
[SPEAKER_28]: Define what a raid is for our listeners, Alan.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Blaziken again.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind, DJ Blazkid?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, not much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just putzing around Virtual Liberty City in GTA Ballad of Gay Tony now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Finally getting past that stupid chopper mission.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, okay, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has anyone here played Metal Gear by chance?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, none of us in here have played Oh, No, The Truck Have Started to Move.
[SPEAKER_28]: The Truck Have Started to Move.
[SPEAKER_28]: Basically, I'm stuck on the Psycho Mantis battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the best battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: It made me almost want to crack my PSP in half as we speak.
[SPEAKER_18]: I see you are a careful man.
[SPEAKER_18]: You save often.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know if it does this on the PSP, but it was so hardcore.
[SPEAKER_28]: That guy would read your memory card, and if you played other Konami games, he would freaking know.
[SPEAKER_28]: And he'd be like, oh, you like to play Castlevania, do you?
[SPEAKER_28]: And you'd be like, oh my god!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm possessed by the devil!
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I have a Castlevania save on there and a DDR save on there, just for a random point.
[SPEAKER_09]: And let's just say here, yeah, you've read that, and you're like, you know, Rhythm Banner, something around those lines.
[SPEAKER_09]: But on top of also anger management and gaming, another thing that almost made me want to break on my controllers and or system is Guitar Hero 3, the freaking devil battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: I lost so many times on Hard, an expert to that guy What was that song in Guitar Hero 3 that killed me?
[SPEAKER_28]: That song in Guitar Hero 3 that used to kill me was the Muse song, the Knights of Cydonia I probably broke my guitar over that, I don't know how many times
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, but that's an epic song in itself.
[SPEAKER_28]: It is a pretty epic song.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hurry up, hurry up.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's your last thought?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um... Oh god, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I tried, well, the War Puffer tried to activate a trial account, and it won't work.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a little trial disk and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: It won't work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what'd you do?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_09]: You broke it!
[SPEAKER_09]: You broke WoW!
[SPEAKER_28]: Call Blizzard, technical support.
[SPEAKER_14]: The trial accounts are so crippled because of people, spammers use trial accounts so they can spam without having to pay.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the accounts are so crippled, like when I played with a trial account like two years ago, I hated it because I couldn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then when I actually paid for it, it's like, oh, this is a completely different game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So is it worth it for the $15?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I've
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a wife.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I play other games other than just one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I say this here real quickly about Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_28]: The reason why I play so much Warcraft is because of the social element and a lot of my friends play and it's so much fun to raid with them and stuff and it's always fun to meet new people too that are like you and stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: First off, two things.
[SPEAKER_28]: Apparently this has suddenly turned into the Robin Allen Guild radio show because one of the guild members who I've never seen join chat before joined and said, what do you mean Alan has the best DPS?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I finally figured out because I've been watching the guild the old web series and I've finally figured out the whole some of the emphasis and some of the lingo the thing is she really did play WoW and that's why like that series is so spot on because I'm sure it's a lot like some of it is probably like you know obviously fiction like some of the weird dating storylines to get into but a lot of the stuff they talk about in game is so true
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, what about the stuff in the South Park Make Love Not Warcraft episode?
[SPEAKER_28]: Mom, bathroom And this is I just got a screenshot from one of the guild members Who apparently, yes, in guild chat At 1.56am I'm assuming that's eastern time One of the guildies said That bitch ain't coming to raid tomorrow because he's going to get Pinkberry That fat bitch I just got a screenshot of somebody talking shit about me in guild Wow I know they're listening too If it's one something that would be central time
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, one of my girlfriends ended up breaking up with me via Wi-Fi connection on a live Metroid Time Hunters game where we could do voice chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had friend codes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone in the whole room heard it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then my character died.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just like, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Worst.
[SPEAKER_28]: Basically, it was because I was a gamer and so she
[SPEAKER_09]: She said, either you quit gaming or I dump you and get this.
[SPEAKER_09]: This girl was a cheerleader and freshman and I was kind of done with my life trying to find love.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: If there's one lesson we could teach you here on Orange Lounge Radio, look, I want all the young men to listen up because I know we have some strapping young lads that are, what, between 16 and 21 that listen to this show, young guys trying to find the girl of their dreams and so forth.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is what I want to teach you, and JB, back me up on this, is that if a woman is going to break up with you because you play too many games, she's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's a bitch, and you can do better.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's... I'm dating a girl who knows more about anime than I do.
[SPEAKER_28]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, she's just a nerd.
[SPEAKER_28]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nerds are okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're gonna let you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's one thing you could learn from Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's... I'm not saying if a girl doesn't play games, she's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's... But if a girl doesn't understand, you gotta respect the games.
[SPEAKER_28]: She's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm gonna get so much hate mail alright well I think I don't know if it's like honey get the keys the baby's coming now and it's like Festergut is at 20% the baby is harshing my mellow right now good news everybody the baby is coming hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this wait wait let me hear it straight did you say raid or rave cause I got my glow sticks here ready for tomorrow night
[SPEAKER_28]: Why not both?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's rave during the raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_24]: Light switch raid!
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you been trying to call us for 30 minutes just to make that joke?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, but it's not like you said raid or rave, so I had to call in just to say something about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: R-A-I-D.
[SPEAKER_28]: Use it to kill insects.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know, I know, but I just couldn't resist raid.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, no!
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I gotta play the one you sent me or you're gonna throw a fit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I actually got an email from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is play this, ho-bag.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was actually the subject.
[SPEAKER_28]: She's so respectful.
[SPEAKER_26]: So respectful.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Big thanks to those of you guys that have been listening the entire time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, I don't know how you do it.
[SPEAKER_28]: You guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, I can barely tolerate being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll just leave it all in the other room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll leave...
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, we'll be right back, guys, with more of the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know what we're going to do in the next segment.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just tune in and find out.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll be back after this break here at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, and now we're back, everybody.
[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on Hour 9 of our marathon episode.
[SPEAKER_28]: We started at 2 o'clock today, and it's now 1116.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, we are taping here live at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, we...
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_28]: He'll be back.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's why Dan's not in here.
[SPEAKER_18]: He's ignoring us in favor of video games.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, we asked Dan to come play a match game, but he's like, I'm in the middle of a game.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: How about more Facebook questions from earlier?
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's do it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: I feel energetic.
[SPEAKER_18]: I feel like we could go longer
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I make mine with decaf, but decaf still has caffeine in it, except I make it kind of strong with a good scoop of Hershey's Cocoa in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then I add some Splenda and about a teaspoon of vanilla flavoring and use a soy creamer after I add the water.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it actually tastes like sort of intermediate chocolate.
[SPEAKER_18]: It sounds so hippie.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you want some?
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe later.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not tired yet, but give me about another hour.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see how we do.
[SPEAKER_28]: I say we beat 12 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, we've only got 45 minutes to go.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll probably beat it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_16]: Play some more Para.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to be doing a list list.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's cheating, though, if I play too much music.
[SPEAKER_28]: Playing about 10 minutes every hour, that's okay, because we need to be able to take breaks and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: But if I play much more than that, we're cheating.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, hi.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to be doing a list list here shortly.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tonight's topic, if you want to start thinking about this, and I know Bradley's going to want to think about this because he needs to get his list together.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thing I most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011
[SPEAKER_28]: It's going to be the topic tonight, so start thinking about that and get your list down.
[SPEAKER_28]: The thing I most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_28]: Meanwhile, more Facebook questions that we got earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: We had Liam earlier ask us, what is our favorite video game of all time?
[SPEAKER_28]: What about this?
[SPEAKER_28]: John on Facebook asked a very similar question, not just what is the best video game ever...
[SPEAKER_28]: What is the worst video game ever?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is there a game that you can think of that would qualify as the worst video game ever?
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: There was a game that was so bad that when Dan and I rented it we were horrified by it and called Blockbuster and asked them if we could take it back.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it was WCW Thunder.
[SPEAKER_28]: That bad, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: It was really that bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you know, I actually kind of thought the Spice Girls game was bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it's so hilarious!
[SPEAKER_18]: It was hilarious, but it was kind of hard to play.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the American Blue Stinger was bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Japanese one was cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: Worst game ever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, you got something?
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably that King's Quest Mask of Eternity game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I bought it the day it came out for full retail price, which was like 50 bucks, and it is hideously awful bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Terra bad?
[SPEAKER_14]: Terra bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, I would, uh, what is the worst video game ever?
[SPEAKER_28]: Fusion Frenzy 2 is probably the worst video game.
[SPEAKER_28]: One of them.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's close.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, that was that one I made you play on the 360 that was so, so bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like it was like Mario Party, but not fun at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was like when you had me play Yaris, I couldn't help it because I was laughing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was just laugh, just laughter came out of me playing Yaris because it was so, what is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: I do not even.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's, that's worth something.
[SPEAKER_28]: and BitBoy was really a special kind of terrible that I played earlier this year too that was really bad or last year and going like if I want to go way back I remember renting this game on the Nintendo Entertainment System and thinking it was just like the worst fucking game I'd ever played and I bet nobody's ever even heard of it it was a Color Dreams game they made the bootleg carts it was called Master Chu and the Drunk Nerd Who and I remember this game because it was so terrible
[SPEAKER_28]: I bet that's a game not even Jamie knows.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, that's how obscure this shit is.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_28]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_28]: It's bad, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's really bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: A lot of those color dreams were really bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, any Terra bad games you can think of?
[SPEAKER_28]: Worst freaking video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The worst, a lot of them that are really terrible are like these girl fighting games on like the Japanese Saturn ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it was like Asuka 120% was one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game was actually fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking of one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might have been a different one from that one, but usually they're slow and crappy moves and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other games were craptastic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see, some of our chat room saying DDR Dollar Bill says Silent Assault was another Color Dreams game that was worse.
[SPEAKER_28]: GreenDragon says Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom The force you had to get through was a bigger pain in the ass than the Doom Dungeon Let's see Dash of Destruction, Yaris Kabuki Warriors says Amaze Satsuma was a really bad game SirDorksalot says the PS1 version of Samurai Shodown 3 was terrible There you go, those are some of the responses there from our chatroom More Facebook questions
[SPEAKER_28]: John on Facebook also asks the best geek moment ever.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is a good one.
[SPEAKER_28]: The best geek moment ever.
[SPEAKER_28]: What was your best geek moment ever?
[SPEAKER_28]: This is kind of tricky.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, mine's easy.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's beating the dragon blindfolded in Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: That is pretty geeky.
[SPEAKER_18]: and and uh doing you know doing Mario 8-1 blindfolded if if you know your rhythm it's not that hard but the dragon because and that one was also kind of precise timing too so I and I've only done it three times nice I can't do it now hell no but when when it was out yeah okay all right Alan do you have a best geek moment ever that you can think of
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: I thought though this year's E3 was like a close second.
[SPEAKER_28]: My first E3 was definitely my best, but this year's E3 was a close second.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is a really good E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_18]: What about though going to E3 for the first time as press?
[SPEAKER_28]: That was cool too, but I honestly didn't notice that huge of a difference because one thing I've learned about press is that if you don't book your show like six months in advance, then you're pretty much having the same show as everyone else.
[SPEAKER_28]: Plus back in 06 or 07, I don't remember what year we actually went as press, maybe it was 07.
[SPEAKER_18]: I booked us with Bethesda well in advance so we could get in for the Star Trek screening.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, which ended up being a mediocre game, which was too bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, and I got into... Though I got in one time as not as pressed, though, for a pressed thing for PabloCross.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry to steal your thunder.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it was good.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, there were some really good parties, depending on what year it was, you know.
[SPEAKER_28]: uh looking in our chat room and some of the questions uh questions here uh JV Mon says my best geek moment was meeting Matt Smith at the New York City premiere of Doctor Who series 5 and being on the 13th episode of Doctor Who Confidential uh Ranma says beating Mega Man 3 Dan Shadow says the parties at E3 were insane yep yep uh what was that place that we went and got beer at
[SPEAKER_18]: They had like 200 taps on the wall or something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: That place was epic.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was Seattle.
[SPEAKER_28]: For PAX, that was epic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, maybe some people are there right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although, you know, I did enjoy my Facebook style photo with Jonathan Colton.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got one, I've got one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just thought of one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anime Expo 2000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie says he remembers seeing me there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was my last day X. I actually stayed up all night at the DDR room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I only played it once there, but I was just there watching people because I was waiting for... They were having signings in the morning.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was the one at Disneyland, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_18]: Was it 2001 at Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because then I was there for one after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember if that was a Long Beach one or a Disneyland one.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it had to have been Long Beach.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, 2000 was the one at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_18]: 2001 was in Long Beach.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was at Anaheim.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one of those long piers down there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We went down there and waited.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, basically staying up all night watching people play DDR, waiting to get signatures from artists and stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_18]: That was the year of the chair.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here's some more geek moments from chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: GreenDragon says, biggest geek moment, speaking Klingon with my dad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dude, your dad is cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Gilroy Spars, which I think is Nathan, says, being told about a weekend cabin retreat of drinking and massive D&D playing and being very excited about going.
[SPEAKER_28]: That does sound kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: That pretty much means have a good year because Rosh Hashanah is this Wednesday night slash Thursday during the day.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's like I'm the translator of Jew speak tonight or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just Hebrew, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought of my geek moment.
[SPEAKER_28]: You thought of your geek moment, yay!
[SPEAKER_14]: When I was in D-Malay, which was the youth group that I was in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, I'm going to out myself.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was in it too.
[SPEAKER_28]: I haven't talked about it a lot on the show because not a lot of kids were in it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, it's youth masonry, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's like not a lot of... The Shriners and the Masons before their son.
[SPEAKER_28]: Usually if your grandpa's in it, or in my case, you end up being in it, or you have friends that were in it or what have you.
[SPEAKER_28]: But the reason why I bring this up before he says this is because Alan and I were both in this organization.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we're convinced that we met each other when we were 15.
[SPEAKER_28]: We met each other at camp.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like at camp, at the leadership camp or whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like we're convinced we met each other and just didn't like, you know, we weren't really...
[SPEAKER_14]: Super Nintendo Super Nintendo Super Nintendo
[SPEAKER_14]: At the convention, which is basically like four days of a bunch of 15-year-old boys just staying up and doing convention things, I think we hooked up a Super NES up to our hotel TV room, and we played, I think we played Rock and Roll Racing and Street Fighter II, I think for like 36 hours without sleeping.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is something that you can only do when you're 15.
[SPEAKER_18]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: When I, it was probably my, I'd have to say my second year of college or my first year, somewhere around there, I was working in the game room and so I brought in my TV and my Super Nintendo and my friend brought in his import Saturn and we had gaming going on in the pool hall all night and I ran D&D games and we did this three nights in a row and I did not sleep and on the fourth day of having been awake,
[SPEAKER_18]: I sit down at my friend's dorm room and lean back on the cushions while they're playing whatever I think it was Doom at the time and wake up in my own dorm bed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, so they carried you.
[SPEAKER_18]: They carried me to my dorm room.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't remember any of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't remember.
[SPEAKER_18]: But...
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry, but the best dorm slash frat house story that you possibly have was when you missed this show because you were in San Diego one weekend and you stayed at the gay frat house.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can you tell this story again on the show real quick?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, God, right.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's been years.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went with Julie to San Diego to see some friends of ours.
[SPEAKER_18]: One of them lives in Japan right now and the other one lives somewhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: Because the only place that we had to stay was the gay frat house.
[SPEAKER_18]: To stay with our friend.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, your friend was a gay frat boy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: He lived in the frat house.
[SPEAKER_18]: So the only spaces, like Julie slept on, I think, on some couch.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I slept in a little room under the stairs where there had been a mattress.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like the Harry Potter room.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what it called it, the Harry Potter room.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it had a little light in there all on its own and everything.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm very, very glad they washed the mattress before I used it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know, I was just like, think about all the handjobs that have taken place in that little closet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bro, I'm so drunk, bro.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bro, where we at, bro?
[SPEAKER_14]: I slept in the Harry Potter room, Rob!
[SPEAKER_18]: I read Harry Potter in the Harry Potter room!
[SPEAKER_28]: And I was like, wait, there's gay frat houses?
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, I didn't even know they existed at that time.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's like a national gay fraternity.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I know that now, but like ten years ago I didn't, or however long ago that was.
[SPEAKER_18]: All that long time ago, oh no.
[SPEAKER_28]: Been a long time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Red Entertainment is following up saying, bro, don't stop doing that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to get something else to drink.
[SPEAKER_28]: Best and Worst Game Tie-Ins
[SPEAKER_28]: I think honestly the best as far as movies and all that go, the Silent Hill movie was pretty kickass.
[SPEAKER_28]: Even though it wasn't perfect, it was still miles above anything else that I think has come out to this point.
[SPEAKER_28]: So the Silent Hill movie is probably one of the best.
[SPEAKER_28]: As far as the worst...
[SPEAKER_28]: That Maniac Mansion shows up there.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or maybe the Pac-Man cartoon in the 80s was not that great either.
[SPEAKER_28]: It really didn't work for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: The best and the worst video game tie-ins, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like movie, TV.
[SPEAKER_18]: Best was Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you know how many times I watched it and I bought it on Blu-ray because I'm a fucking addict.
[SPEAKER_18]: Saw it four times in the theater.
[SPEAKER_18]: Worst...
[SPEAKER_18]: Captain N because the characterizations in that were just so awful.
[SPEAKER_18]: They were hideous.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I also have to say the Street Fighter movie with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
[SPEAKER_18]: Poor Raul Julia having that as his last movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: But Kali Minow was hot.
[SPEAKER_14]: any uh alan about uh captain n yeah you brought it up i love that show now when i think back on it why did kid icarus always suffix everything he said with icus like that was his speech impediment what was that well and megaman was always mega this mega that and simon belmont was an idiot and he was supposed to be like this courageous vampire hunter
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: IDK.
[SPEAKER_14]: Best video game tie-in?
[SPEAKER_14]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: cereal.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because you like food.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would eat all... That's funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would pick out all the marshmallows and then eat... Save the dry cereal for later.
[SPEAKER_14]: The one... Whatever Nintendo cereal had the two sides, it was like two bags in one box.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I remember.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Nintendo breakfast system.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Nintendo cereal system, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Worst...
[SPEAKER_14]: I had one, I blanked.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_28]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know, I'm yawning.
[SPEAKER_28]: We haven't even gotten to the games yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: We gotta get to that segment pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, let me know if you think about it, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, I don't know if you have anything you're thinking of?
[SPEAKER_28]: Best and worst video game tie-ins?
[SPEAKER_28]: Can't really think of anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Amy and all of the marketing related to Dante's Inferno last year.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the worst video game tie-ins ever.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, what was so terrible about it, do I ask?
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, see what you can get away with with a booth babe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or maybe tied for God of War 2 when they served a goat or something at the press conference and they had the girls in the togas.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, it was a fake animal.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they're like, oh yeah, we have a dead goat for God of War 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's dumb and you're a bad person for thinking of it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, Sony just, in general, has a lot of really bad tie-ins.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, sometimes they do really well, like the Kevin Butler stuff, but sometimes they do really bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, remember the black and white PSP?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh yeah, that was not good.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, you just feel second-hand embarrassment for them, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or the PSP commercial with the squirrels.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: How about a game to perk us up, everybody?
[SPEAKER_28]: How about an OLR game?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: LISTLESS
[SPEAKER_28]: So the way this works, we're going to put together a definitive list.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to go around and get the top three answers on the list from each person here in studio.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we have a top 12.
[SPEAKER_28]: But then we go around the room and ask, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_28]: And we reduce down to the top eight, which then you, our chat room, vote.
[SPEAKER_28]: And we'll come up with the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_28]: And tonight we've got a great topic for you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tonight's topic is...
[SPEAKER_28]: The thing I most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011 The thing I most want to see in next year's OLR Marathon Now we've almost survived through one What do I want to see most next year?
[SPEAKER_28]: Now if you guys in chat have things you want to add to the list You can try and yell it out in chat And if somebody doesn't have any ideas They can try and steal some from chat We'll see
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so we'll start off, DarkSakura, you ready to go?
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to read the first item on your list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Number three on DarkSakura's list, thing you most want to see at the OLR Marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually playing games while we broadcast over the web.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually playing games while we broadcast.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dan's in the other room playing his game going, I regret nothing!
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Bradley, do you have a number three thing you most want to see us do next year?
[SPEAKER_03]: A balloon drop.
[SPEAKER_28]: A balloon drop?
[SPEAKER_28]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_28]: Will there be confetti and all sorts of things as well?
[SPEAKER_03]: We can count down.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can just do everything you saw in that video.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think our next marathon should be on New Year's.
[SPEAKER_28]: OLR fucking New Year's.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: I like this comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob and Alan Ray chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: That'll just be the theme.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Number three answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki sings hours of uninterrupted disco karaoke classics in the background of the news story.
[SPEAKER_20]: What sorts of uninterrupted classes would he sing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I know he's already infamous for doing I'm Coming Out, so I will survive YMCA in the Navy, you know, see how long he can go before he starts to cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Before he starts to cry?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Number three answer for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: My number three answer is corporate sponsorship.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because I will sell out like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, very practical.
[SPEAKER_28]: Corporate sponsorship.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hour 19 of the OLR Marathon brought to us tonight by Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like sugar!
[SPEAKER_14]: Every now and then we have a delicious Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_28]: And my left arm is tingling and I don't know why, but... Who was that you were talking about once and it was like a, I don't know, it was like some really dumpy actress or something that was a total slut and you said, ah, she looks like she's been glazed up like a Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who was that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Were you talking about one of our friends?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do we really want to go there right now?
[SPEAKER_14]: We can.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, she was in her hotel room with her boyfriend and I said she's getting... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's getting frosted up like a Cinnabon right now because I'm gross like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_28]: We were in Reno and we were gambling.
[SPEAKER_28]: We were downstairs because they have a queen slot machine, which is the most amazing invention ever made.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like the band.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like the band, not like, you know, hey girl.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, it was a queen slot machine with Freddie Mercury, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: But Alan and I went upstairs because Alan was kind of sick and I wanted to set some stuff down.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're like, we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_28]: We get back downstairs and my friend's gone.
[SPEAKER_28]: Her and her boyfriend are gone.
[SPEAKER_28]: Answer number two.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Dan-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_28]: The Dan-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dan's been ignoring the show mostly tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_28]: Bastard!
[SPEAKER_28]: I thought we would need him to get through the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: We haven't needed him.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm very proud that we've gotten through this all by our lonesome selves.
[SPEAKER_18]: Relatively Dan-free.
[SPEAKER_28]: Pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, your number two answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: A laser light show.
[SPEAKER_28]: A laser light show.
[SPEAKER_28]: I could do a light switch rave.
[SPEAKER_28]: Will that help?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know how that translates to radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares about the listeners?
[SPEAKER_28]: That's right, who cares about the listeners?
[SPEAKER_14]: We put on Pink Floyd's The Wall and it's like... Oh, it just all makes sense now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, when I watch The Wizard of Oz, it has a whole new meaning.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, um... Alan, your number two pick for thing you most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011?
[SPEAKER_14]: A live web stream of booty poppin' go-go dancers in 8-bit cosplay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Slow that down and say it one more time.
[SPEAKER_14]: A live web stream of accompanying go-go dancing people in 8-bit cosplay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because we've been doing this for 10 hours and I'm delirious right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: My ideas are going to be kind of whack.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_28]: My number two answer is somewhat similar, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thing I most want to see on the OLR Marathon 2011?
[SPEAKER_28]: Nudity!
[SPEAKER_28]: But not from the hosts.
[SPEAKER_28]: So the thing I most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011 is nudity, but not from the hosts.
[SPEAKER_28]: We should hire a stripper.
[SPEAKER_28]: For the next... Oh, I should have put that down.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, what is your number one answer?
[SPEAKER_28]: Showgirls Edition
[SPEAKER_28]: How does Showgirls Edition work?
[SPEAKER_28]: You are a whore, darling.
[SPEAKER_18]: The whole thing is just us answering questions in Showgirls quotes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: And with a topless dance show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, you're stealing my answer.
[SPEAKER_18]: Gaming ain't fucking.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: So many of our listeners have never seen Showgirls and can't appreciate the humor of that line.
[SPEAKER_28]: Episode 380 of Orange Lounge Radio Gaming ain't fucking Bradley, what is your number one answer for thing you most want to see of the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon 2011?
[SPEAKER_28]: Big money, big prizes
[SPEAKER_28]: I love it!
[SPEAKER_28]: Big money, big prizes.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know where that money's going to come from, but okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, it's our dream world.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, your number one answer for the thing you most want to see in the OLR Marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_14]: No one is allowed to switch to their next story or segment until they can beat the next level of Battletoads.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lots of dead air on that marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: No one is allowed to switch story until Beat Battletoads level.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just had to shorten it somehow.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's going to be very tricky, and there'll be a lot of cursing, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's going to be tough.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: My number one answer for thing I most want to see at the OLR Marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_28]: Gabe and Tycho show up and exclaim, this is where the real party's at, bitches.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: How do you like that, huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: This joke's on Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: The list as it is so far.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually Playing Games on Video, Balloon Drop, Loki Sings Hours of Disco, Corporate Sponsorship, The Danathon, Laser Light Show, Livestream of Go Go Dancing and 8-Bit Cosplay, Nudity, been off on the host, Showgirls Edition, Big Money, Big Prizes, No One is Allowed to Switch Story Until They Beat a Level on Battletoads, and Gabe and Tycho Show Up and Exclaim, This is Where the Real Party's At, Bitches.
[SPEAKER_28]: They have to say bitches.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_28]: One of them is about to be eliminated.
[SPEAKER_28]: The chatters cannot vote on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually, let me read quickly while you think about that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to actually read some of the suggestions from chat because they have some good ones once in a while.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm getting private tells.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let me on and I will strip for the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Showgirls is an amazing movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Took you this long to get to the stripper?
[SPEAKER_28]: Laser, Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_28]: Lady Gaga would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: OLR, the musical episode.
[SPEAKER_28]: LARPing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Put LARPing on the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: We could do LARPing the whole episode.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki reads every line ever used by Tingle in all the Zelda games, including Japanese and Tingle's voice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can I just go ahead and pick something?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, all right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_18]: Nudity.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nudity?
[SPEAKER_18]: How could you eliminate nudity?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we can just get that on the internet anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, nudity is stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_03]: Corporate sponsorship.
[SPEAKER_27]: You'd never... Alright, why?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because it just wouldn't be LLR without sponsorship.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_28]: If we sell out, it's just not the same.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, I'll support you on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: It is stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, which of these is not worthy from the list?
[SPEAKER_28]: um Gabe and Tycho show up why are you my entire list just got eliminated fuck all of you seriously no I'll pick another one no if that's the one you feel should be eliminated then we should eliminate it it's fine it's fine I'm just your boyfriend and you know you want to just ruin my day that's fine no I'm fine with it it's fine let's just see where we are at 8 o'clock tomorrow um Danathon Danathon
[SPEAKER_28]: The Dan-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, Alan took Dan off the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why'd you eliminate the Dan-a-thon?
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to take off.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love this answer, but showgirls edition just isn't going to work for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Darling, you are a whore.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're a whore, darling.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: It is stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: You don't know me.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: So that leaves actually playing games on video.
[SPEAKER_28]: Balloon Drop, Loki Sings Hours of Disco, Laser Light Show, Livestream of GoGoDancing and 8-Bit Cosplay, Big Money, Big Prizes, No One is Allowed to Switch Stories Until Battletoads is Beaten, and Gabe and Tycho Show Up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so you're going to place a vote over Private Message to Sky in the chatroom with your number one and number two answers, and then we'll tally them all up.
[SPEAKER_28]: I gotta type this out.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we will tell you what won.
[SPEAKER_28]: Not our favorites.
[SPEAKER_28]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not in our hands anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's in the hands of the listeners.
[SPEAKER_28]: The voters.
[SPEAKER_28]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_18]: We need to do match game very soon.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because if we don't, Happy Bunny will be sad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now we have to fill time while I wait for votes to come in.
[SPEAKER_28]: How are we going to do that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Usually I'd be doing, I don't know, like freaking phone calls or something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Should I open up the skyline?
[SPEAKER_28]: Open up the skyline.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's almost midnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just want to point out, we're almost to our 10th hour of doing this.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm getting crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, did you realize what you were signing up for when you were like, sure, Rob, I'll come be on the marathon show with you?
[SPEAKER_28]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_28]: You having fun?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm glad you're having fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm glad somebody's having fun.
All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: We open up the Skype line and see if we get any calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're going to have to talk to whoever calls in, though, because I've got to tally up the votes.
[SPEAKER_28]: So 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We are open to take some more calls here.
[SPEAKER_14]: We could play silly YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Did we get a call in?
[SPEAKER_28]: We got a call, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, DarkSakura's gonna take this one.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ghostbusters, what do you want?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it's Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I am good.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Besides being delirious from being up for ten hours straight.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not the delirious one.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob's delirious.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because Rob is Mr. Sleep Deprivation Party Pooper.
[SPEAKER_02]: He hasn't been intaking much alcohol, has he?
[SPEAKER_18]: He has had two entire drinks.
[SPEAKER_18]: He hasn't even had the Guinness that I accidentally saved for him.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I've been making delicious beverages all night.
[SPEAKER_18]: I made one out of Patron and Grapefruit Juice, which was entirely very tasty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then Patron and Orange Juice, and then Brandy and Apple Juice.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it tastes like pie, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That all sounds very delicious.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alan had some.
[SPEAKER_18]: He had lots of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like pie.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's actually part of how I make my apple pie drink.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except when I make the apple pie drink, I let it sit for like a couple of weeks and throw in some cinnamon and spices and it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you have a question for us?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't care what it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just ask something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been eagerly awaiting questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new Pokemans in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I'm a big enough nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am importing and very excited.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh no, your Pokemans let you show me them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I hear you like Mudkips.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just thought it was funny at Faname someone cosplayed as a Mudkip.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course, that was also the same year that someone cosplayed as a Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_18]: Did the little pig cry wee wee wee all the way home?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, we're getting towards the... We've been doing what?
[SPEAKER_18]: For how long?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think this should be an annual event.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm having fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would pay to...
[SPEAKER_28]: I would pay to see it I've got a PayPal account if you want to contribute
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, we'd only be up against DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, no, I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_18]: A bunch of my friends are DragonCon right now, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not doing that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also have a statement for you as well.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_28]: Look at what you've done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at what you've done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love this app.
[SPEAKER_28]: Which one do you have?
[SPEAKER_28]: You know what's awesome, though?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because I have a button in front of me, too.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know what my button does?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, no, not that button.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you know what my button does to us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: One, two, three.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is the stupidest marathon in the history of the internet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, wait, Sterlok, you want to know what my button does?
[SPEAKER_28]: What does your button do?
[SPEAKER_28]: It hangs up on callers.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're such a... Rob, you... Alright, dirty, dirty ho bag.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: Why are we still getting calls?
[SPEAKER_28]: I want to get to the answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why are people calling?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, hi.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're so happy to have you.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello, Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up, gang?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: This is Scared, though.
[SPEAKER_28]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_28]: Barely.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up, dude?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm at Walmart, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm at Walmart just doing some shopping, and I'm listening to you guys for my shitty all-games app radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought I'd give you guys a call.
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't criticize the app because it was done, I think, at a very low cost, if not for free.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we love that app.
[SPEAKER_28]: If it doesn't work, it's usually the Internet's fault.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been listening to you guys since about 2pm I'm sorry
[SPEAKER_28]: I need some preparation, eh?
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_18]: Needs some hemorrhoid pads.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe I need some Propel because I know back in the day Jamie loved Propel.
[SPEAKER_18]: Propel has been replaced by Vitamin Water Zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love Vitamin Water Zero.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go get some Barbies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm in the blue jean section right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you?
[SPEAKER_28]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, have fun at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm glad you're still listening.
[SPEAKER_28]: I love the fact that you're listening on the go on the handy dandy app.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see how much longer we can go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I hope they're not sold out of preparation.
[SPEAKER_28]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm going to let you go because our connection is kind of wonky.
[SPEAKER_28]: But you have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Later.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was really, like, cutty and out.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I had to cut that one short.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry, caller.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's nothing personal, I swear.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, 1877 GameOLR, username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_28]: You think everybody would stop listening by now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, usually during the normal show, everybody's tuned out by the time the afterbirth starts.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nobody cares anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: But, nope, tonight, almost midnight, still going.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh man, Legend of Zaku again Zaku again What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah, just like watching paint dry, in other words watching my hard drive format for the past four hours And listening to this show, yeah, I know Yeah, I know But yeah, I guess, I don't know if you mentioned any Bomani related stuff like, um, hold on I'll put John's picture I mean, that's supposed to be location testing in New Jersey now
[SPEAKER_28]: Wait, take us off speakerphone.
[SPEAKER_28]: This sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_17]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Rob's got a wedgie right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: I do not consent to speakerphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: DDR, it came up on the show a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_28]: Somebody went to the LA premiere and we, I don't know, somebody was talking about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess the pads are better and the interface is pretty, but otherwise, hey, it's still DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that and they started unlocking songs now, so we're getting a lot of, like, crossover, a lot of B-Mani crossovers, like, pull it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it was, like, as early as a few days ago, they had some, they had, like, I forgot what songs they had, but I know some of them, like, ah, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: They unlocked, uh, there's Vanessa's from 2DX15 that was unlocked.
[SPEAKER_06]: other songs so like songs from a series I stopped following four years ago basically pretty no yeah around that pretty no what is a pretty no is that like a pink you know tending to my girlfriend and other things in life I mean I do play but not as much as I used to and that's due to age like I'm getting old I'm getting pretty old now
[SPEAKER_06]: New York City scene is on its way out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of almost dead at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone goes to New Jersey now.
[SPEAKER_28]: You got a girlfriend now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I've been in a relationship since April.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_28]: How often does she have to be inflated?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I had to.
[SPEAKER_18]: You have my permission.
[SPEAKER_28]: You have my permission to call Rob a hoobag.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kidding, come on.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's a little, come on.
[SPEAKER_28]: I gotta give the listeners some crap once in a while.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: But okay, so the New York scene is dying.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_28]: But hey, at least you're getting laid so all's good with the world, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much, I mean, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: As I said, DDR is like
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not as big as it used to be here, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still play somewhat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I try to avoid CF like the plague at home in New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coney Island scene is pretty much a wasteland at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to say it, but everyone's going out to either deep parts of Queens or New Jersey to play.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wasn't Coney Island supposed to be getting this huge makeover?
[SPEAKER_28]: Like now or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Even then, Luna Park doesn't have arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: that's a problem all the other arcades they used to be an arcade they used to have DDR but it burned down this past year so I don't know whether they'll have DDR when they rebuild all the other places are pretty much the same I mean it's like I can't think of any good places to play now even the one that we had in Queens basically the mall kicked them out so they got sent further into Long Island
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it's bullshit now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I usually go out to, like, Bayside, you know, to Peter Pan Games to play, you know, 2DX, and now we have Poppin' 17.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we got the latest version of Poppin' in New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why, but that just came up recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I'm just trying to keep this show going with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_28]: I appreciate your dedication.
[SPEAKER_28]: But we're going to let you go real quick because we have a special announcement to make, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, make sure to go to 2pm.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ladies and gentlemen, we have made it to midnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: It is now midnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: The goal was to make it for 10 hours and we have successfully been broadcasting at Lovely All Games Radio for 10 hours and this is the point where we would call it off, but...
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's keep going.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got another hour.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got another hour in this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's keep going.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then we were forced to eat Robin's minstrels.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, did you see the screen was lit up with calls?
[SPEAKER_28]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_28]: I did.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we'll try to get a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: How about listless results real fast though before I go back to the phones?
[SPEAKER_20]: Listless results.
[SPEAKER_28]: Listless results.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm hurrying.
[SPEAKER_28]: The definitive list of the things you most want to see in the OLR marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oops, I never counted.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are such a dork.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's two leaders, clearly.
[SPEAKER_28]: 21 votes for that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well then just read them, shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fine, here it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tied for number three, the most definitive things you want to see on the OLR Marathon 2011.
[SPEAKER_28]: A laser light show!
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: I love how the radio listeners voted for a laser light show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Gabe and Tycho show up and say, this is where the real party's at, bitches!
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: Although they won't have to now, because PAX got moved a week back, so they really could do that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_28]: The number two definitive answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Once we're past this, guys, this is the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's no arguing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just read it already.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_28]: Livestream of GoGoDancing in 8-bit cosplay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: And the number one answer is a tie.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's a tie.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Read it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually playing games on video.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_28]: And these are landslide.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki sings hours and hours of disco.
[SPEAKER_28]: At the car wash.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I brought a bunch of PSP and DS games that are still in the car.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I didn't know what we were going to do today.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't either.
[SPEAKER_28]: I just showed up.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're still in the car.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, hello?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, this is DDR Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_28]: DDR Dollar Bill, what's up?
[SPEAKER_28]: $50 bill.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like 3am and I'm half a loopy, so... Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Join the club.
[SPEAKER_28]: You'll be a perfect fit for our show.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was on the call earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Sakura said about going older and not playing games as much and DDR just fading out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Man, I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, there's next to no place to play DR anymore and even I stopped playing and I didn't get bored of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just got tired of all these new kids coming around and causing...
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: There's Dance Central for those folks that really want something in the mainstream and like their music to be in the mainstream and top 40.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then for folks that have really grown up on the Bomani hits from Japan, there's Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_28]: I really think there's something for everyone on Kinect, and it's kind of exciting where that's going.
[SPEAKER_28]: And it almost makes me excited about music games again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is that game DDR?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, but DDR's been around since 1998.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's...
[SPEAKER_28]: It's been an epically long series.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's okay for it to be dying out right about now, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not disagreeing with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't mind it dying out because it's been around forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my only thing with the two dance games that I was thinking about when I actually saw it was, both of them, I would actually like to see something where you can make your own choreography, not just follow what they have on screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like everything seems to be set to, so you pick one song,
[SPEAKER_01]: You follow that choreography for that song and it never changes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I kind of want to see, because they have, it's the way it looks like is that they're broken to sections.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you have a four beat for one step, maybe two beats for another step.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, you kind of like put it together the way it looks in the commercials.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the way I'm thinking is, if there's some way maybe to shuffle something around so you can kind of make your own choreography to the song, your own version to it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's one way I was thinking it would actually make the game look better, because otherwise, I mean, I could see it being good, but at the same time, I don't know, it just seems kind of too limited.
[SPEAKER_28]: I honestly, honestly think that Dance Masters is the future of DDR.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, I think that's where Konami's putting their stock, is this whole Kinect thing.
[SPEAKER_28]: And if it takes off, you're going to see something like it in arcades, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Man, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if they fix the lag in the Kinect...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, this will definitely take off like crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I can even see dance schools utilizing this.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Buddy, I'm going to let you go to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_28]: But thanks so much for the call, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll get some coffee.
[SPEAKER_28]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll try and get some more calls in.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We still have one more game we want to play before the night's over.
[SPEAKER_28]: And we'll probably do that in the last segment here after another break.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm trying to at least get a couple more calls in if there's still people interested in calling.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we'll give it a couple more minutes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on the OLR-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_25]: It's Misty.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, Misty.
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_25]: The Walmart thing, though?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_25]: In the middle of the night, it's called I Closed and I Need Some DVDs to Burn Shit To.
[SPEAKER_28]: I see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you actually close to Walmart where you are?
[SPEAKER_28]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_25]: I got a ride home that night, but still.
[SPEAKER_28]: I see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sometimes you need to make the emergency Walmart run, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_28]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I wish they had 24-hour targets.
[SPEAKER_28]: And yes, I realize I'm supposed to be boycotting Target, apparently.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I can't.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're less evil than Walmart.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, it's the lesser of two evils.
[SPEAKER_28]: Still.
[SPEAKER_28]: They could donate another $150,000 to whatever organization.
[SPEAKER_28]: It still is less evil than Walmart in my book.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I'm a hippie like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, what about games and stuff?
[SPEAKER_28]: Any game-y related things you want to share?
[SPEAKER_28]: Things you've been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_25]: I've been working on some Green Day Rock Band on during the show, admittedly.
[SPEAKER_25]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_25]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_25]: It turns out that I like more Green Day stuff than I thought I originally would.
[SPEAKER_25]: Because I never got to play it back in the day.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you ever done that when you get one of those type of band packs or band games or whatever, you're kind of like, oh, I didn't realize they sang that song.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because I've kind of had that happen, like buying Greatest Hits CDs, you know, you're listening to it and you're like, oh, this band did that song too?
[SPEAKER_28]: And I never realized that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you kind of have that going on?
[SPEAKER_25]: For rock band DLC, it's been more, I got, I sheaped into buying some DLC and it's like, oh, this ain't bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, well, Misty, we'll let you get back to some Green Day Rock Band so we can take some more calls, but enjoy your future trips to Walmart and enjoy Green Day Rock Band, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, it's Tiara.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hi, Tiara.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just wanted to call in and say that you are complaining.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you're not really complaining about how long you've been doing the show.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're kind of bragging.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I've been doing this since 11 o'clock this morning, and so has DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I think both of us kind of beat out the rest of you.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, you women.
[SPEAKER_28]: You always have to assert your dominance over the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I think DarkSakura is crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like when she told me that she was doing a podcast, she's like, oh, yeah, 2 o'clock is fine because I've got to get up to do another podcast at 11.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm like, and then you're going to do a 10-hour show?
[SPEAKER_28]: You're crazy.
[SPEAKER_23]: She just told me that she wanted to do a 12-hour show and be up until 2.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was like, well, you've already done 12 hours.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: You don't have to do that.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're on hour 13 if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like, come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_23]: Let's wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want to go to sleep, all right?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm trying.
[SPEAKER_28]: The phones will not stop ringing.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're still at, what, over 100 listeners right now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, not quite.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: But, I mean, for internet radio, we're sitting pretty.
[SPEAKER_18]: You guys are really popular tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, a lot of old listeners, for some reason, have decided to come back tonight to hear the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, it's great.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, any stunt to get ratings?
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_23]: And you know, my companion, Rob Kidman, the doctor-ish guy, he's listening now.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's actually, he went to sleep before the show started, or maybe right after the show started.
[SPEAKER_23]: And now he's awake again, and he said he's listening.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, hi, Rob!
[SPEAKER_23]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, hello!
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello, Chop!
[SPEAKER_28]: He should call.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, if he doesn't have Skype, he can't, because overseas it's really hard to call the 800 number.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not really toll-free.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I'm not sure if he has Skype or not, so if he does, then he should call.
[SPEAKER_28]: He should get on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: but yeah, I just wanted to call and tell you guys wrap it up, I'm getting tired we're trying, we still got a match game to do we're gonna try and get through that, okay alright, take care, Tiara kisses, kisses Tron, Tron in December yes, Tron goodbye, Tron Alan, you look like you're actually falling asleep over there, are you doing alright?
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: More booze!
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you okay if we do match game or do we need to wrap this shit up?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because we've made it.
[SPEAKER_28]: We promised midnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: We made it to midnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't owe him anything else.
[SPEAKER_28]: We can pull the plug whenever we want, guilt free, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: Just putting that out there.
[SPEAKER_18]: You watch out because then I'll start doing a return of my old show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Pump Up The Volume Pump Up The Volume Pump Up The Volume
[SPEAKER_28]: This is SSJ100Mad SSJ100Mad, it's only what, 311 where you're at?
[SPEAKER_28]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much, I'm on vacation right now I'm at a buddy's lake house Oh, okay, you're at the lake house Was Sandra Bullock there?
[SPEAKER_28]: No No, that's a good thing Alright, so what's up?
[SPEAKER_28]: Just a lot of nerds Oh god, is it like a nerd lake house party?
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you playing D&D?
[SPEAKER_07]: Almost
[SPEAKER_07]: about 20 of us running out of Buddy of Ours' lake house for the weekend so we basically just brought up all sorts of gaming stuff and whatnot so right now we got people playing Axis and Allies upstairs we got a computer room where we're just kind of doing land battles how can you not have a computer room in a nerd party?
[SPEAKER_28]: you have to have the computer room are there any dice with more than 6 sides there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Then you're playing D&D.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Descent, we have Settlers of Catan, we got a lot of board game stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: I see, I see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Playing all the classic nerds.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually sent a couple pictures to a mailbag.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, you did?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, DarkSakura should open that mailbag at some point.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was that from you?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, well then let me... She probably thought it was spam.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't delete it, I didn't delete it, so let me pull it back up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, no, we got a lot of gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, what are some of the epic battles that have taken place at the beach house where you guys stay indoors and play games all day and don't go to the beach?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we all got StarCraft II hooked up, so we've been doing, you know, we have about, let's see, we've got about ten computers there, like four desktops and the rest laptops.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's winning, Terran, Protoss, or Zerg?
[SPEAKER_18]: Holy crap, a Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I just saw the Nintendo 64 controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Super Nintendo, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_27]: NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_18]: NBA Jam on Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Mortal Kombat 2.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're already making me quite proud of you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we tried to play Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't work out too well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear...
[SPEAKER_17]: You have the same Dreamcast controllers.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: They took away the lane battles.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, you have to do it through Battle.net now.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is horrible because we've got like 10 people playing and it's constantly lagging on a shared connection.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we've got it wired connected through a switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_28]: But of course, there's so many of you on it, it's lagging, of course.
[SPEAKER_28]: Look at all those nerds.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that you posing at the end of the laptop table?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, that's not him.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm the one taking the picture.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Your friend's doing epic posing.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, we're going to let you go, SJ100Matt, so we can take one more break and hopefully wrap things up in the next segment.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep trucking us.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, have fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell everyone we said, suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, Rob?
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_28]: I will.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You too.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm so sorry to those people that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_28]: I cannot control that the Skype line is just ringing off the hook tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: We've got another email.
[SPEAKER_28]: We've got to go to another break.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll read the email when we get back from break.
[SPEAKER_28]: Will we have time for match game?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, we will.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we'll do match game.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll do match game.
[SPEAKER_28]: and then we'll wrap it up because I'm getting tired now alright let's do another quick music break while we save the part of the show we've done so far we're up to about another hour worth of show so we're going to take a quick quick break we're going to come back and do the last segment I think of the marathon and then we're going to call it a night but hey we're moving into hour 10 will we make 11?
[SPEAKER_28]: IDK alright we'll be back right after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio stay tuned
[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome back everybody and a happy Monday to you here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: September the 6th of 2010 where we are continuing taping the marathon episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hate my life and I want to die because I'm getting loopy.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, we're in our 10th hour of broadcasting now.
[SPEAKER_28]: We've been going since 2 o'clock Pacific and it is now 20 after midnight here on the West Coast and we are still going with our show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Match game roll.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, we'll do the match game.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: We need contestants for the match game.
[SPEAKER_28]: The way we're going to get contestants for the match game, if you want to play the match game, you need to type in chat in all caps so I can see you one time.
[SPEAKER_28]: And if you flood, you disqualify yourself.
[SPEAKER_28]: One time you type, I want to play the match game in all caps and you can play the match game.
[SPEAKER_28]: or while we're waiting for people to type I want to play the match game, you can call us on Skype right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you want to be a contestant on the match game, give us a call on the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: And did I connect?
[SPEAKER_28]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_28]: So if you want to play the match game, give us a call right now on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, and we were going to find somebody to play a match game with us and it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we're getting some folks in the chat room typing.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're still waiting for that call, but we're waiting for the encoding to go through.
[SPEAKER_28]: This probably will be the last segment of the marathon, you guys, because it's getting very late.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we got a call on the line.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_23]: again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tiara, guess what?
[SPEAKER_28]: You get to be a contestant on tonight's match game!
[SPEAKER_28]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we get to sleep, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just making sure.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, our Skype line's ringing off the hook.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: We now have a contestant on the line.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, I'm definitely 21.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm definitely not older than 21, I swear.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I'm from the lovely Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_23]: And any games and TV shows about Las Vegas, they're usually about my life, but I have to kind of moderate them and tell them not to tell all of my secrets at once.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what do you do?
[SPEAKER_28]: So since you live in Vegas, what do you do for a living?
[SPEAKER_28]: You're a showgirl, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, of course.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's only one of two callings that you can be as a woman in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what's the other?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I shouldn't say, but I think you know the answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: A woman of the night.
[SPEAKER_23]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, I need you to pick a number between 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
[SPEAKER_28]: 1 and 12.
[SPEAKER_28]: 5 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 AZHP is gonna play Oops, stop it Wrong show Alright, AZHP wins in our chatroom AZHP I gotta start a little thing with him here Winner Stand by
[SPEAKER_28]: to play.
[SPEAKER_17]: Standby to win.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_28]: So he's going to play over private message there.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hopefully he knows how to work the private messaging system or I'm going to get very frustrated very fast at this late hour.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, Tiara, have you played... Do you know how the match game works?
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you familiar with the match game?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you know how this is played?
[SPEAKER_23]: I have been in studio when you have played match games, so yes, I'm aware.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why don't you lie and say no so that I have an excuse to explain the rules?
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, Bradley, and me.
[SPEAKER_28]: The A-lister.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob's our giggling schoolgirl.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's right, I'm the giggling schoolgirl tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Question number one tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you ready for question numero uno in Video Game Match Game tonight?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Usually we have one question about each host, but Loki's not here.
[SPEAKER_28]: He decided to go have a baby or something.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's that guy.
[SPEAKER_28]: AZHP, you are to send me your answers over private message.
[SPEAKER_28]: Capisce?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, SalaciousPop, was very upset to be missing tomorrow's raid for the Guild in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_28]: Getting crafty, he came up with an idea to make the raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob, he said, if you let me go to the raid tomorrow, I will blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, don't yell out your answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: When you have an answer and you're ready to go, you're going to say...
[SPEAKER_28]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: So when you have an answer ready to go, you're going to say ding.
[SPEAKER_28]: So let me read that one more time for you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan was very upset to be missing tomorrow's raid for the Guild in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_28]: Getting crafty, he came up with an idea to make the raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob, he said, if you let me go to the raid tomorrow, I will blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: So think about your answers.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tiara is very quick at this.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think I got one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, you have one yet?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, it's Ding.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bradley?
[SPEAKER_28]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, just listen to the music again while he thinks about his answer.
[SPEAKER_18]: Totally dig the 70s here.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay, we got it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Kill the music.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan was very upset to be missing tomorrow's Raid for the Guild Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_28]: Getting crafty, he came up with an idea to make a raid.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob, he said, if you let me go to the raid tomorrow, I will... Tiara?
[SPEAKER_28]: Dress as Frankenfurter for you Dress as Frankenfurter for you Alright, we'll see if it's a match Let's see what AZHP said Because you know you're playing against somebody right now AZHP said If you let me go to the raid tomorrow I will be on this show again Is AZHP's answer Alright, let's go around the room And see if either of you match So we have Dress as Frankenfurter And be on this show again DarkSakura, I will...
[SPEAKER_28]: Service your hog.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was listening to Patton Oswalt the other day.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know what that means.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're a liar, sir.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't lie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, I will... Scream like a little girl.
[SPEAKER_28]: Scream like a little girl.
[SPEAKER_28]: If I let him go to the raid, he'll scream like a girl.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know if that's incentive, but okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just thinking of a different answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dare I ask it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, if you let me go to the raid tomorrow, I will... Pay for your Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Pay for your Pinkberry!
[SPEAKER_28]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: And my answer was, quote, if you let me go to the raid tomorrow, I will... Buy you Pinkberry!
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_28]: Look, I wrote it down.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're meant to be.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're so cute.
[SPEAKER_17]: There was boy smooching in this house.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sadly, not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, but hey, you still have a chance to make it all up on question number two.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's still tied.
[SPEAKER_28]: The board is tied zero to zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, AZHP, you didn't get a match either.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Question number two.
[SPEAKER_28]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie is getting very excited for her upcoming Disneyland trip to see Tron.
[SPEAKER_28]: I am so excited to go see Electronica, exclaimed Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have everything for my trip packed.
[SPEAKER_28]: My money, my Disney pins, and my blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie said, I am so excited to go see Electronica, and I have everything for my trip packed.
[SPEAKER_27]: We dinged at the same time.
[SPEAKER_27]: Too bad you don't get a point for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
[SPEAKER_28]: and her hoes!
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know how you pack the hoes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like panty hoes?
[SPEAKER_28]: Or like my pimps and hoes?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, your whores.
[SPEAKER_28]: Her hoes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, I don't know how you pack them.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you have to use a lot of that like styrofoam?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, well you never know.
[SPEAKER_28]: There has to be holes in the box.
[SPEAKER_17]: I use Charmin, Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: I use Charmin.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, AZHP said my money, my Disney pins, and my Pinkberry!
[SPEAKER_28]: Pinkberry!
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_28]: I have everything for my trip packed.
[SPEAKER_28]: My money, my Disney pins, and my... Light cycle.
[SPEAKER_28]: Light cycle!
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, I'm stealing Bradley's answer because I agree with it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's still not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, I have my money, my Disney pins, and my... Shermie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shermie!
[SPEAKER_18]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shermie would be afraid.
[SPEAKER_28]: That might be a match on Ho.
I...
[SPEAKER_18]: Jeremy is a stinky little hoebag sometimes.
[SPEAKER_18]: She is.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's a whore for petting.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd say that's a half point.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Jeremy's a whore.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, Tiara.
[SPEAKER_28]: The judges backstage have issued an order that you are not to get a half point for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go judges.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: and my answer is my money, my Disney pins and my sure me.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't say the same answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: My money, my Disney pins and my glow sticks.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was hot.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's all going to be a party without any hoes.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, because they'll be in L.A.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's plenty there already.
[SPEAKER_23]: I need my bitches.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, I need my bitches.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Final question, guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Final question of the night.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob is getting very nostalgic for DDR.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, we played a lot of DDR songs tonight, and I'm getting nostalgic for DDR.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I think it might be time to finally get a DDR machine for his apartment.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hope you're not upstairs but he has no money I know how I'll make the money Rob thought to himself I'll sell all my blank oh dear Rob is getting very nostalgic for DDR and wants the DDR machine in his apartment I know how I'll make the money Rob thought to himself I'll sell all my blank ding ding ding ding
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm getting yelled at because Anaheim is not LA.
[SPEAKER_28]: And my SoCal friend Ben is... Former SoCal friend Ben is yelling at me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know how I'll make the money.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, Bradley says ding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Waiting on AZHP, I think.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, did you ding?
[SPEAKER_14]: I dinged, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I think I heard Tiara.
[SPEAKER_28]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we got everybody in.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Some of you people in chat are sick.
[SPEAKER_28]: You are sick people.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know, totally sick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Your public acts are show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, geez.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, never.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tiara, you're first.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know how I'll make the money, Rob thought to himself.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my...
[SPEAKER_28]: Old Console DDR Games.
[SPEAKER_28]: A very practical answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're going to lose.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry to say, but practical answers never work.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: You'll never know.
[SPEAKER_28]: AZHP says, I'll sell all my porn collection.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, I know how I'll make the money, Rob thought to himself.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my... Surprise butt sex.
[SPEAKER_28]: Surprise butt sex.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, how do you feel about that?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_28]: Bradley, I know how I'll make the money.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my... Blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's just that serious.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not the answer, but it's the way he said it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, this is serious business.
[SPEAKER_28]: Blood, this is serious business.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alan, I know how I'll make the money.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my... Battered hilts.
[SPEAKER_28]: Battered hilts.
[SPEAKER_28]: Warcraft joke.
[SPEAKER_28]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: And here it is, and I think this is an appropriate final answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know how I'll make the money, Rob thought to himself.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll sell all my dignity.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's tally it up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just like the Jerry Lewis telethon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh yeah, that's going on, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, that's going on right now, and I'm sure it's a lot more entertaining.
[SPEAKER_28]: And he's still alive.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good for him.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's look at the big tote board.
[SPEAKER_28]: Drum roll, please.
[SPEAKER_28]: The big tally is... Oh, oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Zero!
[SPEAKER_28]: Zero to zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_23]: So it's just like football for the World Cups of soccer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I win, technically, because obviously I'm the best out of all the zeros.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we'll let you plug something anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: And AZHP, if you want to send me a private message, I'll plug whatever you want to plug.
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you want to plug, Tiara?
[SPEAKER_23]: I think I will plug Geek Life, which is a blog that I run with a couple of other people, including DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's geek-life.com.
[SPEAKER_23]: We do a lot of geeky stuff, sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_23]: We have a lot of different interesting perspectives on a lot of different stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: We have a former military man who's interested in tabletop gaming and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we have, actually, Sterlok does a column for us where he talks about his experiences as a blind gamer.
[SPEAKER_23]: Rob Kidman, my doctor he does a tech blog every week and Jamie does some cubicle stuff and geeks and history and all sorts of cool stuff so it's definitely a cool site to check out
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, check that out.
[SPEAKER_28]: Geek-life.com And someday when I get motivated, there will be video.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I keep bugging you about that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I actually shot some video last night, but not enough to make a full blog.
[SPEAKER_28]: So I'll have to do more later.
[SPEAKER_28]: But hey, the good news is, now that I have this fancy schmancy iPhone 4, I can do the HD video on the go.
[SPEAKER_28]: And it's actually really good quality, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, it's better than the $400 camera I bought two years ago.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's kind of sad, actually.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm kind of sad about that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Tiara, good luck with the site.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_28]: and AZHP in chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I just got it here.
[SPEAKER_28]: I am organizing my 12,000 MP3s because I ordered the new iPod Touch 4.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have to plug Music Brains Picard because the program will analyze your MP3 files and attempt to tag them with the correct title, artist, and album.
[SPEAKER_28]: Works even for my mislabeled pop and music albums.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's insane how good it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Recommend to anyone.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_28]: Music Brains Picard, which is a good name for it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Music Brains with a Z. There you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now the person that I know that is the most anal retentive about their MP3 collection would be Alan.
[SPEAKER_28]: So would you ever subject your MP3 collection to a program like this?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm too OCD to let anything automated affect my MP3 tags.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I could see that it would put the space in the wrong place, and you'd just be like, no!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if it took all of my compilations and unchecked the compilation tag, and like a batch process, I would die.
[SPEAKER_28]: It'd be over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's ever going to happen if that drive dies?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you have a backup somehow, or what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_28]: A tape backup somehow?
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_18]: But we have 20 more minutes.
[SPEAKER_28]: We made it over 10 and a half hours tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: I hope you guys enjoyed the marathon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Next year we just have to top it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hopefully I won't have a show the night before where I have to stay up until 3 in the morning and we can go a little longer.
[SPEAKER_28]: And DarkSakura won't be taping something in the morning.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the after show, honey.
[SPEAKER_18]: You really should play that one song for X-Link that was going to be my cage match pick.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll play it as we fade to black.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go back to the all games feed.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I still have to edit another podcast.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know you do.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, first off, the chatters are yelling because we apparently haven't been going long enough.
[SPEAKER_28]: And to that I say, oh my God, we've been going for ten and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_18]: How many people are connected right now?
[SPEAKER_28]: You savages, 88.
[SPEAKER_28]: If I'm to believe these numbers I'm looking at.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know how the stats work and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: But thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, seriously, thank you guys for staying up late with us.
[SPEAKER_28]: Late with us.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, you guys rock.
[SPEAKER_28]: But we're getting kind of delirious and I gotta sleep soon.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, don't leave us, please.
[SPEAKER_28]: But we'll be back next week, you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't cry for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll be back next week at 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_28]: right after Bobby Blackwolf he starts it off at 5 o'clock pacific and we'll be on at 6 o'clock so that's about it we're gonna go around and get everybody's final stop yawning we're gonna go around and get everybody's final thought DarkSakura, your final thought tonight Bradley, thank you for sticking it out with us tonight especially considering we didn't play a lot of games but hey, what's your final thought for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_28]: and Hydro Thunder Hurricane on the last level of the area 3051 at the first waterfall in the building go up actually stop there and turn back and go up under the waterfall you'll fall into the abyss and it's fine the abyss awesome my final thought is I actually don't want a taco tonight I just want to go home and sleep after our daily you bastard Alan your final thought of the night
[SPEAKER_14]: Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: I wish they were still open, but they're not.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll go to there tomorrow at 7.45, okay?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it, you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Everybody's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_28]: You guys really... Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: Let me look at the chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell them no.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just type N-O, period.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's very easy.
[SPEAKER_28]: You have to learn how to say no.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: You give them ten and a half hours and it's still not good enough.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, DarkSakura is now yelling at chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_28]: I would almost say this is like the longest program in the history of all games but I actually don't think that's true like I actually think all games interactive went longer one week I really do I think they went for like 12 or 13 one week we have to beat those bitches well next year next year we will and we say that endearingly I don't want anyone I don't want somebody running back saying the 11 times radio was calling you guys bitches we love you bitches we love you bitches alright I call everyone my bitches that's right
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you guys so much for staying up late with us and if you like Orange Lounge Radio, you like what you've heard, you want to support crazy ass independent podcasting, tell a friend about our show or about at least the All Games Network if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_28]: Help spread the word about independent podcasting because there's a lot of people that work hard to bring this stuff to you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Leave the stream on while we sleep.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's creepy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'd be like Sleep Talking Man.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's cake o'clock all day long.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just help us spread the word about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell two friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that's really all we ask.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's all we want.
[SPEAKER_28]: And if you didn't like our show, if you thought we sucked, then, well, first off, screw you.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Second off, tune into another show at All Games Radio because there's lots of talented folks there that talk about other games and maybe, you know, we didn't know the answer to the infamous two question.
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't know a lot about sports games, but I guarantee you there's other shows on the network that will be able to answer those like that.
[SPEAKER_28]: So check that out at the All Games Network, allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, Cyber Beast wants to sing us the national anthem of Belgium.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh no, he's going to plug us on national radio in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: I totally misread.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can we get a tape of that somehow?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I really want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know, I want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thanks, you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dude, we're big in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_28]: David Hasselhoff, look out.
[SPEAKER_14]: They can listen to us while they eat their waffles.
[SPEAKER_14]: While I eat their waffles.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like that line from Singles to paraphrase, we are loved in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you just forget already?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I didn't know who said what.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say, Belgium guy is going to record it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cyber Beast is our Belgium buddy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't go to sleep yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got shit to do.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are we out?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Good night?
[SPEAKER_28]: Fade to black?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess we're going to play the credits.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you so much for tuning in to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's do it again next week.
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you say?
[SPEAKER_22]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!