[SPEAKER_01]: A new mini-game is found in Halo Reach, a classic video game show as rated by the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_01]: What website will bribe you with Microsoft Points to use it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are that video game talk show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_11]: We tape live at All Games Radio every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_11]: www.allgames.com to listen live.
[SPEAKER_11]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crunchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crunchy the Bagel Queen Crunchy the Bagel Queen
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, also, I just got the finger.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, also say hello to special guests we have in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, they had so much fun last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're back for more, suckers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, and Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like that you're psychic to the point where you can't remember your own name
[SPEAKER_11]: It was dumb.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, even repeating the story is really dumb.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't that mean I have ESPN?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because you're psycho and have ESPN.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is really, really dumb.
[SPEAKER_11]: For real.
[SPEAKER_11]: For real, real.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, it's for reals, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com if you want to join us live and chat with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: You got a fan in chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkKisuke's in chat saying, Rice Princess, we loves you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Aw, thanks.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love you too, whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't even know him.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I really don't, but thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like you too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma says, I thought tonight was a repeat as many times as Jamie said crunchy, lol.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's we're live here on this lovely September evening of 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's 2010 of course, we're live and we're going to talk about all the latest and greatest in video games and all that But of course we're going to start off the show as we always do with a little bit of How was your gaming week, DarkSakura, CrunchyTheBagelQueen?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_14]: I love Plants vs. Zombies a lot Like, I was supposed to go to bed at midnight a couple nights ago I was going to Apple Hill on the weekend Okay, your mic is full of fail, you gotta grab it Okay, I got it Alright, starting over
[SPEAKER_14]: I had to go to bed early one night because we were going to Apple Hill the next day.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It has lots of apple juice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apple Hill's awesome?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: But instead of going to bed on time when I was supposed to, I was up for three hours playing Plants vs. Zombies and didn't even realize how late I was up playing Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I did it again yesterday.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I love that game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plants vs. Zombies is freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then I played some Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_14]: How many times can this dude say hero?
[SPEAKER_09]: For those of our listeners that aren't local to the Sacramento area, Apple Hill is a place a little bit up, I guess, a little eastern from us.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Camino, California.
[SPEAKER_09]: Up the hill, I guess, if you will, where they have a lot of apples and crafts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the apple cider is awesome, but apple cider is awesome all the time, but it's crafts.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Swamp Hill.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've got crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing that Apple does have going for it is there was a place there that had a really good lamb burger of which I got lamb burger juice all over my hands and wiped it off on a lamb.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a lamb burglar there?
[SPEAKER_09]: That is sick.
[SPEAKER_11]: PETA's going to be calling any minute now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's your sister.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come here.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's gross.
[SPEAKER_14]: For the record, I went shopping at the organic market up there and
[SPEAKER_14]: I picked Heirloom Tomatoes Fell down the hill My knee looks better than it did You took a tumble down Apple Hill Did it shake you to your core?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, I'm leaving This was the awesome part When I fell on my knees I really bruised up my knee really bad But I did not tear my jeans So you were a bruised Apple Hill I'll be here all night everybody Don't forget to tip your waitress
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_14]: So.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love how your gaming week is like, yeah, I play Planet vs. Zombies and a little more Final Fantasy XIII and oh my god, apples.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apples, apples, apples, apples, apples.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm not talking Max.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got fudge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do have an apple cider milkshake that's pretty good though.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's where we have lunch.
[SPEAKER_14]: We had lunch at the place that had the apple milkshakes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was so good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Video games are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to Apple Hill and pack some fudge just like Crunchy the Bagel Queen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't need to go to Apple Hill to do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys have earned it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_11]: What I love is that your mic is so crappy it won't pick that thing up anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: My mic is not crappy.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the cord that's crappy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should bring the swear bear in.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have a swear bear?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a swear bear.
[SPEAKER_09]: At my desk.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is a swear bear?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a bear that makes really obscene comments.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's what it sounds like, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has two different settings on the back of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has a switch, which I thought was an on-off switch, and for the longest time kept saying, kiss my ass, instead of all the wonderful things he normally says.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he'll say, of course, kiss my ass, and he'll say, eat shit and die, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I have it on my desk, and it's a really cute-looking bear.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says, hug me, or press me in its chest, and some people are like, oh, it's a bear!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck did they just say to me?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, seriously, why do we not have a swear bear here in the studio?
[SPEAKER_11]: I will bring it in next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm not going to be here next week, so I think that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't you have the swear bear sit in for me next week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss the ferret, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I ate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't help it, it's so addicting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, it's an awesome game, so you should get it really on any platform that you can.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then also, of course, more Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: We went back, like I said, to the Lost and Damned expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of missed the old open world actual death matches and stuff instead of being confined to a really small portion of the map.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of nice to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to be modding it again soon, so I'll be back to the incredible games that we used to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, since she brought up something completely unrelated to games, I thought I'd bring something up that...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: It didn't break at any point?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, different carrots.
[SPEAKER_09]: He shoved one through a guy's throat.
[SPEAKER_09]: He stabbed a person in the eye with a carrot.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was just... The movie, from the beginning, was just so over the top.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the fuck movie is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's with... Oh, what the fuck is his name?
[SPEAKER_15]: That actor that nobody knows.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I can't think of any.
[SPEAKER_15]: That guy who did that thing in that place.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but no, it's a really, really just over-the-top movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, they spend, like, two minutes where it's just kind of okay, normal, and then it's just like, boom, all action, just all the time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, over-the-top, gratuitous.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're having sex in a gunfight at the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there's...
[SPEAKER_09]: There's parts where he is... He was doing something with a baby.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shoot Em Up is a 2007 action film starring Clive Owen, Paul Giamatti, and Monica Bellucci.
[SPEAKER_11]: She was the hot chick in The Matrix, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: And she was the hot chick in that movie, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: She was a lactating prostitute that he brought the baby to feed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, sounds like a real family fun film.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, it is, like, such an awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I do idolize the fact that he killed people that annoyed him.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, he's all, you know my pet peeve?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, there's, like, one part after a gunfight, they're, like, getting away from these bad guys, and this guy cuts them off without, you know, he merged lanes without signaling.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he chased the guy down, slammed him off the road, and then, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: I could have swore that Loki said let's talk about actual video games this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did!
[SPEAKER_09]: This is his Apple Hill moment, just give it to him, Rob No, seriously, I mean, I totally missed this when it came out in theaters but, you know, on DVD and Blu-ray and stuff like that until it was on cable TV No, seriously, it's such an awesome movie, just way over the top I don't understand why it didn't do better than it did in the box office because it was just such a crazy movie
[SPEAKER_15]: If I'm understanding this correctly, he's killing anyone that even slightly annoys him.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's no anger issues at all in this movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not everybody, but usually it's like, I don't know, lots of funny one-liners in there and just really ridiculous stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: At one point he gets both of his thumbs broken and he's firing the gun in really weird ways.
[SPEAKER_09]: He uses the carrot a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: He uses the carrot to fire the gun.
[SPEAKER_09]: He jams a carrot into the trigger of an Uzi and throws the Uzi at the bad guys and
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just so ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's one scene in the warehouse where he rigs this elaborate pulley system with all these guns and they're coming after him and he's watching them on security cameras and firing different guns in remote places.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it would make such an awesome video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's how we bring it back.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this is called again?
[SPEAKER_09]: Shoot Em Up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shoot Em Up.
[SPEAKER_15]: That sounds like a lot of video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, seriously, I think it was one of the most incredible movies I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I think it even surpasses Wanted for me, because Wanted I thought was a pretty awesome action movie, but this is just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is like big hit ridiculous and then some.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love the big hit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that movie is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Back to shoot-em-up radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a torrent ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I have a YouTube clips of it ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Today I actually played Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played for like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there an echo in the room?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other games I played this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played a little more of Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light because I hadn't really played it since the week it came out and I was like, oh, I want to
[SPEAKER_11]: and beat more of it because it's such a cool game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I wanted to play more of that, so I did.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I remembered another game I played.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is she just going to cut me off for your game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you made me think about it wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Droplets.
[SPEAKER_11]: The hell's that?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: You should think about fitting Earthbound into there somewhere, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: At some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're a little behind like many years.
[SPEAKER_11]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played World of Warcraft a lot because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: You played too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I did play something new.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played Need for Speed World, which is the free MMO because it's free.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's an MMO?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a free Need for Speed MMO.
[SPEAKER_11]: It came out on the show a couple of weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty much like that, but it's kind of such a clusterfuck that I guess around a race or something, there's no collision detection because seriously, there'll be like 20 cars piled up where all the cars happen to start.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it looks kind of funny with all these names.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I didn't really get the MMO part of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The cops are very dumb in that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Talk bad about a free game because it actually was pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only free games I can think of that I can talk bad about are Yaris, of course, Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was really bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, there's only a handful.
[SPEAKER_11]: But this is worth your time to look, especially if you're a fan of racing games or you need free speed.
[SPEAKER_11]: It plays a lot like one of the Xbox games that I've played in the past.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other than that, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was playing some new iPhone games because who doesn't love iPhone games?
[SPEAKER_11]: The Game Center games.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a game in there called Word Challenge and I was a little scared at first because it's by Zynga.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could go in and look up some obscure words.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have that one game that's on the App Store now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like some pirate version of Scrabble where all the words are like R. Okay, there's only so many words you can do in pirate speak.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like R and then R.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but that's literally what it was.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was literally that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it was kind of a joke for Talk Like a Pirate Day or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: How do you know that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually launching the game right now so I can read some of the obscure words.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going into the challenges because X-Link dared to send me some challenges.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I whooped them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, because it's X-Link.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are some of the... Wagerers, Eagerer...
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me look at some of the, like, these aren't words you think of, like, as you're playing these games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me look at some of the, like... Did they say eager?
[SPEAKER_11]: Eager.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not a word!
[SPEAKER_11]: It is a word, according to this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's bad English.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, more eager.
[SPEAKER_11]: T-W-A-E.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tway.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never heard that word before.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought you were going to spell twat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to spell twat.
[SPEAKER_11]: T-W-A-E.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tway?
[SPEAKER_11]: Tway, did you say?
[SPEAKER_11]: I see tire, and I see twas, and I get those, like twas the night before Christmas, but tway?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I almost said twig, but I know what a twig is.
What's that?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's a VIGA?
[SPEAKER_11]: V-I-G-A.
[SPEAKER_11]: VIGA.
[SPEAKER_15]: VIGA?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds dirty.
[SPEAKER_11]: A VIGA.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's like, it sounds like part of a word, like vegetable.
[SPEAKER_14]: VEGA, like vagina?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, the definition of VEGA.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of the heavy rafters and especially a log supporting the roof of an American Indian or Spanish architecture of the Southwest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I fucking know Spanish architecture in the Midwest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't you feel sheepish now?
[SPEAKER_09]: I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: You don't know that word.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: If only you were more eager.
[SPEAKER_14]: And TWA is the Scottish variant of TOO.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, some fucking Scottish words are in the game?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: That word would be banned in Scrabble, just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so anyway, that's my one problem with this game is that you could just drag your finger around the board and connect three letters and as long as there's a vowel, you'll probably have a word.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, you might be able to make a word out of nothing but vowels, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, how about our guests?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_11]: The Doctor?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, much like Rice Princess, I only own a Nintendo Wii So Nintendo of America, I haven't been playing video games at all
[SPEAKER_11]: What have you been doing in real life?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you go to Apple Hill or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: I went... I did, and I ate Captain Picard.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bryce Prince is just showing me Captain Picard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Captain Picard and I went to Apple Hill, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we ate lots of apples and had sex.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, don't make things up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should make a drink that's themed after, you know, Star Trek and call it Picard-y.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_11]: Salacious Pop in our chat room says, Aviga is a little vajay from Italy that hipsters ride around on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's sad that I understand that joke.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rice Princess, I don't know if you have anything you want to share about your gaming week, but I thought I'd try anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played homework for the PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_15]: And insomnia for the bed.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's my game in week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Full of action.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to get a little like one of those like books to read in bed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Rub it in my face.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, loves you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can just take junk mail, staple it together, and pretend it's a book.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, I have books.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to buy, like, $500 books for school.
[SPEAKER_15]: I should probably read them.
[SPEAKER_09]: No book should be $500 nowadays.
[SPEAKER_15]: I realize that.
[SPEAKER_15]: You realize that.
[SPEAKER_15]: But publishing companies are like, well, we can't make money on the books, so we have to keep re-releasing the same crap and charge $500.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and plus they're not giving a discount on the iBooks and stuff now, which I think is ridiculous for schools.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I prefer like paper books anyway, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems to me, though, that they should be giving, since they're not distributing the paper, they should give a discount on iBooks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of the books end up being cheaper anyway, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've gotten a few through Amazon that are, just end up being something like maybe $30 cheaper than buying a full textbook.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the Kindle or whatever?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I use the Kindle app on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, then it's a lot better than bringing a whole big book with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually bought a book in iBooks this week on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: So, good luck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Suckers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So enjoy next week's show while I'm not here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also join us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_11]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and Twitter.com slash OLR is where you can find us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any housekeeping you want to add?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, IGM claims to have received technical specs for the Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: We know what's in it now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Years after it's come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, the handheld system will be using the DMP PICA 200 GPU.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, that's impressive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Running at a slowed down 166 MHz along with two ARM11 CPUs running at 266 MHz.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a lot of MHz, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: No?
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_09]: which of course it doesn't seem to back the rumor that it was running the Nvidia Tegra chips and it says according to IGN as well they will also have a looks like a gig and a half of flash memory for storage much like the DSi's do now except a little bit more
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, numerous developers are working on software for the platform, obviously, since they showed out a bunch of stuff at E3 anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: And said that they've likened the graphical capabilities to current generation consoles like Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3, albeit on smaller, lower resolution screens.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently, I guess, it's only going to have 64 megs of RAM.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Do the cartridges not have it on there?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, see, that's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't understand why you couldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say, for example, have more RAM on the cartridge or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't skimp on important stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I guess their reasoning behind it is that, first off, the 3DS doesn't have an iOS or some sort of operating system to hog resources.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also because it's low resolution, it's not going to use as much RAM.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does it explain how the 3D without glasses works, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: 3D Without Glasses, it's basically like... We talked about that like six months ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody should have been listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it works very much like those... Of course, I can't remember what they're called now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you seen those, for example, kind of little hologram things that they have?
[SPEAKER_09]: Lenticular.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a lenticular page or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: where basically there's lenses in there that force half the image into one eye and half the image into the other eye and it makes it seem like it's popping out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or not necessarily popping out, but going back in.
[SPEAKER_09]: It gives it depth.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's actually a person standing behind the DS and holding stuff in front of your face.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tiny, tiny digital midget is how it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there will be plenty of sex games on the 3DS then.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: I would assume so, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's powered by the Force.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I don't know what powers this game, but there's going to be apparently a reboot rumored of Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_11]: This has been rumored for some time, and it's kind of a duh, because Tomb Raider... It's been rebooted how many times now?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't the last one a reboot, and then the last one before that a reboot?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then this Lara Croft game was also kind of a reboot, but it was more like, let's go this way with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's make kind of a different game with the same character.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of different.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's worked well all those times.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, some of them weren't bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this most recent one, the Lara Croft game, is the most interesting one I think I've played since the first two on the PC years ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if they got it right, then they wouldn't be rebooting it every few years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I think there's supposed to be different franchises.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I think there's going to be new Lara Croft games for arcade download, and then the DVD Blu-ray games will be these, this reboot or whatever that's been rumored for some time.
[SPEAKER_11]: and in an interview with I'm sorry not an interview but a report from Eurogamer apparently says the latest issue of PC Gamer I guess I get their eyes on it first says that the new Tomb Raider is indeed happening it's supposed to be set on a Japanese island and it will offer Laura in an open world it's a quote cohesive level with multiple ways around the puzzles so it's one giant level I guess is how this game is supposed to work Supercroft 64
[SPEAKER_11]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to say that Laura is, quote, younger and inexperienced in the ways of raiding tombs.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that quote.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's inexperienced in raiding tombs.
[SPEAKER_11]: She just needs a strong man to share the ways.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're guessing holiday 2011 for Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Notice how I left out the we.
[SPEAKER_14]: As long as you can lock everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: Butler in the freezer, I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_14]: She looks so mad in that picture, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: That little picture, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, obviously, I really like the game that was on Xbox, the download that's coming out on the other platforms really soon, so if that's kind of the direction they're going with it, I'm all for it, although it's not supposed to be that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've said it's going to be a completely different kind of game, I guess more like the original, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, the latest game on the arcade kind of has me excited about Lara Croft again, so this could be good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I liked back when the early rumors were suggesting it was more of a survival horror game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, if that's true, I think that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: That doesn't even make sense, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: How is there a segue between Tomb Raider and then Haunted Tomb?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you ever see The Descent?
[SPEAKER_11]: The movie The Descent?
[SPEAKER_11]: I did see The Descent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where it's all the chicks in the cave, and it's like one of the scariest movies I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be so corny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be so forced.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think I've ever seen a scarier movie than The Descent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a pussy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry, but The Descent was not that.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, you!
[SPEAKER_15]: It was not...
[SPEAKER_15]: Why are you mad though?
[SPEAKER_15]: I ain't mad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I ain't mad at you girl.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it wasn't that scary.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes it was.
[SPEAKER_11]: I sat there the whole time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've seen much scarier movies than that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like the Care Bears movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: That shit was scary man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Assholes.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're assholes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You talk about scary movies in, like, you know, caverns or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fraggle Rock, the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, did that movie give you nightmares?
[SPEAKER_11]: It didn't really give me nightmares.
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually, like, I'm kind of sick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, it actually made me want to go, like, explore a cave, just so I could get scared more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now you know, though, what every gay guy in Amateur County does, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to go spelunking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Were you going to go ass spelunking?
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'll laugh if I tell you the only movie that gave me nightmares.
[SPEAKER_14]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_14]: Poltergeist 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of the Poltergeist movies were kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was the mirrors.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was freaked out over mirrors for like a week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not even kidding about the Care Bears movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like there's this one part where they go into the fun house and it's like the guy's chasing him and he looks like, you know, crazy.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm just like, ah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh no, we watched Labyrinth last night and I always get freaked out with the creatures that take their heads off.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, they're creepy.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that, when I was a little kid, I would fast forward through that scene, like, no joke.
[SPEAKER_11]: That scared the crap out of me, and... You guys are fucking trivializing my skin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or the helping hand.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm for real.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the fuck does this have to do with Tomb Raider?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm for real.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, she was, she was in a scary forest.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Vice Princess and I, earlier, we were talking about, you know, Return to Oz, and the... I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, Return to Oz... I'm sorry, like, I don't know how, like, any of you that are in, like, your late 20s, early 30s, that saw Return to Oz when it was in theaters...
[SPEAKER_11]: That movie scarred me.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: She had the fucking heads and glasses.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was scary.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was based directly off the books and not all watered down like the other movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think that they should do more of those types of movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not watered down.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta go to our chatroom, chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bonds006 says, the Transformer movie from the 80s because someone died and I almost cried.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they say shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Bumblebee's like, oh shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it wasn't Bumblebee, it was Cliffjumper.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it was Bumblebee.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, no, no, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was What's-His-Face's dad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Said, oh shit, it isn't dented.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spike
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I got one more.
[SPEAKER_11]: One more quick line here from chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chat.OriginalsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: SalaciousPop says, LOL, Irene.
[SPEAKER_11]: I ain't mad because if I was mad, you would be dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm on seven.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't want to see me on ten.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of the other movies being named in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Legend with the young Tom Cruise.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do your... No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: Legend, there's a scene I cannot watch in that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: The scene at the beginning where he's talking about the unicorns?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, when he...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that scene that we can't talk about because it's a spoiler?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the scene at the beginning when Tim Curry's talking about the unicorns, and he's like, Mother Night, let your dark arms surround me.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm like, oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys are both wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Frenzy that said, oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's Frenzy?
[SPEAKER_14]: They even have the clip on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm talking about when they blew up the ship on Unicron.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was the one that Spike said.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because the line is, oh, shit, it isn't even dented.
[SPEAKER_14]: That one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wasn't telling you about that
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you IMDB Anyway, and Robert Stack's character said, damn it, anyway There's somebody we need to bring back as a zombie Robert Stack?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hell yeah Okay, anywho, Atari launched this thing called Atari Go And they want to make classic games good for social gaming
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, Tom Kozik, who is the executive VP of online and mobile gaming, said that they're going to use Atari's catalog and independent developers to, I guess, provide more casual and online social gaming.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, it's, here's our old shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't have an Atari.
[SPEAKER_14]: Play this.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I can go, no sir, you're wrong, I have several I don't need your online gaming But we've played their games on like every system that's been released ever Yay, I can play Missile Command again And then like I could put Mr. Awesome on my friends list on Facebook And then just, you know, get all these little like pokes and graphics About how much better he is at Missile Command than me Why can't we just like have Atari go sit in their corner And stop putting out their old shit
[SPEAKER_14]: How about Atari?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they also, though, are doing more things for the core games as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have a Facebook tie-in that's going to unlock extra content, or might unlock extra content for Test Drive Unlimited 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then Asteroids Online and Deer Hunter Online, there are going to be reimaginings of those in a socialized context.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I quoted that.
[SPEAKER_09]: How does one socialize in asteroids?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, dude, shoot that rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, I shot your rock.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, my rock's now three rocks and you can't hit them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's what's going to be on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, it'll come up and it'll be all, Jamie, shot your rock in asteroids.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click here to shoot her back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bitch, I can't believe you shot my rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is all free, though, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's Facebook, it's gotta be, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: They use the word that I hate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Microtransactions I will make the most microtransaction possible A transaction is a transaction But I've been on that site recently I think after this whole thing launched I was able to play Missile Command for free Some of the newer ones were going to have the whole microtransaction I literally played one level and I was like Ah, Missile Command Back to porn A different kind of Missile Command
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically everyone's night on the internet every day, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, look, something cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, wait a second.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't they do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if you think about it, it makes perfect sense to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody is looking for casual gaming and porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: So why not make a Facebook that's full of porn?
[SPEAKER_09]: AskBook.
[SPEAKER_09]: and just have like, you know, tons of casual games.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they could be like Missile Command and stuff, but they're, I don't know, they have porn in the background or, you know, you're playing against porn stars or they're porno themed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or like asteroids where you have like a big dildo shooting floating vaginas or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, sure, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, sure, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, just porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any kind of porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on, porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Coming soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: To the PC, it's the Atari Go I don't like it, stop it Rob Hey, remember that porn we bought years and years ago for Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was like Summer Boys or something like that And the back said like, watch these boys beat the heat and their meat In this crazy sex-stravaganza Are you really bringing this up on our video game talk show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's the best line I've ever seen on the back of a DVD ever Why?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's why we bought it for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you like to watch gay porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: So does Jamie.
[SPEAKER_14]: So do I. But Rob has the ability to sleep through very noisy gay porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: At Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, I remember this.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was the clincher right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: At Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_14]: We all went to Disneyland on the trip with the giggling lesbians of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: That sounds like a story.
[SPEAKER_15]: The giggling lesbians of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was Kristen and Megzi.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go to play Atari Go.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then we're all like awake and Rob's like...
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, all the girls, we had a suite, and it was like a living room with a hide-a-bed, and then there was a closed-off room with two double beds in it, and so Chrissy Megzy had one, and I ignored their slurpy noises.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_14]: and I was and I was I was you know so we all were awake before Rob and Rob's just like dead to the world and very interesting kind of dramatic like with this pillow half over his head it was funny hold on if you listen carefully can you hear it yeah you hear all that clicking yeah that's all the people unsubscribing from OLR right now so so Kristen takes out her laptop and
[SPEAKER_14]: I brought gay porn!
[SPEAKER_14]: And so it's really loud and she turns up her computer all the way and Rob's just like, snore.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we let it play through like the biggest, you know, this aquatic scene that would make showgirls, you know, completely be shamed.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Rob's just like...
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one more idea for a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, this is actually not too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how they have that kind of hobby that's geocaching or, I guess, GPS hunting, that type of stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: You call it find porn, or found porn, and basically you hide porn around there and mark it on your GPS location and people can go find the porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or there could be a naked slut.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that's way too much work.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to do that on my computer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I found porn and I'm going to watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the new Google Earth little click that you can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like just randomly, you have to search the Google Earth for like random porn place and random place.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did I tell you the one time at work I was trying to type in Google and I typed in goggle and it brought up porn?
[SPEAKER_14]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a typo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, whoa.
[SPEAKER_11]: Clever.
[SPEAKER_11]: How about Video Game News?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you know we do that here on Orange Sons Radio once in a while?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why would we do that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, do you have some... Are you busy looking at porn?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's looking at porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're making sure... Oh, it's not a real website anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it used to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: It used to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: Big Brother was watching.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they were amused.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Super Street Fighter 4 is not coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know people are probably surprised considering it's been months since it's been released.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's not coming out on PC because apparently games are pirated and stuff on the PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they didn't want to release it on PC, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: What does that mean?
[SPEAKER_15]: What does it all mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that their first Street Fighter 4 game got pirated a lot now, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, apparently they said in a recent interview with 4gamer.net, uh, that, uh, Yoshinori Ono confirmed that, uh, while the PC version of Street Fighter 4 was a big seller worldwide, well, wait a second, that sold a lot and wasn't really pirated that much since...
[SPEAKER_09]: The publisher has no plans to put the new and improved Super Street Fighter 4 iteration on home computers due to the platform's high rate of piracy.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said that the port is still possible if Capcom can find a reasonable DRM solution for the title.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, just forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to waste all this damn time, spend all this money on a DRM solution, and it's going to get cracked in a day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just put it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not going to get pirated any less than if you have DRM on it than not having DRM on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I keep thinking in my mind, I kind of am surprised that companies haven't got to this point.
[SPEAKER_11]: As much as I don't like it as a consumer, it wouldn't surprise me at all if they started going there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's possible that they do that, but even sometimes there's ways around that, around getting the phone home and typing stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: you know that kind of thing you could for example have a program running in the background that mimics their authentication server and you just change the forwards on like a certain IP address on your computer so that it forwards to that they've done that for a few things you know like some of the Adobe programs and stuff like that phone home and you can disable that not that I would know
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you hear that, listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want folks to hear me the wrong way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not saying I support this DRM to start happening, but I wouldn't be surprised if companies felt like there was no other choice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big companies like Microsoft and stuff that put out these operating systems and they supposedly have these ways that the system calls home to authenticate Windows and that kind of thing, and yet there's still pirated versions out there despite the fact they're, oh, Windows 7!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we're going to have stronger security.
[SPEAKER_09]: And pirate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, okay, so that took three seconds instead of two seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well, in the interest of the companies, I mean, DRM is not...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: you know pirate the game probably weren't going to buy it originally so you're technically not losing sales because if they can't pirate the game they're just not going to download it and they're not going to play it they're not going to you know unless it's a really really good game they're not going to go out and buy it
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you guys remember the old, like, pathetic ways that they used to, like, try to stop pirating?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, we're going to put a crazy word in the instruction booklet that you have to know, like, to get past the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, and then you just tell all your friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's the second word on page four of the manual here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and what's the crazy, you know, third day of the week, the way we say, you know, it was like, and then you just tell all your friends and it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or the wheels.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember the wheels.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, for the LucasArts games, they had wheels that you had to rotate around at different things, and then you'd have to read a code number out of one of the slots or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_09]: and those even didn't work either because you could either photocopy the manual or you could rip apart that disc and photocopy the disc so once again it doesn't matter what DRM solution they put out there even if it's a USB dongle or something like that some really expensive programs like graphic programs and stuff like that that are you know thousands of dollars will actually have a physical device that needs to be plugged into the computer to work those still can be pirated though because people find ways to mimic whatever that device is and
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no way around it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody's going to find a way around something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Given a significant amount of time, there will always be a way around something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because if you can make it, someone else can make it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, speaking of a game that was somewhat hurt by piracy, allegedly Halo Reach came out, of course, a couple weeks ago and if you already have beat the game and you're already bored of it maybe there should be a mini-game that you should go play that is actually hidden in Halo Reach It's called Reach Racer and it's a warthog racing game that is inside Reach What happens is that if two people get to a spot in the Oni sword base you can actually play this little mini-game
[SPEAKER_11]: and Reach Racer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you all right over there?
[SPEAKER_11]: You made me drop my mic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Trauma!
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like when there's fun little things like that in a game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just know all morning I was hearing boom, yay, boom, yay, boom, yay all morning.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why, was Dan playing Halo Reach?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that what he actually says?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it has a little party mode thing in there where you get a headshot and the kids go yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they put on the duck boots from Castlevania and go Sorry Bones006 in chat says, okay, that almost made me want to get Reach That's kind of cool Well, the Forge editor and Reach anyways is just really credible anyways, so maybe that's your thing
[SPEAKER_11]: Going back up a little bit in chat, Robert M is talking about the copy protection thing and says, the pages with red paper to keep it from being copied.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember those too.
[SPEAKER_11]: There were manuals that would have like the red paper.
[SPEAKER_11]: So ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dorks.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it kind of worked for a little bit, like until the internet came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Until they had color scanners and they're like, ah, foil again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Color copies.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why didn't we think of that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not available to copy these CDs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, release date's coming up in a minute, but first, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there has been something that has been spotted.
[SPEAKER_14]: A new Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's actually the Wii Remote Plus that seems to be a combination of the Wii Motion Plus and the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's going to be coming with a game called Fling Smash.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it looks like tennis, but with a crazy-ass ball.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you have to use this ball guy named Zip, and you use your controller, I guess, to smack him around the different places.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd have to see more than just this picture.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, there is no date out for the UK.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game is listed, but not the special controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know when they're going to get it overseas.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't help but feel this is kind of like a Wii Play type thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where you throw in a controller with a subpar game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is no interest in this game whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that I'm judging this game without playing it, but I'm just going to take a wild guess and guess and say it's not very good.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be the best game of the year.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be the best selling game of the year because it comes with a stupid remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if you think about it, the game's $50 and you get a remote that's probably worth at least $50 because I'm sure it's going to be more than just the normal remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: And people should get pissed off because now they bought a remote and stupid Wii Motion Plus and now they come out with something that's all-in-one despite the fact that perhaps they should have, I don't know, put it all-in-one to begin with so that they could do all the stuff that they said they weren't going to be able to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: It prints money!
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkKisuke in chat says, whatever, Wii is dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you guys agree?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a Wii.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I use it for Netflix.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's... Poop.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's doing alright, it's just there's... I mean, the game's coming out that are big releases for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't really care too much about, like, ooh, it's Donkey Kong Country again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, that's awesome!
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember playing that back on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's not forget how amazed and in awe we all were after E3 at, you know, their lineup and the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I was impressed with Metroid Other M, and then it sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm glad that Team Ninja really pulled it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, but it sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, you know, ooh, new Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoop-dee-shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a brighter, more colorful, cheerful Twilight Princess with new gadgets and shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's... It was... Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a difference between, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: What it looks like on paper, what it actually comes out to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something that works in theory but not in practice Something that works in theory but not in practice
[SPEAKER_09]: Except now that it has a stupid controller thing in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's travel around the world and look at some release dates, things that are coming out to a store near you real soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week, actually, some pretty cool stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, Dead Rising 2 will be out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guitar Hero Warriors of Rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, what's kind of funny is a lot of the music games coming out nowadays, people don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, uh, but Guitar Hero Warriors of Rock is coming out on, uh, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and we never forget they're all $60, because Activision is fucking lame, and so they decided to charge $60 for all three games, because I don't know, you're suckers and you'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let them get away with that, and then they're gonna be charging $60 for all their Wii games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, but it doesn't matter, because people don't buy games on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, of course, Guitar Hero Warriors of Rock will be coming out in different bundles.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have one with the full band set up, which is really just the instruments from last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: So don't expect the new guitar in that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can only get that in the guitar kit, and they aren't selling the guitar separately.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you want the lame new guitar that's out there, you're going to have to buy it in that stupid bundle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other fun stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: A re-release of The Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're calling it the Deluxe Edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe that's with some of the download content.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or not download content, but the expansions that were in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Sims 3 and Sims 3 Ambitions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Save you a little bit of money there, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Farm Frenzy Animal Country on the DS Deer Drive on the DS, it's a deer hunting game Front Mission Evolved on Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 this is kind of not necessarily the tactical strategy game as before but it is a armored core clone so that'll be coming from Square Enix and I don't know if it'll be very good oh and it's also on PC
[SPEAKER_09]: Otlier Rorona, The Alchemists of Arland.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's coming out now on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a role-playing game from Tecmo and I believe Nippon Ichi.
[SPEAKER_09]: MorphX on Xbox 360 from 505 Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tropico 3 is getting the Gold Edition coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quantum 3, the Gears of War clone on Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 from Tecmo Koei.
[SPEAKER_09]: And crap from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pets Fantasy, Moonlight Magic and Sunlight Magic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are coming out this week on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like fishing, Rapala's Pro Bash Fishing 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii, DS, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also have a bundle for the PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those actually come with a wireless fishing rod, except for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: It comes with a crappy attachment for the controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: FIFA Soccer 2011 coming out in pretty much all systems except for Playstation 2 I believe My Sim Sky Heroes on Xbox 360, Playstation 3, Wii, DS and what else we have coming out
[SPEAKER_09]: Plants vs. Zombies Plants vs. Zombies
[SPEAKER_09]: Greg Hastings Paintball 2 Oops!
[SPEAKER_09]: Prank Party
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's have a prank party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you guess who this is coming to us from?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're a company that used to make really awesome stuff and then they purchased this smaller company.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Hudson coming to us from Konami.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Konami, because we really need some more party games on the Wii because there just wasn't enough party games.
[SPEAKER_11]: What kind of pranks can you pull?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_09]: What kind of pranks can we pull?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, it's incredibly fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a smart mix of 100 brain-teasing, puzzle-solving, and reflex-testing games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a prank at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Haas fooled you.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually brain games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pranks on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: No pantsing, no putting rice in the freezer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently while you're playing the game, though, you can tease the competition with outlandish pranks.
[SPEAKER_09]: All in the name of good, clean fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Embarrassing outfits, side-splitting, family-friendly pranks that make light-hearted taunts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_09]: Prank Party will have players coming back for more off-the-wall four-player action time and time again.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they won't!
[SPEAKER_11]: No one cares.
[SPEAKER_11]: Frisbee in chat says, I thought Loki was going to say, oops, pregnant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops, pregnant party.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd go to that party.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops, I got pregnant.
[SPEAKER_11]: My baby!
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft in chat says, Oops, prank party.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that OLR every other week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, zing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, Sid Meier's Pirates coming out on Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Guild 2 Renaissance on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haunted House, the remake of the Atari game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Atari, for bringing out wonderful games that are not... Oh, wait, no, this is a remake of an old...
[SPEAKER_09]: Classic Atari game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guess I'll just have to wait for my Xbox 360, Xbox Live Arcade version to come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm highly anticipating that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Frisbee in chat says, cutting the brakes out of someone's car.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that's a prank party game I'd play.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like really horrific things you can't do in real life.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or you know when you offer someone a Jamba Juice and there's no Jamba Juice in there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up, you're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: And thanks to our wonderful DJ friend from the Bay Area, Get Fit with Mel B's coming out this week on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it'll be the first, guess what, this is a collector's item because it's the first PlayStation Move fitness game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I'm not really excited about that, it's going to be crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, I'm Mel B.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Jenny McCarthy fitness game on the Wii, and I would love to do all those nasty exercises that must be in this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every time I think about the Spice Girls in a video game, though, I just can't help but hear in my mind, let's put another girl through her pieces.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you've ever played the Spice Girls game on PS1, which none of you probably have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still a few more things coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, it's getting in the fourth quarter stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I love how it's all crap like Oops!
[SPEAKER_11]: Prank Party, just bogging down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, okay, there's a lot of crap that comes out in between our Call of Duty games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make it snappy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Script Spelling Bee.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a Spelling Bee game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be exciting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Death Smiles, the version without all the fun extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's slightly cheaper on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a re-release there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fantasy XIV, the I Had to Wait Another Week edition that is coming to us on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Painkiller, Pandemonium on PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's pandemonium about it is it's probably not good.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think this dates right, but they're saying the Sly Collection is coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's later in the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then finally, this is high quality Wii games for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is one of those first party games from Nintendo that's really going to innovate and change the whole landscape of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wii Party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Coming to us on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's also from Hudson that made the Mario Party games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played it at E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's another party game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just like them complaining on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_09]: People only buy it for kids' stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's only got kids' games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why can't we get people to actually develop mature games on our system?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I have a question for anyone.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, when you've heard of this game that's going to come out and it's really hyped and it sounds really good and you really want to play it and then you actually get it, lately, has it lived up to the hype for you?
[SPEAKER_11]: You mean like Final Fantasy XIV when I played the beta?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I wanted to cry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tears of joy?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tears of pain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're limiting the amount of suffering you actually have to endure because you can't play long hours on this game because they will start dropping your XP.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't played the full game yet, and like, here's the sick thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Y'all, I am really sick, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: We know you're sick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though, like, I really hated the beta, I still feel like I need to buy the retail game to give it a fair chance.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I spent so much time on XI, and it's a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sub!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's exactly what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just say no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_15]: The state of the industry these days.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: You do have a problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's called wasting your money on shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't do it, Ron.
[SPEAKER_11]: How about you just wait for the reviews to come out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm gonna try and see if some of the reviews, what they say.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought Final Fantasy XIII was pretty awesome and it had a lot of hype behind it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, not XIV, but XIII was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sometimes the hype machine can kind of ruin games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think part of the reason I didn't want to buy Halo Reach is that you just can't get away from it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was playing Lara Croft online and I actually got an Xbox Live message from somebody who was like, what, you're not playing Halo Reach?
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm just like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Screw you!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll play what I want!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, I'm gonna put in frickin' Cameo or one of the Xbox 360 launch games just to irritate you.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I realized I'd actually have to play Cameo and I don't know if that would actually be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw someone this week playing on my friends list and you know who you are, I think, because I don't remember who you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone was actually playing Lost Via Domus.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Lost console game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's go to Japanese release dates of Loki's done with the U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising 2
[SPEAKER_11]: A game called Quantum Theory comes out on the Xbox 360 this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks like a Bayonetta-y type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of epic-looking cutscenes and guns and swords and limbs falling off and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's from Tecmo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder if it's a Team Ninja game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think it is, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Going over to the Nintendo Wii to check out the releases over there.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have really not a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really, the next big, big release is the Kaito no Kirby game, which would be Kirby's Epic Yarn over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: That comes out in Japan on the 14th of October.
[SPEAKER_11]: Before that, not a lot of big stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: PlayStation 2, obviously things have really slowed down, so nothing of note there.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the Nintendo DS, Okamiden, Chisaki Tayo comes out this week in Japan, so that's on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's Okami, Okamiden.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Okamiden comes out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's Okami, they added an extra syllable to the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Made in Kakeriko Village, instead of Kakariko.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it just threw me off because I was like, wait, wait, brain reorganize.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks very cute.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I know we've seen some of the stories on this before.
[SPEAKER_09]: Y'all right over there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I just noticed this little post on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: They put like screen grabs every now and then.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all on this one.
[SPEAKER_09]: The official Kirby's Epic Yarn website.
[SPEAKER_09]: So check out Kirby's Epic... He's throwing a star and it looks like a giant penis coming out of him.
[SPEAKER_11]: Penis.
[SPEAKER_11]: It does.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of stuff on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_11]: In Japan this week, Dragon Ball Tag vs...
[SPEAKER_11]: Iu Densetsu Zero no Kisuke comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: A game called K-On!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hukago Live comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a big thing for a lot of fans who are... It's a little music game with chicks who rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's from an anime.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh boy, so it's like a music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and people on Twitter won't shut up about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tales of the World Radiant Mythology 2 gets a price reduction and then I'm sure DarkSakura is going to pre-order this game maybe Rice Princess 2 Twinkle Crusaders Go Go in regular and limited edition I'm going to go go and pre-order that now that looks wonderful looks like a little fighting type of game Rob go out there and get us ice cream so I can do I will not yeah it's an ice cream truck
[SPEAKER_15]: You can't hear the ice cream truck?
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't think they had real ice cream trucks anymore except for like the pedo vans.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, when I have kids someday, I'm going to tell them when they hear that chime, it's the toy collector.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you have a messy room, they're going to come get all your toys.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that way I never have kids.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who was it you that said that you were told it was the spinach truck?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a friend who... That's the kind of thing I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: One of my friends' mom would tell them that it was the spinach truck.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, UK releases, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: A bunch.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the 28th, we have Atelier Rorona.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, I just got an IM.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tiara says she just tuned in to hear Spinach Truck.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the 28th, also Battle vs. Chess, Borderlands, Claptraps, New Robot Revolution, Dead Rising 2, Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light, Swords, and then on the 29th we have Hydrophobia, the 30th, F1 2010, Final Fantasy XIV Online, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Predator, Tom Clancy's Hawks 2,
[SPEAKER_14]: Also on October 1st, FIFA 11, Sean White Skateboarding, Tom Clancy's Hawks 2, again, out for PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: The end!
[SPEAKER_14]: Of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fiend.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, something that hopefully you didn't purchase, APB.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: People have been trying to get refunds via Steam and haven't really met with any success on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But EA apparently is going to try to help people out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says the user's been posting about their experience talking to EA support regarding this issue.
[SPEAKER_09]: Several users have been able to receive a $20 discount code for their inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dragon Age 2 Dragon Age 2 Dragon Age 2
[SPEAKER_09]: So I guess if you bought APB you may want to go chat with EA support which is of course support.ea.com and see if they can help you out and get you some of your money back that you spent on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're gross Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Totally listening to Loki right now I promise.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well I'm not talking anymore so that's not really helpful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Aw, we're still listening to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I was offering Rice Princess some black licorice, and she was like, ew, no, get that out of my face, gross.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, it looks like dog crap.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't want your licorice.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: You want some, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't have licorice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's right, you can't have licorice.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Dan insists on eating it around me in his car, and I'm like, gag.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what I had to do, since Rice Princess loves it so much, I waved the bag in front of her face so she could get the smell.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then she's like, sure, I want one.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that means she just wants to take one to throw it at me.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I let her put her hand in the bag to grab one.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's all, ew, they're slimy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_15]: They are.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like you put them up your butt before you put them in the bag.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's so gross.
[SPEAKER_11]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah, bummer about APB and all that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I feel bad for those customer service reps that have to deal with all the angst.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you know it's going to open the floodgate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Once you hear that one person got something free, now, thanks in part to this show, there's going to be tons of people that go on there and are like, I want my free stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought APB.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where's my free stuff?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I found a Christmas card that was sent to us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, random!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was sent to me by one of our listeners, by Rob Overseas.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it says, Fuck office parties, fuck jingle bells, fuck mince pies, fuck Rudolph, fuck Santa, fuck Christmas.
[SPEAKER_11]: How appropriate, since you're Jewish now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I'm going to put it up on my desk right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100Matt wants to know, so what's the difference?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is the black licorice bigger and longer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just tastier, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, if you like the taste of shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Black licorice is amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's gross.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're gross.
[SPEAKER_15]: Your face is gross.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, this game's awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not gross at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't know Jack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember this game?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is like the best video game ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I loved this game.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's hardly a video game, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like a game show-y type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, anyway, it's been rated by the ESRB for the 360, the Wii, and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what that means?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming out soon because the ESRB always ruins and spoils releases.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it looks like it is really happening.
[SPEAKER_11]: THQ is revamping it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All we know is that the game got rated on crude humor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quote, Yay, more dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_11]: My favorite.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay, I never talk about those.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I'm so excited about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, the picture's going up on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_11]: What'd you put a picture?
[SPEAKER_11]: Of my card.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, of your card.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should put a picture up of Rice Princess holding black liquor.
[SPEAKER_11]: It should be exciting.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, ew, I'm never touching it ever again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, I think this means now that our show is starting to completely derail, it's time to bring it back to some classics.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: You kids and your spinach trucks, you need to stop chasing the spinach truck and play this video game for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, what's the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Elevator Action!
[SPEAKER_15]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_11]: Elevator, go down.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go down the hole.
[SPEAKER_14]: Elevator Action is, first of all, this is Dan's suggestion.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love the sound effects.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is from the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_14]: Elevator Action Returns
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, the game is great.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's, uh, the music was done by Yoshino Imamura.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, let's go on with how the game is played.
[SPEAKER_14]: You play as Spy and you go down an elevator.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you either have to shoot them back or run away or hide.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you get all your documents and you go from the top of the building to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the lower that you get, you actually have to solve more puzzles to get around it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The control was a four-way joystick, two buttons, one for shoot and the other for jumping and kicking.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I always jump and kick at the same time.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, very, very simple, easy game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Two players, you need to alternate times.
[SPEAKER_14]: You play as Agent 17, codenamed Otto.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, um, you don't have a timer, but you do have a time limit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It goes into a hurry-up mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the music will change and tell you to hurry up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you can get crushed to the elevator too if you're not careful.
[SPEAKER_14]: Knock out an agent by jumping or kicking, eliminate an agent by gun, and you get bonus points completing each round.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you also get an extra life when you hit 10,000 points.
[SPEAKER_14]: As far as versions of it, there is actually a parody called Ella Paper Action, which is a
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had two of them on Palm OS, Agent Z and Agent Z2.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's based on Elevator Action.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's Dexter's Laboratory Robot Rampage that's based on Elevator Action 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: 505 Games put a similar game out on the Wii called Spy Games Elevator Mission.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's called Elevator Combat in Europe.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a port on Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's an NES version that made it onto the Virtual Console in 2007.
[SPEAKER_14]: and Elevator Action Death Parade is a light gun shooter that uses elevator doors when changing scenes.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: As far as earlier ports, there was the ZX Spectrum, Amstrad CPC, MSX, Commodore 64, Nintendo Entertainment System, and Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was one planned for the Atari 2600, but it never was released.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, the prototype exists and was sold at Classic Gaming Expo 2001.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was only 95% complete, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then Sony had a mobile version of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: As far as compilations, we have Elevator Action EX for Game Boy Color, Elevator Action Old and New Game Boy Advance, Elevator Action Returns on Sega Saturn, which I think I have, Taito Legends set in the Taito Legends Power-Up, and...
[SPEAKER_11]: So can I be honest about something?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think this game sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, it's one of those things I remember much more fondly as a child, but I actually bought that title collection when it was out on the regular Xbox and kind of revisited this game and I was like, this game is horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I think part of that's just because it's really hard and I always get crushed by elevators.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've seen Dan play through this game just like all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: And when I said, hey Dan, help me think of a classic game, he's like, elevator action.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I mean, it is a classic in some regards.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was one of those games that always kind of looked better than it played.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what game in this vein that I actually like a whole lot better?
[SPEAKER_14]: Mappy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think you've ever done that for the week, have you?
[SPEAKER_11]: You might need to do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe Mappy will be on the list one day.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good Namco goodness.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like it or not, your classic game of the week, Elevator Action.
[SPEAKER_11]: Elevator Action.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a pretty cool YouTube to the guy beating the level because he makes it look so easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_11]: This game is hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you ever played this game, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_15]: Looks like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well that's going to do it for this first half here of Orange Lounge Radio But don't go anywhere, there's plenty more when we come back Including your phone calls and your tweets Make sure you get in those Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR And we're going to talk about PlayStation 3 updates That wrecked some things related to USB We're going to talk about a website that will bribe you with Microsoft points to use it And much more when we come back after this break With more of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_11]: And welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are live on this Sunday evening, September the 26th of 2010, where we are taping the 383rd episode of our podcast, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're almost, 400 is right around the corner, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's gonna be, what, about 17 weeks away?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's about four months away?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, right around Christmas, New Year's?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Crazy, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, wait, a little further than that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like January, February.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe just in time for Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whoa, cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Joining us tonight, as you can hear, Rice Princess and The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we were talking a little bit about the break music, which I know you podcaster folks can't hear it, sadly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's copyright stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we can do it live.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we played a variety of songs during that break.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the last one we played was from Secret of Mana, the Flight into the Unknown.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that made Jamie go, let's have a Secret of Mana party.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm like, wow, yes, that's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_14]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: SRSers Don't take a picture of me please because I'm in my pajamas Or me
[SPEAKER_11]: The Doctor's Taking Pictures in Studio.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: The secret about a marathon would be fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually got really far in secret at Evermore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got really close to beating it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I never did, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think Evermore is nearly as bad as some people think it was at the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: People thought it was bad?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what we should do?
[SPEAKER_14]: We should do RPG a month.
[SPEAKER_14]: RPG a month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good luck tearing me away from WoW.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's Rob's RPG of life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe, oh, something else about Secret of Evermore, because another song we played in that break was the theme to Guild Wars, which I think that composer that does the soundtrack to Guild Wars, Jeremy Soule, I think is how you say his last name?
[SPEAKER_11]: is really talented and he composed that when he was like practically a teenager like 19 or 20 I think he did Secret of Evermore like when he was a teenager he actually I think composed that soundtrack so crazy right so I think actually no I think it took the back he was 19 when he did I think the Secret of Evermore stuff and then later on probably in his 20s he did the Guild War stuff but he was very young when he did a lot of that and he did the music to Oblivion which I know you're not a big fan of that game but the soundtrack is amazing I believe it
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, he's a talented guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: He did the music to Prey, which even though it was kind of a... Actually, it's one of the few first-person shooters I really, really, really liked.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it was made for people who are terrible at first-person shooters because you never die.
[SPEAKER_11]: You cannot die in Prey.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's easy mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you die, you go into the spirit world where you have to shoot these ghost-looking things to regain your health and stuff, and then you go back right where you left off.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Prey is like total easy mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it had really good music.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com You're playing Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Salacious Pop in chat says, People who hated Evermore were just being 16-year-old weeaboo square stands and didn't like it because it was Square USA developed.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Ranma is starting a fight saying, Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: It took a week to beat.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_11]: Throw down.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: It had a dog in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That made it instantly cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's get back into some more video game news here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Twitter topics coming up at twitter.com slash OLR in just a little bit, so make sure you're... Are you alright over there, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, get those Twitter topics in.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to be getting to those in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_11]: But in the meantime, some fast, rapid-fire news, starting with Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, there is an update done to 3D.GameHeroes this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You may remember that game, the one that's kind of like Zelda, but not.
[SPEAKER_09]: This time they've done an update that adds a Sackboy playable character, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then on top of that, there's also some 50 new player-made heroes that have been added to everyone's lineup, plus allows the players to carry weapons over into their new game plus files.
[SPEAKER_09]: and incorporate a handful of bug fixes that they've done to the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's one of those games I played maybe the first third and then stopped.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have not touched my copy of it yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's actually so... Again, it is The Legend of Zelda on PS3 and I am surprised Nintendo has not sued yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is that close to the original Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'd like this game, I think, Grace Princess, because you like the old school games, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: I do like the old school games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, this 3D.GameHero is like one big BJ to old video games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, so which Zelda is it most like?
[SPEAKER_11]: The very, very first one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not my favorite, but I would like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week marked the first releases to the PlayStation Store of PlayStation 1 Imports.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, now we're able to play games from other regions.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the first two releases, you may wonder what they are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cho Inoki and Gaia Seed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Joe Heineke is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you'll be able to get those on the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will run you $6 or $5.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is a fan-made Half-Life 2 movie trailer that was put out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, this is not just some amateur movie trailer, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's actually done by an animator, Marco Spittoni.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he's actually... I believe he works for Weta.
[SPEAKER_09]: So he has one damn sexy trailer out there that...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: New Detroit, which is the city that the game is going to take place in, and also looks like it carries over some of the stuff from Earth Defense Force 2, including a jetpack.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I believe there's four different upgrade armors you're going to be able to get.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm assuming one of them is this jetpack thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's supposed to be coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or not this fall.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, this spring.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of trailers, since you brought up that Half-Life 2 trailer, did you see that freaking Pokemon real life trailer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pokemon Armageddon or whatever it was?
[SPEAKER_11]: That was dumb.
[SPEAKER_11]: What in the heck was that?
[SPEAKER_11]: For those that didn't see it, it's like real...
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you guys seen Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_15]: I started watching it but then I realized it was Pokemon and I was just like, what the fuck am I doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like somebody took Pokemon and made it real life and it's obviously like a student project or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like a big budget student project.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's crazy how kind of... I love the Team Rocket thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: The effects were good enough for sci-fi television because that's what the special effects look like.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like the really bad Sharktopus kind of effects.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this got me thinking here because, again, there's folks in chat talking about role-playing games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Salacious Pop is saying, you know what I really enjoyed?
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy Mystic Quest because I played it knowing it was kiddie.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, that game wasn't as terrible as everybody outmade it to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just wasn't Final Fantasy, just like XI.
[SPEAKER_11]: But actually, I think DarkSakura might be onto something with the role-playing game of the month.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, we pick a role-playing game, like a classic of some sort, that we would see who can get the furthest in like a month.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, sometimes they do, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe we should just pick one night where we've got nothing going on and do the Zelda Fest.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I was talking about role-playing, not Zelda Fest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quit trying to change the subject.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like the Zelda Fest, where you see who can get the furthest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: By a certain time limit.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could do something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to be still playing Damn Plants vs. Zombies because I recognize the music because it plays in my sleep now.
[SPEAKER_11]: and SSJ100 Matt says this will happen when Rob and Jamie actually play their magic card battle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, that was like a year ago, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I found them recently.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have two sealed decks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me get back into some quick news here.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is news that makes me very happy and I know it'll make Loki very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rumors abound once again that Capcom is indeed working on a new Mega Man Legends game.
[SPEAKER_11]: As they should be
[SPEAKER_11]: The Shadow The Shadow
[SPEAKER_11]: and you have to trust The Shadow because Alec Baldwin played him.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: But The Shadow also pegged the release date of Mega Man 9 and some of the very specific details in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's somebody who has kind of done this before.
[SPEAKER_11]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_11]: Could be very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of something we didn't get to tonight but I know had been floating around out there was a Mega Man Doom mod that made Doom look like Mega Man Legends kind of.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was actually kind of awesome I have to admit.
[SPEAKER_15]: So dorky.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we have, let's see, when the Kinect comes out, we're going to have Dance Masters from Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to have Dance Central from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Overseas, they're getting a game called Dance Paradise in Europe.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming from Mindscape and Universal Music.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be coming out when the Kinect comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: No word on a release over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: But just to give you kind of a heads up on what to expect in this game, since it is a partnership with Universal Music...
[SPEAKER_11]: You do have some pretty big names in this.
[SPEAKER_11]: For instance, David Guetta and Kelly Rowland, When Love Takes Over.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gwen Stefani, What You Waiting For.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lady Gaga, Bad Romance.
[SPEAKER_11]: LaRue, Bulletproof.
[SPEAKER_11]: MC Hammer, Can't Touch This.
[SPEAKER_11]: No Doubt, Hey Baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that all of those songs were in the last few months and then MC Hammer with Can't Touch This from 30 years ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's a classic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sophie Ellis-Bexter with Murder on the Dance Floor and the Doctor's favorite song, Jerry Halliwell with It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, MC Hammer needs money.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I'm looking at screenshots of the game and I'm kind of like, oh, this looks like it's going to be kind of a cheap hack of a game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if it looks really that good.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the song list is pretty darn good because they did team up with Universal Music.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So 20 of the 40 songs have been announced so far.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interested to see more in that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, one other story.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's rumors going around this week that Project Milo was canceled this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: 19 contractors that were working on the project were let go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of the other people that were on the project are going to be using the technology in a new Fable-themed Kinect game.
[SPEAKER_09]: When your game doesn't have a title, it's probably not going to come out yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: I got some stuff!
[SPEAKER_14]: How about Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_14]: We have the download content coming out that will be a lot of Anthrax.
[SPEAKER_14]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_14]: I love Anthrax.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the Anthrax pack will be Among the Living, I'm the Man, Indians, Madhouse, which I love that song, and Metal Thrashing Mad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually the later two are live versions.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the whole pack will be 680 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_14]: for individual tracks coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stuff, again, that I have to get.
[SPEAKER_14]: My Chemical Romance, I'm Not Okay, and Welcome to the Black Parade.
[SPEAKER_14]: Totally, totally want both of those.
[SPEAKER_14]: 30 Seconds to Mars, Closer to the Edge, Atreyu, Cough and Nails, Buckcherry, Out of Line, and two Doobie Brothers tracks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Listen to the music in Long Train Runnin'.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still can't believe there's a band called Atreyu.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a band called Ludo.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and they're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: So as far as other stuff, how about Cave Story?
[SPEAKER_14]: There is going to be a DSiWare and what?
[SPEAKER_14]: I heard a gasp.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Cave Story and that looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a screenshot that we're looking at here that's a cool updated version of the Cave Story graphics on the screen?
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, and actually, yeah, this picture was commissioned in honor of the announcement, so I guess it's maybe an idea of what it might be like.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, but at any rate, um, it's going to be a DSiWare, uh, version of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it will, they say it's done, they're just testing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, um, it's apparently going to, uh, have a, uh, classic one and, uh, an updated one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh.
[SPEAKER_14]: and then, last but not least, Donkey Kong Country for Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's called Donkey Kong Country Returns and it comes with a banana pocket for your, it's like a condom for your condom, for your Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, it comes with this banana thing that you can put your Wiimote into.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, double banana?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a banana pouch.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just keep thinking maybe I'm just dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Banana hammock?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a penis joke!
[SPEAKER_14]: at any rate if you pre-order it you get beta access and downloadable skins and the bananas are probably limited edition should be out on November 21st like anyone gives a crap okay I'll probably get it because you just like to have more stuff I want a banana
[SPEAKER_11]: Twitter Topics
[SPEAKER_11]: Every week you guys send us tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to start off tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spazinator sends us one tweet with two topics.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blockbuster's filing for Chapter 11.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, did you hear about this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Blockbuster is... Oh, Doctor!
[SPEAKER_11]: You used to work at Blockbuster, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, indeed I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, does this surprise you?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because I haven't been to Blockbuster in months.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have Netflix because it's the 21st century.
[SPEAKER_06]: all your friends at Blockbuster have you seen that onion bit where it's like a historical recreation center and it's like done up like a Blockbuster and there's like historical figures like posing as employees and stuff it's hysterical nice I love the onion yeah so Blockbuster is looks like it's on its way out of business that's kind of sad
[SPEAKER_15]: A little bit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: More free videos available on Xbox Live and PSN, says Fascinator as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, Actdeft sends us a couple links here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I guess one of them already got brought up because it's the Kirby thing, but there's another link here.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's linking us to an article on Kotaku called How to Hump an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess there's a blog at HouseholdHoles.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: They finally found a good use for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_11]: Has talked about how to modify your Xbox to give it a big hole.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spoiler alert, you drill a hole in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_15]: I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really, that's all the instructions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Drill hole, add handlebar for some reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: You gotta hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously want to see a YouTube video of somebody actually doing this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkKeysK sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Medal of Honor PC Open Beta starts October 4th.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you're into the Medal of Honor games and you want to play the new PC version there, you can check this out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be an open beta.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be an early trial for DICE Multi... What is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm looking at this website here.
[SPEAKER_11]: It runs October 4th through 7th.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to see how you get into this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's the developer.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought that was like a convention or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've heard that used before with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyhow, yeah, a comment from... Sorry, I haven't read the story in advance.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was coming on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_11]: A comment from EA Games President Frank Guilbeau says, quote, We also hope that by offering the multiplayer open beta, we can clear up any misunderstanding about the patriotism and respect that...
[SPEAKER_11]: They are the foundation of this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Medal of Honor franchise has always shown extraordinary reverence for American and allied soldiers.
[SPEAKER_11]: This game is no exception.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you like those war games, you're going to have a blast with this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw sends his tweet, raving rabbits to become a live action CGI TV show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate them so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, apparently it's really happening.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming from Ardman Animation.
[SPEAKER_11]: is producing the TV show.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've got a website and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw also sends us a link that is a little more stateside about that whole Wii Remote Plus thing going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently November 7th is the date they're looking at.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkTsuke sent us another tweet here.
[SPEAKER_11]: FPS vs. RTS players.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't played in a while, but it's a pretty great game to unite gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Battleswarm.net I don't want to visit it live on air because I don't want to break the show computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know how intensive this site is, but I guess he's throwing out a plug for that website.
[SPEAKER_11]: Matt, SJ100Matt is sending us a tweet saying, Remember Bobby Blackwolf's listless idea for a gun con dating sim?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds like someone stole his idea and got linked to this gal gun.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the Xbox 360's shooter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it does look like a gun shooting dating game.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's actually a little video here.
[SPEAKER_15]: What kind of gun?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if we can look at a little clip here of the video.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, so you're shooting the women that you want to date.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, brilliant.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you're rescuing them.
[SPEAKER_11]: With your love juices that you're shooting at them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, no, looks like you're shooting her boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're rescuing them from not having an orgasm.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're rescuing them from their confining clothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you are shooting them with hearts.
[SPEAKER_13]: and Flower.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a neat effect, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just a perspective effect.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a game on the iPad that kind of does that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Labyrinth or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just screenshots.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that's not like what the 3DS does.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is an app, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's neat, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to share something, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: This comes from Tiara.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's about WoW, so you'll like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Goody.
[SPEAKER_14]: That she ran into a level 60 Tauren druid named Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_14]: H-A-I-R-Y-P-A-W-T-E-R.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like that she's playing WoW again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come play with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then lastly from Leo Shen sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: A new challenger approaches for BlazBlueCS2.
[SPEAKER_11]: She has kitty missiles and links us to a little YouTube here I guess where you can see this character in action.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on, let's see the kitty missiles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Might be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, did she just throw a cow?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think she did.
[SPEAKER_11]: I totally just saw a cow get thrown.
[SPEAKER_15]: What is this, Monty Python?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that's going to do it for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to send us tweets in the future, twitter.com slash OLR is the place where you can follow us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should follow us on Twitter anyway, so that way we can tweet you with reminders about what's coming up with the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: And sometimes when we go to conventions and stuff, random things we will send out on Twitter as well, like pictures and all that cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, back into some more news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got Plants vs. Zombies now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got some cool stuff, including... You may remember some of the things that Sony does to curb piracy and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now they've disabled... It's funny because everybody's joking, oh, now they have those USB mod chips, they're going to disable the USB ports.
[SPEAKER_09]: They weren't that far off.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've disabled some USB peripherals, I guess, according to a report that was on their website.
[SPEAKER_09]: The issue, I guess, they were disabling counterfeit PS3 controllers, but it was actually disabling unlicensed third-party controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of these devices affected by this actually were the Yobo PS3 Joybox, which I believe is an arcade stick, the XCM Cross Battle Plus adapter, which was kind of an adapter that allowed you to use an Xbox 360 controller on the PlayStation 3, and the Splitfish FragFX, which is kind of a hybrid controller and mouse adapter.
[SPEAKER_09]: and that's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's part of firmware 3.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other things though that it kind of broke as well, some old Mad Catz controllers, even though they are fully licensed, apparently they are now broken.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you own the 2008 wireless PS3 gamepad or the 2008 wired PS3 gamepad or the PS3 wireless MicroCon, which is now discontinued, they do not work anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, um... Man, if I were Mad Catz, I would be pissed.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would be pissed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially if they're licensed.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they're unlicensed, well then, too bad, so sad, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: But if they're licensed, that's grounds to sue and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Sue and...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about you, but I haven't heard of some big ol' mass problem with counterfeit controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know people out there going, oh man, all those counterfeit controllers out there, I just can't find a good PS3 controller.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, there are a lot of shitty controllers out there, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but these are actually counterfeit controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a YouTube that was on Kotaku as well, where someone actually bought a cheap DualShock 3 controller that was a counterfeit.
[SPEAKER_09]: so you know that's kind of lame that those are out there but I mean I can't imagine this is a huge problem that one that warrants a software update I mean hell I can think of a lot of problems that this console has that haven't been fixed with a software update like home being lame nice
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, well, how would you like to get free Microsoft Points?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, free Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a website that will bribe you with free Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're keeping it in the family because that website is Bing.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, Microsoft Search Engine, the rival to Google.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bing is running this new little Bing toolbar that you can install on your browser.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way...
[SPEAKER_11]: The first announcement said that it was only compatible with Internet Explorer, but some things I've been reading in forum chats and stuff say that it actually works with Firefox.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would make sense that it would only work with Internet Explorer, that whole Microsoft-only stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyhow, if you use it to take part in daily promotions or do searching, you will earn reward points that you can then turn into Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here's the thing though, you can only get the Microsoft points in 100 point denominations.
[SPEAKER_11]: But just installing the tool bar gets you 250 points, so that's kind of cool I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: What I'm also hearing though, again reading through comments and things, is apparently they will only send you the points in cards in the mail.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're trying all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: Their application on... Did it... Oh, no, did it... It made me... I was trying to click cancel and I clicked the other thing, so now it closed all my windows.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great, and it means you closed your next story, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what I have an iPhone for.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're going to bring up stories on the iPhone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, well, I got to stretch for time here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was ready to go on to the next story.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sometimes things just don't go the way you expect them to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, don't be rude.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wasn't being rude.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a realist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bing has pretty pictures on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I like about Bing when you go to their website.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the iPhone app is actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't have an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you like to touch mine?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's got your finger juice on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I have my story.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because this is the joy of the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh great, now it's not loading.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_14]: Miyamoto, basically what the story is about is that Miyamoto has always considered the maker of the Rubik's Cube, Mr. Rubik himself, to be his rival.
[SPEAKER_14]: So he wants to make something along the lines of a Rubik's Cube as his big pet project.
[SPEAKER_11]: So like selling a bazillion Wii's isn't good enough?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, basically, he said, and I'm going to quote, For quite some time, I have viewed Professor Rubik, who created the Rubik's Cube, as a sort of rival.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've always thought it would be cool to create something like a Rubik's Cube.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've told lots of people about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: For 20 years, I've always thought that the Rubik's Cubes are great, and I wanted to make something like that, but I still haven't tried to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I must be taking it easy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: and then he said he wanted to be a manga artist oh he just wants to do everything doesn't he you know what he's created some of the most memorable video game characters ever like that history will never forget some of these video game characters and yet it's just not good enough for him
[SPEAKER_14]: No?
[SPEAKER_14]: And, well, he was, um, said that he, uh, did some, uh, comic strips for, um, Tezuka, who's the Nintendo EAD general manager.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, wait, what, which characters are you talking about that he created?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, you know, the ones that we would never forget, was that like Captain Rainbow or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you remember Captain Rainbow?
[SPEAKER_11]: Good point from, uh, DarkTetsuya in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, didn't Nintendo used to make toys and stuff back in the 70s?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, Nintendo started off as a Hanafuda card.
[SPEAKER_11]: Game & Watch
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably the rest of the steampunk outfit on my avatar.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_11]: You got to put down plants versus zombies and actually do a story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I can do this.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's other Sony news, and this would kind of tie in with the stuff that happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Before, when they were removing things to stop hacking, remember they removed the other OS feature on the PlayStation 3 to stop the hacking of the system via Linux?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apparently there was a class action lawsuit filed against Sony because of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Sony has now filed a motion to dismiss that class action lawsuit brought against the company.
[SPEAKER_09]: And sadly enough, I kind of agree with them because, well...
[SPEAKER_09]: Fails to present evidence that the company overtly advertised the other OS and its marketing campaigns on the PS3 packaging
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony also claims that the PS3 warranty license agreement and the PlayStation Network Terms of Service specifically provide
[SPEAKER_09]: PS3 purchasers with a licensed non-ownership interest in the software and use of the PlayStation Network provided that Sony has the right to disable or alter software features or terminate or limit the access to the PlayStation Network by issuing firmware updates.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also I guess that
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, gee.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, in other words, they're saying you can access this feature by disabling a different feature instead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tricky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, they're saying that because some of the... They should dismiss the suit because some of the plaintiffs did not use the other OS feature.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, there was... Didn't use it in the same way, I guess, or just didn't use it at all because they have ways of checking that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, I guess...
[SPEAKER_09]: They wouldn't really have been affected by it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's some people, I think, doing a money grab, if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure some people are just like that earlier story we had about APB and all the people complaining to EA.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bet there's some people that are going to go try to get money that really didn't even play APB.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just bought it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's different though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they'd have proof of purchase of APB.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'd give them the serial number or something like that and they'd approve of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a little different than saying, oh, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, for example, a class action lawsuit that I was part of just because I hate 24 Hour Fitness.
[SPEAKER_09]: I canceled my 24 Hour Fitness membership and there was a class action lawsuit saying that there was people affected by the fact that when you cancel your membership, they bill you a couple more times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did that happen to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it didn't happen to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I still got... A $5 check?
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a three month pass to 24 Hour Fitness.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, ooh, garbage!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, oh, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait to go back to the gym I don't like going to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is way better than any other compensation you could possibly provide me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I should be able to kick them in the pants or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangelandradio.com for such eloquent comments, such as the one from Toagak, who says, Sony can suck a dick.
[SPEAKER_11]: What they did was wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you agree, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can Sony suck a dick?
[SPEAKER_11]: Derek H in our chatroom says that's like a car company removing your seatbelts because you didn't use them.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's actually a pretty good comparison.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except for the fact that I don't think the other OS is going to save your life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it could.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't make assumptions, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, going on to more stories in our show here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Another rumor going around, and this is about more 3D games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm already over it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But apparently there are yet more rumored ports of PlayStation 2 games being remade for the PlayStation 3 and in 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of them, I've got to admit, sounds really interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the Mortal Kombat HD arcade collection.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you're looking at sample box art that's out there, it's Mortal Kombat 1, 2, and Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 kind of redone in HD.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've got to admit, being that I love the cheesy Mortal Kombat games from back in the day, that actually sounds kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Being able to, you know, play that in 3D Well, I wouldn't play in 3D, but HD and all that jazz Not interested in Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not especially You don't like Mortal Kombat?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's alright, I can play it in it's normal form
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, it's going to have stereoscopic 3D support, and this is being reported by a French gaming website, but they have box art to go with it, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, then, I believe it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What about the Prince of Persia trilogy 3D?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the other one that's being rumored.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard about that one yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only if it has video of Jake Gyllenhaal.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I can imagine that they would because everybody's kind of jumping on that bandwagon of re-releasing stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Prince of Persia games are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the Sands of Time, Warrior Within, and the Two Thrones all coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds like they'd be a perfect tie-in with the DVD release of the movie now, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: And the Mortal Kombat HD collection might make the perfect companion piece to the new Mortal Kombat game, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Jake Gyllenhaal and the oncoming something?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I try to make sex jokes around you, Robin, I just can't because I'm distracted by you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sure how to take that, but I think it's a compliment.
[SPEAKER_11]: Derek H says they should remake every game with parallax backgrounds in 3D that might actually happen on the 3DS actually if what we saw at I almost said Classic Gaming Expo I didn't even fucking go to that what am I thinking at E3 as any indication because you know they had like the Xevious this old old old Namco game from like the 80s was redone in 3D parallel
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they had Star Fox was redone.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were talking about redoing Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to go back and redo all these games in 3D.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because they can just take the code they already have, tack on 3D, and re-release the damn game again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like we can take some GameCube games, tack on Wii Remote Waggle, and re-release it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, look!
[SPEAKER_09]: We're supporting the fans because we released lots of games this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: New games?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would actually be just games.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've got to admit, a game like Pilotwings would be kind of awesome in 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I have to admit, okay, here's the thing though, Rice Francis, keep this in mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like 3D either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I don't like hearing about all these movies and things that are in 3D, but the 3DS is, for some reason, is different.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, A, you can turn off the 3D when it bugs you because it has a slider that lets you adjust the intensity so it's easier on your eyes.
[SPEAKER_11]: and it is kind of a neat effect I gotta say being able to see the 3D without glasses is kind of cool I don't know how long that'll last but here's something that kind of has me thinking you know for the longest time we've been wondering where are virtual console games on the DSi where are virtual console games and virtual consoles kind of slowed up lately what if a lot of these re-releases with 3D end up being downloadable games for the DSi
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to re-release these games all over again, but this time they're in 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, if the price is right, like $5, $10, it could be worth it for some of these games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Only the real, real classics.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wouldn't buy games like Princess Tomato and Salad Kingdom or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_15]: That is a real classic.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my favorite game ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: You wouldn't want to play Clash and Demon Head in 3D?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, you're fixing something that's not broken.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know, it's not worth it to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why would I pay for it again?
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, it was fine how it was before.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know, if I want 3D, I'll just go into real life.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hear they have 3D in real life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just not down with the 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Outro Outro
[SPEAKER_15]: at the naked woman in the window.
[SPEAKER_11]: but some of it here's the thing but then some of the 3D effects what they do is they put the main image on the very very back plane so that way when there's 3D effects it does look like things are coming forward because they'll put the static image on the very last plane in the very back and then things are shooting out like there was one little demo they were showing out on the floor that was somebody opening a champagne bottle in slow motion and the champagne goes everywhere and
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's just to show off the technology.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, like, all I think of when I think of that is just Nintendo saying, we're Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give me your money.
[SPEAKER_11]: And people give them their money.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're still the number one console.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm just worried that when this gimmick fades like it will, that the 3DS, I mean, which, you know, you'd hope that it would be around for a few years, but it's just going to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every seven-year-old is going to want one.
[SPEAKER_11]: every single 7 year old on the planet is going on well we'll see
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, a system is only as good as the games that are on it, and there are a lot of very promising developers hopping in on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, again, it's portable gaming, and I'm not always the biggest fan of portable games, but if it can give me something that the television games can't, 3D in this case, might be worth a look.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it has really, really, really great games that necessitate it, I'm going to have to go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you can go ahead and spend your money.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just going to have to go buy a Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can always steal one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my God, that's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll be over at your house soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're both going to steal yours, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, bad idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: Forget I said that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha, it's your fault.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every week you guys send us emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com DarkSakura's gonna open up the email bag, dive in head first, try not to drown under the massive emails that are in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Try not to inhale any of the anthrax that comes with the messages.
[SPEAKER_11]: And read a few for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, this one is from LabratY2K.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just finished a journey into my own gaming vault.
[SPEAKER_14]: This trip had me play Earthbound Mother in Japan for the SNES for the first time.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like they read Rice Princess's mind.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't speak highly enough of this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It had a great story and I found that I actually cared about the NPCs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Additionally, I truly enjoyed the humor.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is something that's been missing from most of the recent JRPGs.
[SPEAKER_11]: if you haven't covered this on your retro gaming segment it would definitely be worth consideration Labrat Y2K I concur well now if you don't play it all the way to the very very end where you actually beat it then be careful because Rise Princess will make fun of you for the rest of your life so you better play it to completion it's true don't just play the first town like Rob did I played at least four towns
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you sure about that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I had a full party of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you don't get that until, like, practically halfway through the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop laughing at me, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_14]: Greetings again from Rababa.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have been hoping and waiting for Verizon to get an iPhone contract because I'm shopping for a phone keep on waiting let's imagine that if it became reality I have some pretty good reasons to believe that apps that use the network for gaming or social networking will not work between AT&T and Verizon the only ones that will are the ones that push and pull things via the internet like Facebook or Twitter app I think this will be an eye-opening disappointment I hope I'm wrong imagine iPhones with babies
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sure I follow the logic there, why they wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_14]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_14]: With the Plants vs. Zombies talk on the last show, it brings to focus my addiction to the game on Steam.
[SPEAKER_14]: Looking over my playtime is almost depressing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Portal, 2 hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: Half-Life 2, one of the best first-person shooters made, 44 minutes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Team Fortress 2, 2 hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: Torchlight, 8 hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plants vs. Zombies Game of the Year Edition, 40 hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hopefully, I'll have the chance to give the other games the playtime they deserve.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the meantime, I'm really hoping that next year's Plants vs. Zombies DS game will feature the multiplayer elements of the 360 release.
[SPEAKER_14]: Keep podcasting and stay something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Robert M. It's like the listeners are reading our minds this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Plants vs. Zombies, everybody's talking about how they've been playing that, even though that game's a good year too old at this point.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's because you're psychic, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle here.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just wanted to thank you so much for the marathon show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually listened to the entire podcast in one long day of work.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was worn out after that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anywho, I think the idea of BlizzCon is stupid, but is anyone besides me pulling out their hair while waiting for any news about Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_14]: Back in the day of Diablo 2, I never used any form of voiceover IP and still spent hundreds of hours playing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't imagine the addiction this time around.
[SPEAKER_14]: Keep up the great work on the best structured, most informational, and best podcast running on the internet tubes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your loyal turtle in Philly, Serious Turtle.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Diablo 3 Diablo 3 Diablo 3
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it's because I'm not Korean.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I read?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm reading it anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dear OLR, I was listening to Loki's feltastic apple metaphor and thought I'd take a crack at it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I went to take me and a bunch of my friends out to a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could just get takeout and have a party at home, but I like the experience that comes with dining out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, I don't want my house getting trashed.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I treat my friends to dinner at a semi-fine restaurant, paying for the entire meal because I'm a nerd with a full-time job.
[SPEAKER_14]: The restaurant presumably includes the cost of the dining experience, waiters, dishes, silverware, bad music, random crap on the walls, etc.
[SPEAKER_14]: End with the cost of the meal, because if people saw what this actually costs, they might not choose to enjoy the dining experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: This cost comes to me because I'm the one paying.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, if the restaurant is an establishment that makes each individual person pay for their own dining experience, and I'm not going to stand out in front of a restaurant and yell, FUCK YOU AND FUCK YOUR FUCKING DINING FEE!
[SPEAKER_14]: Instead, I will give my business to a different restaurant that doesn't charge outrageous dining fees.
[SPEAKER_14]: That, ladies and gentlemen, is how to craft a metaphor.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stay black, Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_14]: This message was brought to you by 2x plus 2y minus 8 equals 4y.
[SPEAKER_14]: Solve for x. The answer, by the way, is x equals y plus 4.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: None of us are black.
[SPEAKER_11]: You weren't here when that happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had a caller on the show and Dan was just like, at the end, there was that awkward silence and Dan was like, alright, stay black, have a good week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we were just like, what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Now I will explain my answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: 2x plus 2y minus x equals 4y.
[SPEAKER_14]: Subtract 2y from one side.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_15]: Obviously, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: She just wants to show off her algebra skills.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's because I have these numbers running through my brain all the time now, stupid algebra.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I want to go back to the metaphor because it didn't really make any sense to me at all, but I like the story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool story, bro.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stay black.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, is that it for the mailbag or do we have more emails?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all I'm going to read.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if you didn't get your email read, how sad for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com and you should put at the top, like, DarkSakura, read this or I'll send you more math.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's how you get her to read more emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: Threaten her with math.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you say send me meth?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, math.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I could use the meth.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_11]: She has to party all night.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now's the part of the show where we get angsty.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to say an F you to Pollen and... I'd give an F you to people that are too slow to finish a transaction.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know who I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Person.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to buy something for somebody.
[SPEAKER_09]: I paid them and now they're like, oh, I'm really busy right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I'll talk shit about them if they don't come through on their end.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to the fact that I'm having pains in my tooth like three days before I'm supposed to go to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's like, I really don't want to go to the dentist right now because it's going to be so expensive.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm going to be taking a big old box of oral gel with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to licorice Black licorice specifically
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, F you to black licorice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like I just said.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you licorice racist?
[SPEAKER_14]: You just hate all licorice equally.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't prefer to hang around black licorice, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't hate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay, because I hate all licorice equally.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like red licorice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, F you to 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: and The Doctor, lastly.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to money, because I want more of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have any right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_11]: But like, you live in the middle of nowhere where rent is like $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you even have a roommate now?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't have a roommate anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that ship sailed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_11]: Was it bad?
[SPEAKER_06]: It sailed.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're my roommate now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_06]: House party!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: In the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_06]: Prank party!
[SPEAKER_06]: Prank party with Rob!
[SPEAKER_15]: Ship sailed, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Some comments from chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma says, Hey, I'm black and I hate black licorice too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Derek H is calling you a licoracist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys, and then the Skype line is going to be open at 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is OrangeLaunchRadio.
[SPEAKER_11]: But not yet, because we have two more stories to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want people to get their dialing fingers ready.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're dialing fingers.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like playing Flamin' Finger at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_15]: Someone's sitting by their phone like, oh, I'm waiting for them to turn on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft, getting a taste of money because of Halo Reach, has decided, you know what, maybe one Halo game every three years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not frequent enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to be putting out
[SPEAKER_09]: More Halo games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're saying, you know, probably, I guess, Phil Spencer, this is Microsoft's VP.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're saying it's a matter of keeping players engaged and not going dark for two years at a time.
[SPEAKER_09]: They want to do what Activision has done with Call of Duty, which is whore that bitch out like no other.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, and they said, I used to look at annual releases of non-sports games as people just like, uh, just trying to milk me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, I figured nobody had enough time to do a good job and all the negatives that would associate with those kinds of scenarios.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kudos to Activision because they've done a good job putting good game, um, continuing to release each year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the fans, um, like it and it's a good thing that they do it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um,
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because they had two different developers working on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if that's going to work with Halo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think that Halo is just going to go really downhill now that a different studio is going to be developing it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially if it sounds like they're going to try to crank them out as fast as possible.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds dangerous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just do not put Ruffian Games on Halo because they really fucked up Crackdown 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think they're going to try and crank out a Halo game again as early as next year?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because if that's the case, then somebody's already working on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just going to get to the point though, see with Call of Duty even, you know, Modern Warfare was really awesome and then Modern Warfare 2 was still very awesome and World at War that came out in between that was just kind of like, eh, it's alright, but still people went and played the one game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So people aren't necessarily buying every year's iteration of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: and that's also another thing that's really hard to do when you're putting out a really good multiplayer game is like Halo Reach for example people will be playing Halo Reach until the next Halo game comes out but if it keeps coming out each year and if some of them happen to suck or maybe are made by Treyarch then people might not give a shit anymore
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope they don't take a respectable name and really drive it into the ground.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then again, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fresh Blood isn't always a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It could be cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just most of the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be cool, but the thing is, Microsoft, they need more franchises.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fable's a great game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: I fucking hate Peeler and Molyneux so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's such a prick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our game is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It does all these things that other games don't do.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to really care for this dog.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really, I cared so much that I stopped playing months ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: This dog is going to become your life.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, he's annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's like, hey, dig here, there's treasure here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dig here, dig here, dig here, there's treasure here.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can raise your family and it's so wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: This time, you're going to be able to be the king or queen of your kingdom.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to have to run it and things are going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to have your dog still because everybody loves a dog.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's really amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to do this Project Milo shit that's going to be so wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to interact with this kid like you're interacting with a real kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't play with your kids!
[SPEAKER_09]: Your kids can interact with this kid just like they're interacting with real friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: because they don't have real friends aww he's just so annoying with his like new technology and shit I'm sorry like here's the thing he comes out saying that these games are going to be so much more incredible than the last game because of all these reasons and they're like nearly identical to the last year's release it's like what happened to all this innovation that you're going to put in there because this game is kind of terrible
[SPEAKER_06]: and why don't we go back to the original Scrap Milo because yeah, that's stupid and creepy and we can do the we'll get an adult guy, an adult woman and then integrate porn into the games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm glad that they were able to show off this wonderful tech demo where they can interact with a child and stuff but like, if you actually heard about what the game was supposed to be about it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was just like, oh you interact with this child and you help him find snails because he's moved here from Isn't that Connectimals?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, this is a child.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, it's not connected humans, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a child.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a real boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Pinocchio, he wants to be a real boy, but he's just digital.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you interact with him, you help him find snails, because he's just so depressed from flying here from, I think he was coming from Britain or something like that, somewhere in England.
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a British accent, it's a Peter Molyneux accent, that's how he talks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dark Tetsuya says, well, I think Loki's British accent beats Rob's.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not trying to sound British, I'm trying to sound like Peter Molyneux.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, I'm Mel B, and today we're going to be talking about Fable.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, that's bloody awful, bloody awful.
[SPEAKER_15]: What are you trying to do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, buy my new game, Mel B. Blah, blah, blah, girl power.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's put another girl through her paces.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, you know, I remember when he was pimping out Halo, or not Halo, yeah, he was pimping out Halo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Milo in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: He was pimping out fucking Fable 2 and he's like, oh no, I'm going to show you something very innovative.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a ball.
[SPEAKER_09]: You play fetch with the dog.
[SPEAKER_09]: With the ball.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, I can fucking do that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: With my dog.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a dog, I can throw a ball at my cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's way more entertaining than playing... Who seriously is gonna go into Halo and play fetch with your fucking dog for hours on end?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this what I'm really paying money for, is to play fetch with my fucking dog?
[SPEAKER_15]: granted it was fun killing people or like torturing them in this little like you know device you can sacrifice in the devil you can kill people in real life you act like it's impossible it's entirely possible we have salacious pop in chat says that this is Loki right now actually this is Loki right now
[SPEAKER_07]: I apologize that that was very low volume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blame YouTube.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet you anything, though, that Fable 3 is gonna be very, very, very, very, very similar to Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yay, DarkSakura's finally giving me back my Clue DVD.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's only been two years since she's had it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, Rob, it's been longer.
[SPEAKER_11]: It feels like you have like three movies in here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I love Clue.
[SPEAKER_11]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to watch this when I get home.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to play WoW.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't joke with us.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, can I do one more story, then we can open up the Skype line?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Nintendo will sue.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least that's what they've been doing this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Threatening to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've been threatening Pokemon fan sites who have been posting Pokemon black and white screenshots.
[SPEAKER_11]: The game came out in Japan, and of course, folks have been importing it and have been posting screenshots of it on their fan sites.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Nintendo has brought down the legal hammer of justice with a cease and desist saying, quote,
[SPEAKER_11]: while Nintendo appreciates your interest in and support of the Pokemon game series your publication of this content infringes Nintendo's copyrights in violation of federal law your activity also has the potential to cause substantial damage to Nintendo and leaves Nintendo with no choice but to take steps to protect its intellectual property rights some of the sites that were hit PokerBeach PokerBeach?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know PokerBeach.com all your Pokemon I don't know if that's one of the names of the Pokemon Suribee or something
[SPEAKER_11]: and of course they're very upset and this is awesome because Nintendo is so epically horrible at advertising their own stuff now yes they're going to get pissed off apparently when other people actually try to advertise for them like that's amazing it's also kind of disturbing to me that it's like well the game's out somewhere but hold on because there was an update that came out to this that might kind of shed a little light on it
[SPEAKER_11]: and it was some various commenters on websites were kind of noticing that the sites that got shut down were admitting to using ROMs to get the screens so maybe the problem wasn't that they were posting screenshots but it's admitting how they did it by getting ROMs of an import game
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, still, screenshots are just screenshots and the game is already out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, if you're going to go around openly saying, I stole the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if I said, you know, I wished upon a magic lamp and the genie granted me this copy of the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they going to shut down my Pokemon site now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, then, maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I could say that it fell from the sky in a blaze of glory.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or you just don't say how you got the screenshots at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just post them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, isn't that what most websites do?
[SPEAKER_15]: But Rob, that would be logical and sensible.
[SPEAKER_11]: They get their exclusive report.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got an exclusive on Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But someone photoshopped those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't believe that Pokemon has that in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, also keep in mind that the DSi version was region locked.
[SPEAKER_14]: Black and White.
[SPEAKER_14]: I almost said Black and Blue.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the Pokemon bruise.
[SPEAKER_11]: Y'all know Shane, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: He's been on the show a few times.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's playing Pokemon Black and White right now on his Japanese DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the XL.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's playing it on an older one that isn't region locked.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because only the newer ones are region locked, so he has an old DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's not a Japanese DS, but it's an old one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought he was playing it on his XL.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's playing it one way or another.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all he ever posts about on Facebook anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let him tweet it to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you're listening, call in so we can get a review on Pokemon Black and White.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although all he's going to say, he's going to say, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it's Pokemon and they're awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there's the review.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be it right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now we don't need you to call in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because Shane loves his Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let him tweet them to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shall we open up the Skype line?
[SPEAKER_14]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's that commercial I was referring to earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen this commercial on real television.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pick up the phone and call us now.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR I should do this every week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I used to only see those when I would watch USA Up all night.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pick up the phone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Call us right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does the doctor want to do the calls tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: You want to do the call?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's brilliant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, the doctor's going to do the calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're waiting.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're just waiting for the calls to come in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are there any calls?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no one's calling.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a little delay between when we say things and when it goes out on all games and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So can I sit on your lap while I'm doing this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really want to?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love how your legs spread open.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like, you want to?
[SPEAKER_06]: You make it sound nasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: His legs are crossed and then he opened them wide.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a wide stance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Rob's network's open and ready for business.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, again, you're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some nights we get hammerwood calls, some nights we don't get calls at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's my fault.
[SPEAKER_11]: I should have had the woman answering the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Rice Princess, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Too busy in the kitchen baking things.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, Alan's listening right now and you just said, OMG, hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Hero 2 Tracklist
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, so the Prodigy, they're going to have a mashup, I guess just a, uh, beat juggle of Firestarter, which will be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Chemical Brothers featuring Q-Tip, uh, Galvanize mixed with the Chemical Brothers Leave Home.
[SPEAKER_09]: Might be neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, Pussycat Dolls with Busta Rhymes, Doncha mixed with, uh, Pitbull, I Know You Want Me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you want me I know I want ya
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that full list is out there right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a lot of beat juggles this time around, including Daft Punk, Human After All, Omen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, the Omen mixed with Orbital the Box.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's from Prodigy as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be done by the Scratch Perverts.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad Romance is going to have a beat juggle done by Tiesto, which would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love Lockdown by Kanye West mixed with Metallica's The Day That Never Comes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Nucleus, jam on it with DJ Qbert on the vocals.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're doing a remix, of course, by DJ Qbert.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, that full list is out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last one I was going to mention here, Naughty by Nature, OPP mixed with Michael Jackson or with the Jackson 5 ABC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is strange.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like nobody's calling.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, of course, the minute I say that, there it goes.
[SPEAKER_11]: The lights up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, did the doctor go away?
[SPEAKER_11]: He had to go, Connie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll enter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, DarkSakura, that's all you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for calling.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, I'm calling you because I'm a very big fan of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can hear you in the bathroom, dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to speak with Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: How can I help you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't know how you can help me, but maybe we can talk later about video games?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't we talk now about video games?
[SPEAKER_11]: You did call into a video game talk show after all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the worst 30 seconds of radio I've ever had in the... How long have we been doing this show, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: About eight and a half years?
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the worst 30 seconds of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think in the entire... That's saying something.
[SPEAKER_11]: What did I miss?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You missed somebody testing the phone to make sure it works, clearly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nobody wants to talk to us.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's so funny how some weeks the phone will be ringing off the hook like we can't get enough of the calls in and then tonight it's just chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, crickets.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did I say something to make you mad?
[SPEAKER_11]: Listeners?
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what we should do?
[SPEAKER_15]: We should speak in British accents until someone calls.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that'll force someone to call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we'll have a jolly old time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, good lord.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's an amazing idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Perhaps we could nibble on some tea and crumpets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'd love to nibble on your tea and crumpets.
[SPEAKER_14]: How do you nibble on tea?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have made deep fried beer, so maybe they'll have deep fried tea.
[SPEAKER_11]: The phone's ringing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Doctor, are you answering?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's answering?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's your name?
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, dude?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing today?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: My back is killing me from an epic weekend, but other than that... Right on, right on.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it was epic.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an awesome barbecue fest I went to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you hurt your back from fucking?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but you were complaining though, were you not?
[SPEAKER_06]: So what's on your mind, caller?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, I want to bitch about Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to stop making controllers, simple as that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their stuff falls apart within like two, three months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I bought a pair of cymbals for my rock band drum set.
[SPEAKER_04]: They stopped working within three months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they pretty cheap, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, is it like you get what you pay for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I got them replaced, and I use them sparingly, and they're starting to act up a little bit here and there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they have updated them for the Rock Band 3 drum set since they're actually included with that now, and they're supposed to be more sensitive.
[SPEAKER_11]: When's Rock Band 3 out?
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to play it so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few more weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the 16th or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I'm getting a comment from Rice Princess here in the background.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just saying that Ranma was a piece of sexual chocolate.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you, my dear, and I love you too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Doctor and Rice Princess
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay, I want to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tried to get my friend Victoria to do it, but she's kind of being flaky flake on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I would definitely do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, oh heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we have to dress up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like eccentric rock stars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, we need a fourth.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need a fourth, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: What would I do with my broken hand?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you can't do drums?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my God, it'll be like fucking Monocle all over again.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can do interpretive dance.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, that is not... We can't use Beatles rock bands.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then we could have harmony.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to rock star sing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Someone stepped on your toe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or they shot her toe.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was just grimacing musically.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, good stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think this is going to have to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you think, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to get on stage and sing in front of hundreds of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I said I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome, awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to get over my stage fright now.
You'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just put a paper bag on your head and cut out little seats.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like in Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can put a bucket of chicken thing on your head.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, because then I'd have to play guitar like Buckethead.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm talking, you know, like the little icon guys from... Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that game that was made by Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: That could be our band name.
[SPEAKER_11]: Guitar Freaks was first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you want, I give you permission to use my band name.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rhythm and Juice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rama, Jews have no rhythm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, shush.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hugs and kicks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tease because I love.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tiara suggested that I could play with one arm like the drummer for Def Leppard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, that's an amazing idea because what you should do, you should do that whole thing where you put your hand through your shirt so it looks like you don't have an arm.
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: I would rather sing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a good idea at the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll just get DarkSakura good and drunk before she goes on stage.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you get me drunk, I won't be able to sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why get her drunk?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just bribe her with Guinness.
[SPEAKER_11]: That'll work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the best part, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Guinness doesn't get me drunk.
[SPEAKER_11]: They stream Umlaut on the internet so all of you could watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll get the recorder ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft suggests instrument freaks or band freaks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sax maniacs!
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is great because there's people from Harmonix that actually go to the event and it would be extremely offensive if we named it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although I don't want to offend the people at Harmonix because they're wonderful people, but it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Could be freaky guitarists.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could be the 573s.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, why aren't you thinking of this?
[SPEAKER_11]: We could be the Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: We could dress up as Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_14]: More like the Shice Girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get to be Jerry, that's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I just got one thing to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make it quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm tired of everybody bitching at me that I jump on the Skype lane first for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't want me on almost every single week, call in and be relevant about something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get mad at me because I have something to contribute to the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: They had a good 10 minutes to call before you got in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was waiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was not waiting to be first, but no one was calling, so I stepped up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Calm down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Slow your roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just tired of the play.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you can get madder.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Ranma, we're going to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somehow his phone call turned into convincing DarkSakura to sing in front of hundreds of people on the internet at Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are you going to play, Eddie?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The harp.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't have a harp.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever they've got, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob Es Muey Caliente
[SPEAKER_11]: Lucha Libre en Telemundo That's all I know Lunes, Martes, Mircoles I'm from Alabama We just learned how to speak English there Actually, you'll find this really funny This is Actdeft, of course, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: you know what's funny is now I'm seeing because Skype is popping up like all these people who have never called the show before are starting to call in so we're gonna have to make this call quick so we get to some more people but I just want to quickly throw this out here do you know how we used to learn Spanish in high school you'd probably get a kick out of this
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, there's this little song and I still remember it to this day and it's how you learn how to conjugate verbs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, you ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Vamos, hablar, el verbo, caminar, caminar, caminar, to walk, yo, camino, tu, camines, el, camine, y usted tambin.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still remember this song to this day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that pathetic?
[SPEAKER_15]: I took French.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's horrible, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: We didn't have any songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: What did you think of the verb conjugation song?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't it awesome?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: So speaking of video games, what's up in video game world?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, video games, so interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I wanted to talk about...
[SPEAKER_11]: a story you talked about last week about a certain video game site that sells old games ah yes, that site that went up and down and then up again oh I think they're still down though because we're definitely not covering the story that they came back so in my mind I'm aware that they're still down there went my final story of the night aww, what would you want to say about the site that shall not be named?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, not necessarily about this site, but about like Steam and other sites like, I don't remember the other, like Direct2Drive also, that sell games via digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know, it has a lot of people kind of thinking about digital distribution with the website going down.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of like a lot of people were giving it second thought, like, gee, is one day all my games just going to suddenly stop working?
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, to be fair, I believe the games that the website gogged me with a pitchfork was selling, they were DRM-free, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Steam has always said if they ever go down
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's kind of worrying because I have a lot of games I have bought and given to me on Steam.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I kind of worry about that where Steam is going to be down someday.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you'll be okay if you read the terms of service for Steam it sounds like you'll be okay now here's the one you would worry about honestly if I were you it would be that on live as neat as that service is and as cool as it looks with the whole streaming game through the internet or whatever when you buy those games you're basically buying the game on someone else's computer and if that service ever goes down you're going to lose that game now I think they've
[SPEAKER_11]: excuse me they've guaranteed it for what like three years I think but that's you know after that three years you may not have the game anymore which you know after three years you may not want to play the game anymore but I don't know there's some games I want to go back and visit after a long time like the very first Civilization I could still play that game it's great and no I didn't play Civ 5 this week I'm a bad Civ fan anyhow
[SPEAKER_13]: Good thing I'm live.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's not available in Mexico, so I don't have to worry about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully someday.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys always get last in line.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, any other thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have a good one, and I hope you enjoy the new Kirby game when it comes out because I know you're a big Kirby fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's in your icon in case I forgot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, Doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of took over that call.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be really horny tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, this concludes another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: We still have time for a few more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: And to those of you guys, I saw some first-time callers trying to get through.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we'll see if we can't get some of these calls here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a call?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, that is a call coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's take it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for calling Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're online with the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, this is Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to bitch about PSN for a second.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I got Move and I downloaded a couple demos because I didn't get the $99 PSN
[SPEAKER_03]: package with the demo disc in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I set this up to download overnight and usually I can go to work or set stuff to download overnight on live and it'll be done when I wake up or get home.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I wake up and the thing is my PlayStation 3 is still on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still trying to download?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well no, it downloaded overnight but it took
[SPEAKER_03]: at least eight hours because I went to sleep about 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: and left to go see a movie at about 11 and it was still on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was it you were trying to download?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just the patch?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seven demos for Move.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And none of them were any bigger than about 350 megs.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't the same day the network went down, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe they were just getting hammered?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of freaky.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, you can buy full games on PSN, can't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like gigs and gigs of data that would just take you hours.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could just go out the door, drive to the mall downtown and back in less time than it would take for the stupid game to download.
[SPEAKER_11]: Digital distribution might not really be the wave of the future just yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: It works for the smaller games like on Xbox Live Arcade and some of the smaller PSN games but that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I imagine just a bunch of people were hitting it all at once but it's kind of surprising they don't have a better backup system for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well a lot of people must be trying to download the Heavy Rain move patch now because I triggered it to download at about 9 o'clock which is 8 Pacific and
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is pretty good quality for an iPad, I must say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I don't know, sir.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could call Sony and complain, or you could just bitch about it on internet forums like you're doing now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that's probably what most people are going to be doing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Most of what the internet is for.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's for bitching anonymously on internet forums about your products.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to complain about while you're on?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was...
[SPEAKER_03]: I did finally play some of the demos and they're really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Tumble demo is really nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so is Ruse, which is kind of what I've always wanted from out of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think that the PlayStation might have a serious competitor here to the Wii?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It all depends on the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it sounds like you were enjoying a couple of these demos?
[SPEAKER_11]: yeah the uh ruse demo is kind of this militaristic uh strategy game which I might have to pick that up when it finally comes out I don't know I still haven't got the move myself yet maybe uh maybe at some point or I'll just go over to Loki and play his that sounds like an even better idea right Loki yeah all right I haven't even played mine yet uh any other uh last thoughts before we let you go
[SPEAKER_11]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just don't forget to turn off the porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully someday I will be able to play Heavy Rain with Move.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let us know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it might take that long.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: You too.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's walk.
[SPEAKER_15]: I liked his little icon on Skype because it was Daria.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Daria.
[SPEAKER_11]: You love Daria, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Doctor, you ready for another call?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're online with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, it's Salacious Pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up, Salacious Pop?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm calling in so everyone can hear my hot, sexy, I have a chest cold bro voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, I love the bro voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm going to go put on a Dave Matthews band CD and put on a visor sideways.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great visual.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, keep talking, keep talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was calling about Ranma's comment that Mad Catz really just needs to stop making controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a little story about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought one of their 8-in-1 memory sticks for the Dreamcast where it has a switch on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It died after like a month.
[SPEAKER_08]: It deleted all my saves.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I love that it not only died, but it deleted them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and then since he was talking about controllers, I bought a Blanca 6 button, the fighting pad for the 360 when Street Fighter 4 came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I got it off, I think eBay was brand new.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was in like the horrible clamshell where you need like a box cutter and a...
[SPEAKER_08]: I spent like 40 bucks on a Mad Catz controller that was just dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they need to stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I agree with all those stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would probably buy one just to step on it and kick it across the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can hear Rob giggling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Feel better?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, since
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are talking about the Tomb Raider reboot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really think that no one care about Lara Croft anymore and that they need to put that franchise to bed because there are so many bad games associated with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_11]: You enjoyed that Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light game as much as I did unless you were lying for my benefit.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, see, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But because it has Lara Croft and Tomb Raider attached to it, like that's the brand.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are going to go, oh, ew, what's this shit, and they're not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that co-op game was put under a new IP with new characters, people would go, oh, this is a great game, because it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But just, the Tomb Raider games for the PS2 were awful, 3, 4, and 5 for the PS1 were awful, so I just feel that this kind of box office poison, like, I don't know, she's, Lara Croft is...
[SPEAKER_08]: Lara Croft is the M. Night Shyamalan of video games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was genre-breaking in 96 with her platforming and her bad pyramid tits, but now no one cares.
[SPEAKER_11]: No one care.
[SPEAKER_08]: No one care about Lara Croft, which is a shame because I think that Eidos can still put out good games with her.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just that she, as an icon, is bringing their ideas down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think maybe they got one more chance?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe this reboot, if it's really good, maybe people can look past it and forgive?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or no, it's over, put it past her?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought the adventure game that they put out for her last year, or the year before, I think it was for the PS3, was also supposed to be really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But again, I've never really heard of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once it came out, no one cared, and it never really broke any sales charts.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think it may just be a done deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess with the reboot, if they'd have to put a lot of money into marketing it, just saying, like, no, really, guys, this one's actually good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or just put the topless patch in, honestly, and then boys everywhere will want to play, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just release it on PC in the skidding community.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll take care of that for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, anything else you want to share with the listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I managed to stave off having a coughing fit for a good two minutes, so I think now's a good time to leave.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get better before Disneyland so I can spin you around in a teacup.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, I'll throw up on you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR He's funny, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: He's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's a good guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Orange Lounge Radio on Skype if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, good lord.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, how do you smell that all the way from where you're at?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of, that's a little bit freaky, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you have any other last minute stories, Loki, that you wanted to get to?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on, we're getting more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now it's lighting up like crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's get to another call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Doctor, you ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for calling Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're online with the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm online with the Doctor, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on with the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're on with the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm the doctor.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is there any aliens I need to be worrying about then?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's tons of aliens, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my sonic screwdriver and I'm ready to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh shit, I gotta run.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh shit, we better, because there is an awful lot of running, so we definitely need to do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who are you talking to?
[SPEAKER_06]: So besides the aliens, what's going on tonight with you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, who is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, who is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Zappy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Zappy.
[SPEAKER_11]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's talk to the doctor again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the reason I was talking to Colin was because it's sort of related to what Red Entertainment was talking about before.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's because I have a copy of Ruse for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: And let me tell you, that controller isn't cutting it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, I can see it's a really good game, but you're just being held back by the horrible, horrible, horrible controls.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, I try and select my units and I'm always picking the wrong ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: and it's just not working I could see that because that's a lot of games in game room are kind of like that a Street Fighter 4 on the Xbox 360 kind of made me think that because it was just so awful to try and control but it's kind of a bummer that that controller really ruins some games
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: It was like a big gimmick to charge me $65.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that terrible that they're only bundling it with that dumb play and charge or whatever it is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, oh, it's so annoying how they do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just like Nintendo doing that new Nintendo remote with Wii Plus or whatever with a crappy tennis knockoff game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, at least the Wii Sports Resort was at least, you know, fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Super Metroid is like the holy grail of video games to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, I love Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if they botched it, I'm really, really sad.
[SPEAKER_00]: My experience with New Metroid was about five minutes at Best Buy, and it seemed okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: But five minutes, I can't really say here or there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Could be good, just kind of made me honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you can't base an entire review of a game off of just five minutes, you know, because I'm sure everybody at E3 loved it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, the lines to play that game at E3 were like hours long.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was almost as long as the 3DS line at some points because it was moving a little slower.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess the people who couldn't get into the 3DS line said, okay, I'll sell for Metroid.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe not hours, but like at least an hour.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's crazy how long lines get there.
[SPEAKER_00]: That reminds me, I'm getting my wallet raided this week to find out how much they'll be raping me out of my wallet.
[SPEAKER_00]: For?
[SPEAKER_00]: The 3DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they announcing a date this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, from what I'm hearing, they're probably going to announce it in the middle of this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it was Wednesday?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, because Nintendo doesn't do Tokyo Game Show, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: But they always do their own little kind of like spin-off, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: They do their own little fan event around the same time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_11]: so I'm kind of like basically unless they're like charging a thousand bucks they basically got me locked down for that thing I'm gonna say it's probably gonna be $2.49 and it's gonna come with like either I think it'll be like kind of like a tech demo-y type of game that's just a bunch of like the movie trailers and some of the tech demos they were showing it on 3DS and then like Ocarina of Time in 3D or some old ass Nintendo IP that they can just easily do as the pack-in game
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they got me at launch for DS, and I bought the PSP within three months of launch, so I'm pretty sure I'm going to pick this up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you regret buying either of those systems?
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe the PSP a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: The DS I've been having as a paperweight for the last six months, there really hasn't been anything coming out this year for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, yeah, they didn't really show a lot at E3 either because it's all about the 3DS now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except for the little girl games like Fancy Nancy.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing that seems interesting coming out is maybe Pokemon in black and white.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, that's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be a big deal when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But otherwise, I just don't see much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe it's Final Fantasy?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Zappy, any other thoughts for the listeners before we let you go tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't buy rules on the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: The PC is probably the best choice and maybe the PlayStation Move version.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Word of warning of caution to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have a good one, Zappy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys so much for all the calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you should have called when we first opened it because it was wide open.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so sorry, guys, but we got to wrap up and get out of here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend Frodo got through at the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_11]: Clearly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, by the way, for those that are angry they didn't get through on tonight, you can thank that first call for eating up 30 seconds of your time, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quickly, any other last minute stories Loki wants to get out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Any plants versus zombies action DarkSakura wants to share?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm currently owning a bunch of zombies.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what that game needs, and maybe it has it, and I don't know, multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Xbox 360 version, it does.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does it?
[SPEAKER_11]: They've added it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might have to play it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just playing a little puzzle mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if this was mentioned before because I haven't been paying a lot of attention.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plants vs. Zombies is now becoming a quest in World of Warcraft Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Peacebloom vs. Ghouls or whatever they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want the sunflower pet, not gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, there is a fan release of the Command & Conquer 3, The Forgotten.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a brand new expansion for Command & Conquer 3 and the best part about it, it's fan made.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, go check it out at theforgotten.cnclabs.com and check out the new units and different things you get to play around with.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You said unit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, World of Warcraft, I guess, mobile guild chat is coming to World of Warcraft, I believe via the World of Warcraft Armory, which is an iPhone, iPad, or iPod Android device app.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you probably have to pay the premium that you have to pay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a $2.99 monthly subscription fee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not gonna lie, though, it's extremely homosexual.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is homosexual.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, to be honest, I'm not going to lie, it actually sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: You would use that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Being able to sign on and just say, hey, I'm on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I just spent $3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Couldn't you, I don't know, just sign up for some other sort of, I'm sure there's other voice chat options, perhaps through Skype.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not really going to get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, through Skype, which is free, and I'm sure you can do some sort of party chat with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ventrilo on the iPhone, that's what I need.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do they have that, chatters?
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be crazy if they did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Amiga77 says, you mean it's homotextual.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_15]: The baby, not homotextual.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else you want to share, Loki, the last of the stories?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, anything you've got over there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: More plants versus zombies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening to our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what we always say.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you guys like what you hear, please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tell two people you know about the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you didn't like what you heard, oh well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, it didn't work out for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: But continue to support independent podcasts and independent radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a whole lot of great shows at allgames.com or seriously, just go into iTunes and look for some independent shows.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of really great stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, and, and.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: I would also like to make a mention of Comic Insanity, the other podcast that I record.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cheap plug, cheap plug.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_14]: With Tiara and Shadow.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we're really awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you can find us at infamous, it's infamous without the I, .net.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the Robin Extra for Warcraft show is still in development.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to happen soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's just we're having problems being able to tape it like at the same, you know, just our schedules kind of conflict.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then we haven't been able to get the Skype thing to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we have to tape it in person.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now I don't have all the recording stuff at my house.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you're too busy playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I can tear myself away from WoW for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm being whispered secret messages from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's whispering sweet nothings in my ear.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for another show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around and give everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: First off, The Doctor, thank you so much for manning the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any final thoughts for the listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rice Princess, thank you as always for being here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Glad you guys could make it two weeks in a row.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, don't ever come again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm kidding, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rice Princess, any final thoughts for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, any final thoughts for listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: might have some impressions on the Microsoft Connect this week or next week sounds good my final thought is have a good week next week you guys and have a good show without me here I'm sad I won't be here but at the same time I'm gonna be at Disneyland like I'm gonna care please two things Rob number one I like that you're talking to them but neither of them are listening to you no I know and number two you're waving at them I'm listening I know I'm listening that's fine
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want a taco.
[SPEAKER_14]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm back on raw food and I want a taco.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is that noise?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop downloading the Vuvuzela apps right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: That doesn't sound like a Vuvuzela.
[SPEAKER_14]: It sounds like a cat being strangled.
[SPEAKER_11]: One more time.
[SPEAKER_14]: A Vuvuzela sounds like this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_11]: Haha, that's what you get.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dying of fire.
[SPEAKER_11]: Until next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that you have to shake.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll see you guys in two weeks, but they'll be back next week with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a good week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm out.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but were probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!