[SPEAKER_08]: And welcome back everybody to the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, we're doing a marathon podcast this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, just because we can.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to podcast as long as we possibly can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here on this Saturday, September the 5th of 2010.
[SPEAKER_08]: It won't be anything that impressive, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're thinking about going about for 12 hours or so, just talking about video games and reminiscing about old games and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we just finished the normal show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if this is the first thing that you're hearing on the podcast feed, you're going to want to go back.
[SPEAKER_08]: The actual show show was put up earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So just double check your podcast feed to make sure you kind of have everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: at the very end of the show we had some problems with our chat room our internet went down right in the middle of everything and we ended up getting booted from our server and all this stuff it was terrible but we think we've got that all worked out thank you to Alan who is like a bigger nerd than me I never thought I would be able to say that but yes he's a bigger nerd than me he knew how to set this whole thing up what are we doing right now Alan how are we getting an IRC
[SPEAKER_10]: My roommate has a domain name that he uses for a little Linux box that we run out of our spare bedroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little mail server.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're SSHed into that box and we're running IRC from there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're just shelled into my computer at home.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a little OCD with the mic cord.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, tell us a little bit about the vault.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a room in the back of my house that has all of our game crap in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I totally meant to grab my iPhone so that I could actually take pictures and put them up on the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could try doing the Ustream thing real fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how well this is going to work, but I'll try it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm stepping on stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, you could read chat for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you want to be cameraman?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do cameraman for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is all live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So everyone has to come in here and pick one thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we'll come in a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to see if I can do this broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, since we're already in here, Bradley, why don't you pick something?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, I'm going to bring in the camera, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to bring in the camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, just as long as it's not me on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll try my best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just dodge my phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I better put my phone back in here.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had Bradley pick something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're live and I don't even know where we're at.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're at Ustream slash Orange Lounge, I think, is where we're broadcasting at.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to go make my way into the vault.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give my mic to Alan while I walk over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now we have Bradley going through the Saturn section of my house, which is pretty much our domestic Saturn stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, at the moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the dusty little things here.
[SPEAKER_02]: is it like candy what was that is it like candy
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw one up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Blazing Dragons.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a puzzle game where you control the dragon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go ahead and pull it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put it on the camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, there are Capcom shot glasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead and put it up on the... Basically it's a comedy puzzle game where you go around and try to figure out how to solve certain puzzles where you gotta satisfy what a person wants you to do for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like you need to wash all the dishes, so you have to put together a Rube Goldberg device to rig up the dishes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it puts something on top of a fire to blow a turntable around or a fan around so they can put it in a system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's catapulting one place where you have to shoot a cat at a wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, your turn to pick something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Am I on here?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it going through, Alan?
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't usually do remote broadcasting from the other rooms, so this is a little different for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what to pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, you want to hold this while I dig through something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is awesome radio, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see all these NES games up here, and I'm assuming that one of these is going to be something awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_08]: or it could suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, you have like all these like Japanese games stacked on top of everything too.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are those?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Final Fantasy 3 and Mappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Mappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apparently you paid 20 bucks for each one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I paid five.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were marked down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see what's in this one here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gradius, Track and Field, Contra.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just push the button.
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It locked.
[SPEAKER_03]: It locked?
[SPEAKER_03]: Warning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we go live?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, now we're connecting now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we have to plug it in, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we're connecting now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, I wasn't prepared to dig through here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, let me look at Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Got your mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think someone looked up the correct channel name and put it in IRC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's orange-lounge-radio for the Ustream.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's all taken care of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, good deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got all these Mega Man games in this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob started to make the face.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll talk about this game Yep, it's Super Metroid Can you give me a mic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Metroid is the game I picked up there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Metroid is probably one of the greatest video games they ever freaking made, ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably my favorite video game of all time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It happens to be in this little bin right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I can hold this up for the Ustream viewers, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Metroid is amazeballs because it's kind of a quick game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not something that takes you days and days to beat, so you can play through it in a good sitting, in a day.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you wanted to play through this tonight, we probably could.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Show off different tricks or try to find things that are hidden.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it really kind of set the stage for things that followed it that are also awesome, like Castlevania, which a lot of people started calling Metroidvania.
[SPEAKER_08]: And just the music was phenomenal and the upgrades to the weapons, just like everything about it was just super.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's why Super Metroid is definitely a fond favorite of mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's something I've talked about many times on the show before.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's one of my personal favorite games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to find a box for it, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so Alan, it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pick us something that you see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds currently digging through the vault.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I like this whole Ustream thing though because it's too much for us to monitor because trying to run the radio feed is bad enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we might kill this video feed.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to... I've just been running my thumb over it to keep it active.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to kill the video feed for now until we have something a little more worthy of showing on video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's also like killing the battery on my phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Roger, if you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess I could always do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my phone is hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: It feels like it's going to explode in my hands.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's probably not a good thing, is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it gushy?
[SPEAKER_08]: So tell the listeners a little bit about where you collect all of these different games from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every freaking where.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: We used to just go hit up thrift stores and the flea market and a couple of used game places in town and just pick up things when we could find them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, when we got our Nomad, it was right when they stopped making the Nomads and we managed to get ours on clearance for $25.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marvel Super Heroes for the Sega Saturn
[SPEAKER_10]: one of the advantages of owning a Saturn in the US compared to the original PlayStation was that the original PlayStation was crap for 2D games the Saturn could do arcade perfect frame rates for all of the over-the-top Capcom X-Men licensed games like Children of the Atom I got my Saturn for this game and then I got it chipped and I imported Darkstalkers 3 and X-Men vs. Street Fighter so this is definitely a lot of hours logged on this one
[SPEAKER_03]: I really like that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, I wonder what it would have been like if they had released the 1 meg and 4 meg cart in the US, if that would have just made it completely a lot more awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's why X-Men vs. Street Fighter is only really playable on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, my turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shoot, this is all my shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know hue cards are in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you done some rearranging in the vault lately?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan did some.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys took the couch out of here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The futon is gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got rid of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking we'd all have a futon to sit on in here, but I guess that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we will have to go out to the front room at some point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully our mics will get us out there, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I can't think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm noticing Atari 2600 stuff here.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is sort of our, we have nowhere else to put this stuff shelf.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, C-Man, so we can friend your butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I think this is, um, nope, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a soundtrack for Berserk, for the video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been redone since then though.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need to do a new video.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has changed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do need to get some new video other than what we just showed on Ustream.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you can get an idea just how massive this collection is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, I'm looking one way and I see two TVs up on the wall.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 2 rack of games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see Neo Geo games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see all these arcade sticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I look another way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see different steering wheels.
[SPEAKER_08]: I picked something.
[SPEAKER_08]: A CDX.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a CDX.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not picking a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're picking a CDX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I didn't say you had to pick a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said pick something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you want to say about the CDX?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome and it's like having a really tiny Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it does not work very well with the 32X.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to kind of modify the hookup and get these brackets to hold it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the CDX is freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love it quite dearly.
[SPEAKER_08]: How'd you guys end up with two Game Gears over here?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at two Game Gears.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of them's blue and one of them's black.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the blue one is Julie's.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Game & Watch Collection
[SPEAKER_10]: I owned a Game Gear briefly in the 8th grade, and I've seen one now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do not remember it being that gigantic.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like bigger than a VHS tape.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't... And they're heavy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we've got the battery attached to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The little backup battery thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't... Well, you want to see big, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got links somewhere around here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... All of our stuff is so dusty.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to... Do we have another mic on the ground?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we've got stuff everywhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like this stress grip Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a promo thing from E3, I think, a while back.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually had a pink Game Boy Advance, just to be completely opposite of what everyone would think of me, because I normally hate pink.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I actually really dug my pink one and had pink everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you noticed but a reoccurring theme in my Saturn collection is working designs and Capcom.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still have my copy of Rayearth that working designs did for the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of the last games that came out for the Saturn in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see what I've got up here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rayearth is right here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Saga Ages
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, what's that one right there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me, can I actually jump in here, you guys, real quick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually in the other room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Albert Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or I'm watching the chat room, and I actually want to jump in here and say real quick, because it is 6 o'clock Pacific at this time, so we might have some folks tuning in right now expecting to hear Orange Haunch Radio kind of like as it normally is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You forgot that this week is the marathon episode, so we've actually been on the air since 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you're just joining us now expecting to hear the normal episode of OLR, it already happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: We finished that up at about 5.30, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki is gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: He went back to go take care of the baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm here, Rob Roberts, and DarkSakura's here as well, as well as SalaciousPop and Arcadium42.
[SPEAKER_08]: And right now we're looking in the vault at just some old games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kind of thumbing through and seeing what nostalgic dust is awakened from some of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we were going through my list of working designs games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, back here, that's Albert Odyssey, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually decided to sell my copy of that off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I only paid a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've also got Shining Wisdom, Dragon Force, Sonic R. I love Sonic R, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you feel the sunshine?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it brighten up your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, we've got tons of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, now I want to break out the Saturn for reals and play stuff, but Dan has the Saturn hooked up in here, and the monitor's, like, little.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to play the Saturn in the front room.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the stuff that we actually have hooked up right now in here is we've got things set up on Switch boxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got an Xbox 360, Dreamcast, Saturn, GameCube, Neo Geo CD, Super Nintendo, Turbo Duo, and the Sega CD32X.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: What else do we have sort of put away?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where did Dan put the actual Neo Geo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we actually have a Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I think it's funny, Dan got the Atari Flashback 2 that looks like the old 2600, but it's got 40 games stored in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I could break out my What the Fuck game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cardcaptor Sakura that comes with a plate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a clock.
[SPEAKER_03]: And silverware.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you showed all that in the unboxing video that you did on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's in the unboxing video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, man, I'm not trying to sound braggy or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we just have this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, oh, the R4 with the JogCon set.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got that for painting a Sonic on the door of a local used game store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember video game swappers back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: but that's how I got my R4 and JogCon and we've got the boxes of controllers and they're just different systems and stuff here's the box of Playstation controllers which I think the NegCon is in I'm gonna fish that out who wants my mic?
[SPEAKER_08]: GameCube and Xbox MyNedCon
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, you guys have some really obscure stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk about the vault for a little bit, because we had a lot of people in chat, and I'm sure a lot of listeners of the show that are like, wow, you guys are kind of like a special kind of crazy, having your own room in the house dedicated to like a video game museum sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And how did this all start between you and Dan?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, gee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, when Dan and I first got together, he had already had a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, he had a Neo Geo and a few games, and he had a NES, and he had a SNES, and I moved out here with my SNES and a few PlayStation games, and he had a PlayStation and a Saturn, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: We just sort of would get nostalgic about stuff and go looking for things.
[SPEAKER_03]: We ended up getting the Turbo Duo.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think he already had the Turbo Duo when I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me take it a step back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you've told this story sometimes on the show before.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have time to kill tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: How did you and Dan kind of end up meeting?
[SPEAKER_08]: How did you and Dan kind of come together?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, have a seat.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're sitting on the floor of the vault just chatting.
[SPEAKER_08]: No chatters right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, chat room, but you're in the other room where we can't see you, but we'll run back and look in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back in the day, when I lived in Mobile, Alabama, Dan was a friend of mine online.
[SPEAKER_03]: My roommates introduced me to him because he had the name Dark Ryoga and I had the name Dark Uchan.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we hung out for a while and he was my buddy and would be up like really late my time, you know, relatively late his time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just exchanged bad fan fiction and he was, you know, my buddy, he was fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I had a really, really bad breakup with the guy I was with at the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Dan called me and to cheer me up he had like some five minute calling cards and he ended up using like three of them I think that night and when we ended up talking the next night and I called him and he called me and we'd talk on the payphone from Denny's you know and stuff it was
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally one day, at the time I was working at, I think I'd since moved from working at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: I worked for Aladdin's Castle and Cyber Station at the malls.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I went from working there to working at this herb shop kiosk in the mall.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it was really great you know I could sit and read my books all day if I wanted to and so Dan we've been talking the night before because we're trying to open up another store so that we can make enough revenue to keep two stores open instead of having to close the one we had and I said hey if we don't get the show then in the show the store then can I come out and stay with you I was just joking he's like I guess so and so
[SPEAKER_03]: So the next day I go to work and they said, yeah, they gave our spot to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to close the store in a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, so when my boss left, I called Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, so were you serious?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to go see Batman.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll talk about this later.
[SPEAKER_03]: If that dates when the conversation happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: The original Batman was like 91.
[SPEAKER_08]: It can't be that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was one of the sequels.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, 89 was the original Batman.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at any rate, I was actually on the plane probably within two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've been happy here ever since I came out here with 100 bucks in my pocket and a Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you literally pack a Super Nintendo in your luggage?
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever happened to all your stuff at home?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you ever go back to get it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or did you just have it shipped here in little bits and pieces?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or did you just kind of let it rot?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I would go back and visit and bring stuff back with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Grandma would send me some of my stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little things like that, but I lost a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kept bringing back boxes of comics for some reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: But a lot of my books were water damaged from how poorly they were being stored.
[SPEAKER_03]: I lost a lot of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did manage to bring back a lot of cool stuff with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So most of my things, I think, are back with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of stuff from my dorm room I really wanted because they were things that...
[SPEAKER_03]: People picked up for me from Civil War reenactments and Ren Fairs and things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so now we're kind of getting caught up to where we were at before, is that you came out here and you had only the Super Nintendo and a couple PlayStation games, but you obviously had this nerd love thing going on with Dan, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's from the AVA.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you guys just kind of started mutually this collection together?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember what the first thing was you guys bought together?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really remember all that well, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know one of the early things, because I think he already had a Genesis.
[SPEAKER_03]: We picked up a Sega CD together.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was one of the first things that we got.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we really wanted to play Sega CD games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we found it cheap, and then we got 32X after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just kept growing, you know, really fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: We would just find things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh shoot, I was listing out all my stuff and I forgot to put my Wonderswan color on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, I was recently putting all my stuff up for Infamous.net because they wanted the list of my gaming systems and I forgot the Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now you're just going to lose all that cred.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, the way things went, it was just, we would run in and, oh, that's cool, oh, that's cool, oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, you know, would sometimes say, I really want to play this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, we picked up a Neo Geo, not Neo Geo, a Turbo Duo, not Turbo Duo.
[SPEAKER_03]: PC Engine Core Graphics Sorry, I had to think of system and country and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is the Japanese version of the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you cannot play the HuCard games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are not compatible.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's one converter that's supposed to work okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could never get to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you find that one converter, it's super expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we may as well just buy the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we got a Core Graphics so we could play our Japanese HuCards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, a lot of it is just like, it's here, we have the money right now, why don't we get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Dan was working at GameStop and then GameCrazy, so when he knew stuff that come out, he'd be like, let's get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when the PS3 came out, he had just quit GameStop, but he had put in his pre-order as manager, so he was first in line.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he went and got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Discover gave us a $100 credit back because he had spent so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So he basically got our $700 system for $600.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and we still have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our original PS3 works just fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's just one of those things where your collection just kept growing and growing and growing and then it suddenly needed its own room because you're just both gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder what that is behind you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will you grab me that black and blue case, please?
[SPEAKER_08]: The black and blue case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to see what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because keep in mind, we also have a lot of stuff just packed up in... Oh, it's empty, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It feels empty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, then it's empty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we've just got stuff packed up in...
[SPEAKER_03]: bags and things old systems like I think one of the things behind you is an Xbox in that black and red case there that's where we keep the Neo Geo like the AVS cartridge Neo Geo and someone just sold us a Neo CD for like 100 bucks with a bunch of games so I mean like I said when we get these things they sort of fall into our lap
[SPEAKER_08]: Where do you think all this stuff's going to end up someday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you see yourselves hanging on to this forever?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_08]: Passing it on to children?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan's talked about selling it a couple of times.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we get talking about it and neither of us can really see ourselves parting with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: It really just sort of happened up there with all the Bimani stuff when we really got into music games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just kept getting controllers and systems and, oh, American Beatmania 2DX, let's get it!
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, the guitar freaks, we both had to have a guitar and then I found the drum kit really cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: from not Toys and Joys, but it was another importer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking randomly of American 2DX, I want to throw this out here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't news that made the earlier show, but Naoki runs a Facebook, and it really is him.
[SPEAKER_08]: I asked him when I saw him at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's his Facebook, and he was actually asking questions about music games on there this week, and he actually said, like, you know, what type of music game is your favorite, and would you want to see another karaoke type of game?
[SPEAKER_08]: And overwhelmingly, it seemed the response was like,
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we don't need any more karaoke games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And everybody was like, 2DX, 2DX, 2DX, bring 2DX on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please release on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if they did release it, it would be region-free, where even if they released it in Japan, you know you're going to have tons of people over here buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be part of the reason it's getting held up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they're having problems with music licenses or what have you, although I don't think they license a lot of music for Beatmania anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, um... I actually answered on the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was reading other people's responses.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did, but I got in late.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, the pink biscuit's up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we bought a friend of ours, Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: Up at the very top, to the left of Samba de Amigo in Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which soon The Connect is going to be taking the place of some of that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny how technology's come.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really want a Parapara game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a tech Parapara game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, our other thing, too, is that Dan and I like playing games with good controllers.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: What other good, like, back-in-the-day topics can we talk about?
[SPEAKER_08]: We can talk about, try to remember the first time we all met.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I totally remember the very first time I met DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was at Milpitas, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was at Milpitas Golf Line playing Parapara.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: And you showed up with Jessica.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people don't know that is that she and I actually played our very first game of DDR together.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's kind of funny because we both ended up taking... We actually went... And I think this is kind of common knowledge now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a spat for many years.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a personal disagreement that just got way out of control.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was really ugly.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've worked our stuff out since then.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a pleasant friendship and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think it's great that she's back on Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know her and Travis have always had a really funny...
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Freak Radio was a project and it was always I haven't talked about this a lot but you know we're in the marathon part of the show we don't expect a lot of people to listen to when DDR Freak Radio kind of first came out we were at least I think you kind of knew about both projects we couldn't say anything because you kind of had to walk like this delicate line right
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is what I was doing for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: our real name
[SPEAKER_08]: I think a lot of people don't realize that... This is Alex.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Alex.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come in real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hi to everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're actually broadcasting our marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if Dan told you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're on a marathon episode of our show right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing, Alex?
[SPEAKER_05]: Doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have an online... You've got to get real close to the... These mics aren't very sensitive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have an online name you use that you want people to know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose you can tell people that I use the name Five Gears.
[SPEAKER_08]: Five Gears.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Five Gears.
[SPEAKER_08]: What kind of games do you play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mostly single player today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't afford to play Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hear they're jacking up the price ten bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just talked about that earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's... Well, I don't usually play online anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when I did, it was a lot of Halo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm probably going to have to, depending on how Reach goes, because I'm going to try that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that it's here or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just, you know, you're going to try it someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Legally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when I try it out, I'll see if it's worth actually playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And playing online with friends is really the only reason why I ever did it in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have all kinds of online games on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used to play that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was talking about the Cataclysm beta earlier in the show, playing that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: When are you going to get the needle out of your arm, man?
[SPEAKER_08]: When my friends stop playing, because honestly, that's the only reason I play.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're my real-life friends and people I know in the Bay Area and Allen.
[SPEAKER_08]: We all play together, and it's just kind of like the thing now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could give a shit about the game itself a lot of days, but it's just kind of the way we all hang out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of nerdy, but awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it used to be, for me, it was all about just playing first-person shooters online with people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's what my college buddies and I used to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: We used to play Quake online.
[SPEAKER_08]: We used to play Halo 2 for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: All that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, for me right now, if I do play online at all, it's Bad Company 2 on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, you should be voicing movie trailers, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just all just make voices.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another Solid Snake impression?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting my impressions mixed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan's looking at chat and they think he's Solid Snake?
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to look at chat and read us some comments, there's a mic in there that's hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just have to be loud enough for us to hear you back here.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's going in there to see if... I feel bad because we've been neglecting the chat room, but we're having memories here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where was I?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was talking about the conflict that Iguana Girl and I had, but we're cool now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I was talking about... Yeah, now she hates me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well... I can't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to stay with the positive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was talking about the conflict, but then, okay, the day, there was a New Year's,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: from Orange Lounge Studios for DDR Free Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was like the Nintendo and Sega logos appearing at the same time when you first boot up some of the like F-Zero and some of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a huge event.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a lot of people didn't know the difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did the New Year's.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: The New Year's Bimani Countdown.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad that all worked out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't mean to get off on those topics.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were back on talking about how we first met.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's grab a box of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I got to Dan and me meeting and me moving out here and us, our children multiplying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, our games multiplying.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I really didn't though get my own group of friends until I started going to Golfland and playing in the arcades there because I was playing DDR at home already and Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had BM98 if you remember the old emulator.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of Us!
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then everything kind of exploded and our group just got huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I had a birthday party at Golfland on the floor in front of the Fourth Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember the day the fourth mix hit Golfland I actually called in sick well I was already I was like legitimately sick I called in because I was sick to work and then I found out that RVGL got fourth mix that day and I was like I'm going I don't even care that I'm sick I'm going I'm gonna go be one of the first people to play that machine and I was sick as a dog but I played it and I probably gave you all cooties although I do remember that I was the first person of us to play a max
[SPEAKER_08]: How'd that work?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the arcade there was like one of the few in SoCal that had it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, those Golf Land Nights used to be something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: There they are!
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-oh, what'd you find?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura's reaching for, what is this, Saturn games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dreamcast games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wrong!
[SPEAKER_03]: TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: R-Type.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I do have Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome to Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get ready.
[SPEAKER_08]: 40 bucks, according to the price tag.
[SPEAKER_03]: When it was new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Land, Ys 1 and 2, here's my Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twin Bee!
[SPEAKER_03]: Some weird, bizarre shooter called Eldis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Garou Densetsu 2, which is Fatal Fury.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's just Fatal Fury, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: P.O.P.O.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strider, which we actually cannot play this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's sealed.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be one reason why you can't play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's not sealed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just... Oh, it looks like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: In sticky paper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we do not have a system that we can use an arcade card in.
[SPEAKER_03]: The...
[SPEAKER_03]: One system that I really want... And listeners, if you want to band together and do this for me, I'll be your best friend forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really trying to get a Duo RX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it has the arcade card built into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're about $150.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can get them pretty affordable still.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys made websites together.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so adorable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back on AOL.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, why are we making websites together?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's so precious.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Neo... And I want to know if anyone remembers this.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's shaking his head at me like, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know if anyone remembers this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was called Neo Strider's Strider Zone.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I touched up all of his graphics.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I was a junior in high school, I had a Sailor Venus fan page on GeoCities.
[SPEAKER_10]: You fag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, my first cosplay was Sailor Venus.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's the best one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the Holy Grail of the Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm surprised you don't have this framed with laser beams that just cut you like the Resident Evil movie when you try to touch it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or like Catherine Zeta-Jones in Entrapment trying to go through the laser beams.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing I can read on this is Die Something Custom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a tank game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The port that just came out on the Wii, does it look like this or is it different?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't tried it on the Wii yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't bought it either.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I know of those is die.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyway, die!
[SPEAKER_03]: I see anime girlies on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the one right there?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Valus 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then, yeah, the rest of these are PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tempest X. I think we got a... These characters look familiar.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we got an American version of this at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are the N-A-M-C-O games on PlayStation that were all the Namco stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then wasn't there like a trademark symbol game that's really rare?
[SPEAKER_08]: In Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a restricted symbol.
[SPEAKER_03]: And someone is supposed to be getting it for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's in it that's so special?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Man, Galaga, Pole Position, Bosconian, Rally X, New Rally X, and Toy Pop Xevious, Grappler, Super Pac-Man This was the one that was the hardest to find, was the A. Because I wanted Super Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mappy, Grabda, and Dragon Buster.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know we covered that story?
[SPEAKER_03]: That said, oh, Grabda, we're gonna get it remixed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, dude, it already came out in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could play this on the PS3, because they're playing PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had to get M as a greatest hits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dragon Spirit, Pac-Mania, and Legend of Valkyrie
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is it... What do you think made you such a gaming fan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, why do you think you play video games and you love the games and the gaming culture, like, so much?
[SPEAKER_03]: I practically grew up with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember playing the Atari 2600 when I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember the Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just always been there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's always been a fun and kind of integral part of my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope that doesn't sound too sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just always been there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's that because my story is somewhat similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like to go outside that much because I had asthma and allergies and everything and that and I hated everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, no I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was my form of escape.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know, my mom would play Nintendo with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'd play the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when she was asking me for Christmas one time what to get my brothers, a Genesis or a Super Nintendo, I told her a Super Nintendo and then I played it the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but I mean, it's always been kind of, it's been sort of a bonding thing in my family a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when I was living in Alabama and playing games, I could play some things over the dial-up connection with friends in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, it just was my way of kind of getting out of how crappy Alabama was to live in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, at the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying Alabama's crappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love my home state, but I'd never want to live there again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just did not like being stuck with everyone expecting me to be one way when I was clearly something other than what they wanted me to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I would just play games all the time and kind of forget about it and then...
[SPEAKER_03]: It instead expanded my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I met my husband because I loved anime and video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a happy life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a whole bunch of Transformers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, it's really, I think it's opened some doors in my otherwise lack of a social life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now I think I'm a lot more social than I used to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would say video games have a big part of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't say that... I don't know if it was like a social thing because I would like to think I was still like kind of social when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I had friends and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think like growing up especially, I was... You know, my brother and sister were so much older than I was.
[SPEAKER_08]: My brother is 14 years older.
[SPEAKER_08]: My sister is 16 years older than I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my parents then are quite a bit older.
[SPEAKER_08]: My mom was 37 when she had me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So by the time I was around, not only did I have kind of the only child syndrome thing going on, but my parents had kind of done it all with my brother and sister.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, they didn't...
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I think the Commodore 64 kind of enabled me to gaming, even though we had an Atari 2600 that I played and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just found myself like I was really able to entertain myself by like writing these little programs or typing them in for magazines and therefore feeling accomplished and, you know, trying to get these accomplishments in games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the games were sort of something I was able to get into.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I felt like it was something I was kind of good at and that I was able to kind of like follow the scene sorry I'm just stretching I was able to like follow the scene pretty good and whereas like a lot of kids were really good at football or baseball or sports and things that I wasn't so good at I was good at games and I could kick their butt in any like video game and that was always like kind of cool
[SPEAKER_08]: Busta Groove
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was Busta Groove that actually got me into games.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the music games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know Jamie hates that because that's not what they were called, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I didn't know any better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Being somebody who didn't really follow the import gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was funny to laugh about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're trying to get the mics untangled as we move back to the studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're playing mic roulette here.
[SPEAKER_03]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you guys want to ask us some questions in chat, chat.orangelantradio.com Any types of follow-up or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm finally able to look at chat here again.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, the G line should be up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you should be able to get back in.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let me know if you have success.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blaze in our chatroom says, My mom used to whoop my butt in Donkey Kong Country on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, my parents were never really into games at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: My dad...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think would try, but I don't think he was really into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'd rather just take me mini-golfing or something and then I'd want to play games the whole time we were there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't want to really golf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Toagak says Bust a Move is a game in the US.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that was the whole problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Bust a Move was Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think Puzzle Bobble is much cuter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think we're going to take, let's take like a quick, quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when we come back, we'll do some more news stories that we have listed and some of the other chat topics we have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that sound good?
[SPEAKER_08]: And we got to think about what we're going to do for food too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're going to do a take and bake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What time do those places close?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: 4 12 hours in of our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had our main show earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're tuning in expecting to hear Loki and the usual bits and all that, that started at 2 and finished at like 5.30.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're kind of in the extra stuff now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're broadcasting all night long because we can.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like a lot of you guys are joining us.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at our chat room at chat.orangeentree.com which, yay, we're back in after all this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Rama keeps having to remind me it's Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I say it's Saturday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just really want it to be Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you have tomorrow off work.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura actually made a phone call.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're doing what, pizza tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, the food of gamers.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, the food of gamers and the food of marathons, actually, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, hopefully DarkSakura got this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I sent out a second show role full of other stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully you saw that in your...
[SPEAKER_08]: Email?
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a good question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, take a look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we're going to do some more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some things that actually missed the show role originally.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll talk about those.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we got more classic games of the week coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll take some of your Facebook questions in the segment as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to do Ask Orange Lounge, I think, while I'm gone in the next segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some other stuff too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, how about...
[SPEAKER_08]: More DDR music!
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we heard enough of that during the break.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry about that, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I only got one.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I know I sent you one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take a look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: It compressed.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Open up the attachment.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Supplement.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to download it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does it let you click those links?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's ugly, but it works.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, if you want to send us comments or whatever and chat along with us, chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: So happy we found our way back in the chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for firsties, for people who love Sonic Adventure, like me, on Xbox Live Arcade, it will be $10 as of September 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's really, really sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic Adventure is probably one of my, in fact, the only probably good one of the three, you know, 3D ones, so I have to say that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: and um apparently uh I just think this is funny and I want to read this from the article because I I snickered just now it's like we've contacted Sega to find out if the game will arrive on PSN on a similar timetable we also sent them an email with the subject line give us Seaman followed by a body of text which essentially read Seaman so
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to be downloading this to check out and play?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or are you like, screw this, I have the original.
[SPEAKER_08]: Screw this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of screw this, I have the original.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the same time, I would like to support it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sank so many hours into Sonic Adventure 2 for the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's the one that had the little Tamagotchi Pokemon where you had your little babies.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Sonic Adventure had them too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine trying to play them in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's kind of sad, though, that you stopped playing after all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: My first streamcast was Japanese, and we had Sonic Adventure, so trying to make myself read it, it was fun, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, another story for you guys about Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crap, I linked myself to the wrong story, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_08]: Son of a gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to talk more Sonic Adventure, I lost my story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, what was your favorite level in Sonic Adventure?
[SPEAKER_10]: Running from the semi-truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Sonic, yeah, Sonic Adventure 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then also, that's the same semi-truck that is in the beginning of Bayonetta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I love, in Sonic Adventure, it's the Sky Highway, or the Speed Highway.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Bungayoh HD is coming out for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can break out into a sweat trying to dodge 5,000 bullets in 1080p.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, and that's what Bangaio is all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: My question is, though, if Bangaio is going like HD and all this, see, it's horizontal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't Bangaio another vertical shooter?
[SPEAKER_08]: Those don't translate too well into the HD because it's the wrong proportion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you were able to turn your HD TV like on its side, then it might work a lot better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they'll just have borders on the side like the final fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It always looks weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: It always looks so weird because that's like half the screen with those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: to make him well try playing well some games though like I remember Galactic Attack had a scrolling screen where you could scroll from side to side and it was just shorter and maintain your proportion
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, this is the other cool thing about the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got 100 levels in the game, so lots to play through.
[SPEAKER_08]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you finish all 100 levels and you decide, gosh, I need something new to play, use the level editor.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to get to build your own levels and share them on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bunga is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: So all this Dreamcast revival, good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's full of happiness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in other news, there is a game called Aero Cross High Air, the OFLC, the Australian rating thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one put out by Namco Bondi.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's actually the German USK rated Metro Cross High Air GP.
[SPEAKER_03]: So looking this over, they're actually related, from what I can tell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I was looking this over.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you have to remember the stories in this segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't really prep in advance at all, so it's going to be a little bit jankier than usual, but it's live radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's saying that Metro Cross is supposed to be like a redo of that 1985 Metro Cross that Namco put out, which is a side-scrolling foot race, and you avoid giant soda cans.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's Arrow Cross?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those soda cans are as big as that guy's torso.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are huge.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, the soda cans actually are as big as him, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, can you jump over soda cans that are your size?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_03]: They look vaguely like Coke, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, crap!
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, we're not to that story.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I know, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing that Loki didn't mention during the show when he was talking about the iPhone and all those upgrades is that Apple also announced their big new social network this week called Ping Has anyone been using Ping?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, have you used Ping?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no idea what it's going to offer me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking at first like the way they were demoing it, I thought Ping was going to be this like awesome replacement for Facebook because it would be like Facebook but music oriented and then like no FarmVille or any of those games that are on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: And don't get me wrong, there's a time and a place for FarmVille and Family Feud and Price is Right and all those Facebook games, but sometimes you don't want all that bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was also thinking that like, oh,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't even write your own status update unless you're Lady Gaga or one of the famous people on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like you can use it to follow famous people and then see what songs your friends are buying and make its own top ten list.
[SPEAKER_08]: But otherwise, it's kind of like, what's the point?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure that either her or her label is being... I mean, when she recommends an artist, I'm sure it's really from her.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you buy through the iTunes store, someone's making money for that referral for all the Gaga stans that buy what she says to buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, it's none of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just, hey, here's all the shit your friends are buying so you can make fun of them when they buy Spice Girls' greatest hits.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although you really shouldn't make fun of that guy because that's probably me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop hating.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Jessica Harper's in our chat, our good buddy from Under Station Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that explains why she was at the Apple building a couple weeks back.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: When she was at San Jose, she was visiting the Apple building.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we know why.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was getting her ping thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Redertainment in chat says, iTunes has had Genius Mixes for a while now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not a bad way to discover music, although it's your own music.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Genius Mixes run off your own, at least as far as I've seen, it's your own music library.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I have a...
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a lot of people, I have fairly eclectic music tastes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, I have some synth pop for those days.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have some, you know, Alanis and, you know, Tori for my angsty lesbian days.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a variety of music in my collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the Genius Playlist is a good way to kind of like separate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'll be like, okay, today I want to hear Tegan and Sarah and like everything that sounds like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it'll kind of come up with a pretty decent mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: iFarted in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that's their name, iFarted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Says, Sky secretly bought Milli Vanilli songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Admit it.
[SPEAKER_08]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll admit it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought them back in 1990 or whenever they were actually out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I had a single.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was 91, so we were like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I was in junior high.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was actually quoted in the junior high paper during the whole debacle because they ran a story on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I said something like, well, if they just released the names of the guys who really did it, I'd still buy their music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Like in retrospect, how obvious is their faking?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for real?
[SPEAKER_03]: These guys are supposed to have also had a good voice on their own.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and they wanted to do their own stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to hear the chorus.
[SPEAKER_10]: They performed on an MTV Spring Break back when that was still going on and they actually used an actual LP for their lip sync and it skipped.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like an Ashley Simpson thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: so they were doing their choreography and the girl you know it's true was stuttering because I guess they couldn't afford a cassette nice that's gotta be slightly embarrassing alright so let's go back to some gaming news I'm sorry I gotta shut off the Milli Vanilli for now Redertainment in our chatroom says I can't give a 14 year old shit watch me
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some little shits at, like, Golf Land sometimes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm like, the fuck I can't tell this kid what to do when he's, like, 14 years old and, like, thinks he's all, like, a badass.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, um, you know, someday you're gonna, like, be unemployed and hating life and fathering tons of babies and, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: My mom will roll you down with a Range Rover if you don't stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, uh, hey, back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: From Milli Vanilli to Mario.
Ha ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: 25th Anniversary
[SPEAKER_08]: Mario All-Stars came back in 1993, and that was Mario, Mario 2, Mario 3, and the Lost Levels, which was really Japanese Mario 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: In their cartridge, they got our Mario 2 as Mario USA, even though it was really Doki Doki Panic, and I've gone cross-eyed.
[SPEAKER_08]: apparently the Wii reissue is going to have special packaging and there'll be a little booklet and a CD of Mario music that will include stuff from the original game all the way to Mario Galaxy 2 but no word if there are extra Mario games included with this
[SPEAKER_08]: Game Boy Advance got special reissues of each one.
[SPEAKER_08]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, the Advanced, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Mario Advanced.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Mario Advanced 2 is really Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were out of order, but they all got a GBA remake treatment.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were really well done.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm kind of curious, are we just going to be getting the same...
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Nintendo Game Mario World
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: and I guess you are getting a CD full of music, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just seems like there ought to be a little bit more to this or some extra Mario games or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on, it's the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have a lot of extra space to do stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Watch it not have classic controller support.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because.
[SPEAKER_10]: You gotta use the Wii stick sideways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if they put Mario World on it, that won't work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because there were four buttons.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had the spinny jump and the... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Y was run, B was jump, X was spinny jump, and A was... I think also fireball or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it did anything, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were laughing at some pictures you brought up earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's this all about?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're fantastically filthy.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least I think they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's these little additions that hook onto the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are put out by Mojo Wejo, and they are supposed to transform... Mojo Wejo!
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Able to transform the varying motions of the control into appropriate vibration signals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're vibrators.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are interesting looking violators.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're will-dos.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're we-dildos.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're we-dos.
[SPEAKER_03]: We-dos.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to show you chat room and I want to see what you think about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would this be a turn-on or a total buzzkill?
[SPEAKER_08]: One of them looks like something you would use to pick up radioactive material.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it doesn't even really look like... What's that supposed to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, pinch things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet it's for fapping.
Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be an adjustable little clamp that goes around your... It's the claw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it adjustable sizes?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, I need extra large.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are you laughing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just looked over and saw Ellen give you a sideways look.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at any rate, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: One of these...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that I find that attractive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it come with Purell?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that a Wiimote would give off enough oomph.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: What games are you going to be able to play with that?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's just some housewife with a big grin on her face flailing around the living room?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, oh, I'm playing WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_10]: But your hands are free, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing the ping pong ball shooting level.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what it says on the Mojo Weejo website, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: The device is attached to the accessory port on a Nintendo Wii remote control.
[SPEAKER_03]: The control is then connected to a Bluetooth-enabled PC running Mojo Weejo software.
[SPEAKER_03]: Using the Mojo Weejo patent-pending Motion 2 Vibration technology...
[SPEAKER_03]: the device is able to transform the varying motions of the control into appropriate vibration signals and send them to another selected device in the same room or over the internet Wii gaming console not required essentially turning your Wii remotes into shared remote controlled vibrators aka Wii vibrator or Wii brater that's from it kind of reminds me of the original there's a video oh wow there's a video to this oh hooray
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, I should play this over here so we can get the audio over the feed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got my sound turned off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to play this over the feed here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where am I going?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, here?
[SPEAKER_08]: The link?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, follow the link to SF Weekly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if this has sound.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just kind of doing its thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's drawn a little unhappy face.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not really unhappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's like, I'm super happy!
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm playing the Nintendo Wii, but I have this box that says Mojo Weejo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now my Wii has a little accessory that I shake.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's making a little shaky thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm waiting for something interesting to happen here.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's it doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's transmitting to the computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then it's transmitting back to the Wii mode and it starts shaking.
[SPEAKER_08]: and now the eyes are turning all different colors.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what it looks like?
[SPEAKER_03]: From what I'm getting on here, it's for cybering.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's for cyber sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: It runs off the Bluetooth in your computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just using the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, who doesn't have a Wiimote?
[SPEAKER_08]: So here's what you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just explaining this like I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get on your...
[SPEAKER_08]: You get on your PC and you find someone you want to do some naughty things with online.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you take the Wiimote and put on the attachment and...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, attach it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you go on the chat room and you put like, oh baby, I am so hot right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, push the button.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they push the button and you're like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of typing, I am having so much trouble typing right now, it'd be like you, you know, V-E-R-Q, it'd be all scrambled.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you'd have to get one of those little plastic covers for your monitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: You remember when people always had the little plastic covers for their keyboard and everything, and we used to just call it the Jizz Guard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Splash Zone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you just play Rez with it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really what it's made for, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have amused Tara with your explanation Good, good Alright Well, speaking of sensual video games The Wii Balance Board is now supported in a massage game Oh, you're gonna love this, DarkSakura Called Love Press Plus Plus This looks like the type of massage game that has happy endings Not the type of massage you paid good money to go to school to learn
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be shown off this month at the Tokyo Game Show 2010 It's a massage game called Love Press Press It's by Shirai Labs and it uses massage recognition to stimulate the physical communication of lovers
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You choose a virtual partner and you can pick from various shapes and ages.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I somehow doubt there's old fatties.
[SPEAKER_08]: The shapes are skinny and skinnier probably and the ages are like young or 18.
[SPEAKER_08]: No gilfs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because like real people don't ever be in these games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Creepy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actually an announcement.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: There has to be one line in that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, here's this guy playing the game and it just looks like he's having anal sex with a balance board.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really what it looks like to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, tell me I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he's having anal sex with a balance board.
[SPEAKER_03]: Link that in the chat room and put it to a quick vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quick poll in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anal board sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to the following link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that man having wee board sex?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anal sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me type that in bold.
[SPEAKER_03]: I vote too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe the longer we broadcast, the dirtier we get.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some hospitals in Japan are going to get way more weird emergency room visits than they're used to.
[SPEAKER_08]: It pinches!
[SPEAKER_08]: But you see what he's doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's massaging the board like it's supposed to be somebody's back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay, now this actually goes to something which is kind of a recent, and I've actually been reading sociological articles about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: That there's been this... About this?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it has to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anal sex with rebalance boards?
[SPEAKER_08]: It has to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You read a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, it's me.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there's information to be learned, I learn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's actually been this big, and they've been interviewing people who are becoming less and less outwardly social, preferring to stay at home more often, who basically don't want sex.
[SPEAKER_03]: Want, I guess, companionship, but not like with a real person.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like this one guy married his doll.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also the guy who married the DS, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the only guy who married his DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's been this social thing lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was looking up some stuff about birth rates dropping.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had that as a link in regards to birth rates dropping in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, well, you know, isn't this just what we hear about, you know, kind of, you know, fringe behavior?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the norm.
[SPEAKER_03]: But apparently it's becoming either more of a trend or more of a public knowledge type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this totally doesn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I'm just looking at this because they actually put on here, they put tweet love press to give your comments.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to see what comments, but it's all... We have a new president, Kat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like...
[SPEAKER_08]: All the results are more than two days old.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have enough people tweeting Love Press.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we need to change that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like everybody has tweeted Love Press two days ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Red Entertainment, yes, I am very familiar with the term, and I wasn't going to bring that up, but that's actually been, again, coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Asexuality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I think you guys need to tweet about the love press and, you know, how you can't wait for the anal sex Wii balance board game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, the results of our quick poll are in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I'm sorry, the quick poll again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that man giving anal sex to the balance board?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, he is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's some butt sex right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, yes, frown.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, baby, oh, baby, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, yes, he is, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Goes blind.
[SPEAKER_08]: On a scale of 1 to 10, I'm gonna fuck you now.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's friending the Wii's, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, you need to tweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right at the bottom of that page it says tweet Love Press to give your comments.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would like our listeners to send their comments on the Love Press over to the makers of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're waiting to hear your comments on Love Press.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you take a towel and wrap it up and press it down on there, does it then become a waterboarding simulator?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's another sensual game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's not sexual.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just going to teach you how to massage.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know I hate the term happy ending, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you do, which is why I say it all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is not... I'm not going to get on my high horse about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, but I have two questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it something that would typically be done at the end of the session?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it going to make the recipient happy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Therefore, it's a happy ending.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's all offensive and shit to massage people who take the art of massage very seriously, but... Well, on top of that, it's the other reason why we're running into all this legislation going around now trying to put police officials on the board of massage therapists in California who know nothing about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: As gamers, they're trying to say that M-rated games shouldn't be sold unless they have all these restrictions or games are porn and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blame the man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stick it to the man.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you seen DarkSakura, the YouTube where this masseuse is like, oh, would you like happy ending?
[SPEAKER_10]: And the guy says, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all of a sudden, like, balloons fall out of the sky and clowns come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're like, yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: He's like in his towel clapping, like, yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: I should see that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds... Now that's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds entirely too amusing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know how to find that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know what I would look up?
[SPEAKER_08]: We got a marathon show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can look up YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy ending parody?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could probably tell what it is from the cap.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy ending massage HD uncut original version?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_08]: This girl's got big titties.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I want to just see this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't... Mute it in case it's not it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just going to mute that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, this is like softcore right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is awesome radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's because we're amazing people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Cinemax.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to watch this, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Massaging his...
[SPEAKER_08]: Feet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that the type of outfit you wear when giving massages?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a fan of sweatpants and a t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a sign, therapeutic massages only, no police allowed.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want happy endings?
[SPEAKER_04]: You happy now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it really wasn't what I was hoping for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you want a handjob.
$50.
[SPEAKER_05]: For a handjob, right?
Yeah, handjob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, okay.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Handjob!
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're all in grease outfits.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's doing it too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Ellen, for bringing that into my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, chat room, how you have missed out.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those listening on the podcast, YouTube user is Mediocre Films.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is, Mediocre Films.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's called Happy Ending Massage.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to look at a stop motion movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, this I've got to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, we haven't rehearsed any of this, so I'm trying to see what this was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a stop motion animation of somebody doing Kirby's Adventure in yarn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to quote this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it came from...
[SPEAKER_03]: The original idea came from staff at Goodfeel, which was inspired by a stop animation film made primarily with yarn, explains Ellis.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm reading off Destructoid.
[SPEAKER_03]: With the ability for players to interact with the game's environment, such as unzipping the background panels, Kirby's Epic Yarn is really its own category as a platformer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, and they're saying that nobody at Nintendo of America knew what it came from, so I'm seeing if this is perhaps the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this was a stop-motion animation commercial that came out in Japan for Kirby's Adventure.
[SPEAKER_03]: All done with yarn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, it's got that yarn style.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't it amazing what the internet will unearth?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, if you have an unoriginal idea, at some point the internet will find it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, Kirby sure sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he does, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't we get cute commercials like that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Explain it to me, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not watching enough cartoons.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we don't have cool commercials anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: How does a hipster play Kirby?
[SPEAKER_08]: How?
[SPEAKER_10]: Without inhaling any powers because it's a pure experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you want to do that story on the third night's game you skipped over?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you do that one?
[SPEAKER_03]: I opened everything up in order.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I link the same story twice?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I just linked the same thing twice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Skip that story then.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do these two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's the wrong link.
[SPEAKER_08]: I screwed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thanks, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now you gotta do two stories in a row.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
007.
[SPEAKER_08]: A slew of pre-order items for GoldenEye 007 coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameStop, if you get the game there, you're gonna get Invisibility Mode will be unlocked in the game for split-screen multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Each player will be invisible for a set amount of time, allowing you to sneak up on each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: but then I don't know what happens with that so maybe they're going to I don't know if they're codes you put into the game which will end up on the internet everywhere or if it's some type of DLC which doesn't make sense because Nintendo Wii doesn't do a lot of DLC although there's some like the Final Fantasy 4 game has some DLC in it but yeah that's strange oh by the way if you get the game at Walmart you get a t-shirt that says cheater with an odd job hat
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that you can't get with a code.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I hate to say it, but Walmart seems to be the best place to get this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little odd job hat says cheater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's because anyone who uses odd job is a cheap bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, odd job is awesome and you just can't deal with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way,
[SPEAKER_08]: Martin Hollis I imagine it's a business decision, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: This name is valuable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's use it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I find it hard to picture Activision's top management being excited about the original and wanting to do it justice.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, I find it hard to imagine them being excited about any game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's my perception that they are trying to be EA, only more so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're doing a fine job with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a little irritated there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, he does say nice things about the developers themselves.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, quote, they are a good company.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm confident they've done their very best.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a first-slash-third-person shooter that originally came out in 2005, and you took on the role of the Stranger.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was kind of like an Oddworld type of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You used ammo, animals, bugs to actually take out enemies.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to have updated visuals to 720p, updated graphics, updated music and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: The dialogue in the game is also being remastered.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this the... I remember the last Odyssey game that came out where you're a cowboy where you're actually a cow and you're shooting enemies first-person shooter style and I remember it bombed horribly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what this is?
[SPEAKER_10]: Remade?
[SPEAKER_08]: But you're not a cow, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it doesn't look like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a moose or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone in chattel now.
[SPEAKER_03]: How is a cow like a moose?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're both big and stinky.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's going to be 720p and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are targeting an Easter release.
[SPEAKER_08]: One other thing that they're putting in the game, PlayStation Move support.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's almost like a whole different game from what it used to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it the Move?
[SPEAKER_03]: With what Alan said.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't stop!
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I was just thinking about pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll take a break here in a minute and do the pizza stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, as far as there's news for DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The RZA is in the cast of DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: As in, dude from Wu-Tang Clan who also likes to put out kung fu movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've actually got images for his costume up here and I'm pulling those up to have a good look at them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's him being motion captured for the game, so that's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, fully digitized, gonna be in the game, and I'm just double checking to see if there's any other tracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm entranced by the Ice Cream Truck music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ice Cream Man!
[SPEAKER_03]: He's right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is he right out front?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's kind of weird that it started showing up in the last year or so that Ice Cream Truck's been driving by.
[SPEAKER_03]: LL Cool J's I Can't Live Without My Radio and Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five's The Message and then the other one is Damian Marley's Welcome to Jamrock and Walter Murphy's A Fifth of Beethoven which was on the Saturday Night Fever soundtrack which I have two copies of on vinyl
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you're weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got my mom's and my uncle's copies each.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's also a Dollars and Cents BlackRock track for the game, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just thought it was funny because the other article mentioned the other game that he had been motion captured in.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what that was, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wu-Tang Shaolin style fighting game for PS1.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God, I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it was like, oh, God, it was like the new Shaq Fu.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it wasn't really all that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember that Def Jam, the rap fighting game?
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one of those too?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Mega Man Universe.
[SPEAKER_08]: More information was supposed to come out of PAX this week, but I don't remember seeing anything additional on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe somebody in chat can fill us in on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a story saying that more Mega Man Universe information was going to be coming out because apparently they were giving away some little things that look like, I don't know, like little, I don't know what those are supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are those like
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Like little pillows or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, they just look like little pillows.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Ryu is kind of funny, but the Rockman looks actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So apparently some of the stuff at Capcom's booth was supposed to be showing Mega Man Universe with more trailers and game levels, Ghost Trick, Okamiden, Resident Evil 5, Bionic Commando Rearm 2, da da da.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't seen a whole lot of information since then.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about, how about I...
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, stinking trailers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I'm getting it, I'm getting it, I'm getting it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, are we ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we have to go by the sponsor message real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's nine seconds, we're good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally forgot whose level I was doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Metal Man, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: ESRB, da-da-da, who cares, shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Capcom logo Aren't you all pretty now?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, I'm the creator of Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of people who saw the first Mega Man Universe trailer are confused about wondering how this game will play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since the trailer didn't reveal all that much, we want to know you, jerk.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm here to clear up the confusion.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first playable video
[SPEAKER_08]: and you can see how it actually works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Show me already!
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope this video gets you excited and has you looking forward to more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hurry up!
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you mad, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: In your arm!
[SPEAKER_08]: Play us, Rockman.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, the graphics look cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, isn't that Metal Man's stage?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's Fire Man's stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the select music.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the character select music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the stage select.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's Crash Man's level.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, this is like Mega Man 2 redone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's new.
[SPEAKER_08]: A level that says Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's...
[SPEAKER_00]: Play as Ryu.
[SPEAKER_00]: No way.
[SPEAKER_00]: You are Megafight.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says you're World Megafight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so some of the gameplay looks very Mega Man, but then you see this random Ryu.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is that all about?
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta see if there's more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are these all just the same?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all the same trailer, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, they all got different gameplay trailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like different websites got different gameplay trailers.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like that's Woodman's level.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, it's like a Mega Man 2 upgrade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus some, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna play as Ryu, no way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanna see, like, actual one that actually shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see what this trailer has in it here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they're all gonna be Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, there's no controls in that one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do admit that he's actually really cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm not going to play that third one because we can't skip through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so it's a Mega Man type of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, so we say there's a triple video out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at our chat room there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It shows all three side by side.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's see if I can get that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: We have extra time because of the marathon show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to do...
Universe Triple Video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Mega Man Universe Triple Video.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see official teaser trailer, which is that same thing we saw before.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is wonderful radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, shush.
[SPEAKER_08]: You would think that they would have actual footage that's shown up from PAX, but I guess not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's not out there on the floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to some more news.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get more information on this in the coming weeks, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other news!
[SPEAKER_03]: How about EA actually trying to cover their ass?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're basically trying to defend their whole stupid little online pass deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a quote out here put by EA Sports dude Peter Moore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Digital delivery, maintaining servers able to support that volume of people every 24 hours, a solid billing infrastructure and customer support.
[SPEAKER_03]: It all takes time, effort, and money, and we're at the cutting edge of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Online pass is a way of bringing more digital experiences quicker from day one, getting people new content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're just saying, this shit costs money.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need more of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we all need more money.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want more money.
[SPEAKER_08]: EA should give me $10 because I need to have money to buy their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'd have to pay me to play their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, well, not for Sims 3, but like for, you know, sports games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what they need?
[SPEAKER_03]: They need, EA needs to put out Wii Figure Skating and you use the balance board.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you have to balance to do all the tricks right on there with your Wiimotes in your hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd play that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of amazing, this is probably the most amazing news story we've had all week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Commodore USA is going to be making modern PCs, but in replica cases.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that is, like, so badass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, the Commodore PC-64 will actually have an Intel Atom 535 processor with NVIDIA Ion 2 graphics, 4 gigabytes of DDR3 RAM, a terabyte hard drive, and a DVD-ROM, optionally upgradable to Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is so hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually kind of want one.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's in a Commodore 64 replica case so you can party like it's 1983.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a lot else with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see a price though.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the one thing I'd like to see is a price.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, of course they don't say what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at the original press release here to see what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have different news.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a game that the Burnout developers were going to be making, and do you know what that was?
[SPEAKER_03]: Skate or Die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember Skate or Die?
[SPEAKER_02]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were going to do it GTA style, apparently, instead of just having it be all tricks and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would have been kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder why they canned it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they talk about why it got canned or why they decided not to do it or what happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, EA and Criterion basically got on each other's asses again, and so Criterion then went to do Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it just looks like it just kind of fell through the cracks.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could have been kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember Ski or Die.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the quote-unquote sequel.
[SPEAKER_10]: My BFF in grade school used to get blisters on the palm of his hands, like really gross blisters from playing Skate or Die on his PC, his IBM.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I guess I think it was the half pipe.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to roll your palm across the number pad to do the flips.
[SPEAKER_10]: He used to get blisters from that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool story, bro.
[SPEAKER_01]: That just sounds nasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one I remember, it wasn't Skate or Die.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember quite as fondly as I do 720, which was Atari's skating game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you play this, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it a bunch.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where you get chased by bees if you're not fast enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually got to play it again at California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was like a hand killer just because spinning the controller a bunch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because it was all trackball, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, it's a controller that goes around in a circle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right, yeah, the controller's like, but it doesn't stand up, like it's always tilted in one way, so it's really weird to control.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, that's the direction you go in when you skate, so you press the button to kick, and then you're going in the direction that you have the joystick in, and then you spin it around as you need to.
[SPEAKER_08]: but then you would have these like really epically long levels and it ran on there was a very unique kind of Atari hardware at that time because there's other games that look very similar to it like Hard Drivin' I think is one and the Indiana Jones game was on that same hardware you know there's a bulk of games Atari put out that all kind of ran on that same thing 720 I think it's in some of the Midway classic collections too I do believe you are correct yeah so I don't know why they got oh no because they picked up the Atari arcade assets at some point I think so hmm
[SPEAKER_02]: I should say, skate or die.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the next story, this kind of came up earlier in the show, but I have it listed, so I'll mention this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy XIV, the beta, was actually delayed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to start originally on August 31st, but they actually had to delay it a day because of critical bugs and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: but here's the crazy thing a lot of people have been having difficulty getting into the open beta there's been limited signups and all this other stuff going on they stopped issuing beta codes they took down the installer altogether it's all crazy September 22nd is supposed to be the launch of this game three weeks this game is supposed to launch that'll go over well I'm sure so I don't know
[SPEAKER_08]: What made you decide not to get the Final Fantasy XIV beta, Alan?
[SPEAKER_10]: Watching you play it and your less-than-stellar feedback of it when you played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you interested in it before?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, I signed up when you did for the... Oh, I thought you were just doing that for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm into WoW now, so I've got enough interest in MMOs to at least check out the competitions.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you were playing MMOs before, wow, City of Heroes, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, City of Heroes You never got Going Rogue, did you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you read anything on it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I checked Metacritic and I think Game Rankings the week it came out and it didn't have anything So I don't think that IGN and all the big review sites have treated it as a priority Maybe now there are some reviews up Well, let's take a look, we have a little time Because it was an actual standalone release, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, if you buy the Going Rogue Edition, which is like $29.95, if you plug in that license, you have access to the whole game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, no one's reviewed it yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, none.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess people just don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Still going strong, but its community is really underground.
[SPEAKER_10]: No one talks about COH anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see a comment from Ziba in our chatroom saying, I still say Guild Wars 2 for the win.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, after looking at that footage, Guild Wars was kind of like, I can kind of take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guild Wars...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: then Guild Wars 2 that some of that gameplay footage came out it looks awesome like I gotta say I'm I'm really like it's all actiony and it looks really cool see that's where like MMOs are going these days is more actiony and that's cool I'm really excited about DC Universe Online if I mentioned that where's the beta for that I want to play that all right Dark Sakura more news for us
[SPEAKER_03]: I do indeed.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is actually the Sega lineup for Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Sega Konami Level 5 and Tecmo Koei for Tokyo Game Show 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got from Sega Vanquish, Virtual Enforce.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that makes me so happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic Colors, Phantasy Star Portable 2 Infinity, Black Panther Yakuza New Chapter, Shiny Hearts K-On!
[SPEAKER_03]: After School Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other Sega Partner games, Shirin the Wanderer 5, F1 2010, Bullet Soul, Arcana Heart 3, Mafia 2 For Konami, Castlevania Lords of Shadow, Tongari, Boshi to Mahou to Omise, Magician's Quest
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Gear Solid Rising, Dance Evolution, Metal Gear Solid Peace Walker on PSP, Back to Umbra, Maboroshi no Uenchi, Crossboard 7, and Ultimadeus X.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other Konami partner games, Legend of Heroes, Zero, No, Kiseki, Catherine, Metal Fight Beyblade, Metal Fight Beyblade Portable, Momotaro Densetsu World, and UFC Undisputed 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's actually being put out by Ux.
[SPEAKER_03]: Level 5, Ni No Kuni on DS, PS3, and Ni No Kuni, Hot Troit Stories for mobile phone, Mystery Room for DS, Dumble Senki for PSP, and Tecmo Koei, Trinity Zil-ol, like O apostrophe L-L.
[SPEAKER_03]: Troy Musso, Quantum Theory, Ishin no Arashi Shippu Ryomaden, Winning Post 7 2010, Nobunaga's Ambition Online, Uncharted Waters Online, Dynasty Warriors Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, pretty big lineup.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's just so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: People who are going to Tokyo Game Show, get me stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to go like one day, just once, to say I did it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to go longer than one day, so I can actually spend some time in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I meant like one day I would like to go, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the whole show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, this is another story about some big surprises, and I think this will make Alan very happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: In an interview with PC Gamer, Gabe Newell from Valve, of course, has said...
[SPEAKER_08]: I can guarantee you people are going to be surprised at stuff we do.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is after he already... Are you rolling your eyes?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is after they came out and said the whole Steam Cloud support on PS3 and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he said, quote, this isn't going to stop anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just laughing because people will be shocked again.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have three big surprises in the next 12 months at least.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are a Half-Life fan, you really aren't allowed to get mad at Gabe Newell and Valve because if you do, they might keep Half-Life in a closet forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very much an abusive relationship.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, all of the blogs that are posting this story have a picture of Gordon Freeman in his HEV suit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really hope it's something Half-Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I Half-Life 2 came out six years ago and it's I hey it took 11 years for Starcraft 2 just saying oh yeah and I I only really play first-person shooters like Bioshock or Half-Life that have that narrative and the story like the cliffhanger at the end of Half-Life 2 episode 2 was so epic it's like it's like I'm a five-year-old on Christmas morning I want that game
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, there was recently a trademark for Defense of the Ancients, and that of course makes people speculate that there will be a real-time strategy game update to Defense of the Ancients.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, that's that Warcraft 3 mod that Valve is trying to publish as their own thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Blizzard was like... Oh, that's right, because they hired all those people, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: And Blizzard was like, LOL, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's still in litigation right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe they'll just change the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Be interesting if that happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Left 4 Dead 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure that would be a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're rolling your eyes over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't think I don't see you rolling your eyes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a Left 4 Dead fan?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a great game, but I feel that they have other franchises they should focus on more promptly.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't want to see a new IP come out of Valve?
[SPEAKER_08]: The next Portal?
[SPEAKER_10]: They shouldn't work on a damn thing until the next Half-Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't want to see Portal 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: I will go to their office with a ruler and I will slap the little knuckles of their programmer's head and go, what are you working on?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not Half-Life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wap.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then security will drag me out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is how I feel.
[SPEAKER_10]: How does chat feel about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Does chat want their half-life?
[SPEAKER_10]: Either 3 proper or episode 3 proper?
[SPEAKER_08]: Monty Boggs in chat says I already forgot how episode 2 ended I should probably go back if they do announce a sequel Floppy Discourse in chat says Left 4 Dead 3 rocks
[SPEAKER_10]: It probably came out already because they have a six-month development cycle on those games.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yet Half-Life takes six years.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think they're doing to this game to make it just so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess I shouldn't ask these questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: I read the Half-Life 2 book that came out about how big Half-Life 2 was going to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: Half-Life 2 for a first-person shooter is a really long game.
[SPEAKER_10]: all of the conceptual stuff where they want we want this set piece we want this event to happen it was going to be like an 80 hour game and they had to cut out all this stuff so same thing could be happening for Half-Life 3 RedRotainment in chat says I wanted Half-Life 2 years ago DarkCircuitry says more Half-Life heart and DarkTetsuya says no there's only one game I'm looking forward to in the immediate future and it's on the Wii
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm guessing that's the La Mulana game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't that already come out?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I guess it's still in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hoseo Sumiuragawa is looking forward a little more to the Final Fantasy VII remake that still has not been announced and probably is never going to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm really disappointed that we haven't heard anything about a DS or even DS 3D, 3DS, Final Fantasy 5 or Final Fantasy 6.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know how they remade the SNES ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, Final Fantasy 4 was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think 6 might be too big of a game, but they could do 5, it would sell really well here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or 6.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, don't take this the wrong way, but fuck 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, 6 is really where it's at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, again, to put the hate mail down, I still like Final Fantasy 5, but it's just Final Fantasy 6 is like, it's way up here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, Final Fantasy 5 is vanilla ice cream.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's good, and I'm not gonna turn it down, and it's like, you know, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Final Fantasy 6... Final Fantasy 6?
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy 6...
[SPEAKER_08]: is like peanut butter cups and chocolate ice cream.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like words I shouldn't say on the radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're at what time?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we're at 745.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we need a break then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because the place closes at 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, let's break after that story.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll come back and we'll do a few more.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you guys are going to do Ask Orange Lounge, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're going to do Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they should send them to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: To me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you're going to Ask Orange Lounge with Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Via private message.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Skype line will also be open for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: if you want to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'll come over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to, we're going to take a quick music break while we order dinner and then we're going to come back and do some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: So send your questions again, not me.
[SPEAKER_08]: They won't get ready if you send them to me, DarkSakura in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send in some questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take a quick break but we'll be right back with the Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Marathon Show
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: You may have missed last week's show where we told you guys we're going to be doing something special this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki has already come and gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was here at 2 o'clock for the quote-unquote normal show that went until about 5.30 and now we're kind of in the bonus portion.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now that we are getting into the really random stuff, we actually have to eat.
[SPEAKER_08]: We kind of have to stop to eat.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we're not going to stop the marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually going to run out and get what's called take-and-bake pizzas.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to get pizzas and then we'll switch off and Jamie's actually going to bake them while we do some other topics.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to bake them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you're the woman.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll help.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew it was coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to burn down your house either.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it really boils down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll play some Talking Heads while Rob cooks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Burning down the house.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, I'm going to step out to go do that, but Dark Sakura is going to take over.
[SPEAKER_08]: God help you all.
[SPEAKER_08]: And do some Ask Orange Lounge, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, it wouldn't be Ask Orange Lounge if we didn't have a theme song, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: We could do a duet, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't ask me any questions because I'm leaving this house because I know how this segment can sometimes go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you were going to say sometimes suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do I look like Wayne Brady?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do I sing improv songs on command?
[SPEAKER_03]: Make like two live crew and get the fuck out my house, bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky says do the live feed while getting pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could do the Ustream.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not going to do that and drive at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would be forced to yell at Rob for doing something dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be good, kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, chatlings, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haseo Sumiragawa, what's the story with the orange bat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: The orange bat came from March Madness, which was a DDR tournament that they held at Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was me and Rob and Jessica and...
[SPEAKER_03]: At the time, her fianc, and I think, and somebody else who was with us, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we decided that we were just sick of all the people not really doing actual routines when they were doing their thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we actually went and got plastic orange bats and little toy trumpets and stomped them a beat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rob and I proceeded to hit each other over the head with bats while the others played the trumpets.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it was epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the bat went around and was signed and I think Rob has his bat and then I have my bat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my bat, I got signed by everyone in Step Squad and RTF, as many people as I could.
[SPEAKER_03]: The bat is in my garage right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's the story of the orange bat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Circuitry asks, which is the better game in your guys' opinion, Pump It Up Pro or In The Groove?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, dude, caution drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not a big fan of In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's playable.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Pump It Up, they're just different types.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, same theory, yes, but different.
[SPEAKER_03]: Type of game, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pump It Up is one of the more major DDR clones where it's the diagonals.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the five square one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I tried playing that once, and I was so in the mindset of DDR that I made it through like two songs, and it basically broke me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the different mechanics of the diagonals, I couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't touch it since.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know people who are really, really good at it who do doubles on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just remembered how the caution drop used to work on that, is that you'd follow the diagonal, your knee would hit the middle, and then your foot would hit the top of the back, and then you'd slap the bottom two on those for...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had stuff where you had to hit all five buttons and it was really difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: During OLRthon, how about firing up the Wii for multiplayer Mario Kart or the 360 for Rock Band 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's because Dan and Alex have taken over the front room and are shooting each other stupid in a first person, well, not a first person, but in a shooting game, a shmup against each other that we will not mention the name of in this house because it's not here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the target time?
[SPEAKER_03]: 1am?
[SPEAKER_03]: 2am?
[SPEAKER_03]: Midnight is the baseline, I think Hoof Hearted, I guess you like horses, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's Spazinator Your thought on this It's a 1TB hard drive for $80
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, go for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not, it doesn't, transfer at 480 megabytes per second, plug and play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not bad, it's not great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, not like the super most awesome thing in the universe, but hey, cheap terabyte hard drive, why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think last January or February I got a terabyte external FireWire USB thing like that for about $110 just to show how cheap hard drive space is becoming, but I use it as my MP3 slash torrents drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I've actually filled up my $500 gig with MP3s and movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a whole bunch of obscure Japanese Sentai TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like my Tower Rangers!
[SPEAKER_10]: I think your mic's cutting out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_03]: No cutting out, mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not allowed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, next question, and thank you, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_03]: That looks like it would be a decent purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, floppy discourse?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny!
[SPEAKER_03]: Floppy discourse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha.
[SPEAKER_03]: When is Final Fantasy XIV coming out?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know and I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the PC date is, I think Rob just said it, the 23rd, 24th, three weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're supposed to have 14 available for PC in three weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've completely lost interest in the Final Fantasy online series.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: But pretty does not necessarily mean good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm happy with my Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the first video game you ever played in your life?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pinball tables don't count, but feel free to say what those are too if you remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: My first video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Pong when I was little.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then later on we went on to Kangaroo and Popeye and Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got an Atari 2600 when I was 4 or 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So any one of those games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the Pac-Man version was awful though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But not as bad as E.T.? ?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, and I played the hell out of that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because when you're seven, you don't really have taste.
[SPEAKER_02]: With that Pac-Man, I don't know if it was a setting or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: After a while, it was a weird thing where the power pellet moved to somewhere else other than the middle of the board.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had no idea how it happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Programming glitch?
[SPEAKER_02]: The first thing I played, I remember, was when I got the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Atari 2600 for like, I think it was fourth Christmas when I was like four.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we played Asteroids first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I remember the big splashy colored asteroids floating around the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good game to have as your first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pong is kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pong.
Pong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, as far as pinball tables, I played all kinds of pinball when I was a kid, so it's really hard to remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the first one I remember playing was, my dad had one called Genie.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, which one?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called Genie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I know, one of the 50s ones or 60s ones?
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that, I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little rotating numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Found it by Gottlieb
[SPEAKER_03]: Genie, 1979, 4 player, and it is indeed electronic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it played like the place in France where the Naked Ladies dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a hole in the wall where the guys can see their mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was just a track sound.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll link that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hoping I might see it at the California stream, but no, they didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might be able to find it, though, when they do that other pinball expo, Pacific Pinball Expo.
[SPEAKER_03]: They might have them there because they usually have older tables there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I really can't remember what my first pinball was and it was something old.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what's your first video game you've played in roller skates?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, when I would go visit my dad in Dothan, Alabama, the roller rink there was called Bobaloo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Bob, who was the owner, he'd since passed away, and his wife was Lou.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Bob was friends with my granddaddy, and they taught amateur skating, like figure skating with roller skates.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so I would always go up there and just go hang out and talk and talk about granddaddy but they had the same Frogger machine there while I was growing up and it was still always in good working condition the joystick was a little sticky but it was the same Frogger machine and I played that same machine for easily 10 years so anyway so how about more questions huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Tiara wants to add Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles at the roller rink.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember when to play an arcade game it was either the arcade when they still existed or the pizza parlor arcade games there or I remember when Street Fighter 2 came out everyone went to 7-Eleven to play it when 7-Eleven actually had arcade cabinets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, we did go to the... I don't know if it was 7-Eleven, but it was some sort of convenience store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or like Circle K. Everyone go play Street Fighter 2 at the Circle K. This is out in South Carolina, so I don't remember what it was called.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember my high school band trip, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we went to New York, we drove up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually stopped in Washington, D.C.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then went on up to New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was when Mortal Kombat 2 was in beta testing.
[SPEAKER_03]: with all the glitches and the continuous things so we were just Mortal Kombat and the guys would just play it instead of eat but I would play that too because I loved Mortal Kombat and I was really good with Katana but that was that's probably one of my favorite high school video game memories I think other than me letting out a very loud curse while I was playing Zelda Link to the Past while my mom was in the other room oops
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so, ooh, Red Entertainment asked a doozy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which place is more openly hostile to outsiders and those who don't conform to the, quote, norm?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alabama or Utah?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never been to Utah.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are fairly nice in Alabama unless you just say they're very, like, people try, they tend to be nice unless they're just super backwards rednecks, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't tell you about Utah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never been.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyone here been to Utah?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been through there, but I haven't really dealt with the people that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually there for a day and a half, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Couldn't really tell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think everyone's got their bad places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it just depends on who you run into.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, don't go, like, wearing a I voted for Perot shirt in, you know, Alabama or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or I miss Bill Clinton.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Last comes from DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we resurrect Name That Tune now that we have time, that is?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not until Rob gets back anyway, because then Rob can do all that for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, we're a little lazy right now, and we're just sort of leaning back and... Ooh, chit-chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: People, send me more questions, damn it!
[SPEAKER_10]: Comment from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: See if we can figure out what a game is from a description.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you ever play the Odyssey 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: No
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do not have a TV that it will run on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's that old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it have Venture as one of the games on it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it had Venture, but it had this... Oh, that was ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had Casey's Crazy Chase and Casey Munchkin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy Chase was the clone of Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they got sued and had to bury all these copies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you have a copy of Casey Munchkin, it's kind of rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think I've got two copies now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I never played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say 85 or 86.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so then I was... If it was 85, I was 9 then.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, yeah, I would have been 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, my next-door neighbor had a ColecoVision.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we would play this racing game and Casey Crazy Chase and a game called CryptoQuip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where you put in a phrase and scramble them up and you had to guess what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was really good at those word scrambles.
[SPEAKER_03]: but there was another game where you could play as a warrior or a mage or some other person and then a changeling which you could turn into invisible and go through and it was like this you had to get from one side to the other and get the treasure and then it was this weird bizarre game I'm trying to remember the name of it so this is what kind of what I was asking is there's a lot of good games that I used to play and I just can't remember the names of them anymore it's been so long
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the first RPG that you really invested in and finished?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like you saw the ending and you had 30 hours logged or however long it took.
[SPEAKER_10]: First RPG.
[SPEAKER_10]: Video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would almost say Final Fantasy except I really lost interest.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to go with... I know it was on the Nintendo and I'm trying to remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't StarTropics.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was...
[SPEAKER_03]: and I can't really put Zelda in it too because Zelda was more well yeah let's eliminate Zelda from this because that's more adventure maybe it was StarTropics it's been a long time is StarTropics or Faxana do or something like that so mine was Dragon Warrior 1 and then Final Fantasy 1 shortly after that on the NES so
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, mine was Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, for the most part, I was actually watching my friend play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He actually got a, I don't know if he called up Sega or something, they sent him a cheat sheet to walk through the game so that we could figure out how to get through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was a really fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what's kind of funny about that game is that when I play, because it kind of scrolls kind of with six frames between the thing, between when you're in the dungeon phase, that when you play like Shining in the Darkness on Genesis, it only does a three frame thing, so it looks kind of, going between those two is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a question from Ake Ripper.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's what the next Sims expansion is going to be about?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not counting Light Knight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't they doing like a Cars one?
[SPEAKER_10]: For Sims 4?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Sims 3, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think your mic cut out again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, how about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: There it goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't really exactly remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that they were doing like a vehicle-related one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can find out, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never really got into The Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember I tried Sims 1 a year or two after it was out and it had already become a worldwide phenomenon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I fussed with it for a couple hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never figured it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing on here is just late night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing really after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least it's listed anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey dude, nightclubs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be so cool if you can have gay dancing in The Sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I wonder what they're going to call beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They call wine nectar.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should just be wine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they should have beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they need to have hard booze.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should build a moonshine still in your bathroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like in Dukes of Hazzard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sims 2 has so much fan-made content from the 14 whatever expansion packs that came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure you can do that stuff in Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Sims 3 has a lot of that stuff too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people making game mods and everything and EA knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's like, okay, well you get to reinstall all of your stuff again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, okay, Red Entertainment also asks, I'm thinking of building a general media library in my house once I buy one.
[SPEAKER_03]: How large is the room your vault is in?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a small bedroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like 7x7 or something in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's big enough for a bed and a dresser and, you know, bedside table.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd probably put like a... I think a queen-size bed would fit in there, but... We used to have the futon in there, and it took up most of the room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, not a whole lot of... But there's lots of shelves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things are up to the ceiling.
[SPEAKER_03]: We put in a really big two shelf unit that our friend gave us that has a lot of space on it and then we have utility shelves in the closet and a number of bookshelves up on the walls too.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've maximized our space saving options and I totally recommend investing in bins with lids that you can see through.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, no one's sending us any more questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that a Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, the first thing he says when he comes in is bastard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is just like Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back, Rob!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm coming to cook!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't want Rob to burn my house down.
[SPEAKER_10]: He never cooks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: He made toast once.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went to... When he and Loki had the place, I went and made lobster kebabs for Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna go cook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we playing chair roulette?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where am I sitting?
[SPEAKER_08]: You should go sit in Jeremy's chair.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, I'm back everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a good trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did I miss any good questions?
[SPEAKER_08]: What were questions that were asked?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, like, what was the first game you played?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just thought they timed me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Goldanthro says it took Rob about 19 minutes and 43 seconds.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't find the place either.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to drive, because I knew it was at...
[SPEAKER_08]: such and such street in I-80 and I was like okay well there's a lot of shops around there so I was kind of like looking around I'm like do I go I know of this and yeah I had to drive around a little bit so I would have gotten back in like 14 minutes if I hadn't you know gotten lost that's all right okay sorry the game yes the questions I missed good stuff any good ones
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, yeah, first game played, and then I think I asked them what the first real RPG that you played from start to finish was.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first game played?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, like, I think ours was like Pac-Man, Combat Outlaws.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, oh, like the first game I remember playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I have memories of playing Spider-Man on the 2600, but I don't think that was the very first game I ever played.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably Pac-Man on the 2600, that really awful, like, bong, bong, bong, boo-doo-doo-doo, like the old school noises in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you hit a ghost, I can't get my voice to go that high, but the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you read the drama about why that happened?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, when you read about the whole drama behind it, it actually makes a lot of sense why that game turned out the way it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: They would not let him produce it on the cartridge he needed.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's why Ms.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pac-Man was so much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everything about the epic video game industry bust of 84 and all of the shovelware they were putting out, Pac-Man was related to that because Pac-Man was a national phenomenon and they finally got the home version.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the ugliest thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was ugly as fuck, it really was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did that game even have fruit in it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It had the wafer in the middle.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And he still defends that it was not as terrible of a game as everybody says it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just had a couple key design problems with it that really prevented it from being... Yeah, it's hard to understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably hard for some people to figure out what you had to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took me a while to figure out what you had to do to finish it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really does.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not an easy game to figure out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it wasn't intuitive at all, but I remember beating it and getting him onto the ship.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I think every time you do it, doesn't it get harder and harder?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it probably does.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, when you're seven, it's hard to have really discerning taste.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's usually the way the Atari 2600 games work.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the same thing over, but it gets harder.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and then the other one was about RPGs.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you asked a question about RPGs.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the question that I added was not including Zelda, because I think everyone our age has played Zelda and that's more adventure, but just RPG, Earthbound, StarTropics, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the first one you invested in and finished where you saw the ending?
[SPEAKER_10]: That I actually finished or that I played?
[SPEAKER_10]: That you finished.
[SPEAKER_08]: Adventure on the 2600?
[SPEAKER_08]: I never beat Final Fantasy Does it have liquor in it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll try it They can't hear you It's brandy and apple juice
[SPEAKER_08]: That is pretty fucking good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I thought this was for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, poor Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: The look on her face... I'm sorry, the look on her face was of such defeat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, this cross between, oh, you bitch, and, oh, you bitch!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll try what that is, the apple pie thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to try a sip of this?
[SPEAKER_08]: See if you like it?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'll like it, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: What question were we on?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Rama, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just won my heart in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not like actually, but it's the first NES game I played was The Goonies 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game was so underrated for its time because it was so hard.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was so complicated, but that game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I beat that game with the help of the Nintendo tip line where it was like what five bucks a call and what 86 87 and I had to basically cry to my grandmother please let me call you've called that number like four times this month all for the same game and I was like please like
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't have to give me a Christmas present if you let me call the Nest line because that was the shit back then.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd never call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: My mom was like, no, no, no, go to your room.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: She wouldn't budge at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could be like, I have an uncurable disease and the only people that could cure it is Nintendo Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to enter the Konami code to cure cancer and I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's like, do they charge?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to your room.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that would be her response, essentially.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Alan's trying to... We're getting boozed up right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which isn't smart, because I have to drive home in four hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I could sleep here, but... Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: We might go long.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got energy.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was actually sort of thinking that maybe it could have used another shot of Brandy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to get too screwed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Alan gets more and you don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where were we?
[SPEAKER_08]: Goonies 2, Nintendo Tip Line, It Was The Shit, etc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the first game you played in roller skates?
[SPEAKER_08]: The first game I played in... Oh, I never answered the RPG one.
[SPEAKER_08]: The RPG... That's not Zelda.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zelda.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Warrior Dragon Warrior
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Warrior Final Fantasy 1
[SPEAKER_10]: EarthBound was actually Mother 2 in Japan Mother 1 was on the NES
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um, yeah, Mother 2 was on the Super Nintendo, then Mother 3 didn't come out until, like, just recently, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we need to play chair roulette again?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: No?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you're baking.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're baking.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm gonna get baked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, um, yeah, I figured I may as well stay up, because it's got five more minutes left on it, and I'll just harass Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: What pizza did you make first?
[SPEAKER_03]: The pepperoni.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dang, bless your heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I figured most of y'all are going to eat the pepperoni.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can cook my chicken one next.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the veggie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have a piece of the chicken one, I guess, if the pepperoni goes real fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and then you started to ask, what was the first game I played in roller skates?
[SPEAKER_08]: The local roller rink near us had Spy Hunter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was a stand-up cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was the kind where you actually had the drive pedal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I would use the roller skates and the drive pedal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say it was probably that or air hockey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good old Roller King.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still there out in Roseville.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's right by where I grew up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gitan says his first was Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_08]: When's Dan going to be on the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is Dan going to come be on OLR?
[SPEAKER_08]: The game that should not be named Alright Is that it for Ask Orange Launch?
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone asked if we could play Name That Tune And then I think Jamie was like Dark Destiny has been begging me for that all week I didn't really set it up in advance I'm sorry And I don't even remember how the rules to that go I mean I could see Yeah, we want to do match game and list list But I have to set those up too So we'll play with that later
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about when I change out the pizzas, we can do the rest of the questions that are on our list for discussion topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, I'll tell you what, since really the rest of it was on there for you and Alan.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about you guys go ahead and do your thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there were a couple news stories, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we want to cover those?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one about Telltale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't we just do those after I'm done with pizza?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like we don't have all night, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Alan and I wanted to do our own classic games of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I want to let Bradley do one of these too, but I didn't know he was going to be here tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Alan and I are doing our own classic games of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're taking over this segment because, you know, we wanted to have a longer show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're kind of jealous that DarkSakura always gets this segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, don't you get jealous of her?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, don't you want to be just like her?
[SPEAKER_08]: So we have our own little Classic Game of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Breakman's asking, when are they going to play Truth or Dare?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to have to get me drunk or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our own Classic Games of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, you want to start first?
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you pick as your classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to take a minute to re-familiarize myself with the Wikipedia article on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So can you go first?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you asked so kindly, I will go first.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my classic game of the week... Okay, the music to this sucks, but deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I have picked a game that was on the PC a while ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you're going to hear this awesome ad-lib noise in the background because it used the ad-lib card to make noise.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a game called Lexi Cross.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lexi Cross was like, there's like no music.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just has the ambient noise to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lexi Cross was like a futuristic game show that was on the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me actually fast forward as an actual gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're just going to hear that noise like a million times because that was most of the music in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: but basically what would happen is it was a two player futuristic game show and on each side of the board you would have all these monitors or tiles that you would have your little robot Vanna White that you moved around the screen and she could reveal the tiles but if you hit a blank square your turn would be over but if you hit a silver square that was part of the crossword puzzle then you could keep going so it was like this entire crossword puzzle was hidden underneath
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And at the end of the day, you could spin the wheel was another option.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you feel you've revealed enough tiles on the board, you could spin the wheel for money and it kind of worked like Wheel of Fortune.
[SPEAKER_08]: And once you revealed all the letters on the board, they would all kind of add up to what the answer was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like all the words in the crossword had something to do with the, like if I fast forward way ahead in this video here, where they actually start spinning for letters if they ever do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this guy probably runs out of time at some point, but he's spinning the wheel here.
[SPEAKER_08]: At some point, so many letters will be revealed that they'll all have something in common.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like maybe they're all places in Hawaii, or they're all quotes from Shakespeare or something, characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's kind of what you have to figure out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's a cool little old school game show.
[SPEAKER_08]: and is um I don't know if you can even download that like on good old games or anything like that like I doubt it's available anywhere like that but um it's still out there on probably abandonware sites and good stuff like that but there was copy protection in the manual it actually came with a little tv guide parody that actually was the copy protection you had to know like what was on page seven you remember old school copy protection on pc games like
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I remember playing Leisure Suit Larry at my friend's house and also King's Quest, having to dig through the manual to find the right word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, you know what it was?
[SPEAKER_08]: The copy protection was like, what is on channel such and such at 7 o'clock?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's what was in the TV guide.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like a programming list.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm reading the Wikipedia article on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It came out in 1991.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was by Interplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interplay made some other awesome old school PC games in the early 90s and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they finally shut down in 2000.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did they make?
[SPEAKER_08]: They made...
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they make MDK?
[SPEAKER_08]: They made that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They made Bard's Tale.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're the guys that made Bard's Tale.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Descent was also them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they had a lot of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they say it's a combination of Wheel of Fortune, Scrabble, and Battleship.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's a pretty good combination.
[SPEAKER_08]: The words eventually comprise a theme or a quotation which the player must guess to win the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: so that's it, a game show, go figure I picked a game show as my little classic game of the week but Lexi Cross, definitely an underlooked classic
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Alan, you all ready?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Clay Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Tetsuya reminds us in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interplay did make Clay Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's play the music one more time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like this so much, I want to do the classic game all over again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, what is your classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for those of us who grew up playing Sierra online games, whether it be Space Quest, King's Quest, or Police Quest, often came across one of their lesser talked about series, the Quest for Glory.
[SPEAKER_10]: franchise and my pick is Quest for Glory 2 Trial by Fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Came out in November of 1990.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, this guy's talking through his thing here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I gotta try to find some gameplay of this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if there's anything where the guy's not talking.
[SPEAKER_10]: You found the one earlier that had the opening.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, he was talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't listen to the... Let me see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let's look at the introduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, we didn't hear this earlier, did we?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to hear this jerk talk over the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Quest for Glory 1 had a traditional medieval English theme to it, and at the end of the game, after the closing credits, your friend comes by on a flying carpet, and it's sort of a cliffhanger ending, and he swoops the hero up on his flying carpet, and they fly away.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when they land in Quest for Glory 2, they are in Shapir, which is sort of a Persian, you know, 1001 Arabian Nights styled game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is out of King's Quest and Space Quest.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's more traditionally an RPG.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those games are mostly about their puzzle solving and the narrative.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Quest for Glory actually had classes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could be a thief, mage, or warrior.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did play this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, it was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, this game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It didn't trigger until you said that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, I remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you could be the different classes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you could import your save file from part one so you could keep the same character name and stats that you had at the end of the first one, which was a big deal at the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a puzzle towards the end of the game where you had to knock over these candles because if the candles got lit, this evil ritual would complete.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you were a mage, you'd cast a magic missile, or if you were a thief, you would throw your knives.
[SPEAKER_10]: So whatever class you were sort of affected how you solved the puzzles.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about an evil vizier who wanted to raise a genie, the genie Iblis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: and the game took place over the course of 30 days in game time so if you couldn't figure out how to pop how to solve a puzzle for a certain day and your character was tired you would go to the inn and type sleep and go to sleep you'd wake up and then you you had to go out on a fresh clock it'd be 7 a.m and you'd go out and you'd try to solve the puzzles again
[SPEAKER_10]: and you had to wrap up the game within 30 days of game time and the big deal about this game is that if you were super polite and you did all of the optional side quests at the end once you beat the game you would discover that you would unlock the paladin career path
[SPEAKER_10]: and when you saved your game file and loaded it into quest for glory 3 you would be a paladin and that you could unlock that depending on it didn't matter if you were a thief or really important interruption you'll eat veggie right yes okay they're all getting their pizza while i talk about this game um
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, Quest for Glory came along pretty late in the EGA text-based adventure game era of Sierra.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only the first two had EGA graphics and were completely text-driven, as far as entering the commands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quest for Glory 3, which had a more African...
[SPEAKER_10]: slash Mayan setting to it was had by then adapted to VGA graphics and the mouse cursor where you click on look or touch and then that's how you interacted with the puzzles.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I played this game all through 8th grade and freshman year of high school.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it is super awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's one of the few franchises that people often overlook when talking about the glory of Sierra Online's reign.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true, because most people remember Leisure Suit Larry and King's Quest, especially the fourth one.
[SPEAKER_08]: But usually this one gets overlooked.
[SPEAKER_08]: That and Space Quest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: so yeah the fact that you could start with Quest for Glory 1 and use the same save file the same character sheet all through Quest for Glory 5 which I owned but I never played because it was very Quest for Glory 5 came out in I think the mid 90s late 90s when adventure games were dead no one cared no one was doing them anymore so it was very buggy and broken and I never really finished it but this one out of the original classics part 2 is definitely the best
[SPEAKER_08]: What was it about 2 that made you love it the most?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just the music, the atmosphere.
[SPEAKER_10]: It basically took everything that was in 1 and just made it better, like a sequel should.
[SPEAKER_08]: Derek H and Chad asked a good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened to Roberta Williams?
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't she kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: She wasn't happy with the way the gaming culture was going, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: She wasn't a fan of consoles, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last thing that she really consulted on, I want to say, was Quest for Glory 8, which had this guy in it that wasn't from the...
[SPEAKER_10]: and Daventry and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was very ugly, clunky 3D adventure game with real-time combat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: King's Quest Mask of Eternity.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the last thing that she sort of consulted on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But after that, I think Sierra went bankrupt because adventure gaming was over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real quick, I'm looking at a Wikipedia article on her.
[SPEAKER_08]: She also made Phantasmagoria.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, it was also towards the end of her run.
[SPEAKER_10]: Across seven discs when it came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: She retired in 1998, and she's kind of stayed away from the public eye.
[SPEAKER_08]: She really doesn't want to give interviews ever to talk about it, but she did talk about it in 2006, and she said that her favorite game that she ever created was Phantasmagoria, not King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: She said,
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to say, before I go out and check on the pizza again, Fantasma Gloria was amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: The end.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So many epic FMVs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roberta Williams also went on to say that she said that her games are explicitly targeted towards a more affluent and educated audience.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it actually made people kind of criticize her that she was kind of an elitist.
[SPEAKER_08]: But she did sum up her feelings in 99 with an interview on Gamers Depot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_08]: Back then, the demographics of people who were into computer games was totally different, in my opinion, than they are today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back then, computers were more expensive, which made them more exclusive to people who were maybe at a certain income level or education level.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the people who played computer games 15 years ago were that type of person.
[SPEAKER_08]: They probably didn't watch television as much, and the instant gratification era hadn't quite grown the way it has lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think in the last five or six years, the demographics have really changed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, this is my opinion, because computers are less expensive, so more people can afford them.
[SPEAKER_08]: More average people now feel they should own one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well, back in 1987, 88, 89, if you had a computer with EGA graphics, a 20 meg hard drive with 512k RAM, that was like four or five grand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, you were loaded if you had a...
[SPEAKER_10]: IBM Desktop with Color back then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, you had to be really well off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to say our first Packard Bell was like a 386SX16 or something and it was like a $2,000 computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was very expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, also Roberta Williams said in a 2006 interview that designing computer games is in the past for her now but she does want to write a historical novel someday.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was on the cover of Soft Porn Adventure by Online Systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's actually on the cover.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I almost chose Leisure Suit Larry 3 for my pick because aside from the whole EGA boobies, it's an incredibly difficult and fun adventure game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: also her last game she's credited with is King's Quest Mask of Eternity in 98 which I'm assuming is King's Quest 8 which was the last official King's Quest game I wonder what capacity she worked on that game because that was three years after Phantasmagoria in 95 and she didn't do anything in Phantasmagoria 2 so there you go
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was kind of a nice little derivative there to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we'll go ahead and kind of take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll give us a chance to eat here and get the other pizza done, and we're going to just play a little bit of music, save this part of the show we have done so far.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take a quick break, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we come back, we'll do more of your questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do more calls, too, and a couple more stories for you guys as well when we come back with the Orange Lounge Radio Marathon live here at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be right back.