This week we again learned that video gamers are more likely to have better decision making skills and that gaming enhances brain function.
Like physically, verbally, and plenty of other forms of working out that you can see, mental exercise exists too.
Exercising the ability to take in multiple sources of information and use or react to them when needed is a beneficial trait of human function.
This is just one story in tonight's news. Now it's time for your hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Sommers, and Loki to tell you more about this and the rest of the week's gaming news.
Starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
Today's show is Orange Lounge Radio and we are live once again with episode number 924 of our show for tonight, July the 31st, 2022.
It's not quite August, but almost. Hi, I'm Rob Roberts and joining me to talk about video games, gaming culture, all that good stuff are my co-hosts.
Say hello first off to DarkSakura or Jamie Sommers.
Hi.
Hi. I like your shirt by the way today that you're wearing as we are taping live at Vogue Network. Yeah, tacos are my favorite emotion. That's great.
Yes.
Perfect.
One of my most comfortable shirts at that. I believe in comfort today.
Can you quickly, since this is a food show in addition to video games, can you quickly describe the perfect taco?
Del Taco chicken soft tacos.
Okay. You know what the perfect taco for me is?
Hmm.
The Choco Taco and that's why they got rid of it because I liked it.
No, they actually put out an official statement about it.
Oh, did they?
Yeah, it was something about like being able to preserve a legacy stock of it or something.
I don't know.
That's dumb.
Release the Choco Tacos.
Let's avoid the ableist terms.
But it was some article that I just like half glanced at it on Twitter.
Mm hmm.
All right.
Also say hello to Techmaster Loki.
Hello.
Hi, Loki.
How are you?
I am fine.
Okay.
So you do always have a little video of a game playing behind you because we do tape live every Sunday night at nine o'clock Eastern, six o'clock Pacific at the Voice Geeks Network, twitch.tv slash Vogue Network, VOG Network.
We're right after the Bobby Black Wolf show, except not tonight.
Bobby wasn't on tonight.
He had the week off due to family obligations.
So his 17th birthday episode got to last an extra week on his podcast feed.
But we're here tonight and watching Loki having some.
Is that stunt driving or hard drive and playing behind you?
It's one of the Atari racing games.
It's neither.
Well, it's Broderbund and it's stunts is the game.
Oh, okay.
So, okay.
But to be fair, that was like their rip off of better rendered.
Yeah, it was it was their their rip off of stunt driving.
Because, you know, just like when a game is popular, like a lot of clones are made of it.
That was no different in the late 90s with like stunt driving and how huge that game was.
You mean that game was popular?
Oh, yeah.
In arcades and stuff.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
That game was hugely popular.
I had never saw anyone playing it.
Well, yeah.
And again, we also had one at my arcade when I was actually working there and it was the nap machine.
Now, it was dark.
It was dark.
Well, you also have to remember that that game like they tried to port that game to the Super Nintendo.
And I mean, tried.
Like, yeah, it was gold star.
You tried energy like.
No, I know.
But I just never remembered that game getting a lot of play when it was new when I was going to arcades.
It might have also been one of those things where like maybe it was remembered a little bit more for its tech and how it pushed the boundaries that it did maybe its popularity.
But I think I think maybe it was popular just in certain places or circles or what have you.
But people like people love the idea of driving a loop to loop.
That was the first game, first popular game.
I'm sure it wasn't the very first game to drive a loop to loop.
But it was the first one, you know, that you had to run into the way to do it without crashing.
Yeah.
And that game was hard.
So this game is hard, too, but it's cool because it has a track editor.
I used to play this as a kid a long time ago, as you could tell by the graphics.
One of the fun things to do with that is to put a bunch of 45 degree ramps.
I think I don't remember if it was like a bridge or if there's something that had to do with 45 degree ramps and you would put a bunch of those in a big old line and it would basically boost your speed up infinitely.
You could go like a thousand miles an hour or something like that.
OK.
You know what I'm realizing now that I'm seeing more than just the driving parts of the game, then seeing like the UI and the fake profiles of the people and stuff.
I had this game on PC like years on my first like PC.
I had this game for sure.
That's funny.
Yeah, it was fun.
I don't think I ever played the actual racing part.
I just like building done tracks.
And that's so you, though.
That's so you.
You always love to mod and build.
And that's why, like, even though I know you're kind of like, oh, I did Minecraft again this week.
It doesn't really surprise me because that game kind of calls to that crowd who want to build and mod and do all that.
That's what Minecraft is.
So it doesn't doesn't really surprise me.
You've you've surprised me.
Took you there.
Took you so long.
There it is right there.
So there's the jump right there.
So it's a it's an open bridge.
That was the one that that you put a bunch of them in a row and then it would chain it.
And then also they had the pipe.
Yeah, I remember that.
I go up on the walls.
Yeah, that's fun.
Yeah.
OK, that's funny.
Well, hello as well to our chat, because as I mentioned, we do tape live on Sunday nights at Vogue Network on Twitch and some folks talking about hard drive in and stunt drive in and that stuff.
So dark to you says there was a prototype of an NES version of hard drive in.
Oh, God, unless they remade it as a 2D game, it must have been terrible.
Like like Rad Racer was what we had as far as like 3D, I guess.
I mean, Rad Racer was kind of cool.
And I don't mean the literal 3D thing they were trying with the glasses, but like that, you know, first person type of thing they were doing.
Yeah, I don't know.
But then I guess I guess we think about it like first person racing games are as old as gaming in many ways, because like pole position goes how far back.
And that was essentially first person.
I mean, it was, you know, over the car.
But still, still those games go way back.
S.G. 100 Matt says, I was a fan of it in the arcade.
It was hard, but it was neat for its time.
And I think that it was it was the novelty of the bridge hopping and the the you know, because remember right around that same time with the bridge hopping, what was the huge movie Speed where they actually did that with the bus or Spice World where they also did that when the bus.
So people, you know, that hopping bridges was huge in the 90s.
Don't try this at home.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
S.G. 100 Matt reminds me of this other thing about those games is that I liked the gimmick of that.
In order to start the game, you had to turn a legit car key.
That's right.
That was a thing that was on those games.
But like I also remember like Spy Hunter had like all the buttons and the different mechanisms and things.
So, you know, kind of having that very immersive sort of setup goes way back with games.
So that's that's awesome.
All right.
Nice trip down memory lane.
Love it.
I know we're going to talk about more classic games in just a little bit because Dark Sakura, I'm sure has something to say about them.
I'm not just talking about her segment, but we'll come back to that.
Let's start off tonight with our kickoff topic, which is about TikTok.
We couldn't swing the pendulum harder.
We've gone from classic games to games on a service that because I'm over the age of 40, maybe I don't understand as much as other people.
I don't know.
But then again, I joke.
Dark Sakura, you post content on it.
I I watch it, but I I don't know how to find good content.
I get linked to good content all the time.
I don't really know how to find it.
You actually post content on TikTok, right, Jamie?
I do.
And I meant to post some stuff from yesterday, but the Internet was kind of crap.
Yeah.
So I didn't.
That I was too busy playing games and being in pain.
Oh, well, we'll talk.
Mind is young.
Body is not.
We'll talk more about that in a minute.
But so I think we've had some stories on previous episodes of OLR that talked about that TikTok is trying to get into more gaming.
And this isn't the first time that we've seen social media because we know Facebook has tried to get into gaming.
Hell, Google Plus.
Remember that that was Google getting into some of that gaming and they had their own unique approach to it and so forth.
You know, getting games involved in social media is not a new concept.
So the fact that TikTok is trying to get into it shouldn't be that surprising.
But something with the volume of TikTok and because, you know, again, even though we joke that we're all over 40 and we barely use it, the reality is the younger crowd, you know, teens, early 20s and, you know, kind of all the in-betweens really use TikTok like a lot.
So getting games under the service is not incredibly surprising.
What's a little newer this week is that the testing is getting more broad and we're actually seeing what some of these games look like.
So in a spokesperson for TikTok in an interview at TechCrunch said, currently, we're exploring bringing HTML5 games to TikTok through integrations with third-party game developers and studios.
One of the games that they're testing is from a company called Aim Lab, and the game they're making is called Mr. Aim Lab's Nightmare.
Except now here's the thing that I'll show for those that are watching live on Twitch, I'll show like a little clip of this.
So they actually have like a TikTok that they posted.
Finally beat this boss in the TikTok game.
You can actually hear, sorry, the volume came through a little loud.
But let me flip over to the other screen for those that are watching live on Twitch so you can see what this actually looks like here.
And it let me rewind it.
It actually it looks like a cheap honestly, like a cheap little flash game to me.
Like it looks like you're like tapping and describe me for the podcast, folks, you're tapping all these little objects that are flying out at the screen in order to beat some boss.
So the quality of the game looks a little bit, I don't know.
And again, because I'm watching on the website, it says click below to play and there actually is no place to actually play.
And I notice it's actually posted, this particular video is posted by the creators of the game.
But just gives you a little bit of a sense of what, you know, those games look like.
So they're I don't know if they're not very high quality, but it's short.
It's, you know, just like TikTok videos are short attention span sort of things, right?
And it's a start.
Yeah, so aim aim lab.
It's a it's a software game, if you will, to like train your it's supposed to make you like better FPS games by training your aim, I guess.
Oh, interesting.
So that's what they're doing.
IOS games up there, too.
It looks like.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'm sure I'm sure it would be pretty easy if something was already built with mobile devices in mind.
It might be pretty easy to port that over to TikTok.
So anyway, and that's just one example of a game.
You know, and again, we've talked about in the past that TikTok was kind of moving the chess pieces around.
ByteDance, parent company, bought Moonton Technology last year.
TikTok had a partnership with Zynga for a game called Disco Loco 3D and a charity game I'm unaware of called Garden of Good.
It's kind of cute.
And I guess that is actually available on U.S. TikTok.
That charity or excuse me, the Garden of Good.
And then HTML5 games have previously been tested in Vietnam, which is not uncommon for these large mobile developers to test things in maybe one country, one or two countries before they roll it out into the world.
Again, this is TikTok getting behind Apple, Google, Netflix, you know, all these other folks that are in the space to move into TikTok gaming.
So my question is for the group and for the chat, do you think this is a big deal?
Because here's the thing, I feel like these other forays by social media specifically, I think Apple, Google, that's a different category because, you know, I don't think you can compare this to like, I don't know, Apple Arcade or Stadia.
It's not the same thing.
Those other things I named are not trying to embed themselves within social media.
So when I talk about things that are embedding themselves in social media, I think about like Facebook playing the games there live on Facebook.
That never really took off for anybody.
I'm not sure this is really going to do that as well, but I'm not sure.
What do you all think?
Depends like how they're going to implement this.
So like if they just put like, we're putting games on our platform as well.
That's kind of boring, because like, if you're talking about targeting audience that uses TikTok, most of those users are probably accessing it through their mobile app.
And there's so many app stores and things that are inundating them with games that they could really play.
That doesn't really seem like that's worthwhile.
Now, what I see like a better way to do it, which means it's probably not the way they're going to do it.
But let's just say that they could do it in the sense that with TikTok, you can record video and edit and do like some small stuff with that.
But maybe with these games, you can record gameplay and then do commentary and stuff over that.
And then you can make little clips with the game as well.
That would be a meaningful use of it.
This will just be some garbage that they try to shove ads in microtransactions down our throats with.
Yes, I know they're not in it yet.
Yet is the operative term.
So I don't I don't anticipate that they'll do anything meaningful with it.
Jamie, do you have thoughts?
I think it's going to be a big, big thing.
I mean, yeah, it's a way to maybe even I think they're going to do it more with ad revenue built into the games or something like that.
But I mean, I think sites are always like any kind of social media platform is going to look for increasing engagement.
And I think that this is just their attempt.
They think they put a fun game up there, whether or not they're going to make money on any kind of revenue or anything with it.
It's something that builds engagement and something that keeps people wanting to go back and and, oh, I can do this while I'm browsing on here.
Fun, you know, that type of thing.
And so I think in that respect, I mean, it's a wait and see.
We don't really know enough about it anyway.
So no, but I think I think you're right.
It's like even if the games are not a super high quality, it's keeping the eyes on TikTok longer.
And that's one place that like TikTok kind of can pride itself right now.
I'm almost positive.
I saw some type of report that said I don't know if it was people of a certain age or all people, but like TikTok has more viewing hours right now than YouTube.
And that's kind of a big that might only be in one age group.
I'm sorry, I don't have to study in front of me.
But, you know, the volume of TikTok is very large.
And, you know, yeah, it's kind of what you're saying.
If it's just like, oh, this game's just right on over here.
It's still keeping people in that TikTok bubble longer and away from the competitors, for sure.
That's really the goal.
You know, with any kind of social media site, they need something that's going to keep a person on their site.
And a lot of people, you know, especially for anything that may have some sort of ad embedded in it, a lot of us have trained our eyes just to ignore the ad.
You know, to sort of narrow down, but it still doesn't mean we're not seeing it and that it's not on the page and being exposed to people.
So, you know, I just I have this feeling that it's really just an engagement deal.
You know, I don't know that TikTok needs it, though.
I'm going to be perfectly honest.
It was it was just so funny.
I was when I was at the thing yesterday, I had there were people who were like, oh, yeah, I'm on Instagram and this.
And I'm like, are you on TikTok?
Oh, yeah, that, too.
I forget about my TikTok is what I hear a lot.
Then for the people that are on it, they are on it.
Yeah.
And it really like I'll be honest, I have a YouTube channel.
I think I've posted like a couple of things that weren't private.
My TikTok needs more attention, but I've been putting like my my, you know, stream clips and stuff on there, and I've found a lot more success with that.
Plus, it's easy just to make like a three minute video or a five minute video and post it up there as opposed to putting work into like a longer production.
That would be of an optimal length for YouTube.
And now YouTube is doing their shorts thing.
Which is supposed to, I reckon, be like the competitor with TikTok.
Yeah, but TikTok success comes in with the short attention span of people these days.
And I actually went in it went into studying some of this in in my design classes.
If you look at all right I'm actually I'll tell you this, look at an ad for a Mac.
Look at what they looked like in the 80s.
You had the picture, and this entire article written in Adobe Garamond Pro.
That was like this this and this and this and this and don't you feel this and blah blah blah it's like, you know, going to a recipe site.
Now it's item, price, thing.
And that's what our social media is turning into as well that's why people, you know, are more on Twitter, and more on TikTok.
They are smaller more digestible and built for the, the current attention span.
And so why not have games on there, especially if they're a little clicky clicky games that require a short attention span and don't require you to become you know invested in it or something.
Let me get some comments from chat over twitch.tv slash vog network Tiger Claw says, none of that would have been possible if it wasn't for Snapchat, they did it first before Facebook, Instagram and now TikTok and YouTube doing it.
Well, let me, let me see.
Fine.
No, no one, no one here knows better.
We, no one knows better than o LR that just because you're first doesn't mean you're going to be the most popular.
And Snapchat was not the first to do it. No one knows that better than o LR nine and Periscope existed before Snapchat.
You know DJ Rama S brings up a good point. So does that mean TikTok has fixed their algorithms for LGBT and POC creators that I remember they were getting a lot of pushback, because of those algorithms has people have people just kind of forgotten that or did
TikTok ever address that I truly don't know.
There was a big, like, almost like a quote walkout. Hold on, let me double check and see if I can find anything.
Okay, why while you're digging for that, let me get to another couple comments. Okay. Let's see, as Joe and her map points out, remember when Twitter had a live video channel didn't really last long.
If TikTok wants to take a real step into gaming, then they have to take risks and stick things out and not give it three years and trash it.
You know, it's funny, there's so much video and photo content on Twitter, because the one social media I do use, and I think I've done well with is Twitter.
But otherwise, I'm like the people you're talking about DarkSakura, I go, Oh, yeah, I have a TikTok. I don't know how to make compelling content for it. I really don't. So and I can admit that so
You know what you need to do is put something vaguely controversial, or on the edge of taboo.
But I don't know if I want to, you know, like, is that really me? I don't want to force myself to be something I'm not. I mean, I do have hot takes. But you know, I don't know.
So by the way, the NPR did an article about this in February. This year, that's probably one of the more recent things I can find, but I don't find anything about it being updated.
I do know the thing about POC putting up, like dance videos, you know, making those I've created this dance to the song thing, and then the white girls stealing it and making it popular. You know, but
bring it on?
I was gonna say the only TikTok creator that does dance videos that I follow is Paula Abdul. I was gonna say she does some good ones.
It's just like everyday people who make the thing and it becomes really nice.
Deidre Omas does follow up his comments saying they addressed it, but to some content creators, it wasn't enough. My other issue with TikTok is how easily they can pull your data. Some companies have blocked TikTok on corporate devices.
Well, yeah, I mean, maybe here's my controversial hot take companies should be blocking TikTok. That website is a waste of time. That's literally its purpose is to waste time and adding games into the service is to help you waste more time.
So yeah, a company who doesn't block TikTok is not on the cutting edge of it. Like honestly, unless of course your business has a reason for being on TikTok. You are the social media person for your business. Okay, don't come at me with all the exceptions. But on a general level, companies should block TikTok.
They should put cookie clicker on TikTok. It'll create a black hole vacuum of unproductivity.
For the record, in TikTok's privacy policy, it does have a way that you can submit a request to delete collected information and also to submit requests through authorized agents to do it for you. So you can put in written requests to have your information not collected.
Interesting.
So there's also an opt out option for third party advertising. So that's on this other thing that I can, it's like a massive opt out service.
It's called like the NAI. And it's a full opt out service for digital advertising and data sales.
Um, my, I guess, like hot take on this whole thing with TikTok or whatever, I sort of look down the road at what this might turn into in a few years. And I think what it might be, you know, the quality of the games is not great now. But, you know, what's only getting bigger is cloud gaming.
And I think we've seen all of the other companies are starting to make their move really into cloud gaming, you know, whether it's Stadia, whether it's Amazon's Luna, whether it's Xbox, you know, and there's there's many others as well, right?
So there's there's so many companies that are getting into cloud gaming, like, how would it I mean, wouldn't it be cool if on TikTok, you're watching Oh, I don't know, a Dead by Daylight play going on, and then tap this button to jump into a Dead by Daylight match with me right now. Or you know, whatever it is, which ironically, was one of Stadia selling points, if I remember right, was the whole
Did that ever happen?
Did it Jamie? You're the Stadia expert. I don't know. Like you can stream your Stadia gameplay on YouTube, and somebody can jump in and join the game with you live.
Yeah, that's on there. I don't use it. Because I'm on Twitch. And as an affiliate, I can't I can't cross.
Right.
But yeah, um, hold on, I'll just open up my game right now. And I'll tell you what it says. Because there's a side panel.
Alright, so my Stadia thing is popping up.
Okay, so first thing looking for people to play with start a public party. So there's that where you can start a public party and anyone can join in whenever.
And I have open and full screen. And so on my side, I have
I have windowed mode, which I'm going to go into. Alright, so I've got, I've actually got some add ons through some Chrome extensions. But yeah, there are other things on here about
live stream you there's a live stream button at the bottom that says, you know, it'll stream it to YouTube. And then I have another one at the bottom that says parties. So you can have a live party and people can jump in and out through a queue. And yeah,
see, this is fascinating to me, because I feel like this is where everybody kind of wants to be and like Google's there. But I feel like this is horrifically underutilized because of the let's be honest, Jamie, I'm sorry to say this, because I know you're a fan, but the rather lukewarm reception stadia has been getting from the gaming masses and the gaming public, you know,
Google, it has been getting a lot better. Well, a lot better.
Well, but I don't think it made our show this week. But we had another one of those Google stadia is going to get the plug pulled rumors going around this week, which obviously was fake. But I don't know if it's that people don't trust Google. I think well, I do think that's been a part of it from the very beginning.
Yes, it was very beginning when they launched stadia. It doesn't matter how good it was, people said, Well, Google has a track record of shutting shit down too early. So I wonder how long this is going to last to so I get that this case
is under expansion. So they've just offered Portuguese support for Brazil, full Portuguese support, they have expanded more of their, their servers, they've brought in new games, they're in talks for more games. So they're they're expanding, they're just not doing the in house stuff.
Um, and you know, in speaking of some of the competitors as well, which live in a similar space to stadia, I'm really surprised that Luna being a part of Amazon with Twitch does not have that exact same feature. Like I, I'm kind of shocked that Twitch does not have the ability to click a button and join me in this game right now via Luna, the cloud streaming service that you have access to this game as Amazon Prime member, blah, blah, blah, whatever in their universe, I'm, I'm really shocked.
That's not a feature. Now, maybe because Luna is technically still a beta or whatever, maybe that's something they're going to pull the red carpet back on at TwitchCon or something. I don't know. But I'm just I'm really surprised. That's not a thing yet. And I'm sure it's a matter of time. And then of course, why did Microsoft get rid of their streaming service? That was dumb, because they could have, you know, incorporated the x cloud into that, but maybe they have another plan. I don't know.
Silly, silly.
Make sure that we avoid the ableist terms. Do you think I'm an ableist person? No, but it's still people talk about it. So I just want to be kind to all of our listeners.
If you personally are offended by what I'm doing, please send me an email. All right. SSJ100Matt says that's fair, but companies directions change. It seems like Google has spent a lot on stadia. I don't trust Google not to pull the plug. I just see a lot of trends with tech companies doing this and blaming it on the pandemic.
Hmm. Yeah, I mean, I again, I understand, like, I can acknowledge everything Jamie is saying is true. And the reality is, yeah, Google scaled back on column A, but they're expanding in column B. But I can also say, yeah, the skepticism from the tech culture as a whole is still runs rampant because of their track record. I get it. I get it.
Let's see. Tiger Claw says, you probably can side load it. You just need an APK. So all right. Anyway, back on the TikTok thing, though, I think that it's probably just a matter of time before TikTok probably incorporates cloud gaming into it one way or another and really amps the quality of this these games. But until we have, you know, we have a lot of people talking about it.
Devices that better bring games to our phones beyond just touch. I'm not sure that's going to be a reality. But then I guess Sony's got something in the works.
Just don't see the value in adding games. I get it. Like, it keeps people on the platform. But like, they're not really having trouble keeping people on the platform. I mean, that it's well known that if like, people are very much engaged with the content on TikTok, they'll spend hours there, my wife. So I know that it's just, I don't see the value add for adding games to it. Like, like, I can't see any users go, man, I really do, you know, check out TikTok. If it had games on it, I just don't see that.
And unless they're doing something notable with it, like saying, look, now you can make content involving these games as well. You know, that way, maybe that might appeal to a crowd of people that want to watch people play mobile games, I don't know. But like something to that effect, like, I just can't see the value add of adding games because literally everybody is adding games to their platforms. Facebook's added games, you know, Netflix is looking at games and stuff like nobody has more interest in those platforms.
Other games are being added. Like, I just think, read the room, TikTok. I don't know. I just want to see them do something, you know, notable with it, like actually involve the games in the content creation for your platform, that would be something unique, that would be a selling point for your platform. But if you're just like, well, add games now. Just another platform people have to develop for.
step it up with where they're at now this year. So this is interesting. All right. Anyway, I'm sure more to come on this. And we'll talk about it in future weeks. But let's get into our gaming weeks, the types of things that we've been playing this week. And Dark Sakura, I guess this probably is is your gaming week. But I know you got to play a lot of classic games at a pretty big convention here on the West Coast this weekend, right?
Yep. So I went to California extreme. And I have a sinus infection. I'm going to be perfectly honest. I, I wasn't 100%. And by the time it was done, I was even I was like at minus 20%. But I had a great time. And I got to see friends, I ran into Mel and Melody, and they're delightful little girl. And I saw Amanda.
And lots of friends. And but anyway, I was going to go through some of the games that I played because they had some interesting games. There are a lot of staples. But I had played a tiny Miss Pac Man. And I played Well, I was gonna play it and then I didn't. They had a beat mania 2d x beast over. Oh, didn't play it because
people were like, trying to jump in front of me. They had a dance rush. Oh, wow. Yeah, I actually watched someone play it who was pretty good and did some some fun freestyle on it. Zen monkey No, that's that's not happening. I don't know where you're getting any of that information from to talk is not going to be the next periscope. It's already proven that it's not.
Um, they had hold on, I'm trying to find the I took a picture of all the games that I played so that I would remember all the games that I would played. They had a Commodore 64 that I showed you.
Yeah, so in addition to having just like, you know, the old arcade cabinets and the pinball machines and new, I guess it's really not just old arcades. It's it's really a history because you know, the 2d x the dance rush. Those are new games. So there's that but they it's also kind of a little bit of a trade show where people have like classic games or I should say trade should be like swap meet or whatever you want to call it. Like a bunch of vendors will bring, you know, classic stuff to these shows. And I know Yeah, you texted me about the Commodore 64 you saw and I was like, I don't know, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I can't really spend money on stuff like that right now. But I thought it was cool. Like it's it's nice to see like, wow, that Pac Man disc still works. That's cool because I thought those things lost their magnetite magnetization after time.
Famicom. But they, there was cracking DJ, which I always suck at, of course, I played Mania three, the final. They had a game called dazzler, which I played just for the lulls. It's bad. Space Fury, which was one of my mother's favorite games in our clique of vision. I am not great at it. They had a return to Oz poster that I almost bought.
I don't know if it shows up, but they also somebody was also selling a board game called keeping it sexy. And it was Kenny G on the cover. I played Bosconian, which fun little game played in a while. I played Super Street Fighter two and got my ass handed to me. I played journey and got my ass handed to me. I played Strider and got my ass handed. I'm kidding. I actually did okay at Strider.
I played a tabletop Pac Man and did okay. And then I had booze. And then now this was cool. I don't know if anyone can see this on the camera, but they had a Famicom hooked up a Navy Famicom and had goonies in it. Not goonies, but goonies. Oh, wow. Yep. Another person was selling the the baseball team lions in Japan.
Edition Game Boy. I knew a friend who had the game cube that they put out for the hanching tigers. So those are those end up being pretty rare. They're like only sold in this one like baseball store, you know. And I'm trying to find I also met the person who has like the world's high score in a
puzzle wobble and puzzle wobble. Okay. I played the new Toy Story for pinball. Oh, yeah. I didn't even know there was one of those until I saw your husband posted a picture on Facebook. Yeah. Um, I got some pictures of that. I'll throw them up. I beat Vampire Savior. Funny enough, like I've only played like Queen Bee a couple of times. So just it was like a terrible monitor tube. I decided to play and I beat Vampire Savior. Yay.
Um, they had a prototype for Far Cry five paradise lost like a machine gunner game. Huh? And hold on, I'm actually trying to get to where Far Cry five. That sounds awesome. Oh, it let's see paradise loss. Maybe like a spark cry paradise. Far Cry five persimmon. There's a five behind it. It probably looks like a game released around the same time or something. Yeah, weird. Because yeah, that's
artwork for like the original Far Cry game. I thought it might have been actually that's not five. I think that was four. Whereas in the mountains and they had a guy that had like a it's just Far Cry instincts paradise lost. Okay, Far Cry instincts. Yeah, that's, that's, that's a spin off of the original game. So it was it was fun and you got points for headshots and you could blow shit up, which I liked. I love the original part doesn't love to blow shit up. Um, I
played a DJ max technica three. Um, okay, so gosh, this is gonna look absolutely terrible.
Yeah, which again, for our podcast, but she's showing video of somebody actually playing that dance rush game. And it just looks like fireworks exploding under somebody's feet. I as it should be. I played for never looked like that play my game. Um, I played,
computer space ball, which is a version of pong. It's a
SSG 100. Matt is asking about fun pins. We mentioned Toy Story four.
There's more I'm getting there.
Um, I played our type. I love our type bad at it. I played crazy auto. You know, crazy auto was it was a prototype room as Pac Man and they recreated it. Yeah, yeah. Um, I played a little
melody play tapper. I played timber. I played carnival. I saw a group called the tonberries. I played a Rob Zombie spook show for pinball. I know you had a pinball machine. Yeah, it's, it's, it's pretty neat one. I played
um, uh, tinkle Maury shooting, which is kind of, I guess, like the kind of like a point blankish kind of game. Um, I found a Neil, I bought some games, but I grabbed highlight instead of Final Fantasy two. But I have Final Fantasy three, I have
um, uh, Hattori Hanzo, I have transformers, mystery of convoy, and I got, uh, space panic for Coleco vision. And, um, I also bought the, uh, the, uh, mega ranger box set for super Sentai series.
Oh, wow. And I didn't pay a whole lot for it. I'm happy. I also got a, um, I think it's like a necklace kind of thing or a hangy thing, but it has a little rabbite on it from, uh, secret of mana.
Um, but now as for, um, the pinballs, cause there were, there were a lot of pinballs there. I pretty much didn't play anything that I own. Um, but I did play some, some rush. The one that I wanted to play and didn't get to, cause I was so busy was Godzilla.
Um, but, uh, I played some Deadpool played, uh, I, I know the other one I wanted to play was big bang bar. Cause you know, I love big bang bar. Um, and it was either down or in use. Um, I played bride of pin bot. They did not have a bride of pin bot 2.0. You know which one that is, right?
Yeah, it's the one you used to have, right?
Uh, we, we borrowed one. We didn't have, we, we owned, I don't know which tables are yours and which ones are, right. But you know, bride of pin bot, you know, with the eyes and everything. And it had the, just the, you know, standard, uh, clock type scoreboard.
Someone went in and did a mod for it that uses a color DMD and, uh, now, uh, the newer style, uh, rule sets.
Yeah. I remember. Yeah. I remember that machine you had in your house at one point. Yeah.
Yeah. But that it had like extra modes and everything and all kinds of neat music. It really brought bride of pin bot to the modern pinball age. Um, but, uh, they also had a legit cactus Canyon cause they finally, uh, finished and got those just distributed.
Um, but there were also like some other prototype games around, um, some fan games. Of course I have like a killer bee. Um, they had a cyber ball and I was like, so tempted to try to find someone to play it with me. Cause that also is like college vibes. Cause it was right next, it was on the same wall as my world cup soccer.
Um, there, there were, there was also like a middle slug five. There were the, um, there was, they didn't bring like the full scale Japanese, uh, candy cabs.
Um, like they had a few years ago, but they did have, um, like a couple of bullet hell games and they had, uh, um, like, uh, the Sega Tetris.
And the gigantic one, no, no, no, that that's, that's like the ticket spitter Tetris. They had like the Sega Tetris. Um, the, the ones that they do for tournament play now, um, they had like a sit down star Wars.
They had the star Trek, uh, simulator game. They had, um, I called it like my Coleco vision corner. Cause they had space fury and mousetrap and Gorf.
And a carnival, which is all stuff I enjoyed playing on a Coleco vision. Um, and they had that ambulance game, but right when I went to go play it, some guy just walked over and put his kid on it.
And I'm like, he's like, Oh, are you going to play this? You could play this game. It's like, no, I wanted to play this one.
And I had more choice things to say, but I didn't say them because there are certain things that children are too young to hear.
Um, Coleco's got, didn't we just hit like the 40th or 40, 40th anniversary Coleco? I think we did.
Um, but, um, I don't know. I, uh, I had such, such a, a pretty good time. I mean, I got super worn out. Um, Dan said that they did their Epic Warlords game.
Um, and I, I had my customary Amaretto sour and wandered around and talked to people, just random people and got very overstimulated and then went to go sit down and I kind of wish that I had other games on my phone that I felt like playing, but I was kind of gamed out a few moments, you know, here and there.
But I, I talked to some people, made some friends. Um, it was a lot of fun. It was, Oh, there was, uh, last year that we had it at somewhere else and it was a much smaller this year.
They were back to the same place, had the full ballroom. Dan went to a panel with the, the, the creator of Qbert.
That's cool. I didn't go to that one. I didn't know. Cause he didn't tell me until after he was done. Um, but they had the, the, uh, pinball tournament room. So they did the pinball tournament.
They had the console room, you know, with people playing rock band and singing and fun. And I may have been singing edge of glory from the, uh, from the vending area.
Nice. Um, cause the person that was singing it, she did okay. She just was a little off key. Um, and then there was this kid that gets up and starts, uh, like, I don't know, but he did like the death metal version of, um, Oh God.
Now what it was a David Lee Roth era, um, uh, Van Halen song. And now I can't remember what it was and it's not hot for teacher. Uh, no, it wasn't, it wasn't David Lee Roth. It was a Van Hagar era. He did a run around.
Okay.
But he did it like in this death metal voice. It was actually kind of metal though. Um, but yeah, I mean, it was just like, there's the fun experiences like that. They had the Tonberries playing.
They had, um, got some other band that I didn't stay for. Cause it was really loud in that small room.
It sounds like quite the collection of stuff this year. I'm, I'm sad I missed it, but between COVID and I have plans to go to the Bay area next week for a concert. I didn't really want to do two weeks in a row. So.
But you know, that other side room that they would have with more arcade games in it.
Yeah. It's been a while, but yeah.
It wasn't there. It was closed off.
Oh, so we, we had one less room of games, but it was still pretty fun. They had a lot of, um, two player table games. Like they had the joust table and, um, just a few other things.
They had a bunch of, uh, the, the tables laid out in the hallway too, just, you know, I guess some overflow and, oh, for a moment I thought Dan was sending me a correction note.
We now have an insulated garage.
Nice. I wish I had one of those.
Our game room is almost there. We're having our air conditioner for it installed on the 16th.
Oh, that's awesome.
So we're having the gaming garage and I'm tangenting, but this is important.
No, it's, it's the future of gaming at your house.
We have Dan put carpet tiles down that are gray and black in the shape of one of the space invader aliens.
Yeah. You mentioned that last week, but yeah, that's cool. Um, how was the attendance this year? I mean, cause it was kind of back to normal or back to pre pandemic, I guess, whatever you want to call it.
It was, it was busy and there were, there were a decent number of people masked and they were highly encouraging it.
Um, and the employees or the volunteers were masked, but there were a lot of people who were not.
Yeah.
Um, and I had some intervals, but just because, I mean, I do have asthma where I had to take my mask off just to, to catch my breath a little bit.
Um, I tried to do that more in open areas, you know, where it wasn't so thick and full of people.
But, um, I don't know if it's fatigue just from having been up all day. Cause you know, I do have that condition.
Um, but I'm feeling white today and had a sore throat. I did have a sore throat last night too, but I also have a sinus infection.
Well, if I'm going to test, take a test in the morning, it's the only way I know for sure. Nope, five days, three days from initial five days, five days, according to CDC, three days, according to CDC, but that's all right.
I just looked it up today.
Okay. Sorry. All right. Your, your health. All right. Um, let's say, and I just speaking from personal experience, it only took three days, but that's all right. What do I know? All right.
Uh, let's move on with our gaming weeks to talk about, uh, low, uh, low key. We'll go to you. How was your gaming week?
Uh, it's Minecraft. Yeah. I've been, uh, working on designing a, um, it's a robot repair shop. It's supposed to be like an old gas station converted over to repair robots. So it's got a bunch of like broken stuff out front. And I try to make, um, like kind of, I like a lot of the stuff that I build to have some sort of like, not necessarily effects, but like just like action movement to them.
So like stuff moves when you walk past when the robots, you hear it kind of like, um, break down a little bit or like one of the robots that's fallen flat on the ground, like the light in the back of it's flashing and stuff. So like stuff like that, um, try to incorporate in there, but it looks pretty cool so far.
So that'll be coming in a video here very soon. I'm just working on, uh, designing the interior for it. Cause it's supposed to be a shop, but yeah, lots of people have been, um, doing stuff on the server and it looks really nice. Very nice. Um, spawn town there. I was looking at my analytics earlier and we're up to 520 subscribers or 519, I think. So it's slowly moving along. Um, yeah. Yep. We'll get there.
Eventually years. So yeah, that's what I've been working on. Um, yeah, probably should play some other games. Uh, there's, uh, the, the nest maker bite off three is going on pretty soon here.
I have considered making something for it, but probably not. I don't think I can juggle both at the same time. That was my, um, that was kind of like why I wasn't doing like YouTube stuff like months ago is because of, uh, the nest maker stuff.
It's hard to do juggle both of like the limited schedule. So I probably won't do anything for that. I did have somewhat of an idea for something, but like, I don't know. I still want to go through, they put up new courses for the software. That's more, it's way more in depth than what they've done in the past. In the past, they've kind of, uh, gone with the angle of like, okay, you can kind of, you can drag drop stuff to make a game, but this is like, okay, yeah, you could do that. And you'll get something that kind of makes it easier.
Like we could kind of call a game, but like, if you really want to make a game, like you would just not even use any of the modules that we created and go like completely from scratch and just completely code the whole thing.
Um, that's the new course that they have now. So it's like a super advanced course, which is, which is good because you can do a lot of things that you can't normally do if you just use their, um, software for like all of the arrangement of everything. There's, you know, animations and stuff. I haven't even updated their software in months, so it probably offers a lot more now anyways. But yeah, I'm very curious to see what that is. And then of course, all the games are come out from that.
But yeah, the game I wanted to make or an idea for a game that I had would be based off of Hermitcraft season seven, they did a tango did a thing called decked out. It was a game that they played basically where you, you go into this like maze. It's not really amazing, like a bunch of different rooms, like a dungeon, if you will. And then there's these giant monsters called ravagers that are chasing you down.
And you have a compass that guides you to basically a treasure spot. So you it's randomized each time, and then you go and find the treasure and then you have to get out without dying. And then with that you get cards that provide different abilities. So there's like this noise meter that goes up called clank that as more clank is accumulated, you know, the danger gets greater. And so they have some that will like help you avoid getting that.
There's some that adds more treasure and a lot of different things. So that was the idea that was like, okay, cool, I can make a nest version of that. Then, you know, put that out, get like the Hermitcraft crowd interest in the channel, stuff like that, you know, that's way too much work. So I'm just gonna do what I'm doing now.
All right.
Hey, if it ain't, if it ain't fixed, don't break it.
It's just it's a lot of work for just something that like, some cat just people will casually look at. No one's not gonna be like, come check out everything. It'd just be like, hey, it's a neat thing.
You should do a behind the scenes video.
Of what?
Of what you do.
Sure. I could.
I mean, I think the behind the scenes stuff for for, you know, especially might inspire other content creators.
Yeah, there's a few groups that I've been like joining their discords for. So like, I just joined a discord for another group of content creators on a server called Nomadcraft. So they've started their third season, there's some of them I've followed from like other things that they've done. So I've been like giving advice in there because a lot of them, there's a few members that are just starting out. So they're all making the same mistakes I did before where like really horrible audio and stuff like like, you know, like where where they're talking very quietly and they
all of a sudden blasting the music and let's say okay, I can't listen. I can't watch your videos. They're unwatchable like that when your volume is just all over the place. So like I've been trying to offer advice like here's what you do to normalize all this because like, yeah, I wasn't that bad. But like I had some issues with audio because it wasn't the perfect, you know, environment to record in and
Just look at your waveform and see where the spikes are. Adjust the spikes.
Yeah, I get a lot of them. They're just getting started. Like, you know, they have less than 20 subscribers and stuff like that. So it's fine. I get it. You'll make mistakes. You'll learn from mistakes. You get better. So
I'll get into my gaming week, which was a lot of similar things. I played more Final Fantasy XIV, more Dead by Daylight, a little bit more No Man's Sky, finally started that expedition. You might remember last week we talked about a patch and I was like, it's kind of weird that they haven't started the new expedition yet, but they did. They did roll it out this week. Something that was interesting about the new expedition. It's the first time that you don't start on a planet and it has the normal intro sequence. So they actually have a little bit more of a
They changed the intro to a female narration voiceover, which is cool. And it was like a different voice and you start on a freighter as opposed to on a planet. And the theme of the expedition is definitely about freighters. And for what it's worth, if Bobby's out there listening, I have yet to have to fight pirates. And I'm on page two out of what?
Five pages. And I did not see fighting as any of the things. It's all about freighter building and exploring with your freighter and doing things related to that. So that's kind of cool. So I did get to explore some of the things they actually patched in about. Yeah, they really just made your freighter, like just took it one step further so that you could build out like a full base on your freighter, which is really cool.
But now they have tailored rooms and tailored environments, and that you can like build out onto like observation decks. And that's the cool part because you could actually have more windows and like if you park your freighter in front of a planet, you'll see that planet in the background. It's just it's just really cool. So it's cute that they took it a step further. I don't think it's a major content patch. But it's I mean, still, it's like, wow, there's still a lot of content.
it's cute that they took it a step further. I don't think it's a major content patch. But it's I mean, still, it's like, wow, they're still patching at all that game all this time out. So I'll continue playing that expedition. I haven't been streaming it. Just because my energy in general has been low ever since the COVID thing. It's just a little bit slower of recovery. But I'll get back there and do some do some more streaming soon.
I almost forgot. Yeah, I did play Dead by Daylight Final Fantasy.
Of course you did. Of course you did. All right. I would be shocked if you did.
Well, I had to say because I didn't sing with the week and you reminded me. Thank you. Bye bye.
I also played, you know, I play my GPS games, Ingress, Pikmin, and Pokemon Go had an event today for shiny Hoosian Volibies was the thing today. And I did what like something like 15 raids and caught one shiny. But it got me motivated to walk around downtown.
And the other thing that they've added. Oh, what did I call it? Braviary. Oh, sorry. Volibie is the base. Sorry. I was close. Same family.
No, actually, no, it's not even the same family. Volibie is the other one. Whatever. Rufflet. Baby Rufflet turns into Braviary.
But I was gonna say the thing that Pokemon Go did recently that I thought was kind of cool was they added this new incense that's like your daily incense that you use and it lasts for 15 it's a blue incense that lasts for 15 minutes.
And you try to catch basically as many Pokemon as you can in 15 minutes, but you have to keep moving in order for it to spawn more Pokemon. But the interesting thing about it, it works the exact same in rural areas versus cities.
So it's finally a feature that they've added in, you know, as a bit of a response to the role players that say there's nothing for us to kind of, you know, help motivate and, and it, you know, it has all the social media sharing of, hey, look, I caught 26 Pokemon on my walk today and that whole thing where you can actually see a picture of everything you caught.
So you can see just how many fucking the same things I always get. Apparently, the generation one birds reskinned in Pokemon Legends that were kind of redone are like a reward that you can actually get for that. They're very low catch rate and they run very easy, but I thought it was kind of neat that they built that into it.
So I think daily incense is probably one of the better features they put in Pokemon Go for quite some time. And I'm also kind of surprised they should have had the trigger ready to go on this before they reverse the other incense changes. And it probably would have stung a lot less. But who knows, maybe this is because of that. Oh, I didn't realize there were Galarian versions. I thought they would I thought they went into thanks, Steph. Sorry, clearly, I don't know my Pokemon well enough. So they're the Galarian versions. I thought they were from Legends.
So interesting. Okay. Well, still, it's it's, you know, a rarer version of those birds than have been in the game before. So it's kind of neat. They tied it to that feature. But yeah. Yeah. And Mike Deaf says the daily incense doesn't require you to move. If not, it doesn't work at all. And plus you you can't fast catch. And if you catch with the Pokemon Go Plus, I don't think they go into your log. I don't know if it works or not. Plus, I wouldn't want to try to catch a legendary bird with the Pogo Plus.
So like you have to actually play the game. That's the part that sucks is you can't fast catch. I don't like that. But really, Mike Deaf says you can fast catch? No, because they they'll they won't go away. I guess that you can fast catch but then they don't they stay on the map. But if you tap it again, no matter what you do, it'll run away. So it's it's weird. So anyway, really, Deaf says he does fast. I swear when I did it the first day, it doesn't work. But I'll try it again. I'll screen record this time.
So all right. But that otherwise that was pretty much it for make it clearly I don't know what I'm talking about with Pokemon Go today. But I don't know the games. The game's still more interesting to me right now that it's been in a while. So there's that.
There's that. All right, we're gonna get into some gaming news. First off, though, before we get into gaming news, something I just wanted to bring up, I'm sure everybody heard this news today. But I have to acknowledge and tip the hat and express the sadness I felt when I heard Nichelle Nichols passed away today. You know, I know she was not in the greatest health. But still, you know, what a legend. And you might be thinking, what does this have to do with video games?
And I argue Nichelle Nichols broke barriers in television, in sci fi, in everything. And yes, that includes games. She broke down barriers for people of color. She broke down barriers for women. And I think in just, you know, I never had the pleasure of meeting her. But I've always heard nothing but glowing things about just what a nice, truly wonderful person she is. And you can't say that about everybody that was on the original series.
But I digress. Yeah, I mean, 89 is a great run. It's still it's still sad, you know, you know,
Tiara, and I were saying earlier that we need a protective bubble around George Takei and Walter Cohen. And then then then we're like, why is Shatner still around? And I think that he's using blood transfusions from Keith Richards.
That was I mean, I know it's, you know, I'm just gonna say it. That was my first reaction is why couldn't have been Shatner. All right. But maybe I shouldn't speak that. It's probably not a nice thing to say.
Oh, no, no. Shatner is a terrible person.
Oh, I know.
Yeah. Especially the things he says about autistic people.
It's just I didn't I tell the story about the Star Trek. Maybe I didn't say it was about Shatner. It was about Shatner. All right. Let's see. But anyway, I don't want to bring up negativity around her passing because it's it's an incredibly sad event. And yes, she was not in the best health, but it doesn't make it any less sad, especially knowing what a trail that she blazed for everyone. But especially women and people of color.
That pod culture says awesome lady got to meet her a couple of times. As Joe and Hunter Matt points out, Bill Russell passed away today, too, from the sports world. Both badasses that broke barriers and pioneers. And then I'm so sorry, I forget her name in the moment. Pat Carroll, the voice.
Yeah, she did.
Yeah, she was in her 90s. But but still, you know, again, doesn't make it any less sad.
It's classic voice. What a what a horrible day. A little mermaid. Yeah, a lot of people. Well, you know, it happens in threes.
Yeah, what a horrible day. What a horrible day. All right. But anyway, I wanted to make sure we acknowledge that because it's important. So let's get into some gaming news from there. Loki.
Right. So steam is clamping down on some of these. I guess the artwork for different games. You may see a lot of these kind of it reminds me of the box art in some of the retail games that are out there. Batman gave me the year edition. Where you have all of your alco accolades, you know, being put up on there, or like, sometimes they'll put like, you know,
it's on sale right now, you know, more things to try to catch your eye as you're browsing the store. Well, seems not having any of that they wanted to be straightforward. So they're basically saying that no more, we're not allowing a word logos, review scores, you know, basically, they have a set of guidelines now that they're not allowing any of that stuff. So no review scores of any kind, no word names, no discount marketing copy, no text or imagery
promoting a different product, and no other miscellaneous text.
I mean, I understand that promoting a different product and the miscellaneous text and some of that silly stuff. But I'm, I'm a little sorry. I mean, imagine if they did that to movie posters, you couldn't put a word logos or clips from reviews or review scores, like think of how many movie posters you've seen that are filled with that stuff. So I'm a little surprised. They're throwing that out in steam as well.
That's because I think this is more of like, it's more of like, I don't know, I'm trying to think of like, if even if like, Netflix and stuff has all that stuff in there, like titles, but like, it's just supposed to be cleaner to look at is what they're trying to get at. If you want to put all your worst stores full of garbage, we all know that there's so much garbage on the steam store. And I understand they have to do something about it.
Yeah, so if they keep that pretty much clean, you can put all your word text and everything like that in the body of your actual store page. But with the actual logo itself, they don't want any of that.
E3VL in chat says some of the quotes are out of context anyway. Oh, absolutely. But again, movies do the same thing. And you also have critics that will intentionally say things to get on movie posters to bump up their own cred. I mean, it's, I don't don't trust that stuff on movie posters. Maybe awards depending on what you're into might sway your decision a little bit. I would never trust pull quotes.
I do like the page that they they show off examples of that because once again, this goes back to like, I think I saw Twitter posting from the artists before those making these fake game. I guess not screenshots, but like, game art for these stuff. So you have guitar billionaire, it's probably fine. Custard, or was it custard castle small claims court? You know, it's just fun little
mock artworks that they put on there.
I mean, if I were to say something like, let's say like Yaris, and I say, Oh, man, Yaris is the game of the year for me to poop on. You know, they can, they can pull the quote, I called it game of the year, dot dot dot. So it's just the pull quotes always are a little
if there was one game that came out in the year that yours came out, it would be the game of the year. But since there are other things,
any other game is a better game than Yaris is a better game. I don't know what they call it better game better gaming. Anyway,
you know, we we talk so much crap about Yaris. And there's real developers behind that game to develop that. I know. I mean, it was a paycheck. You know, it's a paycheck. Yeah, I'm not it's a paycheck. I don't want anything against them. But I do hold something against, you know, the Yaris at least they didn't charge for it. That's true. That's true. At least they didn't charge for it. All right. Well, for things that might be a little more pleasant to drive. Let's talk about Mario Kart. And yes, still content
coming in for Mario Kart and some Mario Kart DLC that's coming. August 4th wave two was announced and I gotta say some of these some of these courses sound great. So wave two will be including the turnip cup and the propeller cup. The turnip cup has tour New York minute from Mario Kart tour SNES Mario circuit three classic course. calamari desert from N64. That's a classic course and one of my very favorite courses in all of Mario
Kart DS Waluigi pinball is coming out for that's that's worth it right there in my opinion. The propeller cup has the Sydney sprint from tour snow land from GBA the mushroom gorge from the Wii. I think that was a pretty cool one. And some folks were saying, you know, is this mean they're all going to be recycled courses? And it turns out the answers? No, I think there was one new course in the first set. And now we're going to get a new course called sky high Sunday.
And it's a little of course ice cream parlor themed new course that's in the mix as well. So I mean, great. I mean, how long has this game been out like eight years and it's still getting new content. So you can check that out. Again, that is coming out on August 4 is when that releases. Now, apparently there have has also been some rumors about future Mario Kart DLC. You know, we love rumors. Apparently, there was a video that
came out earlier on Twitter that kind of correctly called the turnip cup and the propeller cup that they just knew because of the the the data that they knew that turnip was going to be a tour Super Nintendo and 64 and DS track propeller was tour GBA we and unspecified the new course, right? So we're going to be getting if the rest of this is accurate, there's going to be the rock cup, the moon cup,
the fruit cup. I love that the fruit cup, the boomerang cup, the feather cup, the cherry cup, the acorn cup and the spiny cup. And across all of those there are yogurt cup or the activity a cup. There are six question marks, which indicates six new courses potentially coming. For you classic folks, though only one SNES course in the cherry cup apparently but tour is the big one
every single cup has a tour at least one tour track in it. So definitely it sounds like if nothing else Mario Kart tour kind of donated tracks to Mario Kart eight, but I don't think that's too surprising. You know, considering that Mario Kart tour didn't quite end up having that same reception at the end of the day, but they're sure sure getting the most out of that content, aren't they? So as Joe and her Matt suggests the pinkberry cup Oh, remember the days we were obsessed the pinkberry they're still around, but it is
well, number one, I can't have all that sugar anymore. It kind of ruins it for me, doesn't it? But sugar, they do know where they have a pinkberry. They have one over at the the Roseville Galleria. Oh, yeah, right in the middle. Yeah. Yeah, right. Right in time for round one to finally open. When's that place ever gonna open? On the sixth apparently? Really? Where did you hear that? It was actually posted on their site. I think I saw it in the
the arcade. I forget what they call it now. The previously called Sean against arcade thing. In Sacramento game thing, but
this entire show to look this up. Where Okay, it still says coming soon on the website. Would it back down players? Yeah, it's on the Westfield Galleria at Roseville website. Says round one entertainment opening Saturday, August 6. 10am to 11pm.
Interesting. Hold on. I gotta find this. I gotta find this. Yeah, so it's Westfield Galleria website.
I'm looking at it. I don't see it. Oh, there. Oh, there it is. Oh my god. You're right. 10am to 11pm. How about that? Hold on. Hold on. Yes, I I will shut this whole show down with local news. Absolutely. Because this is important. This is important. But there it is right there. Look at that on the right side. Opening Saturday, August 6. Oh, I have to text Shane. He's gonna be so excited
because he's gonna be here. Like right after that for a wedding. And so he'll be able to go how funny. That's great. Yeah, so I'll have to go check it out. Yeah, I want to go as well. So that's great. All right. Um, let's move on. We have more news. And I need to step away for just a moment. So Dark Sakura, what do you have for us in the news? Oh, some stuff. Um, so analog, you know, the company that does a lot of the
new hardware for old material. Of course, they have the analog pocket, which is a really cool handheld device that resembles a Game Boy in how it's set up. They have announced a, a port of a game that came out in 1962. The original space war. It was done in 1962 by a bunch of engineers led by Steve
Russell at MIT. They used a PDP-1 mini computer and a 1024 by 1024 pixel CRT display. And they had a game with two spacecraft, fighting it out in the gravitational will of a star. And they had different controllers for it. And they could now I remember being on record saying this actually not the oldest video game that there was that one played on a radar back in the 40s.
But this one was legit, you know, a two player game. And now they have it where it will play on the analog pocket. And what's pretty cool about it is that a third party developer called Spaceman 3 had the source code from the PDP-1 computer and space war, since they're both public domain.
So they had that with the open FPGA software and they had it set to emulate and it had some very interesting things about it. So since a 1024 by 1024 vector display would generate the image a slightly different way. They had to make some changes to accommodate it.
So it is a little bit cleaner, a little bit crisper. There's no AI, of course, because I mean, this was all, you know, a game. But it's been released with their software update. And the software update also adds save states and a few other things. So there you go.
All right, well, I think you have a somewhat related story, Loki, right?
Yep. So along with the updates to the analog pocket, because they did put out that wonderful open FPGA program, there's been some folks using the repository to create emulators.
So there's a couple of repositories opened by a spiritualized 1997, who, very quick after the release, had a repository for F open FPGA, GBA and then open FPGA, Game Boy and Game Boy Color. So allows you to basically download these and then run ROMs off of the analog pocket.
And so there's a small process that involves, I think, it allows you to jailbreak the device. And then you can run ROMs because right now the analog pockets meant specifically for actual hardware, running the actual cartridges themselves.
I'm assuming that they're going to open this up for other ROMs eventually, or someone will develop that because at some point they were supposed to have, you know, compatibility with like the Turbo Pocket, and Atari Lynx, and maybe, I don't know if there's like any Genesis or anything like that. Game Gear, that type of stuff. But I don't know, maybe maybe those are coming.
Oh, and actually speaking of Game Gear, it looks like they've already started working on that as well. They even have an archive of all the different title screen images for I guess, I imagine it's for the game browser for that. So interesting, the waste is no time.
Hackers gonna hack. Jailbreakers gonna jailbreak. Yep, toaster installers gonna install.
Sjoener Matt is asking, is it still really hard or take forever to ship the analog pocket? I think they do still have a pretty limited stock, don't they? They're not getting as fast as the Steam decks, apparently.
Sure, I don't know how readily available those are.
All right. Well, let's talk about another classic. And this is an MMO classic. It's World of Warcraft, you know, back when everybody was actually still playing it. Sorry to those that are still playing it. But let's be real. The game probably peaked around the Wrath of the Lich King expansion. And if you want to revisit the game, as it was during the Wrath of the Lich King, when both myself and DarkSakura were actively playing, you can do that with World of Warcraft classic on September 22.
26. So I'm sure many of you know that World of Warcraft a few years ago launched the classic version of World of Warcraft. And since then, they've launched a kind of parallel, some servers that are dedicated to the Burning Crusade expansion, which was the first expansion. Well, now they're going to be doing it again with the second expansion for the game. And that is World of Warcraft Wrath of the Lich King expansion that was announced this week, and it will be coming out September 26.
So yeah, to celebrate the expansion coming, there's a new leveling mechanic in the game called Joyous Journeys. So if you're playing Burning Crusade classic, you can toggle a 50% experience boost. That's a lot. But it is something you toggle at the innkeeper, I'm assuming to preserve the status of the game for those that don't want that or they don't want the help because you know, they're in it for the classic experience.
So, but if you want, you can opt into the Joyous Journeys boost to level up your character to get ready for Wrath of the Lich King classic. If you weren't already aware-
Some people like hard mode.
What's that?
Oh, for sure, for sure. And I believe even though they launched Burning Crusade, they kept vanilla WoW servers available and you could copy to like one that was going to stay there. So I'm pretty sure with Lich King, they're going to do the same thing. And you can choose to have a character frozen in time in either vanilla WoW, Burning Crusade WoW or Wrath of the Lich King WoW, which is kind of neat.
I was just going to ask like, are they just going to eventually update everybody into the modern ones? Like, ah, now the classic servers are the modern servers.
I don't think so. And I'm going to be honest, I think this is the last one. I really do. Because honestly, I'm going to keep it real. This is where the game peaked for most people. For me anyway, I could I could say that because the what was next cataclysm? See, the problem with cataclysm is that it went back and redid
did vanilla WoW. And that was the start of people wanting to do it. Yeah, but you know, that was the start of people, you know, wanting the the older experience. I don't know, I guess maybe they could do cataclysm. But then when you get to Pandaria, I'm sorry, that's when the game really started to nose dive. So I just I don't see them going all the way to Pandaria. But who knows? Who knows? You know, even if it's one server, maybe they'll do it. Who knows? You know, one server for each expansion. I bet they could fill an audience with that.
If you didn't already know, this is included with a World of Warcraft subscription. So, Loki, to your point, you have to pay for modern WoW anyway, to get access to this. So you might as well, right? Yeah. All right. Let's move on. I like this next story Dark Sakura, because this is like one of those sciencey, the science side of gaming.
Um, so there, and you know, I always love to see the like the scientific and psychological research that goes in behind gaming's, gaming's gamers is what I meant. So there has been shown, as published in neuro image reports by Georgia State University researchers, that there are superior sensor motor decision making skills
and enhanced activity in key regions of the brain in frequent video game players as compared to non gamers. They used fMRI, which is functional magnetic resonance, resonance imaging to show how that of different parts of the brain are stimulated.
So what they did, I mean, so basically, they were saying that video games played by the overwhelming majority of young people, they said young people, every three, for more than three hours every week shows that decision making abilities are improved, but they don't know how.
So with the with their work, they're showing that it's, it's basically brain training. They also call it a therapeutic intervention. So it's stress relief.
But it was run, the lead author on the paper is Tim Jordan, who has a PhD in physics and astronomy.
He, in his history, he was talking about having weak vision in one eye as a child. And in a study, he said when he was about five years old, he was asked to cover his good eye and play a video game as a way to strengthen the vision in the weak one.
And he basically went from legally blind in one eye to being very strong in that eye. And he could go on and play lacrosse and paintball.
Now he's a postdoctoral researcher at UCLA.
So basically, they had 47 college age participants 28 categorized as regular gamers and 19 as non players.
And they had each of them lay in an fMRI machine with a mirror. So they could see a cue with a display of moving dots, and they were asked to press a button on the right or left to indicate which direction dots were moving, or resist pressing a button if there was no directional movement.
And then basically, the gamers were faster and more accurate with their responses. And the brain scans showed that there was enhanced activity in certain parts of the brain.
So I'll just read the quote here. These results indicate video game playing potentially enhances several of the sub processes for sensation, perception and mapping to action to improve decision making skills.
These findings begin to illuminate how video game players playing alters the brain in order to improve task performance, and the potential implications for increasing tasks specific activity.
There was no trade off between speed and accuracy of response. They just said that they were better on both of those as opposed to the non knit gamers.
So they're basically saying video games are great cognitive trainers.
And if anyone wants to, wants a link to the article, the the actual study, it is labeled video game players have improved decision making abilities and enhanced brain activities. And you can see it on Science Direct.
Mike Deft in chat over twitch.tv slash vog network says just look at Tetris players. Yeah, I mean, you can you'd see you see the brain in motion there.
I'm putting the link to the published article in chat for our live listeners.
I mean, gamers, we always knew we were smarter than everyone else, right?
Just tell us what we already know.
It's not a matter of smarts. It's a matter of reactions.
No, it is like like there might actually be something to that hand-eye coordination that we always said video games would help with.
That much has been proven, but now they're they're showing where the brain is triggered from it.
It's it's interesting stuff. It's nice to have the science to back it up. There's still a lot of people out there that won't believe it. But what can you do?
I know all of this, you know, wonderful brain development has made me a more effective killer, too.
So I mean, in in a video game, in a video game. All right. In Dead by Daylight.
All right. Moving on. Loki, you have an update of sorts for us.
Yes. Update, if you will. Better, better, better phrases like we're just marking the anniversary of inaction.
So Better Ubisoft was a group that was developed trying to get Ubisoft, you know, to do the right thing and address some of these harassment issues.
Well, they posted that it has been one year to the day that we've signed our open letter to Ubisoft management calling for far more action to take our tackle abuse and setting out our four key demands.
None of these demands have made or been met so far. Their key demands for reference was stop promoting and moving known offenders from studio to studio, team to team with no repercussions.
The cycle needs to end. Number two, we want a collective seat at the table to have a meaningful say in how Ubisoft as a company moves forward from here.
Three cross industry collaboration to agree on a set of group or ground rules and processes that all studios can use to handle these offenses in the future.
And for this collaboration must heavily involve employees in a non management in non management positions and union representatives.
Of course, as we've mentioned, literally anytime we bring up Ubisoft, they have not addressed any of the allegations whatsoever. I think the most that they've done is investigate themselves and found no wrongdoing.
So and it's interesting that Activision Blizzard took all the heat in this whole thing, you know, not enough noise is being made about Ubisoft and the fact that things you know, and literally nothing's changed there in a year is really what we're saying, you know, with all these demands, nothing's changed in a year.
Well, they got there it was at their Ubisoft forward event that's coming out pretty soon, that I'm sure will be full of people talking about that. Remember last time?
I hope the media reports them hand in hand. I hope the media reports it as Ubisoft forward by a company who has not moved forward in the past year happened today.
Yeah, more like Ubisoft backwards. But no, they did that last year when they put out the there's like a brief, silent, you know, wall of text where it's like, we take this stuff seriously. And we're this is about the games. We're not going to talk about this right now. We're not gonna get into the politics.
The the inaction has shown truly the meaning behind all that white text on a black screen.
Mind you that that letter that open letter was signed by 500 employees at the company. So it's not just like one person like I don't think you're doing this right. It's it's a lot of people that think that you're not doing it, as well as the gaming community thinks that you're not doing it right. And then continues to support them by buying their games. But you know, we're unhappy about it.
I showed her Matt says nothing will change until Eves is gone, which isn't happening. Yeah, and that's sad. You know, like, again, the CEOs are not being held accountable, even in the Activision Blizzard thing, even though we see the light at the end of the tunnel with, you know, the Microsoft purchase. And yeah, I do believe things will get better with Microsoft. And I think also, the fact that the unionizations are happening, and they cannot stop it.
I think is, you know, also a good thing to happen. It's just amazing to me that Bobby Kotick isn't unemployed. Amazing to me. But we all know, we all know the board is protecting him. They're, they're all protecting each other, all of them. So that's, that's the one good thing about Microsoft coming in is that, you know, even though they can, they have to kind of say for now, well, there'll be there'll be a transitionary Microsoft can get rid of them all, as soon as the deal's done. And I think they will.
I think I don't think there's going to be a place for Bobby Kotick at the new company. So as shown under Matt says, Eves has said that his family would buy up the majority stake of Ubisoft to avoid a corporate takeover, which is just shitty. Then people have to stop buying the games, quite honestly, but it's, I mean, honestly, like from what it seems like the quality of the games has suffered anyway, like Ubisoft has had quite a bit of trouble in the past year. And if you don't think these two things are tied together.
I've got a radio tower for you to climb then.
Yeah. So just a matter of time before Eves Giamant hopefully is held accountable, but it just might be a long time. Alright, something we'll probably see first is the release of the PlayStation VR 2, of which we got a few more details this week, thanks to a new PlayStation blog entry that showed some of the user experience that will be happening with the PS VR 2. There's going to be a see through camera with the system.
I think we kind of knew that but we got to see it in action, which is nice because you know, you can see where is my dining room table or you know, wherever you're playing at, where's the boundary here? Where am I at in relation to the boundary? Where did I set down the controllers without having to take the whole thing off and all that, you know, and just making sure that you know, like a baby didn't crawl through your play area, the see through camera will be nice for that.
So there's actually I guess a card in the control center that lets you do that. But you can't record when you do that, which is interesting. So you can't actually just record what is happening on the see through camera. I guess they don't want any more. What was that? Dammit, the share factory or whatever. What was that called on the early the room? PlayStation room? Whatever that was that people did that. Yeah, adult broadcasts. I don't know.
Anyway, um, you can also terrible though, you can also customize the PlayStation VR to area you use the controllers and the cameras to establish a custom play area. So that's kind of interesting. So if you have a couch that shaped funny, or what have you, you can kind of work around that, which I think is kind of interesting. And you can also get warnings when you're getting close to those things. So that's kind of neat.
So I don't know if it's like a thing. But I know, like, with a lot of VR, obviously, a lot of it that involves you moving around stuff. I don't know if they have an option with some of these, because like the play space that I have for like those VR things. It's not not very big, especially in the kitchen. But there are some games that I think, like, I would say, like, maybe a no man's sky or something like that, that's less moving, or like you're just moving with a controller and just using the headset for kind of like, you know, like, you know, like, I don't know if it's like a thing, but I know, like, with a lot of VR, obviously, a lot of it that involves you moving around stuff. I don't know if they have an option with some of these, because like the play space that I have for like those VR things. It's not not very big, especially in the kitchen. But there are some games that I think
are kind of like a full 360 camera, I guess, if you will. I'm wondering if they have an option, like I can just sit down and do that. It's not gonna like yell at me going your play space is too small. Like because that would be ideal for a lot of games. I would think so. Yeah, because you're right. There's there's games like that would like no man's sky where it's not about moving around and doing all that stuff. Like you're intended to sit on the couch and play and you just are immersed. Tetris effect to be another one that comes to mind. Yeah, you know, you don't move around. And the I think Tetris effect was great.
In VR, but it's it's, it also was certainly a fine game, not in VR either. So it was kind of nice that it was just enhanced by VR. I should point out, though, the other thing that the blog was showing is that you can now film yourself while you're playing, which a lot of people like to do a Beat Saber, it's not going to be that same, like over the shoulder, because the camera that's looking at you is also going to be able to show you on the screen, if you want to capture that sort of stuff. So you can actually capture yourself playing the
game. So I thought it was inside out tracking what camera is going to be looking at you? That same one, isn't it? How is it? How's the camera facing out from the headset looking at you? No, there's there's a camera. If you Oh, no, I'm sorry. If you have a PS five HD camera on the console, that it will fill me they sell those. I guess so. I that was news to me too. I didn't know that they had a camera
for the console. No, they talked on the blog. Yeah. So no release date for this yet. And we have no idea if it's going to be a this year thing and next year thing or what because Sony still hasn't really point. Yeah, I would think so. But I would say if we get to Labor Day and still don't know, then yeah. I need I need me a new rush of blood game. I'll take I'll take the quarry rush of blood. I mean, I understand that that's not really meant
for a roller coaster. But like, why not? I need me a new one of those. So 100 Matt in our chat over twitch.tv slash vog network says I really hope Sony makes it consumer price friendly. I don't think it will especially since the quest to just got a price increase. And yeah, that also news that is dumb. Yeah. But it is going to be a tough pill to swallow if it's over $300. Yes, the price has to be right. Well, I think also the thing that the PS VR two faces is that still
PlayStation fives are not super easy to get. I mean, I know it's easier today than it was before. But it's not super easy. So there's people that they're going to be trying to talk into getting a PlayStation five and one of these I don't know I just this year might just feel a little early for that. But we'll see. It's too bad because like I think a lot of people like you'd be able to get a decent computer that can run VR like Yeah, hell the
the laptops we bought for kids like weren't all that expensive, like last year, and those can handle VR. And so I don't understand, like with the price of computers, especially with people replacing stuff now that graphics card prices are coming down in price as well, like you would think that they would be on board with trying to lower the cost of that stuff. But once again, you know, it's like, yeah, that sucks about the meta quest. But there's other things out
there that you can get that are just outside of that whole space. And honestly, like, I prefer having those open marketplaces like steam anyways, Facebook has to charge $100 because they can't tie your games to your account anymore and keep stealing your privacy data and sell that to make the money. That's why they have to have the prize. So anyway, let's go to the let's go to a simpler time when we weren't playing VR. Let's get to it.
And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it. It's time for the classic game of the week.
What did you pick for us this week, DarkSakura?
I picked Timber.
Timber!
Which is like pretty much a staple of going to California Extreme. So Timber is a game that was manufactured by Bally Midway in 1984. And you have to earn points by chopping down trees and then log rolling and dodging bees by angry bears and stuff. Timber was designed by Steve Meyer, who also did Tapper.
And so that's why they have very similar art styles.
Timber Tapper.
Anyway, the game you play as a lumberjack and it is a two player, so you can do a versus slash co-op kind of play, but you have to chop down a certain number of trees that pop up from the ground within a limited time.
You have two joysticks. One joystick is to move around. The other one is actually the motion of your axe.
So as you keep going, your time decreases and your quota increases and then you have to avoid bees, beehives that are thrown by bears.
You have to avoid getting hit by the trees as they fall or tripping over stuff and you can sometimes catch these birds that fly out of the trees.
And then every few levels you have a way to get bonus points and that's to try to stay standing on a floating log. The log will rotate and you have to use your reflexes to stay on top of it.
The first two times you're on that log it's pretty big, but the log starts shrinking.
And then the mini game will end if you fall off the log or you stay on top of it for the amount of time and you get all these bonus points.
It is multiplayer. Like I said, you can play competitively or cooperatively.
So you can earn bonus points by pushing trees onto your other lumberjack and then you get bonus points for whoever cuts down those trees.
The cabinet for timber would either be built into a tapper or root beer tapper cabinet since they were also made by Bally Midway.
And then in 2004 in Midway's Arcade Adventures 2, the compilation disc for Xbox PlayStation 2 and GameCube was included.
Also part of Lego Dimensions accessed by using the arcade dock in the Once Upon a Time Machine in the West.
The current world record for this game is by Josh Lumbay with a score of 9,767,550, which was done in 2011 from what it looks like.
But yeah, that's your game.
I love this game.
I don't know if I played it at California Extreme. Probably it's been forever since I've been to California Extreme though.
But it was in that, it shows up in those Midway collections. I remember there was one on Xbox that had this in it. Maybe 360 had it too.
And I would play the crap out of it. I just think it's a neat game.
And there is a strategy to it because, you know, having the stumps and the trees that you can trip on, you have to really think about which way you're chopping trees down.
So there's a little bit of strategy to it. Like you can just see in the video that we're watching on Twitch, the guy just fell over the stump there.
And that can set you back if you're not careful. So yeah, neat game.
Neat game. All right. St100matt in chat says I've only seen and played this machine once, which was a fun spot.
So yeah, I haven't seen an actual machine of this in a long, long time, but I'm sure the collector stuff is out there. So all right, Timber, your classic game of the week.
All right, we're going to travel around the industry and check out some other news pretty quick in a segment called Rapid Fire News. We will start with, I think, Loki.
Yep. So it's good news if you're looking for a Steam Deck, because Valve has just said that they've, they are fulfilling Steam Deck orders faster than they were expecting.
So according to Valve, the company is still able to produce the console, but now instead of the windows being, I think if you ordered now was previously like Q4 or later, they've actually brought that up to Q3.
So right now, apparently, the window ranges from July to September, everyone else will fall into Q4, October to December range, if you were in the queue. So basically moving it up three months if you have that on order already.
So that's not bad. And then we talked about this a while ago, but it's finally happened. Roblox has had to remove the oof sound, their iconic sound that had been, I think originally lifted from an old Tommy Tallarico music produced game called Messiah.
And you may remember there was this big announcement where Tommy was going to allow folks to actually keep the oof sound in the game for their projects if they paid $1 or $100. That never happened. So something fell through in negotiations.
They don't have to raise money for the Amico anymore. So
so in the case of what happened here is they just replaced it with a different sound effect now, which I don't understand why they didn't just do that to begin with, because like, how hard is the say oof, kind of similar to what it was before just rerecord your own sound like that literally is a date that that that's like a half a day project right there. And they would have taken care of the whole thing.
Well, the good news about this is that maybe we'll never have to hear about that stupid sound again, because I'm over it. I'm so over it. All right. Let's see Dark Soccer, what do you have for us?
So, there's a leak of the PlayStation plus a central lineup for August. And that is going to include Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 1 and 2, and Yakuza Like a Dragon and Little Nightmares. In fact, I think it's actually the whole Yakuza series, isn't it supposed to be?
Yeah. So and then, yeah, I think that that's going to be fun for people who have PlayStation Plus.
Yeah. And also, apparently, there is a preview. Someone got a preview of Yakuza 8. And who knows?
I'm excited for that. Although this is where Bobby would say I still need to finish Like a Dragon, which I'm not saying isn't true. Maybe I do. But you know what? There's a lot of games I have to finish right now. Add it to the list. It's on the list.
All right. Get me to stop playing No Man's Sky or Final Fantasy or one of the Forever games, so then I'll have time for it. All right. You want to know a game that is taking a lot of time? Not for me. I kind of I was playing this for a little bit and then I stopped. But Alan is still playing Diablo 3, and he's playing a seasonal character. He got past Paragon 1100.
Yes. Yeah. In the season. I'm like, dang, those numbers are but I think I think it's just getting more and more absurd because there's going to come a point when Diablo 3 is no longer going to get content and when Diablo 4 comes out and we know Diablo 4 is coming out soon ish within the next year or for sure. So all right. Let's see. I think I had one too. I want to talk about Oh, yeah, another another passing from earlier this week. This has just not been a great year.
Great week in the artistic world. But Kenichi Okuma, a composer for Super Smash Brothers, passed away. That is specifically 2008 Super Smash Brothers Brawl. Kenichi Okuma was one of the many composers and arrangers to the game, composing for games like Gyromite, Pokemon Gym and Evolution from Red and Blue, Flat Zone 2.
Those songs did come back in 3DS, Wii U and also Smash Ultimate. So he passed away on July 22 due to esophageal cancer at the age of 56, which is far too young. It should be noted that Sakurai also tweeted about it saying that Okuma's legacy will live on in Smash 4 and Smash Ultimate. So that is, of course, a tragic loss and just the art world not having a good week in that regard.
All right. Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates of some games coming out near you soon. How about the US Loki?
Naragami Gakuden Nanafushiji on Nintendo Switch, Full Metal Alchemist Mobile on iOS and Android. Oh, God. We have another life simulation game.
Guess Hiju, Mina de Chokomaka Muradukuri on Nintendo Switch.
Chomaka Muradukuri.
Oh, because Makaemura is Ghost and Goblins series.
Yeah, I don't know if that's this. I mean, I don't think so. No, it's not from Capcom.
Yeah, it's from Nippon, Colombia, whatever that is. Hard West 2 on PC. Hindsight on PC, Nintendo Switch and iOS.
Kokoro Clover Season 1 on PC and Nintendo Switch. Sword and Fairy Together Forever on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5. Massage Freaks on Nintendo Switch. That's a rhythm game.
Picross X, Pikbits versus Oozboross. I don't know what Oozboross is. That's on Nintendo Switch, I think.
And then Vanaris Tactics on PC. Bukora on PC, iOS and Android. Giga Bash on PC, PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5. And last but not least, The 13th Month on PC, PlayStation 4 and I'm sorry, that was PC, iOS and Android. I'm glad that Smarch is getting representation in game form now.
Izzy Week. Let's go to Japan and check out the releases over there. So on the Nintendo Switch this week, we have that same game that Loki was talking about from Nippon, Colombia.
Gesshizu, Mina de Choko Maka Muradukuri is coming out on the Switch, as well as Let's Get Fit in a regular and one that includes the sports strap edition. We also have coming out in Japan on the Switch Apathy, Narugami Gakuen, Nana Fushigi comes out in a regular and limited edition on the Switch as well.
That's pretty much it for the Switch. Taking a look at the PlayStation 5. Don't really have anything this week. We have Guilty Gear next week, but that's next week. So that's your Japanese releases. Dark Sakura, how about the UK?
Ultra Age on the 5th for PlayStation and Switch. That's it.
All right. A few more stories for you, and then we'll get to listener roundtable. Get to your emails. Participate at orangelandradio.com and any phone calls we might have tonight in our green room over at vognetwork.com slash Discord.
And I would encourage you to join the Discord server anyway and chat with us throughout the week on a variety of topics. Lots of great stories and viewpoints getting exchanged in the Orange Launch Radio channel throughout the week.
And of course, our In Memoriam channel has been going off way too much this week with everything that's been going on. But check that out over Discord. We promise we limit the use of everyone's spam. In fact, I don't think we actually use it at all because I know how annoying that can be when you're in like 100 different Discord servers.
So just get the chat that you want to get over on our Discord server, vognetwork.com slash Discord. Okay, more news, starting with some drama. We love some drama, right, Loki?
Yeah, so VRChat is getting a controversial update very soon. They're going to be implementing or they announced that they're in their next up, they're going to be implementing Epic Games, easy anti cheat technology. And of course, this is going to crack down on any modified clients for the game.
And whereas you may see this to help combat like people hacking in VRChat, it's also affecting folks that are using modified clients for non nefarious reasons. Like for example, the VRCCC mod, which is a closed caption, or adds closed captions to the movie worlds.
So deaf and hard of hearing people can watch movies with their friends that will no longer work anymore. There's an IK 2.0 update that which I are they're saying that there's some user made mods that were working with the client to help with body tracking. So they had maze IK 2.0 update that improve the body tracking that won't work anymore.
Um, yeah, so it's unfortunate to see all of this stuff that is being kind of affected by that.
Well, it's it's one of those things where they didn't think it through, you know, the the company didn't do the adequate amount of research to see what mods were out there, and at least try to address the issue of you know, their game needs to be more accessible by maybe having some of these mods built into the game before they hit the button on something like this, it's just going to kill all the mods. So I think that's just very poor research being done by the company, who for this feels like a reaction to this.
Like something was going on in VR chat that in like, and so they use this as a kill switch that did that overextended it got this and way more stuff than it needed to.
So they did put out a a blog post on basically saying addressing your feedback, in which they talked about their plans, and you know, the security update and stuff like that. But then they just doubled down on it and didn't really apologize for anything. They just said, you know, that, you know, it's just an update, and it's, you know, dressing larger number of players are says, it's clear that the first up wait, you know, it's just an update.
The first up wave of promise updates will be only thing. So they're going to do some other things to update the game to help with, you know, some of these folks that are, you need like the closed captioning or other features in their other accessibility things. But I think that's gonna be too late at that point.
Yeah, it should have been one of the first things to happen. And now, you know, if folks from this community decide to leave there, it's just going to, you know, their friends to leave, you know, why they want you to use, you know, why they want you to use the actual the, its own launcher is because they're going to start. I don't know, well, because I don't play VR chat. But from what I hear, they were going to be either starting to or adding more of monetization to it.
Where they're going to sell things. So of course, I think that they wanted to secure that so that there's no way to hack that stuff in there. But yeah, just start of it kind of going down, unfortunately.
Gdats in our chat says my partners way into VR chat, it's effectively impossible for them to coordinate reports of issues with their intention to expand the game and mods. Apparently mods are known for causing the false reports. Well, and yeah,
that could be troublesome. Yeah, I could see. Yeah, for sure. What what cost right? Let's see. Sjoan Hunter Matt says I've heard mixed things about Oh, talking about a movie that was made in VR chat. Apparently, there's a movie that is on HBO Max. And I was not aware of this. And as Sjoan Hunter Matt says, I've heard mixed things about it. It was shot entirely in VR chat. I wonder if that won't be the first of several. Like it's just this interesting, you know.
You know, why not? We've heard of the Unreal Engine being made for things like animation and you know, the Unreal Engine being used in movies. Why not have this come full circle where you know, games are I mean, because you know, animation is animation, right? No matter how you do it. For some people, it's construction paper, like if you're the early days of South Park, now we have VR chat. So it's just another way to make movies. It's kind of neat. So all right.
Moving on, I had to let dark soccer talk about this because it's a game she talks a lot about. But I understand it's a good game.
Now, we already knew that there was going to be in Dead by Daylight, a Project W, a new Resident Evil themed chapter. And it's supposed to be out later this year. And it's going to have new survivors, new killer, but they've been leaked.
I think the prestige cosmetics were actually leaked is what it was. So we have, and honestly, I'm going to do the killer last because I totally called this though for the first, the first chapter.
Yeah, I also think at this point, it's obvious if it's not Nemesis, it's who's left, you know, there's, there's other Yeah, it could have been it could have been Birkin. I would have loved to see Lady Dimitrescu. I know she's newer. I would have loved that. But anyway, and she's also very minor.
And she'll be back. I get with the fan reception and the fact that that voice actress wanted a word for the game. She'll be back. That's not going to be her last appearance.
But I'm saying right now, she was a minor character. She wouldn't be series wise as important as who they decided on.
And Jason wasn't the killer in the first movie either. But anyway,
But, but Jason actually was the icon of it.
I know. Moving on.
It would be like if they took like Corey Feldman's character from, from Friday the 13th and made him like the main person in like a game now.
But, and it's Corey Feldman. Anyway, so we have from DBD leaks. There is a picture of what the new perks, the new survivors, plural, and killer.
So the first of the new survivors is Ada Wong and her lovely red dress outfit.
The second is Rebecca Chambers. So maybe she'll play the piano as her perk.
That's anyway, that's surprising. I'm surprised it's her because I think the early, early leaks said somebody else.
Ada Wong was always there. But again, like, how could it not be Ada Wong? That's right. Yeah.
That was missing. She's fire. Yeah. Now the killer, the killer.
The person that I claimed it would be for the last chapter is the one for this chapter, and it is Albert Wesker.
And he's got a knife. And I'm pretty down for it. The new perks for Rebecca.
It looks like it's going to be reassurance, react.
Yeah, reassurance better than new and hyper focus because, you know, she was the team medic.
And then for Ada, it's reactive healing, low profile.
Basically, the icon is her taking off her high heels and walking barefoot and then wiretap, which I'm going to guess is an is an aura perk.
And then for Wesker's killer perks, we have terminus, awakened awareness and super anatomy.
And the super anatomy icon looks like he's vaulting. I wonder if he's going to be like Legion.
Yeah, it's hard to know because we don't know what the perks do. We just know what they're called. But yes, we have the icons, though.
Yeah, just that one vaulting. I mean, so far, the only killer that can that has like a survivor style vault is Legion, and that requires being in frenzy.
And some killers can mess with vaults. Like I think a bamboozle from clown is kind of the go to or spirit. Spirit has an add on that can mess with them too.
And chlorophobia. That does it too. And wait, not chlorophobia. Yeah, chlorophobia does it. And there's also that one trickster one. The hex.
Oh, no, that's a blight, isn't it? Or is it?
You're right. Yeah, there's a hex term.
It's crowd control. Yeah, crowd control. Because I know it had to do with like his fandom stuff.
But yeah, so I think it's kind of neat instead of having someone that affects the vault just to have someone who can just say screw it and vault.
Because people don't expect that. That's actually one of my favorite things about Legion is going into frenzy and vaulting something and having someone go, oh, shit.
So, speaking of rumors, if we're talking about Dead by Daylight rumors, the Stranger Things rumors are picking up steam again. I don't know where this is coming from.
I can tell you where it came from. So there were some fake leaks of a half rendered Vecna.
Right. And a few people who I thought were more reputable posted these pictures and said, oh, this is without a doubt, et cetera, blah, blah, blah, my butt.
And then after that, one of the same people, by the way, said, no, this is fake, this is fake.
But then we had in the current tome, there is the scene of the two kids hiking and they come across a bunny and she tries to get the bunny to eat a carrot and the bunny will eat the carrot.
So she bites the carrot, holds it out and the bunny bites her. And then a swarm of those bunnies attack her and her friend. And they have Demogorgon mouths.
Oh, and that's why for the new tome, like some of the charms that came out are our bunnies with blood on them.
Interesting. Of course, you know what I keep thinking of that.
It's like, run away, run away. That rabbit's dynamite. We need a holy hand grenade right now.
I really do hope this, I would love to see more Stranger Things content and more. I love the idea of Joyce as a survivor. I don't know if they would do, a lot of people are saying Eddie would be a great one. I don't know. We'll see. We'll see what happens.
So what you're saying is you want a Monty Python Dead by Daylight update. We can have the killer bunny. We can have King Arthur and then Sir Robin of Loxley. Or Sir Robin the Brave, I'm sorry.
They're not quite so brave as Sir Lancelot.
I'd be a funny April Fools if nothing.
Who personally wet himself at the Battle of Baden Hill. And then the aptly named Sir Not Appearing in this game.
On a somewhat related note with all this, Behavior Entertainment, the company behind Dead by Daylight, and of course, we know is making the Hooked on You dating sim. They're supposed to be having like an anniversary stream.
They're not making Hooked on You. Another company is making Hooked on You.
Oh, my bad. My bad. But they have like a 30th anniversary stream or so, which who knew that they've been around that long.
I mentioned it last week.
Right. Right. But this would be a time for them to announce things like that. Maybe. Maybe. Who knows?
All right. Let's move on. More rumors. But now we let Dark Soccer talk about her game. Now we'll let you talk about yours, Loki. Rumors for the series you're into.
Hasn't been my game for a while now.
Fair.
It's fine.
I will fully play that when the next one comes out. But like, I'm just not, I'm not hyped about it better. It better not be one of those games as a service games without a single player. But anyways, Grand Theft Auto 6, obviously still something that's out there somewhere in development hell, I don't know.
But apparently Bloomberg has a report talking about some of the details of the game and how they want to kind of change up like the protagonists and all that stuff. So they're going to have a playable female protagonist. They say that she'll be a Latina and a part of I guess part of their parrot is going to be like some sort of Bonnie and Clyde type story.
That sounds kind of cool. And then of course, they're saying that some of the things that are going to be different in this game versus other like Grand Theft Auto games is the whole sexualization of women in it. Obviously, you know, in the past, it's been something that they've done quite a bit. And it's just not necessarily something that's as appropriate anymore.
So and that also has to do with the fact that Rockstar is kind of moving away from that whole boys club thing into, you know, acting like, you know, professional people instead. So it'll be interesting to see what comes of all this stuff. I mean, cool that they have a female lead. They've done it before in other Grand Theft Auto games. It's just not mainline stuff that they had that in. But yeah, I mean, that's fine is also stories good.
I don't really care who the protagonists are. Right. It'd be cool if you could just go the same road route and just have a protagonist be, you know, not really a gender just have it whoever you want to be. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I imagine for story purposes, that's why they're trying to kind of build it around a predetermined character. But I get it.
really need to because they've done this in Grand Theft Auto online, like Grand Theft Auto online, you play your own character, and it just works. Now I get it, like with the voice acting stuff like that. But like, you can get around that with just like how Saints Row does it. So I don't know, I think that that I'll be the way I would do it. But they can do it.
You can well in Mass Effect had two voice actors play the main part. So you could, you know, have Jennifer Hale or Marc Meir be your voice, you know, so it's, it's, it's a story that they want to tell. I'm cool that whatever. Yeah. All right. Well, speaking of people telling their own stories, for our last story tonight, let's talk a little bit about what happened with Nier because, man, did people did folks have people convinced that there was a new secret area in Nier
Automata. And I'll just kind of tell you the end first. It turned out this whole thing was fake and was done by a very advanced sort of mod. A Redditor uploaded a video showing a new area in Nier Automata that pretty much nobody had ever seen before. It kind of led its way to like a church looking area kind of like behind like a hidden door or something. So there was a hallway that goes to a church and so forth. And this caused the community to go nuts because, you know, the
creators of this game have said a long time ago, everything has been found. But it would also not be unlike the creators of Nier to lie about that and have something secret there. So people were just, you know, going bonkers thinking, Oh, my gosh, is there this whole undiscovered thing we're just now finding? Well, again, as it turns out, nope, it was just a modder having a lot of fun. But boy, a lot of people bought it, but it was a very convincing mod, that's for sure. By the way, it's interesting, because
Yosuke Saito, who's one of the producers of the game, didn't confirm or deny it, and just said eternal mystery in a tweet. So like they were throwing gasoline on the fire by tweeting like that. But again, that's how these devs are. And it's cool. So some folks in chat, Mike Deff says all that Nier story was fascinating and hilarious. Yeah, that's why I bring it up now. It's just I thought it was just funny how much, like not just the Reddit and the fans were buying into it.
But how the developers were having fun with it, too.
The video did look pretty neat.
Yeah, it was very convincing, wasn't it? It was. It looked really good. Fifth Dream in chat says this is like when the first Pokemon Gen 2 leaks happened. And the group had a Twitch stream where they mocked up a ROM hack and pretended it was the actual game. But a lot of it wasn't fake, but it was in a different form, and they didn't disclose that. So it's the lengths the folks will go to. So yeah, pretty cool.
And a reminder that that game is coming out on the Nintendo Switch pretty soon that yeah, they're gonna scale that down for the Nintendo Switch. So that should be interesting. But if you haven't played it yet, I still need to finish it. But I enjoyed, added to the list, but I enjoyed what I did play of it. It's very, very, the music especially really caught my attention to that game. It's just such so well scored.
All right, let's get to the listener roundtable. So every week we invite you to give us a call over at vog.network.com slash discord. But we also welcome your emails over at participate at orange lounge radio.com. And something I promised to get into in a recent episode was that we would do more tweets over at OLR if you have some tweets for us. So did you want to? Did you want to do tweets DarkSakra?
I'm sorry, not to I'm sorry, emails. Sorry. You're also muted. It's hard mute on Discord. See the icon?
Yeah, I can see it. Oh, I, I don't do tweets.
I know. Sorry. Sorry. You were texting me something and it caused my wires to cross. Yeah.
All right. Hello, LR. Just a few thoughts on last week's episode. The classic game of the week was Mushihime-sama, an excellent cave shoot-em-up that I have very much enjoyed. But here's a bit of information that wasn't part of the segment. The game was actually re-released on Nintendo Switch about a year ago. It's 20 bucks. It's really good if you like games of this type. You should totally go buy it.
Logie lamented about how he can't get sim files for StepMania X and even offered to pay for them. Unfortunately, though, even if these were available, it would be physically impossible to play them on a DDR cabinet because of the game's five panel layout.
Yeah, but they have a four panel mode, though, in the game. So yes, it would be completely possible to do it.
Because DDR machines, like I said, yeah, I know. I'm going to still read the email. Because DDR machines lack a center panel, the charts would all need to be redesigned to not use it. Also, the game does not separate charts into four panel, five panel, et cetera, like DDR used to. There are simply difficulty levels. So there is an actual reason why this don't exist. Sorry to be the bringer of bad news.
They have a no center mode that you can play because I played it in the arcade. It's just, you know, it'd be someone having to dump that. But yeah, I get it. It's not convenient.
Last but not least, I have heard a phrase during last week's show that truly horrified me simply because I believe it is thoroughly impossible to say 10 times fast ABBA album. Good luck. ABBA album isn't hard to say.
Um, thanks again for the show as always. Have a great week. Aaron Yyr.
Maybe ABBA Abacus album, but they didn't have an album called Abacus. Because ABBA doesn't do Abacus. But it's just a note to ponder for future weeks.
All right. Thank you for the email Yyr. Participate at orangesonsrader.com if you want to send us an email. I will do some tweets. I haven't done tweets in a long time, but we have two tweets I want to get to tonight.
Uh, dark to see you tweeted us and I this was great because I checked this out today. I learned arcade infinity was also a hotspot for Street Fighter four. Yeah, it was it was huge for fighting games and not just music games. The times we have found this mini doc on YouTube from one of our former listeners. I happen to still be friends with on Facebook. Who is the former listener because I didn't catch who it was all grown up.
But I did watch the doc and the documentary was called a home for the SoCal FGC or fighting game community inside arcade infinity. And there was a lot of like photos and videos and I fucking took me back. It took me back and it got into the reasons why it closed.
I didn't realize that the business didn't go belly up. The city was basically shutting them down because they didn't like all the kids hanging out there at three in the morning. Because remember how remember how that arcade was open late. It was open late. Like I think their posted hours were 2am like a bar. But I'm that place went to like three or 4am. So Oh, dark to see you said that was ryc three. I didn't know that. I remember that name from back in the day. Heck yeah.
So check out the documentary. I thought it was cool. And it gives a little taste of what because they they do brush the music game thing a bit because they're talking about in the documentary about like, yeah, while people were waiting to play Street Fighter four, they had all of these music games and a lot of people that played this also played these over here. And just talking about the crossover between the two. So yeah, I didn't realize I mean, I probably knew it at the time but didn't forget because admittedly, I'm not as embedded in the fighting game community. I'm not as good as those games.
I appreciate them, but I don't follow them as closely. I did not realize arcade infinity was like the only place you could play Street Fighter four for a while. I didn't realize that.
The thing about selling import cars.
They they brush on that a little bit in the documentary. I think it was just it was that was how they were getting all their machines was because of the inroads they made with the import car stuff. So they that part they brush on a little bit.
I had actually been looking into getting a skyline.
That's cool.
Oh, that's how I when I and when I was looking for, you know, a seller. I came across arcade infinity and I was like, what?
No, that's funny. All right. We do have a call waiting in the green room. So I want to go ahead and take this and then we'll get to another tweet here in a moment. But first, let's pull in our listener from the green room. Hi, you're on orange launch radio. Who's this?
Hey, this is deaf. Hey, deaf. It's good to hear from you. What's up, buddy?
I want to ask you a question, especially regarding a game that recently came out. Basically, my question is that has there been a game that you weren't interest at all? Like you didn't even care for it until you saw someone play it.
And then you it's like, I want to play that play Dead by Daylight.
And also the Mass Effect was like that for me, too.
Yeah, I feel like Twitch has been really instrumental in finding a lot of that stuff, don't you think? I mean, that's for me anyway, I could say that.
I'm trying to think of a specific game, though, like that.
A game that I watched people play and it made me want to play it because I hadn't really seen it before.
You know, it probably wasn't until I really watched, you know, since we just talked about it, probably when I really started watching people playing Nier Automata that really made me interested in it because I kept writing it off because I had that original one on Xbox 360 that wasn't really Nier Replicant.
They kind of changed it for this side and everything. And I was like, it wasn't that great. I don't know why people are really into that. And then when I kind of watched people play, I was like, Oh, this looks like it might be really cool.
So I think that would be maybe an answer for me. Or maybe even like if you want to go way back, maybe the first time I ever played DDR.
I didn't know if it was something for me, but I watched other people playing and I thought this is so cool. But DDR at the time was such an extra machine to begin with.
I mean, let's be real with the flashing lights and the cheesy techno music and also like that machine was just extra to begin with.
So watching the people because I've told this story on the show before I'm almost positive. The first time I ever saw DDR, I was walking into a tournament at Milpitas Golf Land.
But that wasn't the first time I played DDR. This is the first time I saw it because I couldn't get on the machine because it was surrounded by people and people doing stunts and things.
But when I finally came across a machine in Las Vegas, we missed an entire night at the Rocky Horror Picture Show convention to stay up and play DDR instead.
So that was my story with that. Pod Culture in chat says, Halo for me. That's a good one. Because I always wrote off Halo as shooty, shooty, bang, bang. I'm not going to be into it.
But then when my friend had a Halo at his wedding reception, I kind of had to try it. And I was like, Oh, this is really fucking fun. Because they had the local area networked Xboxes.
And we all played like in the same room. And it was it was a lot of fucking fun. So I was I was I was into it after that. I think that's a really good answer is Halo.
Loki, do you have one?
DDR.
Yeah, DDR as well. Yeah.
Yeah.
Well, act deaf to you know, I love to turn the question back on the asker. What about you?
Oh, and this is why I'm calling right now. And it's Digimon Survive, actually.
Oh, I've been hearing a lot about this game this week. Tell me more.
Yeah, I've been watching a streamer I'm up for play this weekend. And I have heard about the game and it was Oh, it's a tactical RPG, hard visual novel and I wasn't like really interested in it, even though it's Digimon and I do like Digimon.
But after watching him play and seeing how the story develops, it's like, Oh my god, I really now I really want to play this game. Like, it's so so good.
And, and it's like, and again, it's like, I wasn't even like interested. It's like, I'll maybe play it if it comes to game pass or if I find it like cheap.
And it's like, No, now and now I want a physical copy of it. Because, again, the story is basically mostly the story that has been like, really, really good.
Because it's not you think Digimon do you think? Oh, it's a it's a kid's game. It's a it's a it's a game for kids. It's nothing too serious.
Just like Pokemon, right?
It lives up to its name. It's survived. It goes like, really, really hard.
Yeah. Okay.
You don't have you don't have any idea. I probably don't.
And for example, for Jamie that I know she loves Digimon.
The first season or adventure, the parallels between this game and that season are like, really, really close.
So I think if you like the story from Digimon adventure, the first season you're gonna you're gonna love this.
The first two seasons were my favorite. Those are the cast that I care about.
You know, the parallels between the characters are really similar.
You know, it's really Oh, go ahead, Jamie.
I just said cool. Oh, um, you know, it's really interesting to me how how influential like the Twitch culture and YouTube culture, you know, just streaming and all that really can play into like there's there's a reason why companies will pay influencers and people with a lot of viewers, sometimes maybe not even a lot of viewers like I've been asked to do it in the past.
I don't have that huge of an audience. But there's a reason why companies will maybe not like I didn't get paid in that circumstance, but I got a free copy of the game.
And I was like, All right, sure. But there's a reason why companies will dangle those carrots to try to get exposure because it's when people watch others play it that they go, Oh, maybe this is pretty cool.
And even though I didn't explicitly stay at dead dead by daylight was absolutely one for me as well.
Because I watched Alan play it and play it and play it and I was like, what is so fucking great about this game.
And then I watched people play it on Twitch. And I was like, Oh, you know, I watched like, a lot of LGBT, you know, a lot of the LGBTQ community plays dead by daylight.
And I watched some really relatable people playing the game. And I was like, Oh, this is actually like, even though I don't like scary all the time and the heartbeat thing kind of this actually looks like it could be a lot of fun.
And I got into it. So yeah, and I keep saying Twitch, Twitch, Twitch, but the same thing's true about YouTube, you know, and the videos over there and so forth.
So it's just, it's interesting how that whole sense of exposure is really important in this day and age for your game. Absolutely.
Which is curious, because nobody got a review copy of Digimon Survive. The marketing is almost unexistent.
Interesting.
Yeah, it's weird, but people are talking about it. So that's great.
Do you know another game that the publisher completely wrote off and then, you know, then just became a huge monster hit? Until Dawn.
You might remember was kind of written off by Sony in many ways, like it was originally announced to the PS3, and it kind of disappeared and got released without a lot of fanfare.
But then, again, I would say in big part, thanks to streaming, and that whole thing became huge. And now we have the quarry, we have the Medal of Medan and the Dark Pictures Anthology and all those games are all because of that.
So it's interesting how that that and God probably things like Minecraft, you know, were huge because of streaming and so forth. You know, it's just interesting how much that has really affected things.
Dr. Tsubita answered your question, and I thought this was a clever answer. It wasn't a video game, but that does kind of start sound like my start with Magic the Gathering.
Everyone in my high school was getting into it. So I had to see what the fuss was all about. So that that pure influence. Absolutely. And pure influence isn't necessarily, you know, in that case, he's probably talking about the school lunchroom table.
But, you know, thanks to technology, we've got a big table now and lots of people showing off what they're playing. But I love the question, Deft. Any other comments or thoughts for us tonight?
No, that will be all.
All right. Well, thank you so much. Have a wonderful week and may all your Pokmon be shiny.
Thank you.
All right. Take care, my friend.
All right. Always good to hear from Act Deft. Let's get to the other tweet I wanted to read while we do a last call for any calls tonight on our Discord over at vognetwork.com slash Discord.
We got another tweet from Blue Swim, who passed along, hey, saw this and immediately thought of you all. And it was a quote tweet for a sad day for Bomani Games.
The last DDR Kids cabinet is going to be removed from public access at this time with a little Facebook post that says for those in the area, the last and only public DDR Kids machine is going away at the arcade that houses it at the end of August.
Sayama Cat's Eye is in Saitama. It is in the kids play area, not the arcade area. So you need to pay to get into that part first and then you can play it for free all you want.
I had forgot there was a DDR Kids machine. But then when I saw the screen, I was like, oh, yeah, that was a thing. So but, you know, a little piece of history.
Let's let's be honest, though, as much as yes, the news is sad. Let's also be impressed that here it is the year 2022 and that machine was still standing quite honestly. I think that's pretty incredible. So all right.
All right. Well, I think that's going to do it. That was all the emails. That was all the calls. That was all the tweets. So thank you so much for that. If you have a tweet you want to send us in a future week at OLR.
Mike Deft in chat wanted to amend his call and just mention, oh, something I did forget to add about Digimon Survive. It is mostly a visual novel. The tactical game is like only 25% of the game. But the story again is really engaging and your decisions have an impact on the story.
Hey, just because it's a visual novel doesn't make it bad. Hello, dream daddy. Need I say more? All right. Hot to full boyfriend. Need I say more? All right.
Yeah, I mean, that's those are the fun things. I enjoy that.
Exactly. Exactly. Wow. As you're wondering, Matt says NYC got rid of the last phone booze in Times Square, which led to young people to say what's a phone booth? Well, you know, people it's it's that thing you go into so you can make a private cell phone call because that's how people only use them anymore is to go into them to make a cell phone call.
But, you know, people, people deface those things in many sorts of ways now. So I'm not surprised to getting rid of them.
You want to know what relic though I still see like certain Kaiser locations like the hospitals and whatnot.
Pay phones with the TTY, a teletypewriter. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which now you have phone relay services instead that that they do. Like, I had to actually break myself of my habits from TTY because I used to, you know, answer phone calls from my uncle sometimes.
All right. Well, I think that is going to do actually I should check in for any last minute stories, Loki.
Nope, don't have any.
I figured it's actually all when I'll send that it was a little bit slower of a Newsweek but you know, they can't they can't all be action packed.
All right. That means it's time for us to get around to final thoughts and good night. I want to say thanks as always for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
If you enjoyed what you heard here at the show, tell a friend or two about the show. Help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
But we need more voices here to put them out on air. So please tell a friend a nice five star review wherever you found this show, whether it be iTunes, Spotify, whatever.
Go ahead and click that five star button and that goes a long way as well. In fact, I don't think we've had a written review on iTunes in like three years.
So if somebody wanted to be so kind as to write us a nice review, we wouldn't say no to that. So thank you. Thank you.
Appreciate all that. Let's go around and get folks final thoughts. I will start as usual dark soccer because I know she's going to do some streaming of her own in a minute.
I am going to be joined by Finora for some Debbie Delight. If you or anyone wants to join us, we would love to have you along.
I might pop in for a little bit. I have to see what Alan's got planned this evening, but I should be able to join for a little bit.
All right. Well, and also I all of you are awesome. And don't forget to to share your awesomeness with the world.
All right. I'll try. All right. Take care, Darksira. Loki, we'll go to you. Your final thought tonight.
My final thought is I will try to get a new episode of my Minecraft series out this week.
Sounds good. I'm kind of ahead of the game, so it's fine if I take a little longer.
All right. My final thought, I will try to do some streaming of my own this week. So follow my personal channel if you're not already at Rob Roberts.
And also trying to brainstorm some things for our lovely network here at the voice geeks network and things to push our website forward, hopefully a little bit, because we haven't had a lot of network content in a while, but I'm brewing some ideas.
So Mr. Black Wolf and I luckily have Dragon Con coming up to talk about them. So I hope to see folks at Dragon Con if you're in the area.
And I understand times are still weird. The pandemic is not truly over, even though everyone seems to be over it.
So I totally get people's hesitations. It's all good. You make the shot. You make the call that's best for you.
But if you are interested in going to a big convention, I love Dragon Con in Atlanta area. This will be my 10th year in person, I believe, if I did my math right.
No, no, I think 2012 was my first year because that was the first year of VOG. But I can't count 2020 because we all know why I can't count 2020.
But it's getting to the point I'm losing count of how many times I've been to Dragon Con. I love it so much. So I'm looking forward to seeing everybody there again Labor Day weekend, hopefully.
All right, that's it. We'll see you in seven days. It'll be August, believe it or not. I can't believe it. It's already going to be August.
Pumpkin spice lattes will be here before you know it. Hang on. I know but you know, you know, it sucks because unless they have a sugar free pumpkin, those days are over for me, which is sad.
Oh, do they? Yeah, they have. Hell yes. Let the pumpkining begin. Have a great week, everybody. We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio. Good night.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
To join us for our live show, tune into vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific, 9 p.m. Eastern.
The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
See you next week.