[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, August 25th, 2013, the PlayStation 4's launch is detailed, League of Legends experiences a security breach, and you can soon return digital copies of games in one online store.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, my friends out there on the Internet, and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 517 for this August the 25th of 2013.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pull up a chair in our live chat room, live.vognetwork.com, where you can participate with the program as we talk about video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name's Rob Roberts, here with you as always every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: My co-hosts, say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sniffy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you sound like you are having heck of allergies today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, this morning I woke up and was really congested and it's all sinus too because it's all just in my nose.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know the city where we're based, Sacramento, California, is not a very pleasant one for allergy sufferers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I always thought that was more of a spring thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can get it pretty bad this time of year too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what set it off, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it may have been left over from the fires.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could have been... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, those fires.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's these horrible fires burning outside of Yosemite, this big national park that's... Now, it's really far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, it's probably, what, like a five, six-hour drive from here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, it caused a minor heat wave for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, oh, yeah, I mean, it's really burning out of control.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't think I know anybody in the OLR listening base that lives in that area, but if you do...
[SPEAKER_03]: I really hope you're safe and taking care of yourself, you know, and my thoughts go out to you guys, because pretty terrible, that fire out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've had Benadryl and Sudafed, and I even laid down, well, it just doesn't seem to be doing much good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I hope you feel better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Despite all the fires and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel awful, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, feel better.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you need more coffee, because coffee helps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm full of Ricolas now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of our hometown of Sacramento, I wanted to mention this real quick with you and we referenced this on Bobby Blackwolf's show just before we went live tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here in Sacramento, California, you know, once in a while we get celebrities because they come up here from Hollywood to lobby for different bills and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or in this case, come from England.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, or we used to have a governor, but I won't go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Y'all know about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in this case... That's actually happened twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there was Reagan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, he was a famous movie actor too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, past all the politics stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Democrat, Republican, and everything in between.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter who you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: You love John Barrowman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you know who he is.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get to that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Tech Master Loki had no idea who he was.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he's from Doctor Who and Torchwood.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he was one of the people in the new producers.
[SPEAKER_04]: He also was on a couple of series in England where it was like one of them was How Do You Solve a Problem Like Maria?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where they cast for West End plays.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did stage stuff and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically like American Idol for stage theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: and he's just, no matter your sexuality or who you are, like you have to admit, he is a very gorgeous, handsome man.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a lot of people like him for that reason alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he's here in Sacramento and we can't figure out why.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a big nerd convention coming up next weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't he just be in town?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, but I'm kind of like, well, why would he... Well, and I'm even thinking about the little bit I know about him.
[SPEAKER_04]: His family's in Florida.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the rest of his... And he lives in England.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe he came to San Francisco and thought he'd swing by.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's my hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since he's supposed to be at DragonCon in a few days, as am I, I got my fingers and my toes crossed that we might be on the same flight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't pray very often, but if anybody up there is listening, I want to be on the same flight as John Barrowman to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_03]: Five and a half hours on a plane with John Barrowman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, please!
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you flying?
[SPEAKER_03]: Delta.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the only one that had a direct flight to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have a first class.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if his husband came along.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he was in the pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listeners are here to... They're entirely too cute together.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're here to hear about video games, not to hear about John Barrowman, although quite frankly, who's going to complain?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Tech Master Loki will complain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Tech Master Loki, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Doing good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: John Barrowman, Adam's Ass in a Photo Op
[SPEAKER_03]: and I bet Adam didn't wash that ass for an entire week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or at least the jeans attached to the ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least the jeans attached to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Techinus in chat suggesting I make friends with a stewardess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're called flight attendants now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alan Alchemy says, Rob, you aren't in first class though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't mean I won't still find a way to run into him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't question my powers.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, how have you been?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a whole ton.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I thought of you earlier today because apparently all this Grand Theft Auto 5 information is leaking to the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And at first I thought, oh my gosh, there's a pirated version of the game out there already and those poor guys are going to lose those sales because it's already out there on the internet when we're weeks away from launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's not totally the case, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going on in the Grand Theft Auto world?
[SPEAKER_02]: The European region had the digital version of it that people had pre-ordered.
[SPEAKER_02]: It became live for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not necessarily live, but you can pre-load it.
[SPEAKER_02]: People were downloading the 18GB file to their PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, they would dump it and try to hack it to get it to run and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, he says there's no way to open up the archives yet because they don't have the keys to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think that the executable is included with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's what comes in the patch.
[SPEAKER_02]: So even if you could...
[SPEAKER_02]: WhatUpG in our chatroom says the soundtrack leaked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so the soundtrack's leaked, and a lot of the spoilers from the game have leaked as well because they have all the cutscene audio, so people are documenting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been pretty good in trying to stay away from all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did read one thing, but I kind of figured some of the people from the other games would be coming back in the game, like a cameo or something like that, so it's not a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm trying not to read any spoilers in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: If there was a working version out there that leaked to the internet, that's a whole other story.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not necessarily spoiling, you're playing through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Illegally.
[SPEAKER_02]: I intend on purchasing on both platforms, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it did leak, you would be downloading it and playing it, and yes, you'd be one of those bad people, but you would still be buying two copies of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: that's why I'm not giving you a worse time about it yeah I'm still you know I'm buying it on both platforms just so I can play with my friends because I don't know what platform they're going to play on you know I still want to play on 360 because I like the controller better but you know my boss plays on PS3 and he's trying to get other people to buy the PS3 version as well I guess there's one of my co-workers in Dallas he's buying both versions as well so I still want to play on 360 but I think a lot of people are playing on PS3 as well so I'll just have to play both
[SPEAKER_03]: and WhatUpG in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com also says, I am not here to spoil things.
[SPEAKER_03]: If people want spoilers, they can look for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's the nice thing to do, so please, chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Y'all are very well behaved, but please do not spoil Grand Theft Auto V. If you want to look up spoilers, it's on gtaforums.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a whole section of their forum dedicated to Grand Theft Auto V spoilers if you really want to look at it, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fine with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll look at the track list.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not spoiling anything for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to look up any of the cutscene audio stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to listen to any of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just too close to coming out to spoil myself on some of the stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like Easter eggs and stuff, that's a whole different thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll look that stuff up because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know you are very much looking forward to Grand Theft Auto V. What's the big day again?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're about three weeks out.
[SPEAKER_02]: 17th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Four weeks out.
[SPEAKER_02]: 17th, but I'm hoping to get that Friday before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Using your connections.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get into what we've been playing this week, but I do have a few other topics I want to address here at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, I do want to say a big hello and hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: It
[SPEAKER_03]: DragonCon
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I've met a variety of listeners at PAX East and E3 and PAX Prime and whatever other conventions I've been at, ASEN, so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I would love to meet more at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get three opportunities now.
[SPEAKER_03]: The folks at DragonCon have been wonderful in just kind of helping us get involved.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Saturday night, 5.30 at the Hilton 203, the VOG Super Show, where several of us from VOG are going to get together to talk about the story about VOG Network and
[SPEAKER_03]: and talk about what it's like to have been podcasting for so long and where we see our future is going and maybe
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a surprise announcement in store.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be recording that, because that would be kind of cool to record that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be recording that, and Bobby will be putting it on his feed later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Bobby Blackwolf says, hello to people in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is literally what I'm doing right now, saying hello to the future people, the tomorrow people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you know, I'd have to give you my little contribution on the whole thing, and that would be sitting in the middle of my classroom, in my portfolio class, using that time to work on Logo.
[SPEAKER_04]: and my teacher being perfectly fine with it because it was all stuff that was going to go in my portfolio.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I'll do for you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that the panel to kind of make it like you were there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just every 30 seconds or so, I'll just go... No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't sound like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just being a jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're being a bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: In all seriousness, giving Jamie a hard time.
[SPEAKER_03]: In all seriousness, though, on Sunday, we're going to be a part of the Parsec Awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have been honored to be asked to be a part of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be like, I don't know, it's going to be like I'm on stage at the Oscars giving an award, although it's on a much different scale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wear a swan dress.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you should do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to wear a swan dress with an egg.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would sit on Travis's lap and lay an egg.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you know what we need to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to go to an airbrush place that does t-shirts and have them make you a swan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you've got 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've had one done in an hour, so you can get a swan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll draw you a swan.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome, a swan dress t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can be Bjork.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that will be that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are presenting one of the awards towards the end of the ceremony.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then on Monday, there's a panel about live streaming and about doing live streams and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby's on the panel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to support.
[SPEAKER_03]: And as somebody who does a lot of live streaming himself through this show, through game streaming and so forth...
[SPEAKER_03]: And that'll be a good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's Monday at 11, 1130 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just look for the streaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: At something in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: At something in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be a miracle that I'm awake because I'll probably still be on the West Coast clock and on convention sleep.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be a miracle that I'm awake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Eight o'clock in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: On convention time though, oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already been told about all the drinks I'm going to be made to consume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's hope I don't end up in the hospital for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I could make it to a morning where I actually woke up as late as 8 o'clock, that would be a miracle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I might sound peppy today because there's a lot of things to be excited about, but last night, thanks to traffic, we went to San Francisco last night and didn't get back home because of traffic until 3 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: and... Baseball game or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, there was construction on Highway 80 where they were reducing it down to one lane.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they repaving lanes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every asshole has to speed up as far as they can to the last minute to merge in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they were also putting up warnings that the Bay Bridge was going to be closed during the next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not even it, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this like national or, I don't know, like California State, you know, Repave Your Street Month or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because everybody is repaving the goddamn street.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody is doing it all like the last couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there's a lot of construction stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, listeners don't care about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But DragonCon, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So things going on Saturday, Sunday, Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to follow me on Twitter, I'll post updates about where I'm at provided my phone has a charge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twitter.com slash Sky, S-K-I-E.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my personal Twitter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can follow me there and get your DragonCon updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Loki, sadly not coming with me to DragonCon, but I know we'll be following the news from PAX at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to SchoolCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually dropping a class and taking another class.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised you're not going to go to SacAnime at least for a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, SacAnime costs money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess who doesn't have a job?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't pull media strings.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually, I tried, it's too late.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm trying to get us in for a panel next con.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes please.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would totally Skype in, I know how con wifi is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, con wifi is a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd love to have you, but that's why we're not live streaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to know why we aren't live streaming the panel, especially when we have big news to talk about, that's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you cannot depend on hotel wifi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I'm sure they bring in the Uber stuff for DragonCon, which is a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of problems going on with Final Fantasy XIV's launch, which is really unfortunate, but they're having some severe network issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you get in the game, it's a fairly pleasant experience, except for the fact that the first day, instances weren't working, which usually in most MMOs isn't a big deal, except in Final Fantasy XIV, you have story instances you have to do about every five levels, and you go into solo instances and beat them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is fun, and it helps you learn about your character and so forth, but when the instance finder's down, that really sucks, because you can't progress your character past level 10, unless you had a character who was already higher level.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't forget about the fates lasting four times as long as normal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so it's just a mess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which wasn't bad, it was a lot of experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: It really sucks that these network issues are taking away that attention from what is otherwise a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it really sucks that Square Enix wasn't a little better prepared for it, which every MMO has the same damn story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every MMO has the same exact story when it comes to launching and servers being offline stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why did Microsoft think that they're going to be different?
[SPEAKER_02]: with their whole online tie to, you know, consoles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's going to screw that up, but we won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: We won't screw it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, because he's saying with the Xbox One, you know, and we were saying at the time, we said, look at what happened to Diablo 3, look at what happened to SimCity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, just add Final Fantasy 14 to that list.
[SPEAKER_02]: SimCity, perfect example of like, well, we saw what happened with Diablo 3 and
[SPEAKER_02]: We're taking precautions to make sure that doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's like, you just cursed yourself, you stupid idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: No matter who you are, these situations are going to keep happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the first Final Fantasy XIV version 1.0 was such a stinker that they probably were legitimately not expecting this many people from North America to give it a second chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's amazing and speaks to the quality of the game that people are giving it a second chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: so he's you know he's a great guy and you know is is also a nerd as well as doing sports ball for a living and sticks up for all this stuff well he was writing these tweets this weekend very angry and he was so mad he couldn't even redeem his code for Final Fantasy 14 that he did a charge back on buying the game you know which wow yeah I know it's kind of a dick thing to do but I get it but there's probably a lot of people out there that are feeling kind of ripped off and it kind of
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: How do we get around that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing is, that's why Microsoft's pushing the whole Azure server thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically virtual servers, so they can scale them back pretty fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Virtual servers, so basically they can scale them back pretty fast when it does die off instead of having all this hardware that they're running.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're running a bunch of virtual machines, and so there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe something like that would help, and then that way...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a hard balancing game because you don't want to buy too many servers or have too many of them running because you're not going to need them past launch once that kind of evens out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you deal with spending less money up front and having people kind of be a little bit pissed about it for two weeks and then leveling off and everybody kind of forgetting about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you spend a lot of money and have everybody be happy but you're out all that extra money up
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think what has to happen is that a lot of MMOs at this point really need to kind of challenge themselves on the multiple server way of thinking that a lot of MMOs do and I see some MMOs and I think Guild Wars and I'm even thinking back to the original Guild Wars is a great example of this kind of has the and you see Warcraft moving towards this too with their whole servers that they're talking about the virtual servers where we need to really like you might be on a different box you might be playing on a different machine but
[SPEAKER_03]: but it's one world it's one world and you are phased to the people that you want to play with and so forth like Guild Wars did this you go into the city and you could pick which one of the 50 different copies of the city do you want to be in and then when you go out in the world you're in your own little instance and I think that was a good way to kind of challenge the traditional you're on your server and you don't leave those servers and if you want to change servers 25 bucks kind of way of thinking
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's just dumb anyways because copying a file across the server Well, that's World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's World of Warcraft right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like charging you $75 to put a cabin air filter in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It takes like one second.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I hated the cross-server instances as well, which is one of the big reasons I quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hated it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would rather be on one server with the people who I know are on one server.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what if you have that one friend who's on another server?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the way WoW does it, I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny for Drew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hated when you're out in the world and it crossed server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loathed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that screwed up the crafting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, I don't... It screwed up everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to get too much into the WoW talk because, you know, I already have another show for a lot of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think this MMO stuff is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I wanted to play cross-server, it was with someone I knew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could choose to play with somebody I wanted to play with.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just need to put out the server program or whatever for Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just let it go.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are dying to hack the crap out of that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to play that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free-to-play would have been awesome for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got to go free-to-play or close pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just released an expansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: The very last PlayStation 2 game ever made was a Final Fantasy XI expansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have to... They don't have to do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't have to do shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't have to do a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have to die and pay taxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even then, you know, corporations get out of the taxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get into how was your gamey week and specifically what types of games have you been playing this week besides XIV and all that?
[SPEAKER_03]: What other games have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fractal, Dragon Age 2, Mass Effect 3, and Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there something going on with a Dragon Age renaissance?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Alan's been really into Dragon Age this week, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Age 2
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um, yeah, I wasn't super impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might go back and play Origins and Awakenings, but I just wanted to finish it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That, and you know, while there was server maintenance going on, I was like, okay, I'll just play something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really didn't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't had the energy to care.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's like, when one thing goes down, well, it's not like I don't have 50,000 other things to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the way a lot of people should look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not to dig up the old topic we just left, but I will say, like most things in gaming, a month from now, who's going to remember all this fuckery?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very few people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we'll still remember it, but we won't be angry about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be past it, because you'll all be busy playing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, remember when PlayStation 3 was hacked?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember when Xbox 360 took all those people's money through the EA games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember all these things that happened that we just kind of... Remember when they... You know, just Red Ring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember when Diablo 3 launched and it was shit?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, Diablo 3 launches in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you think that's going to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's going to do very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't seem pretty popular so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a whole ton coming out in September, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Grand Theft Auto, and then FIFA, and Diablo.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rayman, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's probably going to be the second biggest game of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, was there anything else you wanted to say about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I didn't mean to deviate from it too much, but you were having a sneezy.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, I think something might have set off my allergies worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope it wasn't the kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's the kitty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't be anything in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it the stuff I used to vacuum earlier, maybe?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, but it's now getting into my eyes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, I feel better.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you need to go outside for a minute or something, do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com FifthDream says, I want the Diablo 3 expansion a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be talking about that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: DungeonBuster says, the trailer for that looks nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Codeman says, never forget Final Fantasy XIV, A Realm Reborn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, honestly, Codeman, you could probably insert any other MMO in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every single one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never forget Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Square Enix would probably want you to forget about Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: The smoothest MMO launch I probably played was probably actually Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will give them credit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a pretty smooth launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it still had its share of problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Defiance wasn't so bad, but that's also because no one was playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I only played Saints Row 4 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually started off playing the Xbox 360 version, but then once my Steam version unlocked, I just went ahead and finished up and played on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm pretty much... I'm almost 100% complete.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have just one mission left, so I've been finishing up all the activities, and I'm almost gold in everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have all the collectibles collected, and I have...
[SPEAKER_02]: Almost all the activity is done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a few more that have the gold that I had silver on, but I'll probably be done with it today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which brings me to more about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little pseudo-review, if you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and then as you get to the point where you're finding more of your crew members, you're taking them out of the simulation and you're starting to do the loyalty missions and stuff, it's where they start actually getting pretty creative with the actual missions and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's some pretty funny stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is one with Asha where it's a whole rip on Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so there's...
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole point in there is like, okay, in this section, we're going to need to shoot at the lights.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we're going to have to take out the guard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now this is going to be completely different.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'm going to need you to do is I need you to shoot at the lights.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there was a mission with Pierce where they do a duet with – is it the song –
[SPEAKER_02]: Opposites Attract or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the Paula Abdul song?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's Paula Abdul.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they do that and they also sing some other songs on the radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like that part right there kind of made me smile because that's the part where they're kind of getting down to what made the game as good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the personality in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But a lot of the throughout the whole missions and stuff that this love letter to the fans is basically like, hey, remember how cool Saints Row 2 was?
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, hey, remember how cool Saints Row 2 was?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, remember this guy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how you really did this really fucked up thing to get him back?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how crazy shit was back in that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: or they're just reskins of weapons that were in other games and also what's up with you know them saying hey we're not going to have these missions where we're basically going to have you do the activities and kind of force you to do that no actually all that's in there in fact the last bits of the loyalty missions you have to do for your crew members are all the fucking activities in the game that's all it is they didn't even bother to think up new missions they just like
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, do this fucking activity because we developed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the fact that they're basing a lot of these activities off of, what is it, Cyberblazing, which was in Saints Row the Third, which I think was the worst activity in the whole fucking game, and now they have a whole bunch based off of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the game is still good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just it's sad because they remind you about how great the series was, and there are some moments that are still great, but it's kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like just going through the paces again.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not trying too hard, it seems like, because it's the same world.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's based off the same engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they tweaked some stuff, but the superpowers are fucking from the...
[SPEAKER_02]: They were from the expansion for Saints Row 3rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saints Row 3rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: The superpowers were from Troubled Clones.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just kind of built upon that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my problem with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... I don't see... I mean, there's going to be replayability because the PC version and the modding community is going to be great on it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just been out for a little bit and they already have some pretty cool stuff available already, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Story-wise, I hope the last mission's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm hoping, but I just think it's going to be kind of a letdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God they brought Gat back, because it's very clear once you rescue him and you're actually playing with him in some of the other missions, it's like, why the hell did they kill that guy off?
[SPEAKER_02]: And the way they explained how he came back is brilliant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Once again, it's like, okay, he was a great part of Saints Row 2, and that's kind of why you need him back in the game, because it's going to be hard to figure out where they go for the fifth game from here.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have to scale it back, and I hope that they find a happy medium with number two.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I'm listening to you kind of talk about your disappointment with it, I almost feel like you're saying that you kind of feel like it's still...
[SPEAKER_03]: and that oh my gosh it's not really going to be a full game most people I've heard talk about it say that was really unfounded because they really did all this different stuff with the game and you do get that full game experience but the way you talk about it you make it sound like it is more of an expansion
[SPEAKER_02]: It does seem like... I mean, there's a lot of... There's content in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's missions that are pretty unique.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I'll give them that because... And they do stand out quite well from everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: But a lot of it is just kind of in there just because, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the stuff that they explain in the game is because you were hacking the simulation.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the minigames in there and the activities that they have you do kind of don't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, I understand it's not supposed to make a ton of sense, but it really doesn't make any sense why it's in there other than it's a thing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I have to go in the simulation and throw balls at targets?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or...
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I have to run along this path and collect glowing orbs and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I have to... Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: It worked in Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the problem, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They took so much inspiration, if you will, from Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fucking Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got the superpowers.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the problem with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody wants another Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crackdown got pretty boring after... Well, Crackdown didn't really have a single-player narrative to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically like a, go here, kill guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go here, kill guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've played to 93% completion, so there must be something you really like about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the game and I want to get it done with so I can play Grand Theft Auto V. I've got to finish it before Grand Theft Auto V comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get this out of here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got other things to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the game, but it feels very rushed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know that the team at Volition is great and they worked on stuff, but I feel that they've done so much better work in the past
[SPEAKER_02]: that, come on, there should be no excuse for this kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, it's very, like, I understand what they were trying to do with it, but it just doesn't, maybe it's at the point now where they're like, well, crap, we've got to go crazier for, you know, the fourth game.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do we do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we're going to do superpowers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now, and then it's like, okay, well, we've got to think of a new weapon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got to be really crazy because people are expecting crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the problem, is I think they've gotten stuck in that now, where everything has to be so over the top, and like, ooh, it's a cliche of this, ooh, it's a play on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, I think what they need to do, it's going to be interesting when they have that expansion, the first expansion come out, because they did something similar with Skyrim, the Skyrim team did, where it's like, okay, here's a week, develop something that you want to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we'll put it in the game later on or we'll try to figure out a way for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's where a lot of the great content from Skyrim came from was that kind of like almost like internal game jam type thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really wish that that's what they would do for the fifth game where just put some good ideas together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have been really cool for number four because it is a simulation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take chunks from Stillwater and Steelport and just smash it all together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just take shit from that old map and the Steelport map.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have at least made it different and interesting as opposed to just, okay, we're just going to dump the same map in there and throw some alien shit in the air and call it a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to our chat room with some comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: Live.VogNetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: ShadowNextGen says, the homages in Saints Row 4 are amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have to finish the game, so I can't write a review yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't finished, I haven't done the last mission yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hoping that it just, you know, brings it all back, you know, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you can do She-Ra, but I know that they have the Rainbow Brite costume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty amazing as well, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they do have the Thundercats thing where it's like... That's what I love about... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other real quick gripe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this goes back to just game design and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have three different things that are assigned to the left and right directional pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Left and right directional pad are for selecting your abilities, your super abilities that you're using, or...
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, for changing your radio station, and also for doing a taunt or compliment.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of those have to do with, like, touch the button, hold the button for a little bit, or hold the button for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because, like, half the time, oh, I'm trying to do a taunt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry, I changed the radio station.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, I changed my superpower.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, like, dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is completely stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they have a lot of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I really love about Saints Row is all this over the top shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I need to check it out at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do have a lot of cool costumes in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it'll be interesting to see what other stuff that they add on with DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far, they haven't gone crazy yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll quickly talk about my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already talked ad nauseum about Final Fantasy 14, which honestly has been the majority of my time as the game is new.
[SPEAKER_03]: but there is at least one other game I checked out this week on PlayStation 3 and this was partially a listener recommendation I want to say I don't remember who it was I don't remember if it was in chat or an email I apologize I just remember seeing it on the store and I was like oh yeah somebody told me I should get that and play that so I did download Tekken Revolution which is the free-to-play Tekken game that was that's on the PlayStation 3 now I don't know why I had it in my mind
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why I thought that, but I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I downloaded it, and it's totally not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's where I'm crossing wires or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has nothing to do with cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a straight-up fighting game, just like it was Tekken 7 or something on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a free-to-play game, which is weird, but I...
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually really enjoyed it, come to think of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it was free, and the way that they make their money is that you can play either, I think it's like you can do five player versus player matches, or two versus computer matches before you run out of energy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the computer matches are like arcade style, so if you win, you get to play again and again and again until you get up to like a boss that you kill, like seven people in.
[SPEAKER_03]: and each time you win a match you get a little bit of cash you get a little bit of experience a little bit of these gift points the gift points you end up unlocking characters later on or so I hear I guess it takes a lot to do it because I haven't done it yet the money you can use to up the stats on your character for when you go fight later matches so either now I know I'm not that good at fighting games because I was about to say either I'm really good at fighting games but I know that's not the case
[SPEAKER_03]: Martial Law Arcade Mode Normal
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: a five round match because it's like two out of three and it went the full five rounds like they were equally matched with me and I was very impressed at that especially for a free game so if you like fighting games and you like Tekken why the fuck not it's free now here's how they get your money if you want to play more you got to buy tokens that you can use to play more matches later on
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's little ways that they nickel and dime you in that regard.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as far as a Facebook game on the PlayStation 3, but said Facebook game is like a Tekken 6 or something like that, even though I didn't really care for Tekken 6, but you know, if Tekken 6 had been free, I would have downloaded it and played it still and enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta say, I was pretty impressed by this little free-to-play fighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Overall...
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been pretty impressed with the free-to-play offerings on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jetpack Joyride's pretty good too.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another one I checked out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, honestly, if you're bored and don't really have anything to play right now, or maybe you can't afford to get a new game right now, or just nothing looks appealing to you, go look at what's free on PlayStation 3, because there's some pretty decent stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to be as amazing as The Last of Us or these other big AAA titles that are out right now, but it'll entertain you for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, even if you have PlayStation Plus, it's even better.
[SPEAKER_02]: They announced during Gamescom, Assassin's Creed 3 is coming out later this year as free.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That came out last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the Hitman game was just out last year, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Saints Row the Third, if you haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: ShadowNextGen in chat says, Speaking of free-to-play, Plants vs. Zombies 2 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta put that on my queue because I've been wanting to try that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been able to try that yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really the only new game I can think of to talk about this week is Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what the chatter can think about.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the only new game I can think to talk about otherwise is Tekken Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_03]: I pretty much already talked about what I wanted to talk about as far as DragonCon and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only other thing I'll say for housekeeping is that remember there is no live show next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So enjoy your week off for Labor Day, whatever you're doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a dead show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a dead show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And before I forget, given that we will not have a show next week, I would like to wish my fellow individuals of the Jewish Persuasion, Lashana Tova, Happy New Year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any Labor Day greetings to give the listener?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a Labor Day greeting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That time of year, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: My dad's birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish my dad a happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the birthday of September 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: You doing anything over the holiday, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: You going to barbecue or anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to go to my dad's for dinner on Saturday, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be busy being Jewish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hi to your synagogue friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: To the Jew crew, as Dan calls them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan calls them the Jew crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ideally, Grand Theft Auto V would have leaked out by then, but I can't make any guarantees there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some fun people in the Jew crew.
[SPEAKER_03]: When are we getting some of them back on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, but we had a really rousing game of Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was the first time that, except for me, that any of us had played the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're getting some New Year wishes back there in the chat room from SHA100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Yom Kippur is on the 16th, and I will be busy fasting all day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that on a Sunday?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it was on a Sunday, I wouldn't be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tell you in advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to put up with a Jamie who hasn't eaten.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually all day on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's on a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: No show next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to PAX...
[SPEAKER_03]: Extrofer from Horde House will be there so keep an eye out for him he will be our lone VOG representative at PAX because his partner has family in Seattle so that was the better option for him to go kind of make a trip out of that so they're off to PAX whereas the rest of us are DragonCon
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Time for gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was quite a bit of it this week with Gamescom and all that, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, lots of big announcements.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony came through with what they said they were planning on doing, which was announcing their release plans.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so with that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Germany, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Netherlands, New Zealand, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Russia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, the UK, and I guess Latin America, also Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, El Salvador, Guatemala, Mexico, Panama, and Peru.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the US or North America as well, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't forget.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although no date for Japan yet, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: WhatUpG in chat says, Sony has a press event in September probably to announce the Japanese PlayStation 4 date.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would that mean maybe later?
[SPEAKER_03]: That they get it later?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking that they're probably going to be, it's going to be around the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be later, but I think it's probably... Because that's not usual.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 3, they got it earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I want to say PlayStation 2, they did too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could launch, you know, between that time or like, you know, it's going to be around the same time, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, probably in November still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not get to watch the Sony press conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you watched it, but what did you think of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very reminiscent of E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was weird in the beginning because they basically had someone on stage playing the PlayStation 4 and showing kind of the interface and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also kind of showing that, hey, we're pretty much done with this thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, it's ready to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, definitely we're going to get into a lot more of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, still focused on, like, indie stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They announced some new IPs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, talked more about release dates for different things like, you know, Gran Turismo and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then showed off a lot of the things that, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kind of pulled a few punches still against CM Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, there was a big sick burn at the end, wasn't there?
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a couple, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something about the whole like, and while others have changed their message... I'm going from memory here, this is an exact quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: While where others have changed their messages, we have stayed consistent with our... There was definitely a little...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Shade Throne.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody brought the umbrella to the Sony press conference to make some shade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is a fun time of year because you know who's the winner in this scenario when these two companies are fighting?
[SPEAKER_03]: Us, the gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: hopefully yeah Loki you look a little skeptical at that comment uh yeah we're the winners I think all right all right well let's get into some of those specifics that Loki mentioned a minute ago um here's one about uh and I believe they've announced something similar to this on the Microsoft platform so uh this is you know just kind of meeting the challenge here I think this is through PlayStation Network and I think a lot of it though they're talking more like retailer stuff like Amazon and GameStop doing something similar
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's what we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: The discount upgrade program.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what we're talking about here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, there will be a program where if you buy these games on the PlayStation 3, and these are select games, not necessarily everything, but select games, you'll have the ability to upgrade to the PlayStation 4 version for a, here's my quotey fingers, significantly discounted price.
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty Ghosts, Assassin's Creed 4, Black Flag, Watch Dogs, Battlefield 4
[SPEAKER_03]: Activision and Warner Brothers also publishers that are partnering with Sony on this initiative the upgrade initiative do not know yet if it's a worldwide initiative but certainly for North America at least and if Japan's getting something similar I'm sure that will be detailed at Tokyo Game Show now some other details here even though I just said expect $20 discounts Call of Duty Ghosts has said $10 not $10 off $10 off
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty Ghosts
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would think who this is going to most apply to are the people that are just like, not this year for the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to get their PlayStation 4s in 2014, you know, when some more software comes out, when next year's holiday lineup starts coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's when people want to upgrade their games, but this program is not going to be available by then, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really see a time frame, and I think it's more of like, let's play it by ear and see what happens and...
[SPEAKER_02]: you know it's all gonna be because why would you purchase you know Call of Duty Ghosts and then two weeks later you're gonna get your PlayStation 4 or whatever and oh and I gotta buy the PlayStation 4 version as well it's like you would think that you would just kind of wait it out a little bit yeah but I mean I understand you know
[SPEAKER_03]: I can also see folks that are going to have PlayStation 4s under their Christmas trees or their menorahs or whatever you celebrate in the winter season, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That you might end up with a PlayStation 4 there when you've bought all these PlayStation 3 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm kind of like, if you're going to buy a bunch of PlayStation 3 games...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, now Sony wanted to be clear that these upgrade prices, such as the one that we just mentioned for Call of Duty Ghosts, they are going to be set by the publisher.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not something Sony is going to regulate.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit of a clarification here from UK Managing Director Fergal Gara in an interview with Digital Spy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_03]: is the PlayStation 4 digital file will be made available on the PlayStation Store as it would be anyway at launch and the PS3 discs will be sold through retail.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the consumer can then do for a premium to be defined by the publisher is access the PlayStation 4 digital game and then provided they still have the PlayStation 3 disc, they will be able to play the PlayStation 4 version when they decide to buy the next gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a pretty clever solution because that doesn't allow you to like game fly your PS3 game and then upgrade it.
[SPEAKER_03]: if your PS3 disc is in the drive you can use the PlayStation 4 digital version that's a clever little way to do it yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't got anything to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a clever little workaround.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's not that much different than, let's say, the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: You install a game to your hard drive on the 360, you still require the disk and the drive, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're seeing that bridging between two systems, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially in light of the fact that the PlayStation 4 is not backwards compatible, which is frustrating to some people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm wondering if that would work different than... Well, obviously it would work different if you bought a digital version of the game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't have to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twitch
[SPEAKER_04]: It was at GamersCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They basically said that players would be able to broadcast over Twitch channels.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there goes the need for a capture card.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll just be doing it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but Twitch is a very popular streaming solution for people.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, uh, in fact, there isn't a lot of competition out there to Twitch, which really surprises me, meaning like focused on video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know there's others.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've heard of one called Owned, but nothing on that same scale of Twitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm seeing this type of stuff kind of break through on the mainstream media too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I was seeing something on either CNN or Yahoo or one of those sites where they were talking about, you know, more people watch Twitch TV than some basic cable channels.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's very much a new medium or new media.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now everybody's going to get to do their own broadcast right from their PlayStation 4 or their Xbox One to be fair, which is detailed a similar plan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I kind of wish that there was a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm not too familiar with all the export options that they have available.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if you can export those files, like you can... Because I know they have the sharing stuff that you can do where you can share clips online.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I wonder if you can, like, export a huge file or something to, like, YouTube or export it to your computer and edit it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's saving to the Twitch website, you can export Twitch videos to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a Let's Play the Slender Man where I screamed very high-pitched when I saw Slender Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's on my YouTube, which is Rob Roberts Plays, I think, on my YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was an export from Twitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this whole thing bodes well for Twitch itself, just given that they're also going to have the Xbox deal too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, this is huge for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And remember, Twitch started as, and they still run it, Justin.TV, which was streaming your life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think in some ways, I'm just going to give you guys real talk from my perspective.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Justin.TV kind of became a joke in some ways because it kind of became a lot of cam whores.
[SPEAKER_03]: and people that were like, you know, pay me $5 and I'll show you my titty or show you my junk or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of what, even though you're not supposed to have adult content, that's what a lot of that life casting turned into.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's really great that those guys kind of thought ahead and, you know, kind of grabbed on this gaming thing that was going on that was a little more, you know, a little more serious, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, I plan to use this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll definitely check it out, especially since I finally got around to playing around with my video capture equipment, the new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the stuff I might be capturing with the brand new Twitch feature on PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minecraft is a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was something that was kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a very quick reveal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't really show anything other than a logo and some people walking by in costume.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not even really costume, but with a mask on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yes, Minecraft will be coming to the PlayStation 4 at launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's also coming to PlayStation 3 and the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're...
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta say, internet, seriously, people on Twitter, don't harass the Xbox support people regarding, like, announcements and shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox support is for helping people with shit that's wrong on your Xbox, not saying, Hey, I see Minecraft, you know, which was, you know, originally a console exclusive for Xbox 360, it's coming to PlayStation 4, how do you like them apples?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that type of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Technically, if you want to get into it there, yes, Microsoft has an exclusive on Minecraft, the Xbox 360 edition, and Minecraft, the Xbox One edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minecraft on the PlayStation 4 will be created by yet a different company other than 4J Studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, yes, it will be technically exclusive to PlayStation 4, whereas a different version of Minecraft is exclusive to the Xbox platforms.
[SPEAKER_02]: There, you're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop emailing those people or stop tweeting to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, they're saying that it's created by Microsoft Studios, so therefore it is exclusive to Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, their version of the game is exclusive to Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com kind of echoing the same sentiment there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft Xbox 360 Edition is still an Xbox 360 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would be interested to see what differences there are in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it would be very interesting to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, so there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, other wonderful console exclusives.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is basically talking a little bit about the indie games because they were a big focus on the presentation.
[SPEAKER_02]: and some of their exclusives they're saying are going to be Hotline Miami 2, N++, Starbound, let's see, Volume, which is done by the guy that did Thomas Was Alone, Rogue Legacy, Wasteland Kings, and Everybody's Gone Through the Rapture, which I love the parody account, was it the Kazurai parody account who said, yeah, it's a sequel to Everybody's Golf.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Binding of Isaac Rebirth, Velocity 2X, and Guns of Icarus Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guess Velocity, I think it was Velocity.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it wasn't Velocity.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another game they announced free that was going to be available for PlayStation 4 with PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're going to get quite a lineup of free games, especially indie titles, at launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, this is a little awkward, but these things happen, especially in live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're going to say goodbye to Jamie for now, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, basically the allergy thing is getting to the point where I'm now lightheaded.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, but you are safe to drive, because I don't want you leaving here if you can't drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you can go lie down in the other room if you need to during the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I do it now, I'll be okay, but I know how my...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that we just gave away a secret.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's alright, no, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, we'd been out drinking all night, and I crashed out on her bed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I came out, of course, fully sober.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I smell where it had been lit in the front room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I went and threw up everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we can reminisce another time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care of yourself, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for the well wishes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any last minute thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I realized what made myself worse I brought the one thing I thought would be quick and easy to cook and that was Pollock Paneer The Trader Joe's ones uses chilies and I have a super bad chili allergy so that's probably my own fault Allergy plus allergy equals super allergy Yeah I've got tea at home and I've got lots of Benadryl and Sudafed and NyQuil so I might pass out either that or you'll see me in chat
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we hope to hear from you later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Feel better, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_03]: And such is the risk of doing live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki and I will hold down the fort here for the rest of the night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drive safe.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you need me, call my phone, and I will make sure my ringer is on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you need me, call me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have your 3DS charger back now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: AlanAlchemy in chat says, Mark down that timestamp.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an edit.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's live and it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100Matt says, Everyone's allergies change after several years.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tigerclaw in chat says, Sky, isn't everyone allergic to marijuana?
[SPEAKER_03]: It smells so bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know some people that if they're allergic to marijuana, then they are gluttons for punishment because plenty of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, did I tell you about how I found out I had an allergy to it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a girl's bathroom at school.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all the other bathrooms were being cleaned, so I went to the front bathroom that was by the office, which ironically is the one that everyone smokes pot in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got in there, and I was so sick in the stall that I had to turn around and throw up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I had a rash.
[SPEAKER_03]: No fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: On my face.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: No fun at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to be okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drive safe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the music, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet you that there's quite a few marijuana-inspired levels in LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guarantee that there's like, hey, I'm going to totally put pot leaves everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: In this level, you've got to get stowed.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there's a level dedicated to, what was her name, that actress, Parker Posey, that was my favorite LittleBigPlanet level I ever played was the Parker Posey level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which was like creepy stalker almost, but I loved it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: LittleBigPlanet Hub is a free-to-play service coming to the PlayStation 3 that's going to have many elements of the LittleBigPlanet universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: LittleBigPlanet Hub will allow players to collaborate with online teammates for challenges, level creation, wardrobe coordination via a redesigned shop interface.
[SPEAKER_03]: LittleBigPlanet Hub is said to offer unrestricted access to LittleBigPlanet's Create Mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: 16 levels taken from previous LittleBigPlanet games on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the hub-exclusive Team Picks will highlight a new batch of community-created levels every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the new weekly challenges mode boasts a whole new way to play LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm curious if that's going to have access to all the levels that are created out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if that's the case, then you probably don't need a single-player version of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and also, it does sound like, though, they might nickel and dime some of the content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, because, you know, in the create mode in the games, you have to unlock that by playing the single player mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's like, if you want to, you know, you can create these levels, but if you want to use the grappling hook gun, you're going to have to buy that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to use, you know, I think that's how they're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll be able to make very basic levels, but you won't be able to make the really good stuff without buying some of the nickel and dime levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great play.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you need?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, free to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Allows you to get your foot in the door.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if I'm not mistaken, LittleBigPlanet 2 is still a PlayStation Plus title, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: LittleBigPlanet Cardiness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: But LittleBigPlanet 2 right now, it's gotta be dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's been a long time since it's been out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so League of Legends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: They got hacked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently there was info that was accessed and that includes usernames, email addresses, salted passwords, and credit card numbers as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: But once again, those were salted, which means they're encrypted and they have some random stuff thrown in there as well to make it difficult to unencrypt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So while that stuff was leaked out, you probably just want to change your login and password information because that's pretty much the only thing that they do have access to.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you obviously, you know, if you use the same login and password combination on other sites, it's going to be the first thing they try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure you change that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't worry too much about the credit card information and the billing information stuff because that stuff was encrypted and it looks like that it would be difficult for them to crack all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: but still never good to hear that again and League of Legends is a huge game too it's not good to hear that they got hacked now luckily I used a unique password for League of Legends because I just kind of thought something like this might happen but now I'm going to need a second unique password because they're going to make everybody change it I haven't logged in in a week though
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they say that they're taking appropriate action to notify and safeguard affected players.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be contacting these players via email addresses currently associated with their accounts to alert them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our investigation is ongoing and we take all the necessary steps to protect players.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you didn't have a League of Legends account, so you don't have to worry about it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, don't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, not a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and what's coming out to a gaming store near you.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few things this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lost Planet 3 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little known fact about Lost Planet 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Capcom thinks it's going to do very well, so they're not making any reprints of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once the launch quantities are gone, it's gone, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't believe that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it were to do very well, which I kind of agree with Capcom in this regard, I don't think it will do very well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if it does, I mean, they could always just reprint it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they could.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that what they did with, like, Katamari Damacy and some of these other minimally printed games?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that a lot of that is just to get the buzz out there so that information gets out so they're like, oh, I need to get it because I won't be able to get it otherwise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XIV out this week on PC and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killer is Dead on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 if you're a fan of Suda51.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too bad Jamie left, but Hatsune Miku, Project Diva F on PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last but not least, Madden NFL 25 coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and Painkiller, Hell and Damnation on PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's travel to Japan and then maybe you can pick up the UK dates here that we would usually do because I'm trying to replace the classic game of the week here because I don't want to take Jamie's game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm working frantically on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All while we're doing live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, trying to go to the Japanese release dates, and here they are on the PlayStation 3 this week on August the 27th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XIV makes its way to Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: The name there, Final Fantasy XIV Online, Shinsei Yorza.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Eorza is the name of the realm that we all play in like Azeroth is in World of Warcraft so I'm assuming that is their own interpretation of what we have as the subtitle Realm Reborn that is out in Japan on the 27th as well on the 29th which I believe is Thursday which is a more typical release day there
[SPEAKER_03]: End of Eternity, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure All-Star Battle, and Lost Planet 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox 360 has Monster Hunter Frontier G Anniversary 2013 Premium Package.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragnarok Odyssey Ace Ragnarok Odyssey
[SPEAKER_02]: Ace, I think, was one that was on DS or 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a new re-release or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a re-release, but a port.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sadly, no Wii U games this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw some Disney Infinity on my list, but I think some people over there are importing ours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Disney is very popular in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can imagine, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo 3DS gets Sherlock Holmes Puzzle City and Starry Sky in Autumn 3D in regular and limited edition and I was going to see real quick if there's anything on the PSP because believe it or not they still get releases there once in a while and Solomon's Ring Elemental Pack comes out on the Sony PSP I completely forgot actually on the PSP this week Sweet Fuse At Your Side I think is the name and that's a PSP title coming out over here huh
[SPEAKER_02]: Visual Novel, Axis, go figure.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Putting out those Visual Novel titles, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, just a couple more stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the UK, we're getting Castlevania Lords of Shadows, and this is on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm assuming that's coming to Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn on PlayStation 3 and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also on Mac, Bioshock Infinite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it's also coming out here as well on Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guardians of Middle-Earth, also a PC release.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're getting E3 and Odyssey 4, Legends of the Titan on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killer is Dead on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also Lost Planet 3 on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 and PC, of course PC being on Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rayman Legends actually coming out a little bit early over there on Wii U and PC, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then some stuff that doesn't have a date on it, but it's just marked August.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Walking Dead 400 Days and Payday 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure if that stuff's already been out yet, but it is over here, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's talk a little bit about some other stuff that we discussed during the PlayStation conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, a lot of this was leaked out beforehand, but the Vita got a price drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: $199 in the US and $199 in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, it should be mentioned that the PlayStation 3 12GB system came out here as well because it is in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's also $199.
[SPEAKER_02]: So PlayStation 3 and Vita for $199.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they actually do have a bundle too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The $199 price point is for the 3G one and they also have the Walking Dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a bundle that's also $199 as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Killzone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killzone will be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's supposed to be actually a really good first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard rumors that they may do a Vita version of Ghosts, but it would have to be somebody other than... I can't remember the developer, but the guys that did fucking Resistance and Call of Duty last year that just sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: So as long as they get somebody else to develop that, it would be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Borderlands 2 is going to help too, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Will it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm going to be honest, when I heard the news about Borderlands 2 on the Vita, I was kind of like, don't get me wrong, Borderlands 2, awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know people are really into it and rightfully so, but I'm kind of like, hasn't everybody who's going to get Borderlands 2 already got it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be said for a lot of games, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minecraft on the go, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I understand, yeah, they have the Pocket Edition, but if this version is a little bit more like the PC version, it's all sorts of greatness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too bad maybe it could talk to the PC version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or the PS3 version would be very awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be awesome if it was... Well, I don't think you could do the PS4, but if all three versions talk to each other, that would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony's not as much of a hard-ass on the PC communicating with...
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony servers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we see DC Universe Online is on both, even though I don't think their servers are cross-play, but Final Fantasy XIV just came out, and it's cross-play between the two.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's something else I'm thinking of that's PC and PlayStation cross.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, like the whole Steam integration into Portal?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the problem, though, with doing that is a lot of it, they have to develop the engine to be similar because they want the same draw distance and same features in there, and if one is significantly less power than the other one, they can't really do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so yeah, Borderlands 2, that's supposed to be coming in 2014 sometime.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking maybe holiday because, you know, no date yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really good comment from Monty Boggs in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can transfer PlayStation 3 data, Borderlands 2 Vita would be tempting.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Transfaring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that the whole term that Konami came up with a while ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Transfaring your data?
[SPEAKER_03]: They could.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a pretty good reason to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole thing would depend on if the game is going to have all the same guns in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they develop all the same assets that are in the
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they have all the things... Well, shouldn't it all be in the cloud?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just upload it to the cloud!
[SPEAKER_02]: It all depends, though, because if they have all that information, maybe they could do it without the guns.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Depends on the content that's in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they could bring in all the guns, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the Vita memory cards, one of the things that people are complaining about a lot because they are pretty expensive, are being reduced in price as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, apparently, there are... I don't remember the final amounts to those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, the Vita memory cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Previously, for example, 4GB memory card is now $14.99, whereas originally $20.00.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 8GB memory card is now $19.99, where it was $30.
[SPEAKER_02]: $16 is $39.99, where it was $60.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the 32GB card is $80, where it was $100.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they are knocking the price off of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: It still sucks that it's proprietary, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Might as well invest in a pretty big memory card because especially if you do PlayStation Plus, get a bunch of free games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's also another strong point if they market that well enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, hey, you buy a PlayStation Vita, you get PlayStation Plus, you can download a ton of fucking games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: If they can really bring... If the Vita has a renaissance or whatever you want to call it where it really does kind of seem to take off this holiday season and essentially resurrect from the dead, you can't tell me that the Wii U can't do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need a price drop because the Wii U is still $349.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not going to cut it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have something later on that might sweeten the pot a little bit, but I kind of agree that there's going to need to be a hard drop or Nintendo's going to be in trouble, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that there's not a lot of great games coming, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: to register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use the passphrase, judge.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to one more story here about Killer Instinct and some new information that came out about the game this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those details, in the free-to-play version of Killer Instinct, you will be able to buy the additional characters for $5 each.
[SPEAKER_03]: Killer Instinct will be free to play with one character when the console comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be a $19.99 combo breaker pack that unlocks the game's full roster of 8 characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Including 2 of them that are exclusive fighters that are not initially available for individual purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meaning if you do piecemeal your game, you will have 6 fighters to choose from.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will also be a $40 Ultra Edition that will bundle all playable characters online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, an accessory and costume pack thingy, and the original 1994 arcade version of Killer Instinct, which has a lot of people more happy about the arcade version on their Xbox One than I think some people are about the new Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you think there's only eight characters in this game, you're full of crap, because they're gonna fuckin' put DLC out there, they're gonna make you buy those fuckin' characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think yes and no I think it will be eight this year and then depending on how the game does because this is how they're talking they're saying well you will have the 2013 season that has these eight characters and the next year we can put along eight more characters and put that into the game I'm literally hearing and I'm trying to be open and understanding but what I'm literally hearing is we're making it up as we go along
[SPEAKER_02]: 8 characters in a fighting game seems kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the whole charging $5 for the characters is basically to get you to buy the $20 pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: They never were intending for you to buy piecemeal characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just like, yeah, we'll put it there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They want to be able to say it's free to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll put it there so that people want to buy the $20 pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all it really comes down to.
[SPEAKER_02]: And $20 for a fighting game is not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: 8 characters does seem quite...
[SPEAKER_03]: low but that's the original Street Fighter 2 had eight characters and even then there were still four bosses on top of that
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's just the only, you know, and it's not that Street Fighter 2 was a bad game, it's just not 1991 anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and I did get a tweet earlier this week, and I apologize, I forgot the username of who sent it, but the tweet said, because I said, I was shading the fact that there was only the, you know, eight characters, and I got a tweet that said, what about quality over quantity?
[SPEAKER_03]: and I was I never responded to it because I was mobile or something like that but honestly my answer to that is wait a minute though part of the reason that make fighting games so much fun is kind of the diversity of the roster and you look at the fighting games that come out today eight characters doesn't cut it anymore you know you gotta have
[SPEAKER_03]: At least 15, 20.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many did the new Mortal Kombat have?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, you have a good diverse roster makes the game more fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eight characters sounds like we rushed this game to get it out for the launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a lot of the other games that have been coming out launch for the platform seems like a lot of it's rushed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe, you know, pre-end more characters later on so they can sell it as DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think originally this game is probably going to be a retail release, but they just can't get it done in time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what really concerns me, is that all these signs are pointing... You know, it's like these warning signs are popping up about this game, and it has me really concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't think it's just this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like Forza 5, for example, where it's shipping unfinished.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's day one patch, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, dude, you better hope that your servers are fucking working day one because there's going to be some pissed people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess not because there's still content in the game, but you're just not going to be able to play the full thing yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of don't trust Microsoft to keep it going, and I'm going to use my big old standby that I always bring up on the show and you're sick of hearing me talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, there's two of them, remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, the one I've got in my mind is remember when they said, we're going to bring a thousand games to game room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then what happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: About 200 came out across 13 packs and they pulled the plug.
[SPEAKER_03]: So those thousand games never happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: So isn't it feasible that if Killer Instinct comes out and heaven forbid, it's not very good and people just aren't into it because there's not enough characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think that 2014 pack will ever happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grrrr.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or an actual legitimate use for the Xbox camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weiland in our chatroom says, I'm waiting for PC Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that something they said is going to happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't know if I would see that happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not, just because they want everybody to purchase the Xbox One stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think maybe later on down the line when Windows 8 takes off and a lot more people have Windows 8 and that Windows Marketplace is more of a robust thing, then maybe you'll see stuff like that popping up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: This character has the ability to throw spider webs to attack and ensnare opponents, and she has a pair of blades on the back of each hand and blades on her forearms and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does not look like a previous Killer Instinct fighter, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: New fighting games in a franchise should have some new people, but I bet there's going to be some people that are a little irritated, like, alright, so there's going to be eight fighters...
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're going to fill them all up with slots of people that are new and not like... Where's Orchid?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's Spinal?
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are coming in the DLC pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: The most popular character will be one of the two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you Orchid will be in there, but she'll be one of those characters that you can only get when you buy... You can't piecemeal her.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll be in that $20 combo pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to get her that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is pretty cool news, though, despite all this, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: Negative things we might be saying about Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Creative director Adam Isgreen and producer Torin Redding talking about Killer Instinct mentioned the original announcer, Chris Sutherland, will be selectable in lieu of the new announcer for Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to have the old Killer Instinct experience when it comes to the announcer, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess he did re-record some lines, and even though it's been 18 years later, sounds exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it sounds like he's aged a little better than DuckTales did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't they just have him do it in the beginning?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just have him be the guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a little weird, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because maybe what they didn't say, they said Chris Sutherland will be selectable in a $4.99 DLC pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: $4.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try $40 deals.
[SPEAKER_02]: $40 packs.
[SPEAKER_02]: For an announcer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no, I bet you.
[SPEAKER_02]: $40 because you get the original game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you get the original announcer too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I wasn't... Well, Dota 2 sells these announcer packs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's part of the way they make money.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're free to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw in our chat pointing out that character I mentioned earlier, they can't call her Spider-Woman anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't calling her that, but she looks like that type of character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dota 2 announcer packs, I saw the one for GLaDOS and one of the lines in there is it's Oda, the D is silent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we ready to get to the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Back in the day, you didn't have to pay $5 per character.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got all of it or you got nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that takes us to a segment we call the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura will dive into the gaming vault but not this week because she dived into her bed to rest tonight so I will dive into the gaming vault in her place and pick a game that you all should be playing this week sorry I'm laughing because Ranma in the chatroom says screw you Rob Roberts, DuckTales hater now wait a minute, wait a minute put the brakes on for a minute
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: which is why I wish the sound production would have lended their talents better to that and two, I did not like that the cutscenes constantly interrupted the action all the time in what should be a very action based game that being said
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and one of the games I have on the back burner to talk about I wanted to share with you guys one of these days was a game available on the Commodore 64 because you know I'm going to use this opportunity to do a Commodore 64 game the game is called The Great Gianna Sisters is the game I picked tonight
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the great Giana Sisters, some of you have probably heard of this game because there's the Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams, which is an indie game that just came out on Steam Greenlight, and I think it's available on Xbox Arcade and PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yes, its roots are in this very old...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: the Commodore 64 version was programmed by Armin Gessert and the graphics were done by Manfred Trenz and the soundtrack was composed by Chris Hulsbeck funny note, he came back later to do the soundtracks for these later games that came out there was also a DS game
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I played the DS game, and it was alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most people know this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you've heard of this game, you know it because it was a very controversial game when it came out on the Commodore 64 because...
[SPEAKER_03]: It looked a lot like Super Mario Bros., down to the fact that they did the whole World 1-1 thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do I mean by that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, whenever a level creator comes out for a game, what's the first thing people usually make?
[SPEAKER_03]: A penis, and then after that, World 1-1 from Super Mario Bros., right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, unfortunately, in the case of the Great Giana Sisters, World 1...
[SPEAKER_03]: is pretty much World 1-1 from Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the first level is almost identical in layout to Super Mario Brothers, and the game itself shares some similarities too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You pick up a magical pinwheel, it makes you bigger, and you have a little... You don't throw a fireball per se, but it's a bouncing ball, just like the Game Boy version of Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, Nintendo pressured the makers of the Great Giana Sisters, threatening legal action if they do not take appropriate action.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game was voluntarily withdrawn from sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: No lawsuits or anything like that, but it was voluntarily withdrawn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Therefore, it makes this game very rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what they don't say about the controversy, and you don't know this unless you've played the game...
[SPEAKER_03]: The later levels don't really look like Mario Brothers levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say maybe the second level has a little bit in common too, but I think there's 20 some odd levels in the game, and especially when you get into the later levels and some of the boss fights.
[SPEAKER_03]: It isn't like Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: in that regard.
[SPEAKER_03]: But unfortunately, a lot of the basic game mechanics, you know, with the whole power-ups and getting coins and jumping on the coin blocks and so forth, that is all still pretty similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it probably was in this company's best interest to take the game off the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is what makes this game such a cult classic and why people desire it is that, you know, it was, in a sense, a Super Mario-like game on a 1983 Commodore 64 and...
[SPEAKER_03]: The soundtrack, the soundtrack, the soundtrack People love the soundtrack and rightfully so Great, great music available in the game So it's no wonder that they brought Chris Holspeck back to do the later games
[SPEAKER_03]: Very well received, very highly rated in a lot of old Commodore 64 productions.
[SPEAKER_03]: ZZap64 giving it 96%.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are various ports out there, but the ZX Spectrum port that was planned was pulled back because of illegal pressures.
[SPEAKER_03]: In 1993, the MSX version came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game had been ported to Windows, DOS, Linux, but all unofficially.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also a Nintendo DS version unofficially of the Commodore 64 port, not to be confused with the official sequel of Giana Sisters.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was also a mobile version of the game made for Android phones in 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a sequel planned for the game called Giana 2, Arthur and Martha in Future World, and it was supposed to have a futuristic setting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But because of all the legal troubles, Time Warp renamed the game Hard and Heavy and changed the protagonist to Robots.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you've ever played the game Hard and Heavy, which came out on the Commodore 64 in 1989, that was inspired by Giana Sisters.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was supposed to be the sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: um so Giana Sisters DS was an actual uh sequel that did come out in 2009 and then of course I think a lot of you know uh through Steam and so forth in July 2012 and the Kickstarter Giana Sisters Twisted Dreams became a reality so there you go the classic game of the week the Giana Sisters the great Giana Sisters yeah have you ever heard of this game in your life Loki
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have played it actually
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw on chat says, does that new Giana Sisters game poke fun at Nintendo despite them?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't think it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's pretty badass, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and actually, yeah, the game doesn't play, I mean, the good thing is they turn this, it's still a platforming game, but it's way different now, and it is badass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you flip between the sisters, and it causes changes in the environment, and yeah, I've played through a bit of it on Steam, and it's a fun little game to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I talked about it on a previous episode of the show, but as far as a straight-up platformer goes, it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: ShadowNextGen says, has Rob played the modern port of Gianna Sisters?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played the DS one, and I've played this new one, Twisted Sisters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not even know until doing last-minute research for the article tonight that there was later ports that came on.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, look at what she's fighting here in this video.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game was just ahead of its time.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Great Gianna Sisters, classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I do good with 15 minutes to pick a game?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, we're going to take a quick break, and when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio, we got more news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Fugo Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know our beginnings of the show was a little Sony-heavy, so we are going to talk about some of the goings-on in Microsoft's world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't have a lot in Nintendo news this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was more a couple weeks ago, but with their Nintendo Directs and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we do have at least one big piece in Nintendo news coming up after the break.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, most importantly, your calls, your emails, your voices when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio, in progress with episode number 517 of our program, August 25th, 2013.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, there is no show over Labor Day weekend, so this is a show that's going to have to hold you over for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the good news is, I just said it's episode 517, so if you're newer to the show...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really the only way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so we are here to talk more news and get to the mailbag and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do that right now with some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so this was kind of a surprise announcement out of the whole PlayStation 4 press conference that they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a reimagining of a game called Shadow of the Beast which was an old side-scroller, I guess, for the Amiga.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I know that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so now it's this like
[SPEAKER_03]: At first glance, you kind of go, oh, it's like Altered Beast, although no, but close enough, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and now it's coming to the PlayStation 4, so that's interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely not something you would guess would be coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Dev Tycoon is coming to Steam this week, actually, August 29th, and it will be getting an HD, well, sort of an HD, a
[SPEAKER_02]: High-res treatment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you haven't played Game Dev Story, it was a game on the iOS platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: You run a game development company, and you make games, and you make consoles, and it's one of those kind of management sims.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I'm sorry, I'm getting that confused, a game dev story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Game Dev Tycoon was the one that they offered up out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, there was a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, there was a couple, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the one that- Because I took a look at that first thing, and I'm like, wait a second, that doesn't quite look like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, that's the one they put up on Pirate Bay or whatever, and then- Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ironically, your company would always go bankrupt due to piracy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go play Game Dev Story if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually on iOS.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want Game Dev Story, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: After that kind of move that they're trying to teach people a lesson, I think I'll teach them a lesson by not buying their game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, it was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just not interested in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then...
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Eurogamer kind of asked the question because it does beg to be asked since, you know, last year and wasn't very good because FIFA 13 on Vita and on the Wii
[SPEAKER_02]: What's a reskin of FIFA 12?
[SPEAKER_02]: So it begs the question, hey, guys, EA, are you going to be putting out an actual sequel to the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to just reskin the game from last year?
[SPEAKER_02]: And so EA Sports came out with the best...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: so literally roster update 2014 FIFA 14 is FIFA 13 which was FIFA 12 so fantastic that the game has not changed as people have hoped you don't have to worry about that happening in the Wii version or Wii U version because guess what it's not coming out they didn't make a version for the Wii or Wii U
[SPEAKER_02]: Pro Evolution, now to be fair, Pro Evolution Soccer, same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did that on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do know that this year, though, that is not the case, at least with the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions, since those are using the Fox engine now and it's a completely different thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think actually the FIFA is using their new engine, the Ignite engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com, Bobby Blackwolf, having played both GameDev games, wants you to know GameDev Tycoon is a lot deeper than GameDev Story.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot more difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blackwolf also is telling other chatters that he's going to make Podcast Network Tycoon, where you create a podcast network and have to deal with certain listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you should make that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: that's the next thing VOG needs to get into game development because you don't do enough programming Bobby let's take on another project come on love it all right um let's move on to some more rapid fire news uh I'll do a couple stories here one of them about Retro City Rampage on the 3ds I think we've talked before it is coming uh they're actually going to have it playable at PAX Prime but this is interesting you're not actually going to be able to play it in 3d at PAX Prime
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, this will be the latest version of Retro City Rampage that has the Retro Plus graphics mode that will double on-screen colors and add soft shadows to the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is coming out on the 3DS eShop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it going to be in 3D or is it just not the 3D version?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the 3D version is not actually playable at PAX that's what I'm gathering but yeah it sounds like it will be in 3D but I would imagine it's going to be pretty limited I mean when you see the retro games in 3D it's usually like one layer is this way and one layer I wouldn't expect but who knows it might exceed those expectations remember this is all one guy making this too
[SPEAKER_03]: That's very impressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: More information for Super Smash Bros., whatever the new one might be called, on the 3DS and the Wii U. A new screenshot has revealed that there will be a stage based off of Metroid Other M. It's the Pyrosphere from Metroid Other M, which is a pleasant surprise because, you know, I know a lot of us love Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metroid Other M, on the other hand...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Also of note for Smash Bros., Mashihiro Sakurai has noted that in the 3DS version of Smash Bros., you can actually have outlines around the characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I believe this is to help them stand out on the smaller screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, you don't have to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The mention was that you can have 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thick outlines, thin outlines, or just turn them off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fans very interested in these when the pictures first came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The lines are there to help you see playable characters from the backgrounds and I would assume the various Pokemon that will show up and the other assists that happen in the fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can get a little crazy on that tiny screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's great news.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I love I love it when a developer the more power they put in the hands of the player I mean not to you know use an old game cliche but the more customization that the player has to really make the game they want I say the better instead of saying we're going to do this we're going to put outlines and that's the way it's going to be deal with it
[SPEAKER_03]: So, love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: A brand new expansion revealed for Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: We talked about earlier in the show Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, an expansion has been announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Reaper of Souls.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will have a new act in the game, five new levels, and the Crusader class.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a holy knight, very similar to the Paladin in Diablo 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the loot system being overhauled.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to call that Loot 2.0.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has something called Smart Drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Paragon System No Paragon Level Cap
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so a few announcements.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once again, this is going back to some of the Sony stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gran Turismo 6 is now coming out on December 6th, so it's easy for you to remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would be on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're going to have the most cars on disc of any Gran Turismo game yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guess if you pre-order it some places, like the Evil G, you may get some additional cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: and uh what I thought was interesting though they actually showed like a little bit of a trailer and stuff is that car companies are developing um prototype cars in Gran Turismo 6 like they're making some of their prototypes available to play as I thought that was kind of cool
[SPEAKER_02]: That is a heck of a sign of the times, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not interested at all in Gran Turismo 6 because driving simulators, I'm just terrible at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arcade, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, arcade, fine, but in the exact same way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart, loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blur was a great game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's something I would love Sony to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me a Forza Horizon version of Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forza Horizon was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's what DriveClub is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what DriveClub is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what DriveClub is either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's more simulation or more arcade-y.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me an arcade version of Gran Turismo 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: December 6th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far, I might add, the only game announced for December is...
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think Ubisoft is going to move South Park there and put in the Far Cry 3 it's just my own thought because last year they did it with Far Cry 3 and it worked out really well for them I thought they pushed the South Park game back to next year they kind of hinted that that could be a possibility because Matt Stone and Trey Parker kind of work on it on their own pace and you're not going to get them to hurry up so it's when it's done I guess fair enough
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, uh, Pokemon X and Y. Uh, the soundtrack will be coming out, and it's coming on four discs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a lot of tracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: 212 tracks, to be exact.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three and a half hours of music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's available, I guess, um, on CDJapan for 2,500 yen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um... So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, uh, not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course...
[SPEAKER_02]: There hasn't really been any good Capcom fighting games, or I should say Street Fighter games, on the Wii U. Capcom's basically saying, nope, no Street Fighter on the Wii U. No plans to bring any of the games, no plans for Ultra to come there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe Street Fighter V?
[SPEAKER_02]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, there will be some eShop versions of Street Fighter coming to the Wii U. Street Fighter 2, they're coming out with Street Fighter 2, Street Fighter 2 Turbo, Super Street Fighter 2 will be out on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those are going to be $7.99 each.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you miss your fighting game that only has eight playable characters, at least you know this one's solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Classic Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they ever put out Killer Instinct on, uh... I don't believe they did.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what I have sitting right over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: A Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you see that black cartridge lying on top of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That can only be one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not too worried.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I gotta thank Alan for that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's his Killer Instinct cartridge, not mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You take Facebook, you take Google, slam them together, you get Fugle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every week we ask a question of our Facebook community at facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and our Google Plus page over at plus.google.com slash 110... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just search for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very simple question this week because most of the news this week, most of the heavy-hitting news was centered around Sony's big press conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know the date.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know the details.
[SPEAKER_03]: We pretty much know all there is to know about PlayStation 4's launch at this point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a few surprises at a Tokyo game show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's the verdict?
[SPEAKER_03]: I figure most people have made up their mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the verdict on the PlayStation 4?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you getting one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why or why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start with an answer on Google Plus from Jamie Monn who says, I was already sold on the PlayStation 4, but the fact that they came out of the box with no shady online requirements and it's cheaper was a plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: What they revealed this week wasn't anything to write home about, but didn't sway my opinion either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: That being said, I plan on buying both systems at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Black Dynamite says, Getting one absolutely day one no way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Using the show's golden rule, a console is only as good as the games that are on it applies here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any worthwhile game, Grand Theft Auto V, Call of Duty, Final Fantasy, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: are coming out for current gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no real reason to get one unless you just want the latest and greatest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I believe is an answer that echoes where Loki's head is at right now, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I still probably will get one, but Grand Theft Auto, man, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of where I'm at, because I'm like, I still want one, and the gamer that has to have all the new toys wants one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, I love that you invoked the golden rule of gaming, and there's no games I'm dying for at launch, but I kind of want that console still.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to buy Grand Theft Auto V.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, you just need to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me know what system Bobby's getting it on because at least I know I'm going to play against you and get killed, but I can play against Bobby and we're about evenly matched.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't play against me.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're in a crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: We go do heists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's like Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get a VOG crew together and we do heists.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's just like Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Mass Effect is lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're supposed to say yes because that gets me to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it's like Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft says, I'm going to wait to see where the consoles go and what games really do interest me on consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: For now, I'll stick to my PC and my 3DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Redertainment says no not because I don't want one but because project buy a house takes priority well real life sometimes does Techie Q says yes I will get a Playstation 4 at launch I need to trade in my 360 because it's gathering dust because I'm using my PS3 as my main console for gaming and video streaming the Evil G was offering 50% more in store credit towards a Playstation 4 in June oh boy all these incentives the Evil G is going to throw out there I'm just going to throw this out there as a word of advice
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says Grand Theft Auto 5 VOG game nights will be great yep yep that is definitely gonna happen and you're gonna be able to stream them I hope I will and then DarkSakura is in chat letting us still know her opinion she says I've revised my rule I have a new golden rule never buy a game system or an Apple product at launch
[SPEAKER_03]: You're no fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: No fun at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are all our answers from Google+.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's do Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Holy moly, 18 comments on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to try to do this relatively quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I apologize in advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I may not read all of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to try to pick out people I don't usually see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kurti K says, I won't be getting one this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not looking forward to any of the launch titles, so I can wait until at least next year to pick up one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Burr says, I'm getting one, but that's because I'm a consumer whore who has pre-ordered both systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, I feel confident that the PlayStation 4 will be worth it just for whatever Naughty Dog develops for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doug T says, I will be buying the PlayStation 4 day one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love my PlayStation 3 and PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Sony consoles better as they bring out more games that I like, such as RPGs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brian G says, I will wait until there's a compelling reason for me to buy one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a gaming PC, and like Loki, Grand Theft Auto will keep me busy for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loco Poco says, I'll be getting one day one, excited for Knack and Killzone, also because I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Renee, one of our buddies from Koopa Club, says, I will not be getting a PS4 this year, not because I don't want it, but because I'm not ready to make that monetary investment just yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeremy J., also from Koopa Club, says,
[SPEAKER_03]: and uh let's see a couple last answers here HitStun says slow down I don't even have a PlayStation 3 yet I still want to play Journey, Valkyria Chronicles, and Tokyo Jungle PlayStation 4 just doesn't have any games I could get hyped about and lastly Codeman says I canceled my pre-order I have a PC but I just don't have the funds nor do I really need one right now the only reason are games that have sold this to me is Kingdom Hearts 3 and Final Fantasy 15 I
[SPEAKER_03]: Although they are developing Kingdom Hearts 3 on PC, so there might be a PC build.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will wait just to let the dust settle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And tacos.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the answers there from Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: I apologize I didn't read them all just because there were so many answers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I do encourage our listeners to check out the variety of answers available on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: Facebook.com slash questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio and I did read them all on Google tonight because there's just less people over there but you can check out the full answers I did truncate some of the answers a little bit you can check that out on our Google Plus page thank you to everybody for responding let's get back into some more news Loki
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so let's talk a little bit about the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_02]: Europe, they made an announcement that, hey, we're going to get you to buy the Xbox One because we know what you Europeans like.
[SPEAKER_02]: You like FIFA.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you get FIFA, you get FIFA, you get FIFA, you get FIFA, you get FIFA, everybody gets FIFA 14 with the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the soundtrack's by Adele.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go figure to try and get more sales.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yes, it'll be also available on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get a bundle as well for €199.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So FIFA.
[SPEAKER_02]: FIFA 14.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how they're going to sell it to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting that it's a third-party game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the part that gets me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, wow, it's a third-party.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it really does sweeten the deal, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, with the fact that the console's $100 more expensive, it goes a long way to put a game in there to give that extra value.
[SPEAKER_03]: I realize a game is only $60, but remember, Kinect and blah, blah, blah, blah, whether you like it or not, that is all stuff that's coming with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which FIFA 14 does not, or I don't believe uses Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if it uses Kinect because they don't say anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of the Xbox One games aren't right away.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some, but, you know, there's a lot that aren't.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least if what we saw at E3 is to be any indication.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if they use it on the 360, let's assume that the features for the Kinect are going to be pretty similar on the Xbox One as they are on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, the advantage that you get with the Xbox One is you paid $100 more for that stupid camera and they're going to penalize you for swearing at the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, count me in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's not going to work in my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, just the other night, actually one game I've been playing a lot of this week...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bit Trip Runner 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't talk about this in my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that's free, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's free on PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought it months ago on Wii U, but I was like, well shit, it's free and I want trophies.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to play it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And every time I'm playing that game, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, doot, fuck!
[SPEAKER_03]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_03]: All the way back to the beginning of the level.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's me playing Bit.Trip.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't need the Kinect penalizing me further for swearing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although a lot of that is obviously overdone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What Kinect games are really going to penalize you for swearing unless it's like Sesame Street Adventures?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to card you in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or flag you, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems kind of lame that they have that as an option.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's the best you could come up with for Kinect is that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of the stuff, yeah, that doesn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in Europe, that's a huge deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not knocking that, you know, they're bringing in... That's a big thing for... I'm talking about Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, what they're using it for is just like a lot of this voice recognition stuff that I think you could probably do just fine with...
[SPEAKER_02]: A headset.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't understand why they need a whole thing to watch you to do this voice stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, some other big Microsoft news this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure many of you have heard that the current CEO of Microsoft, Steve Ballmer, no, Bill Gates is not CEO.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually Steve Ballmer is the Microsoft CEO.
[SPEAKER_03]: He will be retiring from that position over the next 12 months.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know exactly when.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would imagine a lot of that depends on when they figure out who is going to be replacing him.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how well the Xbox One does.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about... First retirement.
[SPEAKER_03]: The problem is people were already criticizing Steve Ballmer and it's not necessarily related to the Xbox One because like you said, it's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Windows 8, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that and the tablets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Windows Surface.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the tablets, the phones, they haven't really been doing as well as they should have been.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, you get a lot of that stuff, and the stockholders are saying maybe it's time for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is a panel put together to try and find a replacement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the panel includes Bill Gates, Chuck Nusky, Steven Luxo, also on that panel.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, if you're interested, just give Bill Gates a call and let him know you're interested in the position, although I kind of think they'll probably be looking at other...
[SPEAKER_03]: Big companies, tech companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's where I insert my fan wank that they should hire Reggie Fils-Aimé.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you like that fan wank?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we're talking about, for one, Reggie's obviously a very game-focused company.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we talk about the Microsoft CEO, that is much more than just Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they'll promote from within, kind of like how, you know, what they did when Don Mattrick left.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that this would probably violate some contracts and stuff, but they need to hire fictional character Kevin Butler as president of Microsoft because it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there anybody that jumps out at you who could be the person to jump in as CEO?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what else they could... Clippy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clippy B?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not Clippy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Clippy, the Microsoft Office Assistant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what they could do in good old American tradition to find the new CEO of Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reality TV show.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Microsoft's Idol.
[SPEAKER_03]: America Voted.
Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another show for Seacrest to host.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: He does need work.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he's going to be hosting an NBC game show coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Million Second Quiz.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is, and I know, oh God, I can't believe I'm going to admit this.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's an app that's available.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a pretty long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 11 days.
[SPEAKER_03]: A million seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know, that's a pretty long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: when the guy won the million dollars and used his lifeline to call his dad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like that was like epic television, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was event television.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why NBC's kind of trying to make that happen again because it's been a while since we've really had, you know, who wants to be a millionaire is kind of faded away into a, I shouldn't say faded away because now it's like a syndicated game show like your Jeopardy, like your Wheel of Fortune, you know, it's there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But NBC's trying to make this event game show happen again.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we've seen other networks try this like ABC had one a couple years ago called Duel.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a pretty decent game but it just didn't really take off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Telephone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, remember the telephone?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well now, what was that, 1999?
[SPEAKER_03]: So here we are 14 years later, now it's an iPad app.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can actually download the Million Second Quiz iPad app, and I may be guilty of having played this, but you get matched up against other people, and you take a 10-question quiz, it's all multiple choice, and it's like a mixture of, like the same thing you would expect to see on Trivial Pursuit cards, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have to pick the answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, supposedly, and I don't know how this is going to work, but if you hit a certain benchmark score in the iPad app, you qualify as a line jumper to go beyond the real show when it debuts, I think, in a week or two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's coming up here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm going to try it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because now when they say, oh, you might win money, like a million billion dollars or however much they're giving away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll take a few thousand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not...
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's how they make it event television by saying, you, Johnny America, sitting at home with your iPad, get the app now and you can be here sitting and winning all this money in a couple weeks or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: How did talking about Steve Ballmer leave us to talking about NBC game shows?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, but I agree with Codeman in the chatroom who says, at least it's not Candy Crush.
[SPEAKER_03]: True facts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deleted that from my phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was embarrassing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet you anything there will be a Candy Crush-themed game show at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because wasn't there, like, a Hasbro-themed game show?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there still is.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's still the Family Game Night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Family Game Night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft in chat says, imagine if Rob gets on that game show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it would also be nice if I won some money because then if I win enough money, I could possibly leave my day job and do VOG full time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wouldn't that be fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I could win a million dollars?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so Humble Bundle, the Origin Bundle, has earned a record-breaking $8.7 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was based on 1.791 million bundles being sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: And average price, $486 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I guess the record previous to that was 5.1 million with the Humble Indie Bundle 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they did add a few more games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They added Command & Conquer Red Alert 3 Uprising, not Red Alert 3, which would have been an awesome game, but Red Alert 3 Uprising, a four-level standalone expansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft and ChatCorrecting, by the way, it's over 9 million now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Populous and... Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the fact, by the way, even though Populous, you have to get it through Origin, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the classic game back from... When did that game come out?
1989?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was very happy that they threw that in the bundle as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's so funny about it is because the game is so old, Origin actually has these prompts that says...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: You can quit the DOS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, DOS.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also, this is the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember how games back in the day, the copy protection was the manual?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is the third word on page 45 of the manual?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or use this chart in the back of the manual.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was in Populous.
[SPEAKER_03]: You had to identify these crests in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's still in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they fixed it so that it says you can input any word and the game will accept it as the correct answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, what does this shield mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Boobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it'll take it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's correct!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then something else about Origin.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're now allowing returns.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, returns with an asterisk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, what's going to happen is if you buy a game on Origin and they have this now great game guarantee, if you're unsatisfied with your full game digital download from Origin, and this includes full games on pre-order and other discounts and stuff,
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe you'll be able to return it within 7 days so 7 days after purchase without activation or 24 hours after launching it for the first time so 24 hours if you've activated 7 days if you haven't activated the game
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting to see Origin and EA really making these big customer service grabs between the Humble Bundle and the great thing they're doing for charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hate to make that sound opportunistic, but the reality is it's... It was opportunistic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's putting a lot of people in Origin's good graces right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now this, which is hard to say this isn't good news because I think it's great news.
[SPEAKER_03]: It isn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It isn't terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not bad news.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good news.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good that they have that option in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's good for a few reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: One, if you run into a situation like SimCity where the whole launch was fucked up, you can get your money back, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, for example, if you buy a game that just doesn't run well on your PC, then you can get your money back.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or you just don't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah or you just don't like it so I think that's kind of cool that they have that in there I wish Steam would do something similar but let's be honest here this is far and away from like you know I'm selling a used copy of my game that I finished or something like that this is not anything like that this is just kind of like that almost like the Evil G used game thing where it's like okay within seven days you can return this you know except you know seven days without playing it um
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll give them props for at least having some sort of return.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you said in passing, you said, I wish Steam would do something like this because, yeah, they don't really do refunds on Steam unless there's a huge... I mean, they've done it before, but it was like a huge thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this whole competition now, you know, if Origin does get more and more market share, it's going to force Steam to look into doing these types of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: to make themselves competitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they'll have to do that because I think what's going to end up happening is they're probably going to come out with some sort of way to sell or trade your game online using their services.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's what's going to end up happening there so they may not have the whole returns thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think this is a good direction.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I can't say I'm going to go buy a bunch of games and then return them, but it does take that awkwardness out of returning things too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't like to go back to the store and return something because I feel like that guy, unless it's like very clearly broken or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I just, who likes to be that guy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, some people do, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can be any guy or gal you want to be in a series known as Fable.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Fable Legends is a new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a multiplayer game that's set in the universe of the other Fable games, Albion.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was announced at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be a beta test actually happening next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So not to be outdone by...
[SPEAKER_03]: Say Elder Scrolls Online on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox will have Fable Legends.
[SPEAKER_03]: No release window for the game currently, but I would imagine if they're going to beta test it next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: No later than holiday next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holiday next year would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can sign up on the game's website if you're interested in more information.
[SPEAKER_03]: FableLegends.com There's a little trailer and you can see all the other stuff they put out at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked neat, but I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: After playing the last few Fable games, it's always so much hype and then they play...
[SPEAKER_02]: especially if they have Peter Molyneux talking about Fable oh my god you know they just hype it up so much and it's just kind of like yeah this is kind of very similar to the last Fable game um so I don't know it looks all right but I mean it'd be something my wife would be into I'm not buying it she loved the Fable games didn't I'm not buying an Xbox one for that game but you know my wife would probably be interested I forgot she really liked the Fable games huh yeah she plays through because she like what did she like to do really weird things in them didn't she
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does she play them good or evil?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, usually.
[SPEAKER_03]: She tries to.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well let's see if our emailers this week are good or evil in a segment we do every week here on the show called The Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send us emails each and every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the absence of DarkSakura tonight, I will dive in the mailbag head first.
[SPEAKER_03]: And oh my gosh, it's pretty empty in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at the very, very, very bottom of this mailbag, way down there at the bottom, one email here for me to read tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: One email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of a long email, so it'll work.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to email us for a future week, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: When DarkSakura gets back and she's over her allergies and all that, let's make her work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us like 10 emails for next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you can send 10 emails from 10 different people, I will get DarkSakura a taco.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that bet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragenator is our emailer tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that we all in the VOG community have at least one thing in common.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're all gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to actually stop you right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: VOG is actually the voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I think most of the people do play some games, but certainly not every show on VOG is about games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think we do have a couple hosts who maybe don't play nearly as many video games as the rest of us do.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please...
[SPEAKER_03]: Please do make that a note, even though OLR, Bobby Blackwolf, Girls Gone Wow, you know, we're all strictly about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Under Station Live dabbles in it, PodCulture dabbles in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are not strictly video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyhow, I think you would be right in saying gaming is one big part of geek culture.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: He goes on to say,
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty, Madden, Mortal Kombat
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: This email has been brought to you by Bobby's googly-eyed Oculus Rift.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now if only DarkSakura can get him to use the damn thing to play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Garrus all the things.
[SPEAKER_03]: That email again from Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the question from Ragenator, why gaming?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll ask Loki here in a minute here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me read some of the answers from... No, no, let me go to Loki, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, why gaming?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do you play video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a medium, I guess, to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just like if you were to play with Legos or if you were to draw or you're going to do something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just what I ended up doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's what I started off early with, like, you know, PC games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I did other things other than just, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: All sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for some reason, it's just something that we do nowadays.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, why watch TV?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why listen to the radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's to the point now where video games are kind of like watching TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that common.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really... It's like, why eat food?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a little bit me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go back to my senior year of high school and you look at me in the yearbook, I'm in six different clubs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that doesn't even count.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to do a public access TV show.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people don't know about this because I don't want Travis Donovan ever finding the tapes of it because God knows what will happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was doing all this stuff when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think a lot of that was just because...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it was out of boredom or just out of the fact like, you know, when I was sitting at home doing nothing, I just felt really depressed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had to kind of get out and do these different things, and I just almost overdid it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And video games, to some extension, were a real social thing at that age.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the reason why I got into it, to answer the question, actually very similar to what Raginator said at the beginning there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Being able to kind of control the pictures on the TV I think was a real kind of novel thing when you're like six years old, five years old, and very impressionable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to the chat room and some of the answers there let's see Brad from PogCulture says why not gaming?
[SPEAKER_03]: Black Wolf says, I don't do underwater basket weaving because I don't have a pool.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is no place to practice.
[SPEAKER_03]: But a game console is cheaper than a backyard pool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Degenerate Johnny says, why gaming?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it makes me harder than Peter North in a Bukkake festival.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where every gamer has a voice, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100Matt with a far more serious answer saying, Escapism is the thing for some people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, DarkSakura is still listening to the show, and she sent an answer over private message here, because if she were here, I'd ask her what she says.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she told me over chat, she says, I had a rotten childhood, and I would hide in books.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: as far as why I like it over another medium it's that again that process of immersion having an active hand in what happens in the game makes it a lot better than being a passive participant so there you go
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think, you know, I use this kind of example today as like some of my friends ask me like, wow, you play a lot of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't you addicted?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you addicted to World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I go, well, how have you spent your free time?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've watched every single episode of Lost twice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you addicted?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you addicted to Lost?
[SPEAKER_03]: Game of Thrones?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you addicted to that?
[SPEAKER_02]: TV tells me that you're addicted to, wow, because you can't just like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You must be addicted.
[SPEAKER_02]: TV, TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: so yeah it's like yeah I may play a lot of video games but if you ask me like what movies I've seen lately I see maybe 10% of what I really want to see I saw the first half of Plains yesterday and you asked me about TV shows I'm especially clueless the fact that I watched Orange is the New Black from start to finish says a lot about that show because there's very few shows I've watched from start to finish very few so there you go
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the only email tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com if you would like to send us an email for a future week.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the meantime, let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is the part of the show where we give our angst.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, well, Loki, would you like to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, uh, big fuck you to Cyclist, because you're always in my goddamn way on the street.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this guy that was in front of me today, you know, not on a bike lane or anything, just kind of in the middle of the goddamn street, riding his bike super goddamn slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't go around him, because if I go try to, you know, share the lane with him and go around him, then I might hit him, and that would be bad, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, what is up with all these people?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that you're not on a fucking team practicing for the race, but wearing your stupid, like, skin-tight, you know, uniforms with all your sponsors on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fat dude wearing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do not have sponsors.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not in a race.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not practicing for a race.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My boss has, like...
[SPEAKER_03]: a group of people that he rides with and they all have like jean uniforms and stuff it's ridiculous you're not in races okay you don't have sponsors what the hell all right uh DarkSakura sending her FUs uh by private messages she wants you all to know FU to my fucking sinuses which makes sense uh and 115 school books for one fucking class oh my god a lot of money um
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU of the week goes to construction on Highway 80 between Vacaville and Dixon.
[SPEAKER_03]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I realize, look, construction workers don't hard... Construction workers work hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't blame you personally.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you have to do that stuff, but here's the thing that pissed me off about it is that there was no warning.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you know traffic is going to be backed up at 1.30 in the morning for one hour, have
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have sympathy if they chose to show an abducted child message over a construction message.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be okay with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to show nothing at all that warns me, hey, try taking a back road is a little bit irritating.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't know that this month is California Repave the Road Month.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Spare the Air Day tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, Spare the Air Day!
[SPEAKER_02]: Spare the Air!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or click it or tick it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else do they put on those Amber Alert signs that have nothing to do with their purpose?
[SPEAKER_03]: Report drunk drivers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's some of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of this stuff is important, and I'm not trying to belittle it, but I sometimes feel like when they do this, it's like when the text message... Remember when they sent the Amber Alert text message to everybody at 2 in the morning about the kid that got kidnapped?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tons of people disabled it right after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did they do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they assholes that don't care about kids?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's because that hideous thing showed up on people's phones at 2 in the morning going...
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And then at the end of the trailer, also announced the bundle that was going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thankfully, there are some people that took screen caps.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is this new bundle going to have in it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's basically a Wii U, black Wii U system with the gamepad having what looks like a decal on it with some, you know, the Zelda, like, flourishes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's, like, some little bit of gold...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of a hard sell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, when other systems like the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 are $199, that's a lot of games you can buy in between that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, it's not Zelda, but this is not technically a new Zelda either.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is an HD remake that you're trying to convince people to buy a system for a brand new Zelda, which it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they'll announce said brand new Zelda next year, but there's still a lot of ways to go from there, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you put a demo for brand new Zelda on that disc, then you're talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then those things will go flying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, unfortunately, some sad news to end on tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that has to do with a studio closure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seattle-based studio Big Fish has gone through a round of layoffs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is closing its Vancouver studio and has gone into a 30-day consultation period about its Cork, Ireland operations.
[SPEAKER_03]: CEO Paul Thelen sent a letter to staff that talked about the changes.
[SPEAKER_03]: They talked about 49 layoffs in its Seattle headquarters and another 70 employees realigned.
[SPEAKER_03]: 524 full-time employees in Seattle previously.
[SPEAKER_03]: 9% of the studio cut.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to stress that our decisions are not based on company-wide performance or that of the people working on these initiatives, both of which are strong, but because of where the market is growing and, quite frankly, where it is not.
[SPEAKER_03]: The most significant decision we are making today is that we are discontinuing our premium cloud delivery business.
[SPEAKER_03]: This service is not growing as fast as we had hoped it would and is not on a path to profitability.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That does it for news tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is time for us to open up the Skype line and get some calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, or you can still call us on the good old telephone, 1-877-GAME-OLR is where you can call us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio, all one word on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of calls, there's this weird new thing happening on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I should talk about it, but I think we're getting spam voicemails.
[SPEAKER_03]: I seriously had seven voicemails throughout the week from random numbers, but I would try to click play because I thought, oh, maybe somebody's actually leaving us a bumper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's actually a new listener.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I click play and nothing happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I go, all the voicemails are the same length.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all four minutes and 22 seconds.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm like,
[SPEAKER_03]: that's probably spam probably tell me to go to some website and put in my social security number for a chance at some credit card or something lame alright well somebody's calling in on the phone right now so let's see what happens when we pick up the phone and go do it hi you're on Orange Launch Radio who's this hey it's Jim Sally guy hey Jim Sally what's up buddy
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally forgot you guys have an old school telephone man sitting on your show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do have the old school telephone sitting on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I was surprised to hear from you on it because usually you call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you just wanting to test that it still worked?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm outside in my garage and the Skype lady was saying she didn't like my Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to call you and be all choppy on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Jim Sally, to what do we owe this phone call tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to give my own little fuck you of the day today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It said I'd have a fucking paid subscription if I wanted to use goddamn Internet Explorer on my Microsoft machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, you want to use any of that premium shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's behind the freaking paywall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why didn't the fucking Internet Explorer premium?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the shittiest browser out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should apologize to me when I turn it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I make me pay for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I went to go to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuckin' Sesame Street videos and motherfuckin' YouTube don't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay, they make up for it by letting you use Bing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my fucking god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bing doesn't work either.
[SPEAKER_06]: You go to Bing and you search something and it says you gotta pay for shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You go and look for what's on your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that would be nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should allow you to set your... Maybe we should do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Set up some type of website on OrangeLaunchRadio.com that you could set your home browser to in Internet Explorer on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: That way, every time you open the browser, it would take you to a page that says, Welcome to Internet Explorer 10 on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're very sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else doesn't work that I'm going to find out now?
[SPEAKER_06]: The X button on the fucking controller?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Netflix doesn't work?
[SPEAKER_06]: If I pay for Netflix, it doesn't work?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can go suck a dick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you Microsoft for making my decision to buy a Playstation 3 so much fucking easier
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was considering buying an Xbox One for the pass-through, because I do use the Xbox to communicate with people, but fuck, I bet you my Messenger doesn't work anymore now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet you my Amazon Messenger doesn't work anymore on my fucking Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck Xbox, man!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck Xbox, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't buy one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just always put the Kylo on this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy an iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game's free.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fucking better.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know the one thing I'm kind of sad about with these new systems is that they don't have... They only have HDMI out, and they don't have options for... I understand, like, component and stuff, you know, would have been nice, but, like, I play a lot on a PC monitor that has just a VGA in, and I'm sure there's a cable I could get, but it's going to be an elaborate setup just to play
[SPEAKER_02]: on a VGA monitor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really wish they'd have that so I could use a VGA cable like they had with the Xbox 360, because I get a lot of use out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox One, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone forget about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just buy a PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 4 or 2 does the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of sucks, because there's only really one TV I can play that on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I'd do PC monitor, which I really don't want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'd really encourage, you know, those looking for podcasting tips or whatever, take a look on the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: But is this something that might happen, Jim Sally?
[SPEAKER_03]: We looking at a Jim Sally show coming soon?
[SPEAKER_06]: We are, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're doing a little experimentation episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not going to be... I always thought I'd have to do a video game show, but even Bobby says don't even worry about video game shows on the VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wants lots of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to do a... It's called Jim Sally's Macho Man, where Jim Sally teaches geeks how to be macho men.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of us are too geeky.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't know how to do things like drive a fucking stick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have my friends that can drive a stick in Gran Turismo all day long, and then they get into my little Porsche and they can't back it out of my driveway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of love this idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as it stays on that line of being tongue-in-cheek and not insulting, but I know you can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you can do it, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, a little bit insulting, because you should macho up, but then obviously teach the person how to do something.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jim Sally, I'm going to let you go so we can get more calls, but it's always a delight to hear from you, and look forward to your new show soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright everybody, stay tuned for more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, night Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to send Jamie a special message?
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, I want to send you a special message right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now I'm snuggling my pillow and I'm sending it to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just squeezing the sinuses juice right out of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, gushing out of your nose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, can you feel it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, Jamie, that's for you, baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally, I'm going to leave you to your pillow, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wasn't creepy or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie's in chat right now going, ew, the snot is everywhere now.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, do you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to talk about the release of a homebrew game for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Aperture Science DS and as you might imagine, it is a DS version of Portal.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can download it for free on smelium.net it's S-M-E-A-L-U-M dot net slash A-S-D-S Aperture Science DS so check that out it looks pretty impressive actually for a DS game
[SPEAKER_02]: For homebrew, I guess, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the GamePop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember them?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're one of those Android consoles that we kind of forgot about.
[SPEAKER_02]: But GamePop was the one that had the monthly service that you would subscribe to, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've actually announced some partnerships with different mobile game developers, including TinyCo, who does Tiny Village.
[SPEAKER_02]: uh, Animaca, I guess Pretty Pet Salon, and Creative Mobile, which does the drag racing franchise, also, uh, Halfbrick with, you know, the Jetpack Joyride guys, uh, Vector Unit, who do Riptide GP, and Glue, Heroes of Destiny, and they're saying that they're gonna have about 500 games available when the GamePop launches in winter, and, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so it's going to be, I think if I remember correctly, it's like a streaming model.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you would be able to get a free mini model that requires a $6.99 monthly subscription or the more powerful model of the console, which is $129, but the subscription service is still required.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then also GamePop games I guess can be played with a smartphone as well instead of just the controller if you really want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although why the hell would you buy a gaming console to play on your phone when you can just play these games on your phone to begin with?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sometimes with the Wii U you're going to play on the tablet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But remember it's not all a card.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's $6.99 and you get access to 500 games so there's that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me give another call for the Skype line if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boy, Bobby didn't get any calls tonight either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody's shy tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least we got Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_03]: If nothing else, God bless Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the meantime, I want to get to Twitter topics here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trying to bring it up on my iPad right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except I had the Rocky Horror Picture Show up on my iPad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, just a couple tweets tonight from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tigerclaw sending us a couple tweets.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them, a Metroid fan film Kickstarter taken down over IP dispute with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does this surprise anybody?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised somebody thought they could get away with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys, it's Degenerate Johnny Hey Degenerate Johnny, how you doing buddy?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't complain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to apologize.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of missed most of last week's show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was over at Gen Con last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understood you sent in an email to the show and we somehow missed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't purposely omit it, but I worry that we get a lot of spam at our email address and it might have been accidentally thrown in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I totally understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to call people's attention to the VOG Network forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: You posted your poem that you'd written there and it was brilliant, so I just want to make sure people see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, alright, I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was going to let you guys know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just came across, during my time at Gen Con, I came across a certain game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think you guys have covered it, but I might as well just let you guys know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played around with it, and I know we're talking about Hearthstone and all that, but this game, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a card game.
[SPEAKER_07]: but the MMO card game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you guys have heard of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Hex Shards of Fate.
[SPEAKER_03]: The title sounds familiar but I don't know much about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like it's one of those games we probably had a rapid fire news story on at one point and I didn't really look into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you have my attention.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us more about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like MMO card game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's being developed by Cryptozoic Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are the ones that, for those who listen to Horde House, Cryptozoic has a license for the World of Warcraft games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I don't know if you heard about this, Degenerate Johnny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blizzard announced this week, I'll throw this in here as a last-minute story, that the latest expansion of the WoW trading card game is the last, and that they are no longer going to be making it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are ending that relationship, and there's no plans in the future to continue the WoW trading card game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that's because of Hearthstone or what, but I thought I would throw that little nugget out there just because I read that the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard about that, actually, at Gen Con.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was talking with one of the Cryptozote guys, and
[SPEAKER_07]: They did mention that it was going to be the last expansion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Their relationship has matured with Blizzard to a degree that now they're going to develop their own type of games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this Hex Shards of Fate game is actually evidence of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just wowed about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, Hex Shards of Fate is a...
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually had a Kickstarter earlier this summer, actually, and they just wanted a Kickstarter just to finish off the game, but they managed to get like seven times the amount that they were asking for it, so now it's going to be able to be available for Apple tablets and Android tablets, so lots of stuff is going on with this game, and
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's due to be released in sometime this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's free to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually following probably the same type of business model as
[SPEAKER_07]: Blizzard is doing with Hearthstone, basically $2 a pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, they're also adding a freemium service.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want to have a discount on your packs and gain access to tournaments free of charge, they're offering a VIP access, which is basically $4 a month type of thing, kind of like a subscription, but you get a pack every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a card of the month club.
[SPEAKER_03]: The card of the week club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just say cancel at any time and we'll stop sending you the cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so it's going to have an auction house for you to trade your cards, buy
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's so much information, and I just want to let you know that they are going to be at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anybody who's going to go there, or if you, or Bobby, you know, if anybody wants to see around, they will be at DragonCon, so you can see it for yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Degenerate Johnny, I thought of you recently because I know you're a big card game fan and a friend of mine introduced me to a card game and I did the whole thing where I actually went to the comic book shop and played this game with my friends he was actually doing a lot of demos with this game at GamerX so I want to give a shout out to this game because it was a lot of fun totally not the game you called in to talk about tonight but I hijacked your call, I'm sorry but the game is called Sentinels of the Multiverse have you played this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen it being played at
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds very familiar.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds kind of similar to Lord of the Rings because Lord of the Rings is a game where you basically go up against a
[SPEAKER_07]: Deck, that it's not you, but it's not another player, it's just you taking on scenarios.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can do it in co-op, so you can be in your own fellowship.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's very interesting, and I'm seeing that it's pretty interesting that card games are now making the rise of basically you don't have to find someone to play with, you can play it with yourself, or
[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: what's the name of the game again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sentinels of the Multiverse and we actually might get the guy on one of the shows later on or one of the developers of the game because I don't think it would be a good fit for OLR but I'm going to see if some of the other VOG shows are interested in it so if not we'll do a Google Hangout or something but yeah anyway Degenerate Johnny I should probably let you go so we can wrap up the show but thanks for your call always a pleasure to hear from you my pleasure take care
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys take care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: A couple other tweets here from some listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do want to give us a call, we can try to squeeze in one more call.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blizzard on World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd be lost without casuals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, before I get to that, I should... TigerClaw sent in that tweet on Metroid Fan Film.
[SPEAKER_03]: He wanted to clarify, make sure we report on the fact that the fan film was only going to be 10 minutes and non-for-profit, but they were asking for $90,000 to fund it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: 10 minutes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they were going to actually film in space.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't read up on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got another call coming in, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a webcam call.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good to see you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think it's been mentioned either last week or the week before although you did mention some news that was kind of sort of related I think it was last week and the week before you mentioned that Microsoft is getting rid of the Microsoft coins and they also in turn they're getting rid of the games for Windows Marketplace
[SPEAKER_00]: One thing that was not mentioned is that they're getting rid of the Zune marketplace.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in fact, I found this out through an email that Microsoft had sent out to me not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the way it's been explained to me, the reason why they're getting rid of the Zune marketplace is because
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, apparently the Zoom Microfaces set up in such a way that it would only recognize Microsoft points as a method of payment.
[SPEAKER_00]: They won't recognize dollars and cents or pesos or euros or whatever your local currency happens to be.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_00]: To catch 22 is, if you have an Xbox 360, you'll still be able to use the 12-in-2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But with the old tech, you're screwed, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is why, Reginator, knowing a company's exit strategy for the inevitable day that they close their doors in the day and age of digital distribution is so important.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I think that's one reason everybody kind of goes to Steam a little bit because Steam has made it very clear should we ever close our doors we have the magic button that we can press that will make all the games DRM free and you won't have to connect to the servers anymore but you know when we talk about movies and music and so forth that really sucks if you were one of those people who actually invested in a Zune and it's like okay you'll have those movies but you can't really use the Zune now for anything else or like my HD DVD player
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the weird thing is, at least with me, ever since Sony burned me a handful of times, when I still had my PlayStation 3, I had to send my system in to get repaired to have my VOs reactivated, I slowly but surely made my way over to the Zoom service and been getting...
[SPEAKER_00]: TV shows and movies and this and that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Granted, the vast majority of the stuff were the freebies, but I do have my fair share of the paid content.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, case in point, I've just been going to 90's and VOG music soundtrack whenever I've been getting
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been using this service for my PC because I don't have iTunes or anything I happen to have.
[SPEAKER_00]: Xbox accounts set up for when I still had the 360, so no need for extra passwords, remembers, so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragenator, this is kind of a crap situation, but unfortunately, this is the downside to tech, and especially when our tech advances so fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think tough lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_03]: always take a look at that user license agreement even though you're not going to sit there and read all 27 pages or 99 pages or however long it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look for that part that talks about who really owns the stuff that you're buying and what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, Ragenator, we're going to wrap up so we can wrap up the show but any quick other thoughts you want to get out before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, there'll be.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just want to really mention the closing of that particular service since it really wasn't mentioned before.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, did I already check?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we have anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No more last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let me see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I had one other tweet here that I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, TheGarthWolf sent us a tweet that says, I totally got into the XIV Coral server tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got to play the intro quest and now maintenance just started.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just my luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were talking a little bit about the Final Fantasy XIV, kind of the bumpy launch they've been having.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just hope in a week it's all a distant memory.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I want to make sure I got this one in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grandpa from Horde House sent this tweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I almost forgot it because he sent it earlier in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's a video.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, long story short, it's another one of those freaking sensationalistic CNN things where an eight-year-old shot his 90-year-old caretaker and it was because of a violent video game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think, don't quote me on this, but I think this is the one that Piers Morgan on his Twitter said,
[SPEAKER_03]: wrote out there and said, don't tell me after hearing things like this that violent video games don't cause violent behavior and da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da, blah-blah-blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here we go again with the media, you know, well, and this is a nightmare that an eight-year-old boy would shoot his 90-year-old caretaker, but who was letting an eight-year-old game play violent video games unsupervised?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not blaming the 90-year-old.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm blaming the parents.
All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a crazy show tonight, but we're on out of here for the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys, as always, for listening to our show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for your download.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for your support.
[SPEAKER_03]: We always appreciate you supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully you liked what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you didn't, just be sure to support other independent broadcasters.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's many people out there working very hard to put these types of shows together.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we all appreciate your support so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm not going to ask you for your money or a financial donation.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will ask, if you like what you heard, spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Post a nice five-star review on iTunes or give us a thumbs up in Stitcher or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Help us spread the word about the show because that is all the marketing that we can afford is word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, any last-minute thoughts tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to just try to finish up Saints Row 4 this week, maybe even tonight, because I'm almost at 100%.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about how to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I hope I get to play at least another hour of Final Fantasy XIV tonight, but we'll see if that stupid maintenance finishes right at the time I get home from picking up Alan.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fantastic timing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well that does it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a great Labor Day, those of you guys here in the States.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those of you in other countries, have a great week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enjoy your time and have fun playing the various online games that are launching over the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be back for another show live Sunday, September 8th.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll see you then with another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!