[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, August 18, 2013, several more changes are announced that will affect the launch of the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_01]: GameStop defends a high price for used copies of Xenoblade and Metroid Prime, and more details emerge on Grand Theft Auto V.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, episode 516.
[SPEAKER_06]: For this, August the 18th of 2013, we're here to talk about video games, gaming culture, gamer lifestyle, with me, Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm one of your hosts, and joining me, as she does every Sunday night, say hello to Dark Sakura, or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing, Dark Sakura, or Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or...
[SPEAKER_14]: and... All of the above.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can be whoever you want to be.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I'll be me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you do... I'm really out of it today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's been a weird, weird week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you on any prescription medications right now?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm always on prescription medications that keep me from killing people on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I mean, like, are you... No, no OxyContin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Any sickness going around?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have the rockin' pneumonia and the boogie-woogie flu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_15]: That means I'm happy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: An apparently obscure reference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and there's Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, lots of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get to Gaming Weeks here shortly, but I noticed you brought a big box full of Disney Infinity with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I noticed that you were able to get the game early through your connections, and you put up a YouTube, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You did a little unboxing YouTube, because information on Disney Infinity has been kind of not...
[SPEAKER_06]: around, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: The review embargo apparently didn't lift until today, or they didn't have early reviews or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they were afraid the game wasn't going to get good reviews, although it seems like it's doing all right from the minimal things I've seen today.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you did this whole unboxing, you did some playing, and hilarious stuff going down on YouTube, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, just typical YouTube commenters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Demanding...
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to tell me how you got that or else I'm going to report you.
[SPEAKER_08]: To who?
[SPEAKER_08]: The police?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing this game before I have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would have actually done some more actual Let's Plays and stuff, but I just...
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you did, I thought you were up on...
[SPEAKER_08]: Audio, I was trying to split the audio going to the TV So split it between the video capture card and my headset But when I did that, because I needed an amp on it When I did that, there was no audio coming through at all So tech issues Yeah, tech issues So I ended up just listening through my computer But the audio was lagged by a second or so So it was just a little annoying
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not to tap into your gaming week too much, although I'm sure you've played plenty else besides Disney Infinity, but what did you think overall of Disney Infinity?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's alright, because I hadn't really played Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_08]: I checked out just the beginning.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did a couple of the tutorials, walking through some of the sandbox or the toy box stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay, but you don't start off with a whole lot of pieces to build with the toy box stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, some of that you get through, like, these little power-up disc things that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, not a whole ton of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of it's just kind of cosmetic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, it looks like Alice in Wonderland or Little Nemo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just, it's really kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, there's...
[SPEAKER_08]: they have some pre-built stuff that you can look at but a lot of it you have to play through the actual they call them the play sets so like the story campaigns I guess for each of the characters so I've been playing through Pirates of the Caribbean which is alright it
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, it's definitely a kid's game, so it's geared towards that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was going to ask you, what did your young one think of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you let him kind of watch?
[SPEAKER_08]: He didn't really get to watch play, because the only time I get to play is when he's gone to bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and he might be a little too young, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like at three, you don't really... He doesn't really understand how to use controllers and stuff yet, but he liked the figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: He took all the Cars figures and put them on this little table with his cars and stuff and was playing with them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's kind of how I got it, too, is because I'd mentioned to my friend at Disney that my son was really into, like, he loved Mater.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was trying to get Mater figures, what I was trying to do, and they ended up just sending me everything to play with the Mater figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, the game, the Cars playset, and Mater figures.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what all, because I'm having a hard time understanding, like, what all crap are they selling with this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because with Skylanders, it's just the figures.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really the only stuff they sell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, in the Skylanders, it's not just the figures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Originally, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because Skylanders, like, okay, so Skylanders, they have, you know, and they have a lot, a lot of it is figures, but it's so crazy now because they have, like, for Giants, they have...
[SPEAKER_08]: The regular figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have light core figures that light up when you put them on the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have giant figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then with Swap Force, they're going to have Swap Force figures with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they have adventure sets.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they have battle sets that have figures and then crap with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so what all is there for Disney Infinity?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because now we've entered this world where they're not even really microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are literally transactions.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going into the store and buying something tangible.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's physical DLC is basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what all is there?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's character statues, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's individual characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have character three packs.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they have a villains pack that has Davy Jones, Randy, and Syndrome from all three of the characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sets that are in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there's a Sidekicks pack that has Mike, Mrs. Incredible, and Captain Barboza.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I don't even know all the packs, but you've got these characters, and then what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got the hidden discs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have the blind packs of the power-up discs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what do they do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are basically just, they have add-ons, like little power-up add-ons for the characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I got two with that, and then I bought personally four because...
[SPEAKER_08]: and, you know, I haven't invested any money in it yet, so, you know, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have yet to get any of the circular power-up discs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've gotten all just the little, I don't know, hexagonal discs that they have.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do they do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have the full rare set.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, what do they do?
[SPEAKER_08]: They unlock things in the game, so you have, like, it could be vehicles, like, you know, Mickey's Jalopy or, you know, there's Abu and stuff like that, or, like, guns or cosmetic stuff, like, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: different skins for your playset world.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said you had a Wreck-It Ralph one, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it skins the background like Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so what's the difference between the characters and then there's a thing called a playset that has the two characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is playset like another... Yeah, the playset's basically like a single-player campaign.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's a story campaign.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they have a Cars playset and then it comes with two cars with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they've got the Lone Ranger playset that's got the two characters with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, they do, like I said, they do kind of prompt you to like, you know, try to get you the purchase stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, Skylanders did the exact same thing and it doesn't, I didn't run into it too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the trickiest part though because especially when it's for kids because, you know, if you have a six or seven year old that is about the right age to be doing this stuff, you know, they're going to hit these roadblocks and Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, I have to have it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't have to give in to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, of course they're going to try it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like TV commercials, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Daddy, daddy, I want whatever's on the TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to have this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, there's that, but I don't think it's a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're ruining my life if you don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to just die.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried both Lightning McQueen and Mater in the Cars game, and it didn't seem like they played too different.
[SPEAKER_08]: They played pretty much exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so I don't think it's just a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although it was kind of funny to watch Mater, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe the play sets, you really need the play sets, and they come with characters, but maybe you don't need to buy all these extra characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you probably don't need to buy all these extra characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the play sets come with two characters, so it's kind of nice if you wanted to co-op, like if you have kids and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: you know it has two characters in there I just you know other than you know the characters that are you know in these playsets there's not a whole ton else that you might want maybe if you wanted to co-op in like the regular game you probably would want to pick up at least maybe the sidekicks pack or something so that way you have an extra set of characters you can play through each one of the playsets but I mean it's you don't have to do all that stuff and a lot of the stuff you do unlock things as you go through the game and on top of
[SPEAKER_08]: Just the toy box mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a lot of customization within, like, the actual game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, in the Pirates of the Caribbean, so if you can pick up the actual people and throw them into the shop, you can customize what each character looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can customize your ship and what the loadouts are and that and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a lot of it you have to buy with in-game money.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, I had, like, to upgrade my Kansas, I had to, you know, earn money.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a lot of grind to get that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: The ship combat's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't have a store you could just go into and spend 99 cents?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they don't have anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as I saw, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Daddy, daddy, daddy, buy me!
[SPEAKER_08]: Buy me!
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they're going to do anything like that because I think that could be a big problem if, you know, all of a sudden kids racked up, you know, hundreds of dollars in online transactions.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's go to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mean to neglect you folks, but you got a lot of good questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to let Loki get his thoughts out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I wanted to have a coughing fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern on Sundays, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we do have our chatters there at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see some of the questions here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Claw says, Do you guys think Disney Infinity could be huge this coming holiday season, given how successful Skylanders was?
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be bigger because of the Disney's name.
[SPEAKER_06]: well I think that's the idea and I think a lot of like if this game flops which I kind of don't think it will but if this game flops like Disney Interactive will close I think that's kind of what's riding on this for real because they've invested a lot into this I don't see how it could fail right now
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: so there's that going forward and really like the new Skylanders game is just kind of a very linear action game and so I just don't know don't think there's a whole lot of incentive to buy stuff for that E3VL wants to know what your YouTube channel is where you had the unboxing where he can leave nasty comment no I made that part up but where can you leave it's just LokiOLR it's all one word yeah just all one word
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, Dartetsuya at live.vognetwork.com asks, you think the figures and discs and so forth will get to be like the pins at the Magic Kingdom?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's what Disney wants.
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely, and they have rares in each one of the sets.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got a full set and then some of the rares so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure some of the Disney souvenir shops are already selling this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they have exclusive rares.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, they have Mike's car that's exclusive to Toys R Us right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that would assume that I would have gotten you the Disney Infinity Star instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're playing make-leave.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but if I was being a parent, I wouldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, then Uncle Loki was spoiling and bought it for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so now I have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you, Uncle Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy, you have to buy me!
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy, you have to buy me the cars!
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy, Mommy, Mommy!
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to buy it!
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have to buy you shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go to your room.
[SPEAKER_13]: You little ingrate!
[SPEAKER_13]: Time out!
[SPEAKER_13]: Ten minutes in your room on time out and you're not allowed to play with any toys.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to stare at the wall.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then come back and tell me what you did wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or you could go to the backyard and pick a switch.
[SPEAKER_06]: that's what happened to me when I was a kid alright let's see I love you guys chat it's live.vognetwork.com let's see other comments here back on a serious note Black Wolf wants to know how much story is included in the base game without buying anything else you have the full thing for Pirates of the Caribbean The Incredibles and Monsters U so you have three play sets basically
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like three little mini-adventures you get to play through.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're pretty long.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I've already played through about a few hours of Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not very far into it, so there's a lot there, a lot of content, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw wants to know, does the game actually end if you don't have all the figures?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you just play the core game and finish it?
[SPEAKER_06]: So you get the three little adventures, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob's Annoying Kid Impression is Awesome
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XIV Final Fantasy XIV
[SPEAKER_06]: and we're going to talk about this by just you know straight up the first version never happened bad figment of the imagination not going to go talk about version 1 anymore because this is now the real Final Fantasy 14 it always seemed like the intro was like we blew up that world lol yeah well he said he was inspired by World of Warcraft Cataclysm the producer so
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Ragnarok Online Back in the Beta
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, seriously, when I was in the beta of that game for seven years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you haven't had a console game come around lately that sucked you in like that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, when I had hand surgery, I was high on Vicodin and played Blue Dragon and almost finished the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Which actually, that happened to me once, but it resolved itself within 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I didn't really have the serious issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: And besides full servers once in a while, which seems to also go away after 15-20 minutes, I'm not hearing of a lot of issues that my friends are having.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I go over to Reddit or forums, I see you would think the entire world's having problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sucks that people are getting locked out of this beta, but...
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, there was the world full thing today.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I actually went and made a character on the European server, on Shiva, just so I could see what the server lists looked like.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there were maybe four servers that weren't blacked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: so Midgarcimer is what we picked well finally it took a good 24 hours but Midgarcimer filled up too now and they had to actually open new worlds and unfortunately people can only roll on the new worlds they can't go to the worlds so I kind of think that part is a bit of a mess that Square is going to have to figure out a solution because why would you fucking play an MMO if you can't play it with your friends it gets really boring that way I mean we'll go make new friends moron why did I stop playing WoW
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why am I playing less and less WoW?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, more and more people I know left.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, if we were, and I was actually saying something to that, I prefer playing Alliance to Horde, and unfortunately our Alliance guild just sort of dried up, except for Grandpa.
[SPEAKER_06]: but you can't blame people for not having fun anymore and not enjoying the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they left because for whatever reason they were having fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I said I don't blame anybody but that's why I left because I had no one to play with that and Pandas was kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pandas as in the expansion was I hate the grind.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate the grind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, every expansion has its own noun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, so Final Fantasy XIV is going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And despite those things, I hope they are able to institute... I think the World Pass thing that they had in Final Fantasy XI actually worked out really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where, like, if you're friends on the server, they buy you a pass that you can use to get on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it costs them a lot of gil, depending on how many people are already on the server.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bought me mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but people will do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: People will do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, otherwise, I mean, the good news is I'm just God, the game is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love running instances with friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was myself, Shane, Captain Spike from Game Buoy and Tim Tripp.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're all running it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just we have the perfect layout of classes that the four of us can make a light party.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we did the beginner instances just back to back last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're they're so fucking gorgeous and having fun with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, you actually pretty much learn how to do that when you're soloing your duties.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for folks that liked Warcraft back in the very beginning when it was minimal abilities too, I think they might find something kind of fun in Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm definitely buying the game when it comes out and I will sub for at least a few months while I figure out, you know, am I going to cancel WoW to play this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I going to
[SPEAKER_06]: stick with this I'm really curious to see what the end game is like because I know a lot about Final Fantasy 14 from level 0 to 20 because I've actually been in since the alpha so I've done that grind like 5 times 0 to 20 and so I know a lot about it but I don't know much about what the game is past that and that kind of concerns me but it could I mean it's only a concern that doesn't mean it's gonna be negative I just don't know and if the end game isn't exciting enough it's not gonna really keep me there once I get to 50
[SPEAKER_15]: I will tell you one thing though is that I mean and you were online for a little bit of this when I went exploring in the level 30 area it actually had a lot of really neat stuff there were some neat characters I've found Costa del Sol which you can't get to right now except by walking because it's the fairies are disabled and Limsa Lominsa yeah Limsa Lominsa that's hard to say just say Limsa but which by the way is my favorite town so far
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the leader of that town, the female Rogadin.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's great, and her voice acting I like the best.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm super enjoying Arcanist.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, just because my carbuncle is so cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a great class.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I haven't had nearly the same problems I did with Thaumaturge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because Thaumaturge, well, I mean, they've also fixed the duties, but still.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I had to say that just what I saw, there were some pretty encouraging things for stories.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we're going to get more raid-like content and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like they're really going to be developing it and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if they fuck up some of these basics, like getting people who want to play together able to play together and in the same guild, if they fuck up these basics, it isn't going to matter how much they invest in the game in the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I really hope...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm at 14 right now, and I figured that when I hit like 18, I was going to start trying weaving or something, you know, whenever.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I've already decided that I'm probably going to be selling off some of my services so that I can afford to buy the game, because it really is...
[SPEAKER_15]: I was excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It has some of the elements I liked about Cataclysm that made me finally think WoW was fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because you remember how many times I started WoW and then just said, oh, boring, oh, boring, oh, boring.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had a lot of the fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had characters that made me, I laughed at my desk.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, especially with the Moogles drinking all the wine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see that bit?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I rolled a Lalafell this morning.
[SPEAKER_15]: A really cute little teeny lalafell
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha ha ha Maybe it was mining, I don't know But anyway, it was just funny The names of the quests have been funny I've really had a lot of fun The other big thing for me is that I have really been enjoying having my friends on People to chat with You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd give you a hug for free, Jim Sally But you have to come out here and get it
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm doing logos for people.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm working on a logo for a couple of people right now and making fabric art.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, good luck with all of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Check back in like 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check back in an hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure this will be the case in early access as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does open up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Midgarcimer is not supposed to be one of the super populated servers.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you will be able to get in eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just might be frustrating that you can't get in right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: But all of us that were super eager about this game, we all got in.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's going to be too tough to move everybody at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to stick it out on Midgarcimer.
[SPEAKER_06]: VOG Network
[SPEAKER_06]: So it'll be something like Vanquishers of Garland or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we want something that'll be VOG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gilgamesh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's very Final Fantasy-like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're gonna... So if you have some good ideas, throw them out there, especially Shane, because he'll be the one that puts it all together, I'm sure, because he's gonna... Verp of gastritis.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, we're looking at something where the abbreviation will be VOG.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just to kind of tie it together, be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Codeman says in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com, like I asked before, if you roll on that server when live, will you still be on that server?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the characters are not supposed to delete between open beta and live at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: If there is a huge game breaking bug, they may still erase them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because of all these issues people are having, maybe that'll be justification for them to erase them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this is why everybody was very much about like they wanted to get on the server they want to get on because this is your real character now that you're going to have in the main game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, Bobby said very old gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would mostly be accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Technus in chat says, if you can't think of a name, find a Latin phrase.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you don't know how many Warcraft guilds that worked for.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Final Fantasy XI to be fair alright Geeklet in our chatroom says they might have to wipe the server to fix that dumb error that is a distinct possibility so we all have to kind of be prepared for that that's why I kind of I leveled my and we'll wrap up this discussion guys I know we're going to get to the other games I leveled one of my jobs to like 18 and another one to 13 and then did some crafting stuff
[SPEAKER_06]: and so if they wipe them all I would be kind of mad but at the end of the day that's the reason why I stopped playing too and I'm not going to play anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I logged out and I'm getting my rest bar because if they do wipe it then fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll deal with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's kind of my logic too.
[SPEAKER_15]: The other thing too is that I'm probably going to stick with just caster classes for a while because and I love this so much over some of the stuff they did in 11 is that your gear will carry over
[SPEAKER_15]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and I can keep using my leather gear as a gladiator or whatever if I wanted to, so I wouldn't have to, because I sold all my old gear.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, anyhow, let's talk about officially our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So besides Disney Infinity, besides Final Fantasy XIV, what kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is there anything else, Rob?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, and clearly I'm playing Animal Crossing right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: My village is open.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if people want to add you, be your friend on 3DS so they can visit during the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: How do they do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'd have to add them back.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I might close and then reopen in Part B so I can put out my friend code because I don't memorize it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be here live, live.vognetwork.com Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's how you get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to be here live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's how you're going to get it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Unless one of you guys, like, I know Actdeft has it.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I would point you to the friend code thread at vognetwork.com, but I know Jamie doesn't check it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I posted it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, did you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I posted there.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Rob, thank you for your assumptions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm never happier to be wrong.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so insulted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, get over it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played some Mass Effect 3 because I am still working on trying to get a custom texture, not texture, a custom mesh to work, but unfortunately it's not using any of the default textures in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I hate using text mod with Mass Effect 3, so I'm just sort of like, bleh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, I am also, I've, what did I play?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, I played more Fractal.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm back to playing Fractal.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because that is my game that I play when my brain is too busy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, if I have all these thoughts that I just want to get out of my head, I completely blank out and play Fractal.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's such a good game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've also um I got Dan DuckTales and I got myself a copy I haven't touched it yet but basically I've been watching Dan play through the whole thing and humming along with the music because it's so good and he found a 8-bit music mode so he was super happy and playing through it with that um I played some other stuff what did I play oh yeah this well I went to Scandia this morning um because we went to breakfast and then played um mini golf which um
[SPEAKER_15]: It's 102 today, and it was already like 90-something at 11 this morning, so I was like, I'm not having any more of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've got a sunburn.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I went inside, and poor Scandia.
[SPEAKER_15]: I met a person who works there named Danny, who apparently owns 2DX machines, several of them, and a Pump It Up, and a DDR, and a Poppin' Music, and has the actual arcade cabinets.
[SPEAKER_15]: He showed me photos of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, I'm gonna be friends with you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he was fixing one of the machines that I lost some tokens to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sean again, it's Sean again, that's what it was
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: Dan played Crazy Taxi Crazy Money
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's make some crazy money!
[SPEAKER_15]: I was a little dismayed.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I shouldn't have been surprised.
[SPEAKER_15]: They have no more pinball.
[SPEAKER_15]: All the ticket games, of course, were in perfect condition, but the Tekken 5 had no monitor in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was another game that had no monitor in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: The X-Men vs. Street Fighter had such bad burn-in.
[SPEAKER_15]: The monitor was green.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really in bad shape.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played some Silent Scope, a little dark silhouette, because that one is really the best of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really did play a lot of stuff this week, relatively.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've loaned me Kid Icarus Uprising, which I started and then had to put down because the cat threw up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Midna has been the queen.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a crappy reason to stop playing a game.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's a barfy reason.
[SPEAKER_15]: She threw up on Dan's chair.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was such a brat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, so yeah, uh, and I was gonna start, um, Birth By Sleep, but I borrowed it from a friend, and I was like, I'm already playing too much, I just gave it back to her.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, is there anything else you actually played, or is this all thought about playing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, no, it's, I started stuff, and I, oh, and Final Fantasy 7, but I just cannot play it with keyboards, so, fuck it, I'm gonna find the controller somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It didn't play a whole ton of stuff other than Disney Infinity and Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I played a lot of Saints Row 4 the last couple days here and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely a lot different than Saints Row 3 with the whole superpower thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the same time, some of the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's kind of the only annoying thing is that there's not really a point to the cars at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was one little, I don't know if it's a glitch, but a design flaw, if I were to call it, where when you're buying stuff at a store, if people happen to be attacking you, it will kick you out of the menu that you're in.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, I was in Friendly Fire once.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's kind of dumb that they had that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand that, yeah, you can't hide in stores anymore to drop your notoriety.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, at the very least, they should pause the game when you're in a menu because it's kind of dumb that you can't browse the menu while you're in the middle of a fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I don't see why they should do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But whatever, that's their choice.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a little annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did find a couple hidden weapons in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have the penetrator, the giant dildo bat hidden in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, it's back.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's back, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also have a tentacle bat and they also have an anal probe that has a tongue on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes licking motions.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they've got that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Y'all need Jesus.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then some of the weapon skins they have in there are kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I didn't really mess with a whole ton of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have a lot of the upgrades are kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just... It felt like I... I don't really like the whole having to pick health pickups.
[SPEAKER_08]: Having to gather health pickups instead of having just a regenerating health, which has been in the game forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they decided to switch it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a huge deal, but it's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to think of what else.
[SPEAKER_08]: So far, the story's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't really played a whole bunch of the story missions yet, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was moments that I was laughing out loud.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the new... You know how the third had these wrestling moves you could do if you hold down sprint and hit one of the attack buttons?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now they have super-powered attacks, and they're just goddamn ridiculous, like throwing people up there and just stomping on their skull and
[SPEAKER_08]: Just ridiculous stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I kind of dig that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then what else?
[SPEAKER_08]: So I've been playing on an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just preloaded my Steam copy, so I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll be playing this for a while until Grand Theft Auto V comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then all bets are off.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just going to be Grand Theft Auto until I die.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk about Grand Theft Auto V and your excitement a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anything else for your gaming weakness?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you notice that they did change a few things around?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh god, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's that new level in the beginning, and then they totally changed the end, where in the NES game you used to go back to Transylvania, and that's where you would fight the last boss, but in this one they made a whole new level.
[SPEAKER_06]: They made the, you know, spoiler, sorry, but, you know, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: They made a new level, Mount Vesuvius, that you play instead, which is kind of like Inside a Volcano.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's very different and much harder in difficulty than the base levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: And more spoiler alert, after the final boss, there's a Metroid-esque escape element.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was definitely controller-throwing frustration.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luckily, I own a Wii U, so I wasn't about to throw that controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thought about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and although after you play through the whole thing once, you can skip cutscenes later on, it's still really annoying that you're going through the game and then, oh, stop, cutscene, oh, stop, cutscene.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I get that, you know, like if you have kids or whatever, like they're gonna eat it up, they're gonna love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you love the old 90s show, it's great, you're gonna love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I don't know like I kind of got over it pretty quick and I just wanted to play the game and that experience kept getting interrupted every five seconds and that was one thing I loved about the original game is it was it was this game you could really speed run and you know beat the whole thing in not even an hour maybe if you're good you know so I don't know I did not like that whole stop and go element and here's what really pissed me off the quality of the audio is atrocious
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounded... Not the music.
[SPEAKER_06]: The music's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: The voice acting audio quality?
[SPEAKER_06]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scrooge sounds like he's coming through an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_15]: It sounded really clear on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might be a Wii U thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be, but I heard the same thing from somebody who played it on 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's a console thing then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it is a console thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the quality of the sound itself was really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially the worst is when you're going through and he gets hit or whatever and you go, Oh, ouch!
[SPEAKER_06]: Things like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like...
[SPEAKER_06]: It gets drowned out by the music.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds really out of place.
[SPEAKER_06]: It gets really repetitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, not a fan of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when I was actually playing the game DuckTales Remastered, I was having a great time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could have done without all the other crap, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, what else?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was one other thing I wanted to say about DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I will say this, and I know this has got to be unique to the Wii U. I kind of think it was a lazy port, which shouldn't be a surprise whatsoever, but speaking of sound design, there was no, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to mute the gamepad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I cannot play the game with sound on the gamepad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that's a little bit annoying because the Nintendo games don't have that problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all synced up just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think that's just a lazy port problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I mean, I'm just saying overall in terms of the voices, I didn't notice a problem at all on the PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I might have to stream it when I'm playing through it just to see if anything comes across.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could also just be taste and maybe, you know, not to say you don't have an ear for this, DarkSakura, but having done audio editing for all these years doing the show, I just can hear it and I go, my God, where did they take this guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he sounds awful.
[SPEAKER_15]: After the show, I'd like to hear yours because I can tell you if there's a difference.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I will know next week And it's something I can't control So I'll tell you off air why But we'll talk about that later DarkSakura and Loki may put something else together We have to figure all that out Because I got something dropped on me I will know next week for sure
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, DragonCon
[SPEAKER_06]: So definitely come see that Saturday night, 5.30 is the VOG Super Show Not just me, Bobby Blackwolf, PodCulture I don't even remember, Travis Donovan's gonna be there One of the Critical Myth guys is there I hope I'm not forgetting everybody, anybody But yeah, so it'll be a whole bunch of us that do shows at VOG And possibly some surprises in store during that panel That's all I can say Like magical plane tickets for me Well, and you get a car, and you get a car No, nothing like that
[SPEAKER_06]: If you miss me Saturday night because, I don't know, there's something else going on, a good time to find me would be Monday at 11.30.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a streaming podcast panel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby's going to be a part of that, so I will be there just to support.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do a streaming podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be your second chance to see me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then I fly out of town Monday night.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you don't see me Monday at 11.30, you probably missed me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I will remind you of that next week during the last show before DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, friend us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're also on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to our news tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's been a lot of changes for the Xbox One for sure since the original announcement.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're trying to fix what people didn't like.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so here's another notch to add to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Xbox One will no longer require the Kinect to be plugged in in order for the system to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can play with the system unconnected from the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, if you're going to play a game that requires the Kinect, then obviously you have to plug it in.
[SPEAKER_08]: XBOX One Controllers
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get one for PC, but the drivers aren't coming out until 2014.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically, as we've stated, the Xbox One controller, although it looks similar in many ways, shares no underlying technology with the current Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: New wireless protocol combined with the ability to work in wired mode and additional features like impulse triggers means software has to be written and optimized for the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: However...
[SPEAKER_08]: This week, there was a big announcement for Call of Duty showing off the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the game was being played on PC with Xbox One controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: So those dumb fucks have the drivers, but they're making excuses so that if you really want to play with that controller, you better buy an Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just playing devil's advocate, could they have been developed third party?
[SPEAKER_06]: Could it be a Joy to Key situation?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's not because it was on a PC version of the game because they were able to go in the options and there was an enable gamepad option on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would you purposely delay the release of the drivers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because people then, oh, I want to get the Xbox One experience with Call of Duty and Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just going to buy the PC versions, and I don't need to buy an next-gen console for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what they're trying to do is trying to get the sync in so all these people that...
[SPEAKER_08]: Really need to have that controller are going to buy, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think you just pull, yank the 360 controllers off the market.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess you really can't do that when you're still selling the console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because as I say, for the PC people, make that not an option.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have to get the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a huge deal because, I mean, all you're really getting is those impulse control, you know, the impulse triggers or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess they have to build that in.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's still kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why they would do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever, you know, that's their decision.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I guess I just won't buy another controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that I really need one anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you getting the one at launch?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: At this point?
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't think you were.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not planning on getting one at all at the moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm still kind of on the fence with the PlayStation 4 just because of Grand Theft Auto V.
[SPEAKER_08]: and just because the launch lineup is not that strong I mean there's you know Killzone which looks cool but it's not really a game I'm interested in like I've played some of the other Killzone games and it's just not not my thing if it was a Resistance game or something that might be a whole different story because I'm a real big fan of Resistance but uh Killzone I'm not a huge fan of Drive Club I'm kind of eh and um Knack I just really don't care about Knack
[SPEAKER_08]: Infamous looks great.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'd definitely pick up Infamous next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I still might.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still may pick one up just because I already have my pre-order in with Amazon.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see what they announce this week and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they'll announce that there's a packing game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might sweeten the deal a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru also has a good point in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com when it comes to this Call of Duty ghosts and all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru says people could just stick with a 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that would seem really ridiculous that people, that they would hold back the drivers for that reason you're saying because if somebody really wants to have a console experience on a PC or whatever, like if you really want to play controller on a PC, then just, yeah, use a 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But my point is, so they have the drivers available, so their reasoning behind it is, oh, we have to
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not that hard to develop drivers for a controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it wouldn't seem like it's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think if anything, I'm thinking probably you'd see a third-party solution from some hackers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there going to be a USB plugged-in version?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The controller has a battery pack that you can put in there, and when you plug it in, it shuts off the radio for the wireless, so it acts like a wired controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is like a PlayStation 3 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, speaking of Xbox One, some changes with the launch of the Xbox One, and that is certain countries kind of got screwed with the launch because Xbox One was originally going to launch in 21 different countries.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Microsoft, in a blog post, said that goal was too aggressive and that Xbox One will only be available in 13 territories this November.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Belgium, Denmark, Finland, Netherlands, Norway, Russia, Sweden, Switzerland...
[SPEAKER_06]: You got screwed.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you will get the console in 2014 instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Russia earned it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a whole nother Oprah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's bad ship yields is what they can't make enough to cover all those countries.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe they're just trying to fortify their position in the countries that they know that they can do well in.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's still kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I understand why they're doing it, but at the same time, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially, like, I'm surprised that they're not trying to make more headway in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, they have written off Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we've sucked it up for the Xbox 360 and we're definitely not going to try any harder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I shouldn't say that because they are supposed to be doing Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to build Buzz somehow over there and who knows what they're keeping in their hat to show at Tokyo Game Show that maybe would be something you never know what type of studio they pulled together or something to create a very Japanese RPG or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I guess they tried that on 360 and it didn't totally pan out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was high on Vicodin, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I always like Toriyama's art style.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude designed Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: AkumaJP says we don't care
[SPEAKER_06]: and, well, and you guys clearly have shown that through the Xbox 360, which, you know, fair is fair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, just quickly, these are the territories that will get Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: Australia, Austria, Brazil, Canada, France, Germany, Ireland, Italy, Mexico, Spain, United Kingdom, United States, New Zealand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad Germany's on there because that'd be really awkward to make an announcement at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, this console will be launching this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wait, no, not for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine, mine, mine, mine, mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going on to Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's assume it wasn't coming out in Germany for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might actually be okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And these countries that want one bad enough, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox One games are no longer going to be region locked.
Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox One games will not be region locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in an interview with Eurogamer, Xbox One, they said, when the console launches this November, we will support the Xbox One in 13 markets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox One may be used in all countries, including the non-launched markets.
[SPEAKER_06]: In addition, Xbox One games are not region locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any Xbox One game purchased at retail can be used in any country on any Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was part of their original 180 flip thing, that that was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, clarified that even with this change in the 13 lineups, if you live in one of the eight affected countries, you could get around it and still have a good experience with Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is good, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm glad that everybody's going region-free.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is the obvious answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's still region-locked?
[SPEAKER_06]: Only Nintendo at this point?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tsk, tsk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tis-tis.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the sad thing was they were sort of on region locked at one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they were going that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the 3DS, they're like, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the 3DS is because they couldn't really figure out their marketplace too well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so they didn't know how to, I guess, make the purchase and be region free or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so because of that, that might be why it's locked down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe because of piracy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, yeah, it's, I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was there more later?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought we had one more Xbox story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyway, despite everything you're saying about, you know, the Kinect and the controllers and, you know, the region locking and all that stuff, you know, Xbox is giving people what they wanted and it's kind of impressive.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought originally after E3 it wasn't going to happen this fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's not forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don Mattrick's not running things anymore either.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's definitely been a change in how things are being run.
[SPEAKER_06]: And whether that's coming at his former level or a higher level, who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I'm not sure how much more they're going to really be able to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially with the price and doing a skew without Connect to drop the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think that's going to happen because...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell, all the games they showed at E3 didn't use Kinect I mean, they may have supported it but they sure as hell didn't demonstrate Kinect The one thing I liked most about Kinect was the whole people calling each other to talk during TV shows
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know people that have an Android phone?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know those have Skype on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do, they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're free.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's something about having it right there on the TV, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: My mom.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I can check my Twitter feed and my Facebook and then no it's just it's not alright GameGuru in chat says it is rather admirable that Microsoft is actually reversing their horrible horrible idea though they never should have had it in the first place I'll tell you what though having you know tried streaming this week and stuff I am definitely looking forward to the console you know recording and streaming functionality of both consoles so I think that's pretty awesome it's just you know
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, just anything to make it easier would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's move on to another article.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, well, I don't know how people are going to feel.
[SPEAKER_15]: So for anyone who has been looking into Xenoblade Chronicles, of course, it's an exclusive at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, they are pretty much defending how much they're charging for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically, it's 90 bucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: And when they were contacted, they said that they use feedback from their Power Up members to see what titles they want to bring back.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, you know, talking about Xenoblade Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_15]: and that they basically were saying that the price is competitive.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's based on market value and people will pay it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then they say, but our Power Up Pro members always receive a 10% discount and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So they're basically like, we can charge it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I don't order for GameStop, but I'm just saying it's what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's funny is last week we were talking about something else related to this whole thing and I even said in joking, oh, the good news is all these copies of Xenoblade are going back to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not realize that it was under this fucking outrageous pricing scheme that they're giving to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can understand that there's an actual shortage on the game and stuff and that it's rare and that maybe the...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: All of the stores happen to have copies of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's very coincidental that all of a sudden all the stores have copies and they're used copies that happen to also still have unredeemed Nintendo Club codes in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's so convenient.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say something that I'm probably going to regret saying, but this is my honest to God reaction when I hear this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe this is just the, you know, I don't know, the Les Miserables revolution person in me or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But honest to God, Xenoblade is a great game and you should pirate it so you can play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is what I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should pirate Xenoblade so you can play this game because it's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's instructions on how to mod your Wii out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on a bunch of sites when the game was only out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo restricting its release to only GameStop and they no longer sell it on their shop.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Nintendo was selling it on their shop, I'd say, oh, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you should definitely support it by going to buy this game on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if this is what they're going to let happen, Nintendo is letting this happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should go pirate the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're gonna limit who can actually sell those games?
[SPEAKER_08]: You really think they're gonna come down in price like Steam?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's very funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby in our chatroom says, I rented it via Gamefly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great solution.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably a better one than I suggested, quite honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as much as you may think I'm terrible for what I said or whatever, I mean... I don't think you're terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reality is...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: They go print more copies of the game and they sell them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now what they've done is they're going back and reprinting it because you guys demanded it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to reprint it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I don't think the fans demanded that you charge $90 for it either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know what they ought to do is they ought to just release it on the Wii U download shop?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I would say, go ye forth and download this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great and you should play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be a great thing for them to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the same thing that people were fessing at people for going out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it's why Target and places like that were restricting the number of Wii's people could buy because they knew that they were a limited number and they were going to go on eBay and charge a bajillion for it, which would hurt their chances later on of actually selling the system for retail price.
[SPEAKER_06]: FifthDream in chat says, oh, it's a Wii game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who gives a fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because honestly, it's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_14]: I give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you are missing out on not playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think when I originally reviewed the game, I said it's the greatest PlayStation 2 Japanese RPG you'll play on a Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, before I say something else that's going to get me in trouble, let's go on to another news story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so Sony's got some news that they're going to be unveiling this week at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that news is rumored to be their release plans for the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: And those are going to be shared on August 20th during their conference.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're emphasizing that they're going to have a brief announcement regarding the release plans for the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: and also I guess Microsoft was to have some sort of announcement as well though they're saying that their conference is really short and emphasizing on developers in their games yeah I think it's basically really short because that news that they were supposed to be unveiling about the you know Xbox One systems being dev kits and stuff like that that already got leaked out so they don't have anything to talk about anymore so that's kind of unfortunate but
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm interested to see what both parties have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm also interested to see what release date they're going to give the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to come out this week, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably November.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything's November.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd be surprised if it's October.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of rumors pointing to October for some reason.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe trying to get a jump.
[SPEAKER_08]: Originally, I thought October because there were some placeholder dates that I had from a third party that were...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: There might be some more game announcements from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know everyone's expecting maybe like a Crackdown 3 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although Saints Row 4 is coming out the same day, so there's your Crackdown 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the Crackdown 3 would be slightly interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it was a launch style, that would be even more interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the free game on 360 now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Crackdown was the first half of the month, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dead Rising 2 and Dead Rising Case Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm going to have to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I put it in my queue.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been putting everything in my queue, except for that last Xbox Live Arcade game, because I don't give a shit about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I've been just putting it all in my queue, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, they're okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just at the same time it's not exactly like PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did put Hitman Absolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: The problem, and this goes back to the whole digital download thing, it's a 17 gig download for Hitman because it's PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's 17 gigs and my network timed out in the middle of the download because it was a few hours even though I have pretty fast internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, you have PlayStation Plus because you're downloading the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't you just trigger it to start downloading and then turn off your PlayStation and let it download overnight when it does the... Because any outstanding downloads will download overnight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I could.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just... It downloaded most.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it would resume it, but it's just, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, we kind of knew they were getting into some TV things from the earlier press conference, but now it's really starting to gel together what this might actually be, and it looks like it's going to be some type of paid TV service.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have thought it would have been an enhancement to PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it still is.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's free TV and PlayStation Plus, fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You would think that they would sweeten the pot with that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's according to a report in the Wall Street Journal because Sony made a big deal with Viacom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Viacom is a huge media company.
[SPEAKER_06]: They own CBS, don't they?
[SPEAKER_06]: And Paramount and all these companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: To carry Viacom cable channels on an internet-based service for Sony products.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you will be able to get Viacom cable channels, which is MTV and that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: MTV Comedy Central, VH1, I don't remember what else they have.
[SPEAKER_06]: So assumably, you will be able to get these channels through your PlayStation 3 and essentially bypass your cable box.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see how the cable companies are going to let that fly.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Viacom, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Viacom, they're higher up than the cable companies, so I can see how they can let that fly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've seen throughout this whole mess of Time Warner and CBS that cable companies will block whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of surprised that they're going to be able to get away with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They can block it on their own.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as negotiating with other companies, they can block it on their own service, but they can't really block it off the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's so many people that are ditching cable TV in favor of Netflix and Hulu.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll just start raising internet prices.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's costing us a lot more to expand.
[SPEAKER_06]: We gotta put these bandwidth caps on because bandwidth is super expensive.
[SPEAKER_15]: But also keep in mind, how many people do you know who have ditched their landline for their cell phone?
[SPEAKER_06]: True.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's more the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: True, and AT&T is still kicking, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're still putting out that blazing fast DSL.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony also, to do on-demand programming and cable channels online, there'll be a recommended programming feature that will be influenced by content providers and an algorithm of what you've been watching.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: June 26th, it should be noted, my birthday, Sony renewed a trademark for PlayStation TV, likely to be the final name of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: We might see more on this at Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though they just inked this deal the other day, Apple is notorious for inking deals the night before they make an announcement.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you could see something, but it may be a rabbit in their hat.
[SPEAKER_06]: They keep till later when we have more of what that's really going to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am really curious to see how Comcast, Time Warner reacts to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru in chat says Viacom doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're the guys who own CBS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Viacom is probably really excited about this because fuck Time Warner at this point if they can get CBS on PlayStation boxes I mean this is a dream for them if Sony's giving them what they want I mean this is this is a huge piece in their favor as far as Viacom is concerned you're just bypassing the whole you know because now you can get your you know you bypass everything
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, an interesting point, and I've seen this on Twitters and so forth, so this is worth discussing.
[SPEAKER_06]: BlackWolf says, TV, TV, TV, TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft talks TV equals Microsoft doesn't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: How lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony talks TV equals this is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well, there's a little difference between having an IPTV service that you have going through your game console and...
[SPEAKER_08]: Plugging in a video in through your goddamn console just be to, you know, you can watch TV on the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can watch TV on your TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, they're saying, hey, look, we have this wonderful feature that's been featured on almost all devices since a VCR where you have a video in and then you can watch TV on your device.
[SPEAKER_08]: All they're doing, what functionality are they really adding to Xbox?
[SPEAKER_08]: I basically still need a cable box.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just my cable box is now running through my Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it was like, hey, here's this brand new TV service that Microsoft's putting out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can access it through the Xbox 360 or the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't need a cable box.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: That and their unveil of the console.
[SPEAKER_08]: They focus strictly on a lot of the entertainment things, which people are like, come on, I want to know about games because this is a gaming console type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, too, it's not that I necessarily dislike what Microsoft is doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, to be fair, it's not like this news made me drop down the money to get a PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had made that decision long before it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when I hear about this enhanced value, of course I get excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it is all rumor.
[SPEAKER_06]: It may pan out to be nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if it costs too much, I won't do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if Sony talks all about TV during their Gamescom announcement and stuff, that might be a little boring.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yeah, I'd still rag on them about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, okay, that's cool that you have this TV service coming, but I kind of want to know about your games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, unless they announce the Tester Season 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, will you go on Tester Season 4?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I remember we tried to get her to go on Season 3.
[SPEAKER_15]: They wouldn't want me anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm too bitchy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they would absolutely want you for being bitchy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would lay the smackdown on everybody and go, you know what, I remember when the only access we had to Sony in video games was when they made the Super Nintendo sound processor.
[SPEAKER_06]: And some limited games.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, well, you know how PlayStation started, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was supposed to be the whole CD expansion for Super Nintendo, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, one more story before release dates.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was putting out my friend code.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm putting myself out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, some people may or may not be happy about this, but the games for Windows Live Marketplace is closing on August 22nd, which is pretty much next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: so anyway they put out an FAQ on Xbox.com so that for people who have purchased games on Windows Live and their DLC they'll still be able to play them but they won't be able to purchase additional content and basically they're afraid that there's people who are afraid that they're going to be pulling the games out of Steam as well
[SPEAKER_15]: But as far as that, I don't really see anything about that.
[SPEAKER_15]: They said that the games that are on Steam are still going to be on Steam.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just that the Microsoft points are going bye-bye, you know, which we already knew.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's just because they're putting everything on their Windows Marketplace now and no point in having two different marketplaces.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're putting everything out on their inconvenience marketplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, you know, the Games for Windows marketplace, my only marketplace I buy games, said no one ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Said no one, exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just, for the people who have bought things through there, they're really inconveniencing their consumers, but... There was a free game you got when you signed up for Games for Windows Live that had achievements in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember that's why I got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tinker or something like that was the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just know that they have achievements in like Solitaire now.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I mean, it's kind of a big thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, yeah, they're definitely working on getting all their stuff ready for the X-Bone.
[SPEAKER_15]: But in the end...
[SPEAKER_15]: Nobody could see me shrug, but that's all I can say is shrug.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I shed another tear for my Microsoft Game Room, which was a part of Games for Windows Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you have that, my assumption is that you won't be able to buy the packs anymore because that was all integrated through Games for Windows Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, shit, that game's pretty much long gone if you don't have what you wanted out of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't gotten a single thing on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had like 15 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think I was so mad when they pulled the plug on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Too soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and out with the old, in with the new, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, this week is actually quite a bit of stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of a little bit of a kickoff for the fourth quarter, which is creeping up earlier every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this week, Saints Row 4 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell Blacklist on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii U, and PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: We also have The Walking Dead, a complete first season on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it has an additional DLC in there as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: New Super Luigi U for the Wii U, and that's the physical disc version of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, the Bureau XCOM Declassified on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this isn't a game, but I still think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The GameStick, the second Android console, is finally making its way out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they're going to have that and the dock as well available for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's $79.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, undercutting the OUYA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we'll see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving to Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PlayStation 3 this week in Japan, Disorder 6 in regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dungeons & Dragons Mysteria is out this week as well, which we've talked about before on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: The disc release, even though there's the download release too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Medal of Honor Warfighter gets a price reduction as it moves into the best hits.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also out this week, Super Robot Taisen OG Saga Masoukishin 3 Pride of Justice comes out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: on the Xbox 360, because yes, there are still a few things here and there on the 360 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disorder 6 in its regular and limited edition, and Medal of Honor Warfighter gets that same price reduction on the 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving to the handhelds, on the PlayStation Vita this week, Super Robot Taisen OG Saga, that same game I mentioned before, is out on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Conception 2, Shichise no Michibiki to Mazuru no Akumu comes out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know what this is about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Conception 2... Did you say 7 World something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying to see what kind of game it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks like it might be like a tactical RPG-ish type of thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've seen that design somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, very... Let me look at the name again?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the box art if you want to see it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, yeah, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's 7 something.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: 7th World something and I don't know
[SPEAKER_15]: Ikuma, translate for us, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ikuma-san is our hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Wii U this week, yes, the Wii U sees a release in the Wonderful 101, which is out in Japan on August the 24th, which I believe is the same day it's out here, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And lastly, on the 3DS, that Saiyan Conception 2 game, as well as Nanami to Ishii ni Gabuko English Jotsatsu no Kutsu comes out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I think that's an English teacher.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, let's learn English with cute anime girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, learn with Nanami.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hold on, go back to the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Nanami is missing her belly button on her... No, she has her belly button, we can see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: On her shirt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's like a study with Nanami.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Nanami also is showing a little cleavage.
[SPEAKER_15]: He said you need to link that other game to chat so that Ikuma-san can translate for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I will work on that while you travel to the UK.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_15]: On the 20th, Disney Infinity for Damn Near Everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: On the 22nd, we have Skullgirls for PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Splinter Cell Blacklist for Wii U. On the 23rd, Saints Row 4, XCOM, XCOM, XCOM, no, The Wonderful 101, which would be my reason for getting a Wii U, and Splinter Cell Blacklist.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, if you get The Wonderful 101, I'm just going to move into your living room.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a demo available on Wii U. I've downloaded it, but I've not played it yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe after, well, I gotta go get Alan, so maybe during the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You better do it for him out of town.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alan can walk.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hard, hard, hard, hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: If he's listening, he's going to cut you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alan, I was joking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't cut me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just a couple more stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I was listening to a Nero song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is more important than this show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nero song?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I did watch the Call of Duty multiplayer preview thing that they did.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did some new stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for example, they have now more character creation in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can actually...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's kind of cross-platform as it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the DLC thing is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically if you buy a season pass or whatever on Xbox 360, you'll be able to take it to Xbox One, same with PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: and that's not just limited to Call of Duty as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's also something that Battlefield 4 will have as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can do a one-time transfer between the Xbox 360 and Xbox One and PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 4 for your stats, unlocks, ranks, award assignments and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of lame though that it's a one-time deal for Battlefield 4 because what if I have an Xbox 360 at my work and an Xbox One at home and I want to
[SPEAKER_08]: Play them both.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why limit that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why, but that's something that they're supporting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if it gets to Xbox One saying they're supporting the season pass guarantee, that this is going to apply for a lot of different things, including, well, they had mentioned Call of Duty Ghosts and Battlefield 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm wondering if it's other games as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to have some sort of tie in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think a lot of people will be using this or do you think people will just kind of already be upgrading or not?
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as I go, oh yeah, this is a neat idea, I kind of think to myself, well God, you have to buy the games twice?
[SPEAKER_08]: How many people are really going to do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: There might be some people that will do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what's going to basically be is if, you know, say I want to buy Call of Duty this year and I'm not buying a next-gen system and then next year I want to, okay, we'll say mid-next year I want to buy a PlayStation 4 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I buy it on PlayStation 3, I can buy the Season Pass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buy the Season Pass and then, you know, I buy my new system and I know how to buy the Season Pass again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand why it's such a big deal in the first place because they do a lot of cross-buy stuff already on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think this would be more news for Microsoft because they don't really do any of that cross-buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It...
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it's a cool feature, but it's something that I think should be kind of expected instead of having to buy the content more than once.
[SPEAKER_08]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I guess that's cool if they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we live in a day and age where they didn't have to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's one of those things now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was just going to check here real quick to see if we have that story later on about...
[SPEAKER_08]: uh yeah i guess we do later on but uh you know a lot of this nowadays they're talking about features that they necessarily they they're already there but you may not be completely familiar with them or you may have forgotten that they have them there and now they're new you know it's like you know this whole uh what was it with the xbox um
[SPEAKER_08]: There was just something recently.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's something coming up in Part B. Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was the game sharing thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember we talked about it last week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you ranted about that last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that's not a new thing, but it's something that a lot of people don't really think about, or maybe they can spin it in a way that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might be better on Xbox One, to be fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is with the whole live sharing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of cool, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase BAR.
[SPEAKER_06]: This would be awesome if it's actually happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's a thing going on in Japan this week called the Pokemon Game Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And during this event, Nintendo actually teased...
[SPEAKER_06]: Potentially, don't get your hopes up, but a Pokemon title for the Wii U in 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which would be weird because there's never been a straight up Pokemon main franchise game on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've always been the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now there's been tons of spin-off stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like the Rumble stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, Pinball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no, I guess Pinball was on the handhelds too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Pokemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there was the GameCube Coliseum.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also have the weird spin-off games, the Poke Park games that have been on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what happened in this video is that it was playing on the main screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had a CG Pikachu leading Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander in a Game Boy World.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the end of the trailer, there was a 3D Wii U Pokemon title that showed Lusario going face-to-face with Blaziken in a futuristic city.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I did think to myself, I was like, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: If Nintendo wanted to turn the Wii U around real quick, real quick, here's a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's going to be another Coliseum title or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to be anything like a mainstream Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know, and I said before, with the whole Skylanders and Disney Infinity stuff, I'm like, it's really only, and I know that Nintendo is doing it in some capacity, but if that's successful or whatever, it could just get even bigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I know with the download thing where you can only get the figures at GameStop or whatever, it does feel in some way like getting the foot in the water.
[SPEAKER_08]: Figures are going to be $90 now, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're scarce.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can't download the figure on the internet, so I don't know what to tell you if you get screwed on those.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically, that's not entirely true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because there are apps, and they have this with Skylanders already, there are apps where people have recorded the RFID, the near-field communication stuff, and you can actually simulate that with your phone.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just put your phone on the communication thing and you can play as that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, I...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think my phone supports that but that'd be kind of interesting to check out with Disney Infinity.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be a way to get around buying figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a strange form of piracy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what you're going to call that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to travel back to a time when there wasn't these fucking figures you had to buy to get the whole experience of the game.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all about patches.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there was no patches back then either.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the game was fucked, it was fucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Games back then went through a process called testing, which I think is sometimes skipped now.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a seal of approval, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_06]: As is the case of Disney Infinity on PlayStation 3, if Twitter is any indication.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, DarkSakura, why don't you step into the gaming vault and take us back to a time when games didn't have all this shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, I did just beat Find Me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, congrats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did I slay the final boss?
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, a wandering hero did.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you almost did it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was one hit point off.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Story of my life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody comes in and snatches all my glory.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said snatch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Story of my life.
[SPEAKER_15]: The game is Guilty Gear X.
[SPEAKER_15]: Guilty Gear X
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's supposed to take place a few weeks after the first game.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's a new Commander gear.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically, it takes everything that was good about the, uh... About the, uh...
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: So, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_15]: So yeah, the Dreamcast 1 had a limited release.
[SPEAKER_15]: It came with a special mini-CD that had different artworks that you could view on the PC.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was a Type A, Type B, and Type C. And it had different images printed on the GD-ROM disc instead.
[SPEAKER_15]: As far as the characters in it, it has a bunch of people from the first game.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had Soul Bad Guy, which is funny because Soul Bad Guy was actually voiced by the creator of the series.
[SPEAKER_15]: and had Mei, Baiken, Kaikisuke, Potemkin, Chip Xanath, Meliorage, Zatoan, Axel Lowe, and Testament.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had new characters like Jim, Kurado Berry, Johnny, Anji, Mito, Venom, Dizzy, and Roboki.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it was a really fun fighting game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually have the Guilty Gear Petite on Wonderswan, by the way, which was also super fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I've enjoyed every game in the series.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'd have to say that I didn't really enjoy the series until this one came out.
[SPEAKER_15]: As far as other versions came out, there was X+, that was an enhanced version that had two extra characters.
[SPEAKER_15]: It came out on the PS2 in Japan only.
[SPEAKER_15]: And...
[SPEAKER_15]: That was on November 29th.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there was basically just a bare-bones port of the Dreamcast 1 that didn't have any of the extra stuff from the Japanese version that came out in the US and Europe.
[SPEAKER_15]: The two new characters were Cliff Anderson and Justice.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had different game modes.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had all kinds of different moves.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really neat.
[SPEAKER_15]: And more in the story mode and password mode.
[SPEAKER_15]: The advanced version came out on GBA and it was basically the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it had all of the characters except for RoboKey.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it was just different stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was version 1.5 as well that had some of the stuff from Guilty Gear XX.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was Petite, which is the one I mentioned earlier, the Wonderswan Color version, which was...
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it was actually super cutesy, guilty gear.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I can say, and I've beaten that several times.
[SPEAKER_15]: Petite 2 came out, and it also had all the arcade characters, except for Bike and Dizzy and Robokai.
[SPEAKER_15]: It had Fanny coming back.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to laugh every time I say that, because that's also slang for girl bits.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really cute.
[SPEAKER_15]: The one I owned, though, was Petite, and then there was Club and Raid of Arms, but honestly, the Dreamcast one, awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now the story about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Back in the day when we used to rip our Dreamcast games, we actually found out the hard way.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the game that my friend Julie learned to...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I forgot her.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone's forgotten her.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's a figment of my imagination.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: She may as well be.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't heard from her in ages.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, Julie was trying to figure out how to rip Dreamcast games, and this was the game she tried on.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we had many, many copies of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_15]: Many copies of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_15]: And learned quite a bit about the data that went to GBROM.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or I should say GDROM, the GigaDisc.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, great soundtrack, great game, great characters, lots of cosplay fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I, you know, still have my Baiken costume, except for the claw, which belonged to Evan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cosplay memories.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: and oh my god I had the worst cramp and I ended up just having to think of another way to tuck it into the sleeve because it was a pain to cosplay but it was fun costume all right there it is your classic game of the week Guilty Gear X all right it doesn't it doesn't feel like the game is that old but I guess it's over 10 years old well in the first Guilty Gear you know was PlayStation
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's going to do it for this half of Orange Lounge Radio, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got plenty more show coming up, including some rapid-fire news, the Fugle Question of the Week, emails, and your phone calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we come back with all more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live on this Sunday evening, August the 18th, 2013, with the 516th episode of our program.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, as always, you can join us.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you are listening live, you can join us in our chat room, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're listening on the podcast feed, be it through an iTunes download or through Stitcher or whatever, well, we appreciate you guys listening along as well, especially...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's a long show, so I know some of you dedicate a lot of time to listen throughout the week, so we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope we're helping you get through your work day or your commute, wherever you choose to listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, I have a request.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: When we're officially into Final Fantasy land, you need to make a version of Sassy Pants.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought about naming my character that, but... Lil' Poundcake is cute, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, I named my character in Final Fantasy XIV Lil' Poundcake, and she's a little... I still want to say Taru-Tarus, because that's the word in Final Fantasy XI, but I guess they're... Lalafel, or Falafel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I call them Falafels.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's a little falafel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah, Lil' Poundcake.
[SPEAKER_06]: And somebody actually asked me in the show... Oh, no, it was you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was me, because I was asking everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you're like, where did the inspiration for your name come from?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there are, like, a diverse amount of... My favorite was Sprinkles Galore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Seymour Guylove.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a character I saw called FapFap.
[SPEAKER_15]: I saw FapFap.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Captain Obvious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet you did, you dirty hoe.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I saw Captain Obvious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I also saw, what was the other one?
[SPEAKER_15]: I saw Ianto Jones.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I said, okay, Torchwood?
[SPEAKER_15]: And they're like, yeah, big Torchwood fans.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you were like, what's the inspiration for your name?
[SPEAKER_06]: And some are named after philosophers or an anime or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, my name comes from RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was actually super surprised that I got the names I got, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, when there's first name and last name, it's much easier to get the names.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but I was going for specific Homestuck characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, I was like, why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I was making a cat girl and wanted to name her after one of the cat trolls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was being asked in chat during the break at live.vognetwork.com by Sailor Venus, who's in our chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sessy's the best
[SPEAKER_06]: I have ADD character at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used to raid with my monk, so I guess that's my main.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it Gordita?
[SPEAKER_06]: She would be the best geared.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Kalmain.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kalmain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was my monk.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I had my priest before that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had Chakwas, my priest, who I raided with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have Sassy on Alliance, who I did get to 90, and I did some five-mans with, and I've geared her that way, but I haven't really done any raids.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've got your Rissa close to being raid ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, the character I was playing the most two months ago was Chocolina, my hunter, who's PvP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had my PvP phase.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's hard to PvP on a hunter, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that was the fun of it!
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: PvP is the whole reason why I never finish Children's Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can be... Stupid PvP bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, if you're going to do PvP, just turn off chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll make your life easier.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, we could talk MMOs all night, and I do on Wednesday nights on a show called Horde House, 7 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pluggedy, pluggedy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And for the record, I didn't get Nepeta.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got Mulan.
[SPEAKER_06]: What unique context.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember how I talked about the podcast and Stitcher listeners earlier?
[SPEAKER_15]: Queen Simia in chat asked if I got Nepeta Lajon, which I didn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got Mulan, which is the one I wanted.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: But Nepeta's cute, but I wanted Mulan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go into rapid fire news tonight and some other gaming news we're going to go over quickly.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's talk a little bit about discounts.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Vita is actually dropping in price, apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it's not apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: During Gamescom, I guess, they're probably going to make this announcement as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I guess the launch versions of the system, the 3G Vita launch bundle and also the Wi-Fi version are dropping down to $200.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: and also at the same time they're going to be dropping the price of the greatest hits games I guess for $15 a piece and that's for PlayStation 3 the other thing too which I don't think is on here and hasn't been announced yet that also includes new bundles that happen to be coming out the new starter bundles which you know there is one that happens to be coming out on Tuesday for The Walking Dead just saying so you can get those for $200 now
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, for $200, and this is allegedly a rumor, but it's not, there is a 12GB PlayStation 3 coming to North America.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I know what you're thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: 12GB?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awfully small.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's flash storage that they have on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you will be able to add a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: to it as well so it's a good place if you want to if you're planning on adding your own hard drive anyways might as well not spend any more money than you have to and 12 gigabytes would be enough to install Grand Theft Auto 5 I'm just saying which is apparently all a person needs right that's really all a person needs yeah you know what you just need to talk to Dan because he's all kinds of happy about that game
[SPEAKER_08]: is going to encompass a lot of my time.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, Fantasia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming soon to VOG, the Grand Theft Auto 5 show, because it's all Loki's ever going to be able to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: They already have a Grand Theft Auto 5 show.
[SPEAKER_06]: My God, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: GTA 5 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That should surprise me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a UK show, and it's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: But hey, you know, since I will be spending most of my time online, I could probably guess Sun Hoard House.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sure could!
[SPEAKER_06]: Horde House was a Warcraft-only show, but now it isn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all online games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, you could guest on Horde House to talk Grand Theft Auto V online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Lord knows none of us will be playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you're really doing yourself a disservice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm super curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: it's not all about murdering people you can play golf and do yoga oh yay yoga oh man hey yoga is my favorite thing in Final Fantasy 14 I don't know about you and that golfing and warcraft that's the reason to plunk down the money right there you know what
[SPEAKER_08]: Fantasia Music Evolved, a new game coming from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also have some more original pieces coming to the game, including some works from Inan Zur.
[SPEAKER_08]: He did some music in Fallout 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: and he's going to be doing some original versions of different takes on Vivaldi, Four Seasons, Night on the Bald Mountain, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I guess he's arranged the orchestral mix of Queen's Bohemian Rhapsody in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, that's coming out sometime in 2014 on both Xbox platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is a little strange, but they have, I guess it's going to be one of those announcements at Gamescom, but PlayStation Vita Pets coming to the Vita.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like Nintendogs, if the dogs talked.
[SPEAKER_08]: They talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's that killer app that's going to sell a million betas.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird that they're talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want you to talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they talk like that generic after school TV kids Disney show or something like that that's really annoying and grinding on your brain.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would really only be awesome if you could take your Playstation pets and import them into Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: See?
[SPEAKER_06]: You and I need to start a game studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tokyo Jungle.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura could come visit once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starts off like Nintendogs and then it gets really dark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now that I like.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Battle Royale for dogs and cats.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but then you talk pet cruelty and I'm like, no, we can't have that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, come on, you're the one who named your horse Politary and beat her.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Derby Owners Club
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it's over the top, then that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, I look at a game like, remember Bungie Ferret Tossing?
[SPEAKER_06]: That game's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: That one's over the top.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's another game, and once again, the name is escaping me, that has, like, dogs with tank cannons on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't remember what it's called, but it's something that... It's got a few games in the series, and it was on PlayStation 2 and stuff, but they had... It's, like, literally, they have, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thunderbluff was it was it there or was it somewhere closer to human lands where there were the metal saga by the way where there were the hamsters and the rabbits that would suddenly you know have knives oh yeah yeah yeah I just hung out there for hours just watching them because I was bored but anyway but like you follow one of them around and you can actually watch them transform but like there was the rabbit with combat knife and the hamster with the Uzi and
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, y'all and your animal fighting issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, see, this is what I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, that's from Metal Saga right there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I have to play this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta move on.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want a Shiba Inu with a bazooka.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Call of Duty Ghost scenes right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dogs with giant bazookas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I don't know how many of you guys have checked this out, but there's the Humble Origin bundle, which is available from the, yeah, the Humble bundle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead Space 3 and Medal of Honor
[SPEAKER_06]: I do want to play Dead Space 3
[SPEAKER_06]: I've already got a bunch of those other games I took my pills
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I, on the other hand, I only... I paid the full amount, because I like Battlefield 3, but I just haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the idea of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just... I'm not installing Origin, though, but I... Mainly I paid more than the average, because they always add in extra games towards the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm curious to see what those are.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I wanted Mirror's Edge and Burnout.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burnout Paradise, dude!
[SPEAKER_08]: That is the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least a dollar you can pay for one of the best racing games this generation.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, the charities are great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you have human rights campaigns.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can just have all of your money go to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: American Cancer Society, San Francisco AIDS Foundation, American Red Cross, WOTC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's for charity.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, hate on Origin all you want, but it's pretty hard to get mad at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although,
[SPEAKER_14]: I've already got those three of those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'm just being the Grinch, but you have to wonder.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to wonder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they just trying to get Origin put on more computers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, because then they're going to say, look how many people have Origin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Origin's a successful service.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look how many people have Origin.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate going there because at the end of the day, this is a great thing, but it's just that you can't help but wonder.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know people are talking about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm super close to patching my Mass Effect 3 so I don't have to go through Origin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I almost bought the Deep Silver bundle, but the problem is I bought the THQ bundle and that had a lot of the games that were in the Deep Silver bundle.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so I was like, eh, I just can't see myself buying yet another copy of Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brad from PodCulture says, with these bundles, I always put all my fundage towards the charities.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you can decide how your money is split.
[SPEAKER_06]: The cool thing about this one is that since EA is not getting any of the money, usually the indie developers, you can give them a chunk of the pot and by default they get some.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this time, it's all charities and what they call the humble bundle tip.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarCraft MMO
[SPEAKER_06]: StarCraft Universe which was originally World of StarCraft it will allow players to create a character and log in to an alternate history StarCraft the Zerg and Protoss hybrids are around I guess Blizzard does bless this project now so StarCraft Universe they can make this in the StarCraft 2 engine it just can't be called World of StarCraft that was the deal I remember they changed something
[SPEAKER_06]: So they won $80,000 that they're getting on Kickstarter, and here's why.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is for the creator Ryan Winsen and the people he's working with to get additional pylons and focus solely on creating the game and getting it out there in 2014 for an open beta, which I'm assuming means I want to be able to quit my job and do this full-time and actually get it out in a timely manner.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm reading.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds about right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are stretch goals and other rewards Zerg character class if they make $100,000 And so on and so on Let me see where they're at right now Just kind of curious for an update here on this Sunday evening They've got 22 days to go and they've almost made half their money They're at $36,000 So not bad They're ahead of the curve a little bit if they can keep that going Although I think most Kickstarters you want the earlier the better So good luck
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised Blizzard's kind of letting them do that because aren't they raising money based off of StarCraft IP in a way?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure they've got some kind of deal worked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess at the end of the day, it's all promo for StarCraft too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, speaking of Blizzard, another beta that launched this weekend that has a lot of people's attention is Hearthstone.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Hearthstone closed beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Blizzard's free-to-play little card game that they've got.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I do think it's very interesting timing on Blizzard's part, and I don't think it's any coincidence at all that the Hearthstone beta started out of nowhere this weekend, when a lot of World of Warcraft and hardcore Blizzard fans I think were a little bored waiting for patch 5.4, and eh, let me go...
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me go try this other open beta that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go try this Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Blizzard releases this to their most vocal people and the people that are some heavy influences to the community and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And suddenly, none of them care about Final Fantasy XIV anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all playing this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a smart move on Blizzard's part, but I will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'll expand a little bit on this on Horde House, but I can't help myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to say something now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because of this, I've seen some people shading Final Fantasy XIV a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm just going to say, don't shade a game you haven't played.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's ignorant.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of these is a free-to-play trading card game that's going to be on tablets.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other one of these is a very intricate MMO that's going to be on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not alike in any way, shape, or form.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: NPC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you so threatened by, y'all?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's so threatening?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because people like to be right.
[SPEAKER_15]: And people like their thing to be better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and that's kind of like blind fandom, and it's a little bit ridiculous, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to give you all a piece of advice.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can like item A and also like item B. I can like Lady Gaga and Katy Perry?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can like Supernatural and Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: I can like the current Doctor Who and the classic Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: I can play Dragon Age 2 and the Mass Effect series.
[SPEAKER_15]: PlayStation and Xbox?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you have to... Loki, that's just cross... You have to buy one or the other.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have both and a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: My God, people.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cats and Dogs, Living Together, Mass Hysteria.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love that line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I look forward to playing this beta at some point whenever I get my little access.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, I do have to make a little tangent.
[SPEAKER_15]: I forgot to mention I was playing Dragon Age 2 because I actually stopped Final Fantasy XIV to play Dragon Age 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I totally missed one part where I could start the romance with Fenris, so I totally cheated.
[SPEAKER_15]: and did the debug mode so I could just change all the romance options.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Becky's husband said, so you gave him roofies?
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, okay, that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, DarkSakura, you have some rapid fire news for us.
[SPEAKER_15]: I do, and one of them is about Shin Megami Tensei, if I can actually get to Safari.
[SPEAKER_15]: There is a UK release date.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is going to be, that's actually Shin Megami Tensei, Devil Summoner, Soul Hackers.
[SPEAKER_15]: The European release date is going to be on September, moved from September 13th to September 20th.
[SPEAKER_15]: and it's going to be available digitally on the 3DS eShop on the following week on the 25th of September.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that is the official release date for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry guys in the UK.
[SPEAKER_15]: We also have a date for Castle of Illusion Remaster in the UK.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's going to be September 4th and it will be 10.
[SPEAKER_15]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: Castlevania, Mirror of Fate HD
[SPEAKER_15]: it has a list date that's on PlayAsia and it says it's going to be for PS3 and Xbox 360 and saying that the collection will have the first Lords of Shadow, all the DLC and an exclusive demo of Lords of Shadow 2 and will be out in October yeah it's going to be part of the Lords of Shadow collection since Lords of Shadow 2 got delayed to next year
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, Brazil's games rating board had, for December 2012, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: In December 2012, Mirror of Fate was on the Brazil rating board.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they're also saying that there's going to be a PC and Wii U one, but there's nothing listed on PlayAsia.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's sad that actually that's like almost the only game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Konami has hardly any games coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pro Evo and this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then next year... Metal Gear Solid 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: Phantom Pain, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Metal Gear Solid 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, shit, they're releasing stuff less often than Capcom is nowadays.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't they have a lot of kiddie stuff though?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're all mobile now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't have a lot of kiddie licenses anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: No DDR anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not even Karaoke Revolution anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week we ask our Facebook and our Google Plus communities a question.
[SPEAKER_06]: You take those two words, you slam them together, you get... Google!
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the question.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's rumors out there that Sony is making some moves to launch an online TV service on the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Certainly similar TV integrative features are a part of the Xbox One as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: How important is the integration of television into your video game console?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this sort of service something you are interested in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think Sony and Microsoft should focus less on these online TV networks and more on the games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Redertainment on Google Plus says,
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft says, E3VL says, E3VL says,
[SPEAKER_06]: Joe C says I live in the UK so it's probably of no consequence to me as these services are non-existent severely limited over here I don't like too many services competing with each other though I don't want to subscribe to them all so I always feel as though I'm missing out that's a good point like sometimes you have to feel like you have to do Hulu and Netflix and you know everybody wants a little piece of that
[SPEAKER_06]: and Techie Q says, bring it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a small but big step into breaking the traditional TV cable model.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are the answers on Google+.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of them, I had to shorten them all because I want to try to get in a lot of people tonight and we still have a lot more answers here over on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to try to shorten some of these.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm sorry if I don't read your full answer, but I'm going to encourage everybody to go over to facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and our Google Plus page, Orange Lounge Radio and read the full answers themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: CriticalMyth says it's not that important to me given that I have several other options currently that I'm very comfortable with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Renee, our friend from Koopa Club says you know it's not really that important to me to have my television services integrated into my video game console.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand the concept of wanting to encapsulate everything into one unit or box if you will to just have one place to go for all your entertainment needs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lauren Z says, what if we had a gaming console that actually focused on gaming?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know, it's an odd concept, but just think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could work, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ragenator says, if this was a year or two ago, I would have said it is very important, but nowadays I'd probably say that it's not at all important.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shane says, they already do that stuff for me as they all play Hulu and Netflix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cable TV is for chumps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Patty E says, I get a gaming system for games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I enjoy the fact that I can stream video from something like Netflix or Hulu or directly from my computer, but that does not at all contribute to why I want the system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marcello L says, all these TV features are nice, but really, I buy a PlayStation 4 or Xbox One for games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if the games had a feature that tied to the channel you're watching or show, that would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still not buying an Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh Daniel S says I don't watch TV so this won't really affect me I mean the wife will use it so whatever I just find it funny because if this is true Sony will get compliments for adding on to their system but when Microsoft makes changes to be more like Sony they get slammed the console war is a fun show so kind of bringing up a point that was brought up by a chatter earlier uh Mason D says I think they need to spend more time making use of the peripherals that they put out think of if Yu-Gi-Oh with the PlayStation Eye that's Mason says you know Sony stop putting out all this shit and then not supporting it
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the Fallen Dreams answers and says,
[SPEAKER_06]: That's definitely an audience I'm sure these TV things are going for, is people that are using their PlayStation 3 as their Blu-ray device.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, I'm sure there's a lot of people like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says...
[SPEAKER_06]: Gally89 says it makes no difference to me as I don't have cable I would be interested in an a la carte service though Geeklet says it's always handy but I don't think it's really a decision maker I'm fine with a console just playing games and lastly Mike B says the future is no TV as we know it only on demand and pay for what you want to watch without commercials
[SPEAKER_06]: you know what those quickly those are some abbreviated comments from Facebook and Google Plus check out the full answers on those respective pages yes Jamie
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just saying, a lot of people are repeating pretty much what's already going on in a lot of homes.
[SPEAKER_15]: It definitely goes on in mine.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have a computer hooked up to our TV.
[SPEAKER_15]: So anything that we want to watch, it's either stuff we've downloaded.
[SPEAKER_15]: We use Hulu Plus and we have Netflix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything that we want to watch, it's all there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Becky got rid of her cable so that she could use Amazon Prime.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's really been happy with Amazon Prime.
[SPEAKER_15]: She gets shows for Julia in that way.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm just saying, it's really...
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, you know, as much as, you know, Mike B kind of took us out there with the whole there's only going to be on demand, you know, my mind kind of goes there, but I actually don't think that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, yes, I think a lot of TV as we know it today will go that way and a lot of the expanded cable channels and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But keep in mind, there's one thing that on demand can't do, and that's live.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, things like American Idol, which whether you watch it or not, it's still a very highly rated show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And all those talent shows, you know, The Voice and things, those are still live shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think in a way, broadcast TV may experience a bit of a renaissance where it goes back to, in the beginning of television, it was all live stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: LiveStream Radio
[SPEAKER_15]: I caught all kinds of new music just by listening to Radio 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: VOG Network is the only radio you need.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about all the crap that went down in Texas?
[SPEAKER_15]: We had live streaming going on from the assembly room.
[SPEAKER_15]: We had the freaking internet catch the Texas Assembly breaking the law.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Live.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I watched the whole... I was like, where's my popcorn?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just watching this.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, I mean, news in and of itself, you've got your people who are still going to listen to your biased sources, you know, like your Fox News or your CNN or all of that, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you also have a great deal more people who are looking outside of those sources who are probably getting pretty fed up with having their world events spoon-fed to them and want to actually see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're looking to those other sources.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another good catch from our chat room, something that you couldn't get on demand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com says, Sports need to be live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Football and baseball will keep traditional TV around forever.
[SPEAKER_15]: ESPN is going to go to a subscription service.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they kind of have subscription services like the NFL Direct and all that and the NHL.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's probably what they're going to go towards.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: You want your ESPN?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you have the ESPN streaming service where you pay X amount and you get all the sports you want.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can get so many sports as you start sprouting the colors of your favorite team out of your skin or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: You turn into a buccaneer.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we're going to move on from our fugal question of the week, but good answers, you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's get back into the news, and I know Loki's been dying to talk about this next story all night long.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, I was.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yes, Grand Theft Auto V finally had their big unveil of their online portion of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually going to be called Grand Theft Auto Online, and it's all sorts of awesome stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's interesting though is it's actually kind of its own separate thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It launches October 1st if you buy a copy of Grand Theft Auto V and thankfully they're doing that because it gives me two weeks to play the game before I have to worry about trying to
[SPEAKER_08]: Hogg online but you get to create your own character you earn money in the game and you can customize your character you can buy property in the game you can insure your cars you can buy cars it's so deep as far as the you know the detail in the game they have it where you can play the stock market for example you can invest money in a car company and you go and destroy those cars out in the street and then they have to make more cars and therefore your stock goes up you know kind of stuff like that
[SPEAKER_08]: Deathmatch GTA 5 O'Clock
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically saying, well, first off, it's GTA Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not actually part of Grand Theft Auto V, although it's going to start off with San Andreas, but it will expand beyond that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they're planning on adding more area other than Los Santos and San Andreas to play in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also saying that, you know, there's...
[SPEAKER_08]: Voice chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can actually talk in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your character will move its mouth matching your dialogue.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will lip sync.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the AI characters in the game will react to the urgency in your voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: So like you said...
[SPEAKER_08]: Get on the fucking floor!
[SPEAKER_08]: They will get on the fucking floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that type of shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But if you go get on the floor... Get on the floor!
[SPEAKER_08]: Then they'll start dancing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or they'll strip.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get on the floor now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, lots of interesting stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not necessarily an MMO because you can play up to 16 players in there at a time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you can play with other people.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can play with your friends and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: You invite random people in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's mediocre, but massive?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be pretty massive, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: And plus, you know, they're saying that there's also... This is cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's sort of like a spectator mode in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, if your friends have a high wanted level or whatever, and they're getting chased down by the police, you can sit back in your apartment and watch on the TV, and it'll show it like a newscast, watching your friends getting chased by the police.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you get in a white Bronco and drive away, I can watch it on the TV?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: What's also cool, though, is you can jump straight into your multiplayer by... They've got the characters selected on the bottom of the screen that you use your directional pad for, and one of those characters that will unlock in there, there'll be a countdown until it gets to October 1st, is your multiplayer character.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can actually jump into multiplayer that quickly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'm just going to be spending a whole lot of time in this game because I've been looking forward to this since Grand Theft Auto 4 came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you've literally said, you know, I don't think I'm getting the new consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not getting Final Fantasy XIV because my life will get eaten up by this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, and that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, I see myself playing a lot more of this than, say, Killzone or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, like, if I get a console, of course I'm going to check out, you know, a game with and stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Just, you know, I'm probably going to dedicate most of my time to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And like, even like Call of Duty and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, you know, Call of Duty is kind of pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I may get that just because we don't have anything to play at work because you can't really play online at work because our firewalls shit and we don't have a lot of bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_08]: If it wasn't for that, if we had access to live and stuff, I probably wouldn't get Call of Duty either.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still not sure if I will get Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably will get Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_08]: At home, I'm going to be playing mainly Grand Theft Auto V. You know what I was just thinking?
[SPEAKER_14]: With that lip syncing thing, we are going to have a ton of machinima.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bang, bang, bang, bang
[SPEAKER_08]: Grenade!
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you need Kinect for that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I know, because you have to still Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to make a reason for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, more Xbox One confirmations and so forth coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing that was coming out from General Manager of Console Development, Leo Del Castillo, in an interview with Gizmodo, said that the Xbox One will automatically detect if it's overheating and will make adjustments to cool itself down.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is, I guess, something that also happens with PCs.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can dial back the power of the box considerably, forcing the system into a low-power state to correct any issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the way they designed the box, they don't want to actually intend it to ever have to go to maximum speed under normal environmental conditions, but there is overhead.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll allow the fan to go all the way up to its maximum speed, and if that solves the condition without the user having to do anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: My assumption is that is to curb the three light special that affected most 360s because the system was overheating, which granted they corrected later on, which I thought was through a method similar to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe Loki knows more about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a thing on the... Well, it was when it got really hot that that fan would kick up to 100%.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they did have something like that, but usually at that point it's like, eh, your system's kind of toasty right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not new, but the whole throttling the voltage down and actually clocking the system down is kind of new.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once again, it just reads as though they're talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, okay, we've got to tell someone, but let people know that it's not going to red ring.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, even though their systems haven't been red ringing since like...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: And it was originally made for the 70 FPS, which was basically creators making a first-person shooter in seven days.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this one, basically, you have to collect yellow orbs that are dropped by dead zombies.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the only way you get guns and ambos is to kill dead cops.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I mean, is to get them from dead cops.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the only way that you get health is to get first aid drops that are left by dead civilians.
[SPEAKER_15]: So they're already dead, so I guess shooting them is okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, you get shot at if you open fire on them, so it's really kind of a weird thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you heard of this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just saw that he did a game jam game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a FPS game jam game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a seven-day, week-long thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it sounded interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's browser-based.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm kind of interested because he did it in Unity, and so that's what I'm working with right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it would be kind of interesting to check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the style of his graphics.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is kind of 90s FPS with the pre-rendered hand.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, they're all very...
[SPEAKER_08]: Pixelated?
[SPEAKER_15]: Pixely, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_15]: With, you know, shadowed out backgrounds and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just like that the zombies are just green.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised he didn't go with Minecraft zombies because that would have been even funnier.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but that would be expected.
[SPEAKER_15]: Still though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like expected from him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, so something else regarding Notch.
[SPEAKER_08]: That one game, um, what was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember what the hell it was called.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I love that one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The OX10C.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played it that time with these people.
[SPEAKER_08]: his space game that was supposed to be like kind of a not a sequel to Minecraft but still sandbox-ish and procedurally generated but anyways he has decided to go ahead and stop development on it and basically shelving it and just this is due to kind of a creative block they had with the game and
[SPEAKER_08]: However, he was saying, though, that there are some fans that are actually interested in carrying on into the project.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, basically saying that they're not using any of his old code or his name or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: That they're going to just kind of, I guess, based on what he had, sort of create a new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really with the story and stuff, but just kind of a new concept with the original idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know which the original idea did sound kind of neat so I was a little sad to see it go but yeah if he doesn't want to do it it is what it is yeah I mean and that's fine I guess to be inspired by them they're saying they're calling it Project Trillic for now and um no idea what exactly they're going to be doing with it other than they're saying that they're not planning on selling it once it's released but um
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still didn't really understand what the whole game was about other than I know that you could create your own ship and then you could visit planets and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't Minecraft, but it was some sort of crafting into it and you can program stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just very high concept, but I didn't really understand how it would play, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them involved is the legendary Final Fantasy composer Nobuo Uematsu.
[SPEAKER_06]: What they're launching on Kickstarter is called Project Phoenix, and it is an indie JRPG that is trying to be developed.
[SPEAKER_06]: The group behind it is Creative Intelligence Arts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a Tokyo-based company, and they do also Eminence Symphony Orchestra that does video game and anime arrangement stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: um Hiroaki Yura will be the director and producer on Project Phoenix whereas Uematsu will score the title uh which it's not strictly Japanese developers because like LA Noire game designer Vaughn Smith is supposed to be a part of it uh but also fantasy novelist Yoko Inoki uh concept artist in Final Fantasy Kiyoshi Arai sound engineer John Kurlander who worked on Lord of the Rings and Elder Scrolls 5 Skyrim so they kind of have this team together but now they just need the money to pay them uh
[SPEAKER_06]: So they say this will be a JRPG with squad-based real-time strategy game design.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be for Windows PC, Mac, and Linux via Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're hoping to also launch maybe some type of different limited version for iOS and Android, possibly a PlayStation 4 port if the group gets enough funding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they got their funding pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: They wanted $100,000 to do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: with 23 days to go, five times that amount.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have half a million, over half a million in their Kickstarter for this right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got lost when they said it was a real-time strategy.
[SPEAKER_06]: A squad-based RTS game, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That just is not fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Buoy Matsu will do the music.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll take the soundtrack, but I won't play the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's see some of the stretch goals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Double the amount of character and monster models and Uematsu will do more music.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they've hit that goal.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to fight inside the Kraken if they make a million.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what that even means.
[SPEAKER_06]: But all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congrats to those guys for getting their funding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope the game's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got to make a game that Jamie wants to play.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, make it a standard RPG with lots of shooting.
[SPEAKER_06]: going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com DarkTetsuya says hey we're at least guaranteed an epic soundtrack on this that is true a game I mentioned in the first half that I'm going to mention again because it was so horrifically underlooked Lost Odyssey had an amazing soundtrack as well and I believe Uematsu did a lot of the music for that game didn't he?
[SPEAKER_06]: To the Google Cave!
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe he did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he did because Mistwalker, he was a part of that, wasn't he?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I should say is.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh but the music sounds right I'm looking it up real quick yes he did do the music no I don't I just had that moment of geek cred intact I know I had that moment of shit he did do the music right uh all right anyhow uh let's get into this music that means it is time for the mailbag so
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com is the place where you can send us emails and DarkSakura will dive into the mailbag and hopefully pull out some letters worth reading.
[SPEAKER_15]: Deleting a spam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh God, it's been really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to tell you guys, we will be changing that address soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, we need to start using Gmail service for our mail rejection.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you have to pay for that now, so... Nah.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk off air.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, I'll start with a short one.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is from Nark.
[SPEAKER_15]: Since you had such a fun time playing Team Fortress 2, I thought I'd put in a plug for a Team Fortress 2-like game that's still in beta but definitely ready for prime time loadout.
[SPEAKER_15]: Keep up the fun casting, Nark.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard of Loadout and we need to do another Epic Team Forgers tonight people ask me like well when do people actually play on the server it's there for you guys to get together talk on Twitter and the forums and so forth and make something happen I myself maybe will be there tonight but I don't want to promise that so probably during the week next week there'll be a night we just need to have a set aside night maybe after Horde House on Wednesday or something
[SPEAKER_15]: Next email?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_15]: I downloaded DuckTales on the PSN.
[SPEAKER_15]: It plays fine, but I can't help but think the game probably looks better in the original 8-bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Since you guys played the original, how does it compare?
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, I love the animation in the vault.
[SPEAKER_15]: It made me smile.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's from Robaba.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played the original in a very long time but from what I remember well I think you know I think I think I touched on a lot of this at the top of the show they did change some of the mechanics and there's the new levels and stuff and when you're actually playing the game the gameplay feels pretty good but there's all these cutscenes that were not I mean the original did have cutscenes but they were just they weren't the same
[SPEAKER_15]: The poses are the same.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I thought that the new animation frames really harkened back to the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did love the way it looked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what warmed my heart in such a lovely way is hearing June Foray.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I didn't mean to rhyme, but it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was... I love her so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate bagging on the sound because I don't want to make it sound like it's the actor's fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is not.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm so happy they got back together, but it's just... I really need to hear the console one because it sounded fine on Dan's computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: It could have been his speakers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think I got... Rob, if I missed something, shoot us another email.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll clarify.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now the jungle music is stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not the moon music?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the best music.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because the fortune cookie will explain it.
[SPEAKER_15]: The fortune cookie will explain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of my favorite names.
[SPEAKER_15]: First, I cannot help but think about the security breach that unfortunately affected Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, Sony had their breach too and when you consider everything that happened between Sony and Microsoft, it's like trying to figure out the lesser of two evils.
[SPEAKER_15]: But Microsoft tried to keep things under the rug and didn't seem like they were taking things seriously, which is utter bullshit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, would you please briefly recap what you went through so I can point people to this episode about the incident?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, go through the archive.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, even though the Sony service was hacked some time ago, we all know how that went down.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know anybody who lost money on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that that excuses what happened, because that was horrible, but I didn't actually lose money.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what did happen is that somebody else signed into my account and bought a bunch of stuff, bought those FIFA gold packs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They ran up...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even remember how much it was at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say it was about $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it wasn't like... It wasn't astronomical, but it was certainly enough where I missed it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was something recoverable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, they had taken this money and I...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody linked my account to one of those, and so I had to call Microsoft, and they took care of it and did what they had to do, but there was a couple days I was out that money, and it was really infuriating, kind of violating.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when that happened to you, the first thing I did was sign up for that EA account thing so that I could... Yes, because I told all the listeners, I said, if you sign up for that, then they can't do it for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I remember doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But lots of people I know, like people who hadn't even touched their Xbox in forever were getting...
[SPEAKER_06]: were hacked like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And everybody would say, oh, well, Rob, you're stupid and you fell for one of those phishing sites or somewhere and I'm just kind of sitting here going, I'm not going to sit here and say that would never happen to me because I'm not going to be that full of myself that I can't think I might make a mistake once in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think it says something when people who haven't even used their Xboxes in so long and would have no interest in going to any website online were also having their money taken.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I kind of always... When Microsoft came out and said, oh, everybody's just getting phished.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a real phishing problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of sitting here going, bullshit, bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that kind of pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: And have I forgiven them for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have I forgotten?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I try very hard not to save my credit card information or any of that anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, there's always lessons to be learned from any experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: Second, putting free apps behind the gold paywall.
[SPEAKER_15]: I outright refuse to support a service that requires you to pay to use a program freely available elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_15]: No matter what features and perks are available, you should not have to pay and continue paying Microsoft just so you can watch Netflix or Hulu.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I have my computer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lastly, Microsoft has a muddy reputation when it comes to indie developers.
[SPEAKER_15]: In the past, we've had indies like Team Meat and Phil Fish comment on how Microsoft poorly treated them when it came to handling advertising and patches on the Xbox Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_15]: And while the recent change to self-publishing is good, we have retro city rampage creator Provinciano
[SPEAKER_15]: and stating to develop that Microsoft's indie development program is not on par with what other companies offer and there are strings attached with the change to self-publishing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hearing all this makes me assume that the ones digital only offerings won't be as numerous as the PS4s.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a nasty canasta.
[SPEAKER_15]: And just checking, no more email.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I got distracted with a private message, but there was something else in that email I wanted to reply to, and I read it before the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you recap the last two points?
[SPEAKER_15]: I closed it.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of them was about how poorly they treat the indie developers and how they're strings attached and they're not very user-friendly and not receptive.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: The stuff being behind the gold paywall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is going to make the decision.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would point at the Facebook commenter earlier who said the dad bought the PlayStation 3 just for the Blu-ray and the Netflix Hulu.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they have to buy an extra subscription, you're not going to sell an Xbox One to that individual.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, especially when you can do Netflix online for free, and I mean, granted, yes, you pay the subscription, but I'm talking about the viewer itself is on any Internet Explorer window for free, Microsoft probably shouldn't gate that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as the indie developers go...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: so I think Microsoft does realize they done fucked up and they're going in the other direction and I think Microsoft should be giving some credit for that I mean they are giving all these bitchers what they wanted you know at the sacrifice of potentially moving gaming in this new vision or this new direction whether it be right or wrong you know they're going back to what what people what works for people now so I kind of don't want to keep dogging them for doing that but
[SPEAKER_06]: um now it is really going to be about the games and that $100 price difference between the two systems which you never know we could still hear that whole now that connect they may remove it who knows or or take a loss to drop the price if they're that desperate enough I don't know um I kind of don't think that'll happen but here's what I could see them doing um you know it's kind of a helping thing is bundling software with it bundling software or including a year of gold
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like the Wii U needs to drop their fucking price already and all they have to do is remove the basic set and make the deluxe set the only set and make it the basic price
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what they're planning on doing with the Wii U, I think they're playing it cool right now because they're wanting to see how the new software, these big titles that they have coming out, what the uptick is going to be with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if that does it alone, then they don't need to drop the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that doesn't do it, then they may drop the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's what they're waiting on is to see how it does it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the longer you wait, the more it's going to suffer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I've said enough in response to that email.
[SPEAKER_06]: So mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to email us in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although we are going to look into changing that this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this might be the last week of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can send it there for now and be safe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't get crazy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have an F you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's to every fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, not everything, but a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm still kind of fucked off over that whole job thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: But then again, I don't want to work for bigots, so I'm of two minds.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Bubba Gump Shrimp Company, because I had your delicious fish and chips and it murdered me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was sick for days after that and could eat nothing but almond butter and honey.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is true, I ate nothing but almond butter and honey for two days.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Grapes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Grapes are good.
[SPEAKER_15]: But just a big pile of fuckery is abounding and I'm getting sick of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Someone needs to take out the leaf blower thing and blow it out of my life.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: So sick of this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to my work because once again one of our reps left and they're not hiring another person to take that person's spot and so I have a ton more work I have to do and a lot more accounts I have to handle and no additional compensation.
[SPEAKER_14]: Convince them to hire me.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: People.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because people are invading.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to drama.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want none.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you try to bring drama into my life, you will not be as big of a part of my life.
[SPEAKER_06]: So keep your drama away from me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you and good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chirp chirp.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk a little bit more Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a lawsuit that was brought against them for their infringement of a 3D display patent.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is, of course, with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they have, though, managed to reduce the...
[SPEAKER_08]: and I guess a reduction of what they were going to have to pay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now it's down to $30.2 million.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're saying that also possibly maybe even being able to reduce it to even less than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds like that maybe the evidence...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, they were saying that it was, I guess, unsupported by the evidence presented at the trial, so maybe they were having a hard case, saying that they violated rights or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: But either way, though, less money having to be awarded means that they can print more of those $90 copies of Xenoblade Chronicles, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what we really want the Oculus Rift for.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the future right here is porn, porn, porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3D Heaven is one that's being worked on apparently, which is a detailed full body 3D scans, which would be like, I guess, a nude model that you can just kind of look at.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at our boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look all around and look at our boobies everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try to reach out and touch the boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be funny, like, they give you, like, depending on how you bend your head and stuff, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see what else there is here.
[SPEAKER_06]: ThryX Games Chat House 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's real-time chat client software called Chat House 3D, and I guess it's like a voyeur mode or whatever, and you can, I guess, chat with babes, and maybe they'll take their top off?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_06]: But whatever, it's all in the real vision, the Oculus Rift 3DX Chap is a multiplayer erotic game that is supposed to have Oculus Rift support It's called the first 3D sex game with Oculus Rift support There's also added support for the V-Stroker adult accessory Do you have a V-Stroker, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I do not have a V-Stroker.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't you Google that?
[SPEAKER_08]: And sadly enough, I know what that is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it like a flashlight?
[SPEAKER_15]: Really, what is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It is like a flashlight thing, but it actually, it's USB powered.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's masturbation for the lazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Move my hand back for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just too much work.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a hand cramp.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody give me my V-Stroker.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mom!
[SPEAKER_06]: Bee Stroker!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okie dokie!
[SPEAKER_07]: Mommy, I have to have the Bee Stroker!
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up, Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're 35.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't make them in Canada.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I have to digress in a second because they have something in Canada on the App Store that I wish we had here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's where you can be a parking attendant and take pictures of people who park badly, record their license plate number, and then you get whatever their parking violation fee is, you get like up to 40% of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_15]: We need this here!
[SPEAKER_06]: We need this here immediately!
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: I posted it on Facebook a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but there'd be so many complaints.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: it's Murica and I can park bad if I want I'll sue you because you misreported me
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You moved my car when I wasn't looking.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the other thing that Canada has is Canada's Worst Driver.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_15]: That show's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was an America's Worst Driver, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: It lasted one season because I fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, do you know who won America's Worst Driver?
[SPEAKER_06]: The guy who started GamerX.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: As long as he's not driving.
[SPEAKER_06]: In one of those weird, it's a small world kind of things.
[SPEAKER_15]: But for the record, Canada's Worst Driver is awesome because it's actually educational.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't seen either one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, it's so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like the only reality show I like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's it for the Oculus Rift games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: We learned what a V-stroker is thanks to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we are going to go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: The phones are open for business, so give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, I'll get to Twitter topics in a minute here, but I want to check with Loki if there's any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought, honestly, it was kind of a slow week, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there's not a whole lot going on this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can talk more about Grand Theft Auto V. Hey, you want to talk about Grand Theft Auto V?
[SPEAKER_08]: IQ Games, they've got a new visualizer that's coming to the PS3, so you can get something other than the rotating globe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you're saved by phone calls on the Skype line, so let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or his name on Skype is Orange Sounds Radio, but we do have a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Ranma, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good, how about you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm enlightened now that I know what a V-Stroker is, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not too much, I just wanted to say a couple things about last week's podcast I believe it was, because I was kind of on the road at the time Oh right, you're coming back from one of your many conventions Yes, I am such the convention whore You really are, but that's why we love you Are you now immune to all the confunks?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll never be immune to the con-funk, the con-plague, or con-anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was a special breed of it, though, that was out around Final Maid 2001 called the Dorbola.
[SPEAKER_15]: People on TBR Freak remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind regarding last week's show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I just want to say, Rob, I really appreciate what you said about GamerX because a lot of what you said reminds me of some of the conversations I've had with cosplayers, con goers at anime conventions because a lot of what you were talking about you kind of find there because...
[SPEAKER_02]: of similar fans of anime, different genres and so forth, to kind of get together and understand and relate to what it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: They all get together and bash the homestucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not, because if we're going to go that direction, nobody's getting on the Skype line, so let's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, you're right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So kind of having a safe place for like-minded individuals, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, yep, definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of, is that the thrill that you get in anime conventions?
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of it, yeah, because, I mean, I ain't gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever since I had this VOG shirt, my desire to cosplay has kind of cut down a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still cosplay mostly for, like, meetups and stuff, but I just like wearing a shirt that has who I'm representing and who I am, and I'm taking pictures and handing out cards, you know, it's like, well...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is where I wanna be, and I'm happy where I am.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: You and I are fighting someone with a sewing machine and we're making your damn Joker costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: In two weeks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Evan and I made my Baiken costume in three days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, come on, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can send you a Black Mage costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did like that costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have an idea for a perfect costume for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go to Dragon Con dressed as Jesus with a rainbow sash and just walk around with a glass of water.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't that be a glass of wine?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob should be Buddy Christ.
[SPEAKER_06]: I better the the most hilarious thing I thought about doing because I don't here's the thing I don't want to have to keep shaving my fucking beard off for costumes so whatever I dress up as I really want to have a mustache and beard so I thought about maybe doing tingle
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't necessarily want pictures of me like that on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joker's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have pictures of me as Joker on the internet.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what I think you should do if you did the Joker costume?
[SPEAKER_15]: You should do the first Mass Effect uniform.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because that one I think is a cool one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brad from PodCulture says that wouldn't bother anyone and Blackwell says my friend cosplayed as Buddy Christ.
[SPEAKER_06]: I underestimate the crowd at DragonCon, clearly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you should just wear a bathrobe and be the dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to be offended at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really hope cosplay pushes the envelope.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: We get you leather undies and you can go like Final Fantasy XI outfit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let me check my iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if we're going the route of leather, we could dress him up as hard gay Razor Ramon.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Rob would have to shave for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I like where this conversation is going.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you need to change the topic or get the hell off the phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll find you something good.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're changing topics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting out of here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: As you haven't heard, I am officially a college graduate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mazel tov.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: and in regards to that in one of my classes we had to do a term paper about an invention so and it was like minimum of five pages so i sat there after drinking thinking about it and pushing myself i pretty much shot out an eight page term paper on the history of the nintendo entertainment system nice
[SPEAKER_15]: that's awesome I have to say by the way because I'm coming up on another degree this semester just because I've changed my major so many times I am super proud of you thank you
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to be a sociologist after this semester.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, many, many... You just have your Ph.D.
[SPEAKER_02]: in Jack of all trades, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have my Ph.D.
[SPEAKER_13]: in bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: You both have your degrees in that shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: My Ph.D.
[SPEAKER_13]: is in bitch and girl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_13]: The both of you.
[SPEAKER_13]: God.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Ph.D.
[SPEAKER_06]: is in reading and the library is open.
[SPEAKER_06]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I got my B.A.
[SPEAKER_15]: in judging you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Ranma, I gotta let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why isn't Ranma going to DragonCon?
[SPEAKER_06]: This makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma, you make me sad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I miss Ronchon.
[SPEAKER_15]: He needs to come back out here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I love you, Fifth Dream.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a bitch of all trades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Master of none.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll show you, Master.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Holy shit!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, it's Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, it's been forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where the hell have you been, young man?
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought a horse farm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been cleaning it up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, you bought a horse farm?
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought a horse farm, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: You remember a while ago, last fall, I moved up north, and we wereI'm going to get a better light for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had to find a house, and I didn't find a really good house farm or horse farm.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I bought it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't come with any horses, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta get some next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I got stables, I got a barn, I got everything, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm ready to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got a little pasture for them to eat their little grass and shit in.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, so when your daughter gets to that age where she's like, I want a pony, I want a pony, you're gonna be like, alright, let's do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta get a horse farm.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got one ready on call for her third birthday next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a racetrack like three hours away and they have the retired horses, so instead of just killing off the
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what they do to racehorses.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where the glue comes from.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to bring a couple home.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's probably cheaper to get to work than gas anyway too, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: DungeonBuster in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says real life animal crossing for Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, except your horse won't ask you to deliver a package to the person standing right next to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations on the house though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty big.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: You mean Phantasy Star?
[SPEAKER_09]: Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking about Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at my eye.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can tell I'm talking about Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can tell I don't know Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what you do on a horse farm.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Phantasy Star, yes, on Sega.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good memories?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a rough time in my life when I was about 12 years old, 11, 12.
[SPEAKER_09]: My parents split up.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'd have to go see my dad every two weeks, and it kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: But every two weeks I went to go see him, I would get to go to the one store in town that rented Sega games, because there was only one store in town that rented them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And sure enough, one day I got there and I found Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a four-mega cartridge or something it was called.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was the only one they had, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you get the four-mega cartridge, and I picked up this weirdo Japanese RPG game and
[SPEAKER_09]: I wasn't really into them because I was only 12, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't really a cool thing to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I brought it home and I played it all weekend and I was like astonished at how awesome it was, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got my, spoiler alert, I got my little mirror shield and I shined it in fucking Medusa's face and suck that bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: She all turned to stone and shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, this is the fucking greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was one of the first, no, you remember that shit, man?
[SPEAKER_09]: Odin gets the mirror shield and only Odin can hold it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember this shit, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trust me, this is a big deal in my life.
[SPEAKER_09]: So listen, I'm telling you right now, Rob, from me to you, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was the first game I had anyway that you could save a game on those old fucking cartridges, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Those old shitty blowing them cartridges.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you could save it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I saved my game to the first spot and I put a note.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember when they used to have game manuals?
[SPEAKER_09]: I put a sticky note on the front of the game manual.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you, Johnny.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're fucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: I put it in, I loaded up game one, and he fucking sold all my armor and shit that I had.
[SPEAKER_09]: He fucking took everything and hid it somewhere in a chest or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had three of my characters are dead and just a little fucking cat was alive and shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: What a dick!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm being serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought Canadians were supposed to be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: That guy was a dick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was video game playing Canadians in 1992, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jesus Christ, a lot of assholes up here, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: So hey, do you still have a master system?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I spend all weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: But check this out.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is where the story gets a little bit dirty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spoiler alert.
[SPEAKER_09]: Teenage or young child, preteen, dirtyness coming up here.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I fucking took the game and I was all upset.
[SPEAKER_09]: I fucking played real hard and I brought my characters back and shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I fucking left a note in there again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, whoever gets this game next.
[SPEAKER_09]: I save my game to level 1 I only get it every 2 weeks when I visit my dad please don't over save my game 2 weeks later I go back and I get the fucking game and there's a fucking note in there again and I'm like oh here comes the asshole and this time the note said
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, my name is Christy.
[SPEAKER_09]: My game save is number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you ever want to hang out and play together, here's my phone number and my address.
[SPEAKER_09]: And she actually left me her phone number and her address in the fucking game manual.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you imagine telling your 12-year-old girl to leave her fucking phone number and address inside of a game nowadays?
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you fucking imagine that shit?
[SPEAKER_06]: But again, this is 1992, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is 1992.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you call the number because I'm thinking 65-year-old man?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, dude, I called a number and it was a fucking 12-year-old girl that lived like maybe five, six blocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was far from my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we would hang out every two weeks for like maybe six months afterwards.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we would play the game for like, I don't know, an hour or two.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we would play another game.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It got me to first mate.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were only 12, but I kissed her.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would kiss her a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: We would snuggle.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we would play the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: She'd be like, no, you should buy the fangs for the cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we don't have to buy the staff for the old man because he's stuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'd be like, Noah's the fucking man.
[SPEAKER_09]: He saved us in the forest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck Noah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get the jewels for the, get the collar jewels.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we would fucking have these little arguments for like, oh, at least six months.
[SPEAKER_09]: Until the summertime came and then she took off for like, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We beat the game like three times together, guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: We just kept playing that same game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's how it ends?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how it ends?
[SPEAKER_06]: She just disappeared one summer and no fulfilling the fantasy star?
[SPEAKER_15]: We didn't go to the same school in the summertime.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't have to see my dad every two weeks in the summertime.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we just kind of fell off, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: We never really got together because that was grade 8.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I went into grade 7 or grade 8.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a sophomore in high school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally, you still got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You still got it and you know it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You still got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I know you're married and you're spoken for and all that, but if you were to find... If you were to find that girl again today, she would throw her panties at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you guys are pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at this old car.
[SPEAKER_09]: I restored this old car so we could drive around and it just started our wedding day.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is absolutely terrible radio and I don't care because I'm getting to see pictures of Jim Sally's wife.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can see these pictures on Jim Sally's Facebook at jimsallysfacebook.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a real website, you fucking idiots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, I can make that happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jim Sally, I fucking love it when you call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I unfortunately have to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But goddamn, don't be a stranger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't be a stranger.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, man, I'll be online a lot more.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got the farm settled now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be online a lot more.
[SPEAKER_09]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pinky swear?
[SPEAKER_11]: Swear on your Phantasy Star save?
[SPEAKER_11]: I can fucking pinky swear on this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't really pinky swear on an iPad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have my pinky up.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have my pinky up.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to pinky swear.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I love everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We love you too, Jim Sally.
[SPEAKER_09]: Before I go, though, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, seriously, tell Dan to let the world see your cleavage.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should never hide your cleavage.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Lord gave you that cleavage for the rest of us to enjoy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually am wearing a rather busty shirt today.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was the bike in cleavage.
[SPEAKER_06]: You played Guilty Gear X, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: How come you're not Skype videoing me then with the cleavage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we have to give you a reason to call in next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Jim Sally, I gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I'm letting you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tits are GTFO.
[SPEAKER_06]: He lifted his shirt up and showed us his boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you think you can top that call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh God, I love when he calls in.
[SPEAKER_06]: He needs a show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to find the pictures of me in the bike and outfit that I had to duct tape my boobs up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what I mean by the duct tape lift that... Yes, oh yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew many girls in Rocky Horror that, you know...
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: It takes boobs of iron to be able to duct tape directly to the skin.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: That shit hurts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to do some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt tweets us that Tommy Tallarico and the Video Games Live crew have taken a Kickstarter to fund the next Video Games Live album.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, that's on Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video Games Live Level 3 that they're currently trying to fund on Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure they'll make it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of people love their Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw sends us a couple of tweets too Warhammer 40k Space Wolf is card based and free to play so if you're interested in that game the good news is that's going to be free to play also he sends us a tweet that a Halo novelist has joined Amazon's game studio I didn't realize Amazon had their own game studio
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess they do, and I know that they're still kicking around the idea of maybe a console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, that's true, because we did have that on the last show, where they might have their own Ouya version or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, the writer Eric Nyland, who wrote Gears of War 3 and Halo Reach, he's the new director of narrative design for Amazon Games, so they must be planning something.
[SPEAKER_06]: They gotta be planning some juicy exclusive for that Android console, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last chance to call 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really pressed that I missed Video Games Live when they were here recently, but I just had so much going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I'll give it another minute here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have no other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: We covered everything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not anything interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we're getting to about 930.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think Jim Sally's call was so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I saw a Sanrio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Poking her nose out.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's ready for KTs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why she's out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Meow, meow, meow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give me something.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we'll close up the Skype line then.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll go around and get everybody's final thoughts and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys for listening to another week of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, there's a lot of fantastic podcasts out there from very hardworking independent individuals and new ones showing up every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just heard of a new one on Twitter today that makes me very excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, just support independent broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you thought this show was awful, I don't know how you made it to the end, but thank you, at least for giving it a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you thought this show was awful, at least try another independent podcast and see if you can find the one that works for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you did like Orange Lounge Radio, all we ask, tell a friend or five about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all we got, because we don't have a big budget to advertise this or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to try at DragonCon, but otherwise we don't have TV ads we can do or magazine ads or whatever, so word of mouth helps a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always leave us a nice review.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't had a nice five-star review on iTunes in like a year, so I would love to see some new ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thumbs up on Stitcher and all that helps too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of people are switching to the streaming apps like TuneIn and so forth, so spreading the word and sharing the show there really helps too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really appreciate it, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_15]: If I have to clean up cat puke when I get home, I will be grumpy.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is... Keys!
[SPEAKER_06]: I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keys were sitting in front of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cents!
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you send me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, cents.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, like dollars and cents.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob has pennies on his desk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we are going insane here at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, last but not least, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to play some more Saints Row this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And on multiple platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Burn a CD.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, your computer's possessed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your laptop is about to take off into space.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can the listeners hear that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was gonna say that the demon jumped from Rob's toilet into your computer I'm just tired of listening to the same CD over and over in my car so I'm burning a new one I meant to do it earlier but fair enough
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright guys, that's going to do it for tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be sure to be here live next week, Sunday, August 25th, when we do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep in mind, it will be the last show for possibly three weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to try to avert that best we can.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, be here next week for that show, episode 517.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until then, thank you guys once again for tuning in and supporting our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that would mean that we're coming back on wit day now?
[SPEAKER_08]: So it wouldn't be the third because that's Labor Day, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right when I'm ending the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will have no show September 1st.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, first that's Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may be out September 8th, which I'll talk to you about off air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would mean we would come back September 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we would miss your birthday.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not worried about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that when Grand Theft Auto V is out?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's out on the 17th.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, Rob, so next week is our last one before breaks.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, it happens the week after that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's my 8th year wedding anniversary.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy anniversary.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: My god.
[SPEAKER_06]: When this show started, you weren't married.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
Ugh.
[SPEAKER_06]: This show's old.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we were cohabiting.
[SPEAKER_13]: We were living in sin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Living in sin's the best.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on that note, I really am ending it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody be quiet so I can play the closing song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pacific, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network but you know they were all still true see you next week
Thanks for watching!