[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, December 16th, 2007, internet radio hits the PSP in one part of the world, Mass Effect and Assassin's Creed boast big sales, and how would you feel about a wee rain check under the tree this Christmas?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that program on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing, Ms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Summers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Long day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Long weekend?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking about it still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm making a decision.
[SPEAKER_05]: A decision?
[SPEAKER_03]: But I can't do it without being fully informed.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should always be fully informed when making a decision
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feeling a little ripped off.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, just a company I've been buying stuff for my new computer with, EVGA, and I bought my motherboard and my graphics card from them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Literally the day after I bought my graphics card, NVIDIA went and redesigned it, made it cheaper, faster, and better.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the motherboard that I bought
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't tell what's wrong since there's no beeps nor indication of what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm looking at the motherboard that they sell on EVGA's site and there's stuff missing off mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I don't know, a PCI Express slot that's supposed to be there that's not and some other shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, they're going to get an angry call tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now you just talked smack about them on your internet show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's just lovely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're feeling hurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our always present fourth guest here on the program, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: We always tape live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there's a lot of folks that listen to us in our taped form on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, of course, listening live is a whole other element where you get to do interactivity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Question from AZHP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which graphics card was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an 8800 GTS.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means nothing to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea what that's about.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an NVIDIA card.
[SPEAKER_04]: They redesigned the GT, which made it a little bit faster using the 65 nanometer chips.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now they did the same thing with the 8800 GTSs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, for example, I paid for my card.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was about $364.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, that's quite a bit for a card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the best part, though, because, see, now I can get an even faster card.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to save for about $100 cheaper, which is annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it'll have slightly less graphics memory because I had 640 megs of RAM on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one now, the GTS...
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be 512 megs of RAM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, it's not that cheaper, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $359.99, but still.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little bit cheaper, and it's even faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, geez, suddenly we're turning into the PC graphics card podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's all right, because I know there's a lot of PC gamers who are really into this graphics card.
[SPEAKER_05]: For me, I just need something to play WoW on, but you all know about that addiction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I really want to ask about, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed you brought one of your Xboxes with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if this is when you wanted to bring this up or not, but I'm bringing it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got to show the Op11 people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know this isn't great for the podcast, but we can kind of talk about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got your Xbox modded, and I don't mean like the piracy mods or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's the other one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have like a glass thing on your Xbox that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where did you buy this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did you do this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we show this to the Op11 people?
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to plug it in for it to look good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, is it not plugged in?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not plugged in right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember you said not to plug to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can plug it in real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, do it real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do it real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we don't blow a circuit and the show comes to a screeching halt.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if we suddenly go off air, you know what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, if it explodes, it'll hit you guys first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Jamie, maybe duck a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have Pyramid Head protect you with his blade while we do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And hopefully the folks on cam can see this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's protected by the power of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the archives in Op 11 are working again, so you might be able to see this in the archives in Op 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, you turn it on, and it glows blue inside, which I think is all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like how a lot of people have modded their PC cases to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I guess the folks in chat have seen enough of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did you do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it just for the challenge, or what was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's not near a microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excellent live radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So why exactly did you decide to mod this and make it blue in there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just wanted something the other kids didn't have, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did it to, well, three of them so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have one more that I haven't done yet because they're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest though, it may look cool, but it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: The brand of clear case I bought, which I think it was like a ghost case or something like that, they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't fit right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, for example, you'll notice that one has still the old faceplate on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's a clear faceplate for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is it jams the DVD drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Tigerclaw has a very good point in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Modding the 360 may be cool, but it also voids the warranty.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you just, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't care about the warranty, you'll just take your chances?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just like I did the other one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one was modded in the other way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well we'll get into that a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and check.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we'll have the wonderful Christmas light effect on there since it's got three flashing lights on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The red rings of death.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and ask the question about our gaming weeks because that's how we're supposed to start off the show before we get into ooh and aahing over a blue 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a Christmas present last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Portal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and I totally knew Dan got it for me because I checked our online banking and I saw that he had already told me how much it was used at his store and then I saw that much come out of the bank spent at GameCrazy and then
[SPEAKER_03]: That day I felt a game in my stocking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't take it out, but I knew what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so last night I went in there and was just playing around with him.
[SPEAKER_03]: And his friend Will was visiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Dan said, oh, and by the way, and took it out of my stocking.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was like, hey, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they were taunting me with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I got it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so Dan was going to play like a level.
[SPEAKER_03]: He ended up playing up to the Weighted Companion Cube level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's addicting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was very silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I played World Cup Soccer Pinball last night because I hadn't played any pinball in a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lots of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a little Elendon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I gotta ask you though, since you put on your investigative hat to find out that your husband had bought you the orange box for Christmas, were you the type of child that looked under the bed for what mom got you for Christmas, or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, first of all, mom kept everything in the closet, and then second of all, the only reason... I like how you know, you have to correct me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, no, if I wanted to look at the presents, I went to the closet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's because that's where she kept them because my mom is not creative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but I happened to be checking the online banking to see if my bonus got in.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's why I was looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I saw 40-something dollars spent at GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, oh, gee, who's been the one talking about wanting Orange Box for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_03]: And there it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's when I got my investigative hat on when the clue presented itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I ever tell you the story about when I got my Super Nintendo when I was 12?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I've told the story on this program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I might have been 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I asked for that for Christmas, and that's all I really wanted was a Super Nintendo, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And so we opened up all the presents under the tree, and I saved the big, big present for last because I kind of guessed that maybe it was the Super Nintendo I wanted for Christmas, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I opened the very last present, and it's a San Francisco Giants jacket.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you know me, you know I love sports.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like crushed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like about ready to cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't want to cry because I didn't want to look like a baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: But inside the gamer nerd in me is like wanting to cry and sob and throw things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be the spoiled brat I am, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then finally after everybody opens their presents, my sister comes to me with one tiny, tiny, tiny little gift and says there's one more thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on it was written on an index card a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drakken
[SPEAKER_05]: which I don't think anybody ever played.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was based on an old PC game, and it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sequel to it, which I believe was called Dungeon View, Drakken 2, was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the first one was a little meh, because it was a role-playing game where you didn't really control your characters at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just kind of hoped they would beat the monster in their own way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of neat, I guess, in its own way.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the reason why they bought that, because the guy at Sears told them it was a big seller.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Liar!
[SPEAKER_05]: To this day, nobody fucking knows Drakken.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember when we bought a PC from Sears a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never buy PCs from them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking at comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger Claw says, Drakken was a 3D RPG.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm not the only one that knows what Drakken is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure there's other listeners that go, I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amaze Satsuma, I like this, says, When I was younger, I wasn't only the type to hunt for my Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also opened the game boxes and replaced the game inside with the game I already own.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's messed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, another year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I, uh, I, my mom went to Target and got all this stuff, and I was, like, looking in the bags when she came back from Target.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not, like, intentionally, I wasn't really hunting around for Christmas presents, I was actually looking for candy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I wanted to see if she bought candy, because I wanted candy.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I freaking saw a copy of Fester's Quest on the NES in one of the bags and I was like, oh crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I decided to screw with my mom later because we went to the video store and I wanted to rent a game so I grabbed the box for Fester's Quest and I'm like, let me rent this game, let me rent this game and my mom's like, no, you don't need to rent a game tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm such a bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, how was your game week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, I played Saints Row again, more of that and I played
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the way the crashes look.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little hard to see where the shortcuts and stuff are in the game, but I guess that's why you gotta drive around more and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll probably pick it up when it comes out in January.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see, other than that, I think a little bit more Zelda Phantom Hourglass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm pretty much done with that game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You really can save pictures to the Wii message board.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of took me a little bit to figure out how to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But basically, if you have Pokemon Snap, you take the pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, Pokemon Snap doesn't control quite as nice as I remember it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, the controls are kind of shitty.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the game itself is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you take the pictures of the Pokemon, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can save your favorites to this gallery.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you back out all the way to the main menu and then go into gallery, you can look at the pictures you took.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the Nintendo 64, kind of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: up-rezes them from when you took them in-game to, I guess, the highest quality picture that Nintendo 64 could render.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're in that mode, you hit the minus key on your classic controller, and that is what will post your picture to the Wii message board.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can only post one a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can send the pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: I took a picture, and I didn't know who to send it to, so I sent it to Bobby Blackwolf because I thought he'd get a kick out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: VX, JasonXVR, Webmaster wants me to send the picture to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I will do that a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's doing the Check Me Out channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other stuff I've looked at.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually looked at this last week, but I forgot to mention it on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox 360, a little demo came out for a game called Cold Step Saga.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the thing about Cold Step is it was kind of like a cult game, if you will, on the PlayStation 2, where not a lot of people had heard of it or played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Cold Step on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you've read any reviews about this game, it's probably... Most of the reviews on it are pretty accurate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Monopoly meets...
[SPEAKER_05]: Magic the Gathering, where you're moving around this board and you're trying to collect the most magical points.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you do that by laying these monsters down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when opponents land on the square where you've put down a monster, they can either challenge the monster with one of their own monsters or pay a toll.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, you're paying boardwalk, so they have to pay with some of their magic.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's basically the gist of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think it translated the 360 pretty nicely.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only downside...
[SPEAKER_05]: is that in playing, you know, obviously it's only the demo, I'm basing my assumptions off the demo, but the demo appeared to be one of the exact same boards from the PlayStation 2 version, I think the very first board.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it does look like there's some more cards and things, but really it looks like all they've done on the 360 is made it widescreen and up-res'd everything to 720p.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not for somebody who likes a fast, action-paced game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if something like Puzzle Quest is more up your alley or something you think before you make your moves and stuff like that, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's certainly not fast-paced.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of card games, I just wanted to mention, I vaguely remember the amount because it wasn't that much, but a little update to the Eye of Judgment sales in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, lordy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we sold yet another 17,000 units last month, so we're up to a whopping 32,000-ish around there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So 32,000 Eye of Judgment units sold, and the goal is, again, 1 million for Loki to wear the Tingle suit here on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think he'll sell 1 million, period.
[SPEAKER_05]: One other quick...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: and Harvey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's Harvey?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the giant rabbit.
[SPEAKER_05]: The giant rabbit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we have Pikachu and Kirby behind us and Cartman.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the clear it up in chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the 32,000 was domestic sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea what it's selling worldwide.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can guarantee, though, it's not anything over 100,000 units already.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fairly confident that it's never going to sell a million units.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rossdale UT in chat says, Kind of like Diablo equals kind of repetitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get that same feeling from Diablo, but I think a lot of the strength that Diablo had was the multiplayer mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be fair, I didn't get to try that mode out on this demo yet, so maybe that's where this game shines, is being able to do multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might make the game a hell of a lot more fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's why I put that disclaimer out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm completely basing my judgment of this game off the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, that's what a lot of Xbox users do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you're going to put a demo out there, make sure it sells everything the game's got in it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll still happen, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's given a little on the bet and says if the game can ever sell a million, a million worldwide even?
[SPEAKER_05]: A million worldwide.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the game can sell a million worldwide ever, then Loki will wear the Tingle suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch one of our listeners win the lottery and buy 900,000 of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it might be like three years from now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope we're still doing this show three years from now or, you know, that could happen like in 30 years and Loki's, you know, getting old going, what do you mean I gotta wear this suit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have Judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some housekeeping tonight before we start tonight's news of the gaming type.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is no show next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not going to be here next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're taking December 23rd off for the holidays because DarkSakura, myself, and Loki all have family and friends stuff to attend to.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're not going to be here on December 23rd.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, for those of you that listen live, it is my understanding there is a very special OLR Christmas that's going to happen thanks to some of our...
[SPEAKER_05]: and other OLR personalities.
[SPEAKER_05]: So stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That will not hit the podcast feed, but it will go up on our MySpace and our LiveJournal and Facebook and all the fan communities we have.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will still be able to grab a recorded copy of whatever mischief happens on the station next Sunday, which I'm sure is going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back on December 30th for our year-end special and more to come on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: About that, a little closer to the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero 3
[SPEAKER_04]: It's getting a brand new patch to fix a few things and add a couple things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the things that they're fixing, improving the online quick match results and also adding a calibration screen improvements, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also one of the things that they're adding for like PlayStation 3 users, the co-op quick play mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: So other than that, various other stability improvements and fixes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish they'd add some new characters or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, other than that, there's also going to be a new download pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they've added two different ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of which is from the Warner Reprise track pack, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's going to include Pretty Handsome Awkward by The Used, Sleeping Giant by Mastodon, and No More Sorrow by Linkin Park.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they have single download packs.
[SPEAKER_04]: including some, I guess it's from popular European bands, So Peoso by Extremodoro, and Antisocial by Trust, and Ernton Was We're Saying by Der Fentigen Veer, I don't know, I probably butchered all that stuff, and then I guess a free exclusive rock rendition of a holiday classic, We Three Kings by Steve Oyment.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's kind of funny, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have hoped that they would have had more Christmas songs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, get the London Symphony Orchestra or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Trans-Siberian Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twisted Sister Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twisted Sister Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: A friend of mine's been linking me a lot of the songs on them because someone uploaded them on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trans-Siberian Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can even do that as a free download pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free is good, especially for Christmas, come on, or the holidays.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, we have to say the politically correct term, the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Credit to Activision or Harmonix, I'm going to say Activision, for actually giving a free song for Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, hey, the rest of those packs, of course, is going to be $6.25.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, here's why I never wish listeners a happy birthday on the program, because of course now we had someone else pipe up and FootyMonster says, it was my birthday last week too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, FootyMonster.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, just so we don't get any more emails going, it was my birthday, it was my birthday, and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you had a birthday between December 9th and December 15th, which would have been last week, or today, December 16th, happy birthday to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rest of you, sit on it and wait for your turn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best to you, if you...
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy unbirthday to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Guitar Hero and Rock Band, there's drama.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's like these two are having some real drama, pillow fights and everything between them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how, of course, there's the compatibility issues with the guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what was supposed to happen is that Rock Band was going to get an update on the PlayStation 3 so that the Guitar Hero 3 controller will work with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it didn't happen, and Harmonix took to their forums to explain the reason why.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, Two weeks ago, Harmonix created a software patch for the Sony PlayStation 3 version of Rock Band that allowed for guitar compatibility and support for third-party peripherals, including enabling use of Activision's Guitar Hero 3 controller with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: The compatibility patch was submitted, approved, and has been scheduled for release by Sony on Tuesday, December 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, Activision objected to the compatibility patch's release.
[SPEAKER_05]: The patch remains with Sony, but we have been told that it will unfortunately not be released due to Activision's continued objection.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, boo Activision to doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure they have their own reasons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Motivating people to just go out and buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your fault that you left.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying that they willfully deceived the consumer with a statement that it had Dolby ProLogic 2 surround sound instead of mono.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a universe of difference between Dolby and mono.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand, but still, lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know they've promised to put out replacement discs that have the sound issue corrected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Activision's not making any comment, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think that they really, it's in their best interest to make a comment at this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not while they're going through litigation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not, especially when they're trying to fix things.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would think if anybody wants to bring the smackdown on Activision, it ought to be Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the consumer suing them in this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think the consumer is suing Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're suing Activision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but I'm saying if anybody should put the smackdown on Activision, it ought to be Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Nintendo should go to Activision and go, you gave us a subpar version of the game than what you gave the other systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Naughty, naughty, naughty.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't be surprised if they would do something too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything's a subpar version on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not as powerful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, in terms of graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have that whole thing as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, look at, like, okay, look, for example, Far Cry Instincts on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: That two-player deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Two players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you really pushed yourselves there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, some of the other control issues that they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of crappy ports of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at you, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, I don't know, overall, they just don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see, the problem is also I think a lot of these people are used to putting out crappy games without, you know, quality checking them very...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: At least you'll be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully you can find a copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, if you're waiting for the PlayStation 2 version in Canada, well, they haven't really confirmed on when that's coming too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But seriously, why settle for Rock Band on the PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because with the amount you're going to pay for that, you really ought to just put that down towards another console, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you do buy it on PlayStation 2, at least if you do get a new console later that happens to be PlayStation 3, you can use all the instruments from that on the PlayStation 3 version because they are identical.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but then you have to buy a PlayStation 3, and I don't know if everybody wants to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyhow, moving on to other PlayStation 3 games, including one that I know a lot of people are excited about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metal Gear Solid 4 could be the game that definitely drives sales of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And another little perk included in the game to further make people want to buy this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember an earlier story, which I think was blown out of proportion, but nevertheless, it was reported on previously that Metal Gear Solid was supposed to move a million units in its first day in order to recover the cost or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would need to, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was originally going to be two separate games, and now it looks like actually they are going to be coming together with one game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Metal Gear Online will have 16-player support, deathmatch, team deathmatch, King of the Hill, team sneak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could this be PlayStation 3's version of Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, certainly not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there are different types of games, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could say Unreal Tournament is kind of their Halo, but, you know, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just like seeing Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops was its own game, and then the online portion was another game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the college is Metal Gear Online, so Metal Gear 4, the online portion of it, I think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of deceiving the buyer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think here's where it comes from, why is this just a demo or is this a full game, is because they are saying in the magazine, quote, expecting five maps in the starter pack that will provide the basic setup to get your Metal Gear Solid multiplayer fix moving.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is starter pack a fancy term for demo, or is starter pack something like a luminous starter pack that you get on Xbox 360 Arcade, and then you have to buy all these freaking add-ons to get more stuff for it?
[SPEAKER_04]: They like them add-ons.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The original Xbox series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought there was one I didn't recognize, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luckily, I can buy them separately.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't have to buy all the crappy ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you get a discount if you buy all the crap together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like how they try to trick you to do that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if you buy ten bags of potatoes, you get them for a buck.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, ten for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, there are like ten for ten dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, Loki's talking about potatoes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please save us.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about some asshattery from Sony?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the Sony CEO, Howard Stringer, is full of crap because he's quoted as saying, I'm happy the Wii seems to be running a bit short of hardware.
[SPEAKER_03]: The PlayStation 3 will come into its own because its games are infinitely more fun, demanding, and exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, the Wii is short on hardware?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's a variety of third-party things out there for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, most of them are shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I think about that little plastic golf club and stuff that you can get, the little fake tennis racket.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, there's the Wii Zapper and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're meaning the Wii itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're just saying the Wii isn't as fun as the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I dispute that claim.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had a lot more fun playing games on Wii than on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, you know, it's not that the PlayStation 3 is horrible, but right now it's kind of close.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're thinking that they're going to sell more PlayStation 3s, but honestly, we saw the stack at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and it's not just at that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's at a multitude of stores that
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not moving the units.
[SPEAKER_03]: People want a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: He does understand that the reason there are no Wiis is because people want them so bad and so they keep selling out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas the PlayStation 3 doesn't have that problem because they're not selling out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And where does he get off saying that their games are more fun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you like first-person shooters and broken games, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see the PlayStation 3 has a lot of potential.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does have potential.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just hasn't done anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I watched that trailer for Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a new one that came out this week, and it looks fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks absolutely fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will be fucking amazing when it comes out Christmas 2009, but I'm not going to wait that long for that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I am so all over a PlayStation 3, like, I don't know, like candy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if they had that, like, you know... Like a fat kid on candy, but I...
[SPEAKER_05]: That trailer was amazing, but for right now, there's not a lot that's making me want to get a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if they had that at launch, we wouldn't be talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd be like saying, wow, look at the PlayStation 3, selling millions and millions of units, and Final Fantasy XIII's fucking awesome, I can play this all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, it's just, the problem is it's not going to come out for a long time, and we got more stories talking about some of the other things that were promised to be out earlier, you know, in 2008, but are probably not, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, just to illustrate a point, Dan says that he gets about maybe 50 calls a day for people asking for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't think he's mentioned anyone calling it at all for a PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii is selling on fat appeal.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Money for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when this whole Wii Fit thing comes out, I'm going to tell you, it's going to happen all over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to continue this fad craze of the Wii until 2008.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I just hope it's a good game and fun and useful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares how they're selling systems?
[SPEAKER_04]: At least they're selling systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't even fucking pick a damn approach to how they're selling your systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a game system.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't fucking make your mind up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's selling.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, OLRPSP.com I think needs an update badly, especially if that ends up coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need people to be able to listen to OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't broadcast over Shoutcast, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you can tap the Live365 feed into Shoutcast somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how, at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we could, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we'll have to look into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I know we get emails once in a while from people, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: They say, we listen on PSP, we listen on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: If that stuff comes out over here, heck, even if it doesn't come out over here, I bet there's got to be at least a handful of people that listen on their PSPs to this program in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: We ought to be able to let them listen live on their PSPs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Get on that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, let me just figure out how to broadcast and shoutcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Homework assignment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already tried doing that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm too stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to some release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of our friends over in Japan, I've got the Japanese release dates for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming on the Xbox 360 December 20th, FIFA 08 World Class Soccer comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on with the release dates, we also have a release of FIFA 08 on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: The GunCon makes its way to the PlayStation 3 separately, I assume.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, Time Crisis finally comes out in Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Time Crisis 4 makes its way to the PlayStation 3 in Japan this week, also on the 20th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Medal of Honor Airborne also makes its way from EA to the PlayStation 3 in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out on the Nintendo Wii, Crazy Climber Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember we reported on this earlier a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were remaking the classic 80s game Crazy Climber for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Japan will finally get its first look at that this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we will soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meet the Robinsons Attack of the Toybots
[SPEAKER_05]: Cats with a Z2 and Dogs with a Z2
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not awesome, but they're not horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, it's stupid, but hey, over here, at least in the United States, it's only like 30 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, wait, find one used for like 10 bucks or something like that, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you feel like paying twice as much, you could import the one from Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would rather not, because it's already out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no point in importing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on with other release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PlayStation 2 is getting some releases as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Myself, Yourself is a game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a limited edition of it as well on the 20th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another game called Pia Carrot y Yokoso, G.O.
[SPEAKER_05]: Summer Fair.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also has a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pia Carrot's old school too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an old school anime, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the games have been out for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess it's another one coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: December 20th, just in time for Christmas over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking at a couple other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see if there's anything on the DS or PSP, because of course those are always crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Port of Meet the Robinsons on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doku Demo Pilates comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not Pirates, that's Pilates comes out in Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dora Base, Dorimon Chao Yakyu Gaiden comes out from Namco on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: A puzzler called DS Puzzler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Numbluff DS Puzzler comes out as well on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure a lot of people are very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one that folks might even be importing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy IV, the remake, hits Japan this week on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure that's going to be the best-selling game of the week as far as the new stuff goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the sound of this game, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pinky Street Kira Kira Music Night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, fun!
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have Pinky Street dolls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: What they are, they're these little plastic dolls.
[SPEAKER_03]: and there may be about, I would want to say like three inches tall.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're smurf-sized.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, no, that's three apples high.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, you can take off their heads and change them out and take off their hair and change them out and it's like you snap them into place is how they work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they're fully customizable and I guess it would be the same type of thing on the game as you customize your pinky and
[SPEAKER_03]: and I've got like a few of them by now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They even did Street Fighter and King of Fighters themed ones and Sakura Taisen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I've got a few of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there any interest in getting this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Importing it maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: After all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's it for Japanese release.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I'm going to cover on Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is that like, you know, build a human type thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll find a link for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go over to Europe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um,
[SPEAKER_03]: Only one game is on the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 19th, Sensible World of Soccer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, coming out finally to the Xbox 360 Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I guess it's slowing down because it's Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: has got a few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as much as usual.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, a few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: MX vs. ATV Untamed coming out on PSP, PlayStation 2, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3 and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Elements of Destruction is coming out on DS and that game is kind of neat looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically you kind of play Mother Nature so you can cause tornadoes and fires and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is also coming to Xbox Live Arcade at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Warhammer 40,000 Squad Command on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dyson Ryaku Exceed coming to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 2 of Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game's coming out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atari Classics Evolved for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another one of those compilation sets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luxor 2 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Knights Journey of Dreams on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can get your Knights fix here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's applauding over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been getting my Knights fix already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you ask Santa for that for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm probably going to get it, but we've been playing Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then one other thing I was going to mention here real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a game, but I thought it's interesting anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: MadCatz is putting out an HDMI conversion kit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for all those people like me that do not have an Xbox 360 with HDMI out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It plugs into the back of your system and it allows you to do HDMI and optical out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's, although the only sting to it is it retails for $89.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo announced this week, you know, obviously they're having some issues staying on top of manufacturing enough Wii's for everybody out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is their contingency plan they announced this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reggie Fils-Aim came out this week and said, hey, we're joining up with GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to create this Wii Rain Check program.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: to be able to take these type of deposits for games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's at least the reason why they did it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only days, however, that you can do this, December 20th and 21st, are the only days that you are going to be able to do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, there are supposed to be tens of thousands of rain checks available, and who knows, that may still not be enough for the demand of the console, because it's the Furby of 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Cabbage Patch Kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the gift of this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I waited in line.
[SPEAKER_05]: for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: For my Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I made my roommate wait in line for mine and it worked.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, it just goes to show that sometimes, you know, waiting in line for...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, these things actually does pay off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, how would you feel if you were one of those kids?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's flash back.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I told the story earlier in the show about me as the spoiled brat when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's flash back to me as the spoiled brat as a kid who wanted a Nintendo Wii this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I open up my present to get one of these rain checks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I going to be a satisfied kid or am I going to cry?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: We couldn't get you one right now, but we will get you one by the end of January.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to say, here's a fucking rain check for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's just like, kids are like, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's the controller?
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's Mario?
[SPEAKER_04]: Santa hates me.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to go take the rain check and soak it with his tears is what he's going to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: In my family, when I was a kid, if there was something that I wanted and didn't get, I lived with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: or you get a job mowing lawns or selling lemonade and you save up and you buy the fucking thing yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or I stole it from my brother.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly what you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, the year you wanted your Super Nintendo and everything, my brothers went into Super Nintendo and my mom asked me, should I give them a Super Nintendo or a Genesis?
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to give them a Super Nintendo and you need to get these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: She got them a Super Scope, Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: She picked out Home Alone for some retarded reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Home Alone, Kevin McAllister's so cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so my brothers played like five seconds of Home Alone and then I beat Zelda that week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So did your brothers even play the Super Nintendo or was this your present?
[SPEAKER_05]: They played Home Alone and they're like, what did I do bad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, why am I being punished?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they actually, my brothers and I played a lot of Blastress and the mole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to get Jamie a copy of Home Alone on the Super Nintendo for Christmas and wrap it in coal and put it in her stocking.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: My little brothers are too busy running around being little terrorists in the neighborhood, so I have the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comments from chat, love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt says, Dear little Billy, I owe you a Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love, Santa.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tiger Claw.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if you lose the rain check?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't you be screwed?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you would be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you would because GameStop sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'd be like, oh, you don't have your receipt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Billy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You ain't ever getting a win.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to recall I didn't have my receipt once for a $5 pre-order and they still gave it to me because it was in the phone number in the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not only that, they actually keep a copy of your...
[SPEAKER_03]: I love this comment from Gerardimo.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mommy wrote me a note from Santa that said the elves couldn't find a copy of Hey You Pikachu because the store was sold out and I would get it eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, what's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma says, fuck rain checks, give me a gift card.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Ross Steel UT in response says, even that would be better than a fucking IOU.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, seriously, because, you know, this is why I love the concept of gift cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because, especially for me being picky as a kid...
[SPEAKER_03]: And again, you know, if I got something I didn't want, I always took it back to the store myself, returned it myself, and got what I wanted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I was just thinking something there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo's quite smart teaming up with GameStop, you know, with this whole rain check thing, because if for whatever reason Nintendo can't deliver those Wii's by the end of January, people are going to be fucking pissed off at GameStop, but no one's going to remember that it's Nintendo's fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to hear more about 10-year-old Jamie marching into the store and returning your gifts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's like, my family would buy me ugly clothes, so I... Okay, now it's just funny, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I would make them drop me off at the mall, and then I'd go do all my exchanges myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: And sometimes I'd get cash back and then go over to Babbage's, because we had Babbage's.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before, you know, before GameStop took them all over.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm not going to wear this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm taking it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: To get games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, shoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, you know, if they wouldn't, I would just, you know, get like a different pair of jeans or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's like, and it wasn't that I was, I am not, it wasn't that I was ungrateful or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or a sick bastard, as GS68 put it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't that I was ungrateful or anything, you know, because I was plenty grateful for the stuff that I got because, you know, when I was growing up, we didn't actually have a whole lot of money.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually, you know, when I was, you know, in first and second grade, we were actually poverty level.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I remember having, you know, icicles in my bathtub one winter, and I'm not even joking.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, now I think I'm really spoiled.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when I was a kid, I didn't have, you know, if I got something...
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, if it wasn't what I wanted, I found a way to turn it into what I wanted.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it was just a matter of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all these kids who say, Oh, but I want a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, tough shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are no Wiis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get a job, Billy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Santa didn't buy you a Wii because you don't have a job.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, but you see...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that there's just way too much of, oh, well, you know, I, and Dan is actually saying, and I'm not going to go into any detail on this, but this person is saying, oh, I spent all this money in your store and I'm entitled to a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we don't have any.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tough shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I think that people need to learn to be, I guess, to take no for an answer and find something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I can just imagine if Jamie had a kid, or maybe I would do this to my kid, and I wasn't able to get a Wii for my kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would leave a note under the tree for something like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is something like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Santa is very sorry that he could not get you a Wii this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has more important things to do, like ending genocide in Darfur.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: He doesn't do any of that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just delivers.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a fucking glorified UPS driver, is what he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but seriously, though...
[SPEAKER_04]: All these people that think they need special treatment stuff are finding Wiis and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get customers asking, you know, yeah, I have someone looking for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, you know, it's like two weeks before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the fuck are they just now looking for a Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why didn't they plan this out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they didn't know it was going to be so hard to find.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, tough shit for them!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should we cater to the fact that they're stupid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure we've got lots of holiday stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we'll get some of them in our mailbag later from our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not trying to be, you know, all kinds of
[SPEAKER_03]: ZenoCore in chat says, Dude, I would do that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, what's the latest news at Jamie's Gaming Outlet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, virtual console stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: For our friends in the UK, we have Pokemon Snap that was on the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Pokemon Snap is great and it's fun and lovely.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we have Top Hunter that was on Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I didn't really like Top Hunter all that much, so I'm not going to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the last one, which is almost as cool as Pokemon Snap, but cooler in its own respect, is Mega Man 2 from Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you don't know what Mega Man 2 is, you need to climb out of that cave you've been living in for the past 20 years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they have Mega Man 1 on Virtual Console over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is Mega Man 2 the first game they're getting?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Mega Man 2 is the first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, I want both!
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want Mega Man 3!
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one was great!
[SPEAKER_05]: It really was!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of the Cutman weapon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was different than all the others, but it was great, and it had some awesome music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of my favorite music ever from a video game was, like, a Lechman stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I really liked the Metal Blades, though, and Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I totally loved Mega Man 3, because you had to beat the game with the top, with, like, the most useless weapon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, Ross Steel UT has a good point, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I already have Mega Man Collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not just get the Mega Man collection and do the backwards compatibility with the GameCube disc?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: F the virtual console for Mega Man, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, F the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should I have to buy games again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you, Nintendo, and trying to get me to purchase stuff I've already purchased again.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, stupid Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing that we're going to be getting over here pretty soon, Dragon Quest Swords.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been announced to come to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: on February 26th.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a really fucking long name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Quest Swords, The Masked Queen, and The Tower of Mirrors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too long of a subtitle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not yet played the Japanese version of it, but you use the Wiimote to slash at slime, so that can't be that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't they have that same thing on the PlayStation 2, I seem to recall?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I remember going to some anime convention and in a back room they had a Dragon Quest game that had a giant sword and you'd slash slimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they had an arcade version of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did have an arcade version, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perhaps, but I guess this has taken a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't this supposed to be a launch game and we're just now getting it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: along with the whole Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the F-square?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the hell did your Wii games go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Crystal Chronicles, I want to say, was like June now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeez, that was supposed to be a launch game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, not June.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's spring, but it's only the DS version.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't announced the Wii version yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crystal Chronicles was kind of underrated.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really loved that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only problem with it is that, God, you had to have a lot of shit in order to be able to play that game, including four people.
[SPEAKER_05]: and four Game Boy Advances and four Link Kills and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, if you want a Wii to be playing the Dragon Quest game on, of course, we've been talking about that they're practically impossible to find.
[SPEAKER_05]: But one thing to keep in mind is that the Nintendo World Store in New York City in Rockefeller Center, they get more shipments of the Wii every morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, a reporter from Game Daily visited the store recently and observed that there were 20 Wiis lined up behind the main counter just waiting for whoever's in line.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's been going on is that more and more recently, WCBS Radio reported not that long ago that there were over 200 people camped out outside the store before the store even opened.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some folks are traveling all the way from Virginia to get a freaking Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well shit, that's a good way to do it if you know that they're going to get some in every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if you don't get it the first day, go see some sites, come back and camp later.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about like your day job?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, is it just me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting a Wii for Billy is more important.
[SPEAKER_05]: I digress, but never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, more Wii stuff is the game Castle Shikigami 3 will be coming out to Nintendo Wii next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a lot to do with dodging bullets.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's bullet hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for those fans of Ikaruga and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a very interesting shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also you collect coins while you play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder how that's going to control the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if it's going to be like Geometry Wars where you point at the screen where you want to shoot or if it's going to have that kind of functionality in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're probably thinking way too much into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll probably just have the controller turned sideways and playing it like a virtual console game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, I guess that'll work too, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because, I mean, a lot of these games don't use the motion controls and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be too hard, especially with, like, pinpoint stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, um, so, there's another game coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of interesting, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I laughed when I saw it because even though there's a game that's just like it that's already been announced, we don't know when that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game, though, however, is coming out, I want to say, in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: Wild Earth, African Safari
[SPEAKER_04]: How can you say that?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't know anything about Africa.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are similar in the regards they are both about Africa.
[SPEAKER_05]: Africa is a giant fucking place.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you are aware.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I will have you know that there's photography in this game much like Africa.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are animals just like Africa.
[SPEAKER_04]: They both take place in Africa.
[SPEAKER_04]: If anything else, I would say this is more authentic because they spelled Africa correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, Safari Photo Africa Wild Earth is a PC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it got released a while ago and took home some awards in the 2003 Independent Games Festival, including the coveted Seamus McNally Grand Prize.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck that's supposed to mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, this game takes place... You are a photojournalist exploring Africa's Serengeti National Park, tasked with taking photos of 30 different animals in their natural habitat.
[SPEAKER_04]: and apparently if you get close to the animals for the perfect shot or if you get too close the Wiimote will rumble making it harder to snap the picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Wii version will include co-op, multiplayer, one player to drive while the other two shoot photos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately we can't run over the animals with the
[SPEAKER_04]: The Jeep, at least I don't think you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only one I'm going to play in these games, is if I can run over the animals.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, what the hell's going on here?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're getting Africa on the PlayStation 3, this Safari game on the Wii, yet still no Jumbo Safari.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is wrong with this world?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, we have no Jumbo Safari, but we also have no Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all those games that came out around that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have...
[SPEAKER_03]: If Sega would give us a dedicated platform, a dedicated system, then we would have all this awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But no!
[SPEAKER_05]: OMG, Dreamcast 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish!
[SPEAKER_05]: Jumbo Safari packing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't Jumbo Safari kind of a gun game almost?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Harpoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Harpoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Harpoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harpoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee calls it Pokemon Snafrica.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only bad thing about this thing, and no offense to Majesco, but Majesco's putting it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, what was the last good game from Majesco that came out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one game that they put out in the Wii that I remember, and that was that... Oh, fuck, what was it called?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bust a Move Bash or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't really innovate that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: The screenshots don't show much detail.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably a reason for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the kiosks where you play the games on instead of there just being one there's a ton of them now they're opening one of these in San Jose and gosh part of me kind of wants to go down and check it out maybe do a report for the show because it's not that far and I go there a lot but anyhow apparently these places are going to have 24 networked gaming stations they're all going to have plasma display on it and they're supposed to be doing various competitions in these places most weekends are when they're supposed to be doing it they're going to kick it off with a Madden tournament
[SPEAKER_05]: and the winner of the Madden Tournament gets a $1,000 GameStop shopping spree which they could spend right there in the store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't see how this is going to make them any money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this like their idea of countering a LAN center?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they're going to be countering LAN centers, but one of their competition chains that's kind of up and coming, they're starting to do this more, Play and Trade.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I imagine they have to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pay like a $20, $30 entry fee, and if you get 50 people to enter it, there's your $1,000 prize right there, and anything additional is just extra money.
[SPEAKER_05]: And with a game like Madden that's so competitive... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be tough, though, because I know like those other places, they don't charge...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, for tournaments and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, plus, you get all those gamers in one place and then what are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to put out a table full of Madden merchandise out there for them to buy, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I can think of DDR tournaments I went to where Red Octane would come in and they would have a table because this was back before Red Octane was big for Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: They would come and they would sell dance pads and soundtracks and all the DDR crap there at the tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's how they made money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or at conventions, anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like selling t-shirts at a concert.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: So GS68, they've seen one at the San Tomas and Stevens Creek GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've shopped there before, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually right next to my grand princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only reason why is I know a lot of people that own land centers and they own places like this where they ran out of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hell, we knew it was Arena.
[SPEAKER_04]: They used to have something similar like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it will be.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we have any listeners in San Jose who happen to check this place out, let us know.
[SPEAKER_05]: If not, I'll try to make it a point to go by there in the near future.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there are some details released about Tomb Raider Underworld that's being developed by Crystal Dynamics.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be out next year on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: And is going to be... They were actually quoted in...
[SPEAKER_03]: Play Magazine is saying it was Pure Woman vs. Wild.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think there's way too many Tomb Raider games already.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I did think, though, that it's pretty cool that they have a new lighting model for what'll be going on in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the more technical side of it, so I would check it out just to at least look at something online to see how it turns out
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Tomb Raider is one of those series that just won't die.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is forced on to prove it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's another series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know if it's going to be a series, but maybe a game that should die.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Prince's Bride game, which doesn't look all that wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it looks like, to be honest, like a CDI game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, according to a new G4 interview, they've gotten some information direct from the developer's mouths.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, well, the game itself, the target demographic, I believe, was women for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said that they're not going to be using a lot of the voice actors.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually going to be sound-alikes for the voices.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, they're saying that the game's going to be out spring of 2008 on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you'd like, you can pre-order it at the official site, princessbridegame.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, the game doesn't look that good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked at that picture, it does look like a CDI game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they'd have to use, you know, soundalikes anyway, at least for some of them, because, you know, Andre the Giant's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should make him talk anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Splice clips together, like that one show after Chef left the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to debut a brand new segment on tonight's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can't say this is necessarily going to be a weekly segment, but it is going to be a segment that we're going to do on the show whenever something makes us feel like we need to do this segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a new advice column or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it is something we call here at Orange Lounge Radio the Stupid Award.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, whenever we here at Orange Lounge Radio feel like somebody has done something extraordinarily stupid this week in the gaming industry, we're going to award them with the OLR Stupid Award.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this week, the Stupid Award goes to this kid, and I'm probably going to mispronounce his name, but that's okay, he's stupid, Alyusha.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did he do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he went on to Xbox Live and he was playing Call of Duty 4 and he sent messages to kids on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was playing Call of Duty 4 and he told them that he was going to shoot up his school and tell everybody on there how he was going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, sure enough, a Call of Duty 4 player from Oregon went to the police department and Microsoft ended up letting out the IP who tracked down this guy and arrested him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the kid later admitted that the whole thing was just a joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: He had no intention of actually going through with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were no guns to be found or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, why would you say this kind of crap on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially in this day and age, in the world we live in.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, congratulations, Alyusha, winner of the inaugural OLR Stupid Award!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of the gene pool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get a little bleach in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to a segment that we've done for a while now, and it's a well-loved segment here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is the classic game of the week, and every week DarkSakura picks a favorite classic game of hers, and we basically pay tribute to our elders and respect them a little bit through our classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So DarkSakura, tell us about what game you picked out for us this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game of the week is the X-Men arcade game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old one you could find either one screen or two screens.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do believe that the differences were a four player and a six player.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played the hell out of this game when I was in 10th grade.
[SPEAKER_03]: My arcade actually had the two screen setup.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you used to play a whole craplet of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was put out by Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's the final fight style game, you know, the side-scrolling beat-crap-up game, you know, or like the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles games, even though a lot of these floating around that time.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you could play as Cyclops, Colossus, Wolverine, Storm, Nightcrawler, or Gavler, and I actually use Gavler almost all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you beat up the world's shortest Sentinels, because they're really supposed to be massive, but they were, like, little.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it had the most, I swear, this would have all been candidates for English.com, the things that they would say in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I didn't realize this for quite a while, but the version that I played at one of the, not my main arcade, but the second arcade was actually a Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they would drop extra power-ups that would refill the power meter, and apparently the German one did not.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was like, this is hard!
[SPEAKER_03]: It was too easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, but it was full of crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it was a really fun game, and I wish that there had been, um, you know, a home release list without me having to bust out the maze.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, some comments from chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw wants to remind us this was also the only X-Men game released by Konami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hence why it feels so much like Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's what I was saying, that it was in that type.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Actdeft sounds like he has the best arcade ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, my arcade used to have this, TMNT Arcade, and Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Turtles in Time was freaking great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this was my game before Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, Dillinger would like to share that the Simpsons arcade game was better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Simpsons did it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually really liked this one a whole lot better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so there it is, your classic game of the week, X-Men, as done by the arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm just pausing our little YouTube-age of the game here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bonus, you are granted a special mutant power.
[SPEAKER_05]: Note that mutant power can be used only when the energy indicator is at three or less.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that like now a second mutation?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone who reads the comics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that's going to bring this part A of our program to a close.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a quick break and we will be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.