[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, December 2nd, 2007, the Wii gets DS demo downloads, Sony swaps out their ad agency, and Dimix comes to Xbox in the next update.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you out there who have recently turned to independent radio this week in light of recent events, a warm welcome from all of us here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We are joined tonight by the lovely Rice Princess filling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not just the Rob and Loki show, because otherwise... It'd be pretty fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be pretty fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: You put two nerds together and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we brought in a third nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hello, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then it becomes great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, three nerds makes it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there was a sitcom, wasn't there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, three nerds, three mics in a pizza place?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate that the cam is down this week, and I'll talk more about that later, because Irene has the greatest nerdy shirt in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this something you got from Hot Gothic?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's a Metroid shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically the box art from Metroid.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what does it say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you defeat the Mother Brain?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or no, beat the Mother Brain.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beat the Mother Brain.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you bought me a shirt too from Hot Topic, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love presents.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to open it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't actually opened it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm opening it here live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really sucks that the cam's down this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but it's not gaming related at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not gaming related at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shit, I didn't take the tag off.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll pretend I didn't see the tag.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you should do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my God, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, that's awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Pee Wee Herman shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cherry.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you should turn it over to the front, because that's the back, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Pee Wee's Playhouse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking at the back that had PeeWee on Cherry.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're like, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love you, PeeWee.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is so exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love PeeWee's Playhouse.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm glad you do.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because otherwise I'd be a pretty shitty present.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise it's like, here's a shirt of a show you don't like.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just thought you needed new clothes, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will definitely wear that next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully the cam's back next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: What happened to the cam, BTW?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll talk more about that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's start it off with how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play as much as I thought I would be playing this week, but mainly my week was filled with Phantom Hourglass And it's fun, it's a normal Zelda game, don't really know what more you'd want Sorry, can I interject here for a minute?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at our chat room, which I neglected to introduce, sorry chat
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com We love the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: They always crack us up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know how just a little bit ago I was saying, what, three nerds, a mic, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Janai comments, where's the cup?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Delayed reaction.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, totally didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were the one that kept, like, asking me, like, all week long, have you seen the two girls, one cup thing yet?
[SPEAKER_01]: I did not ask you.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's perverted and gross.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so yeah, I've been playing Phantom Hourglass and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried the Wii version of the Golden Compass because Nelly wanted me to demonstrate the game for her since she's really into Golden Compass and that's who I got the game for.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess it's based off a video game, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_03]: As if, you know, a wolf versus a polar bear was gonna win in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: This bear is fucking tricked out with armor.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no fucking way it's gonna win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but like, look at Final Fantasy XI, where like, you could fight a bunny, and the bunny rapes you for 500 points of damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's... sometimes video games don't make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I haven't fought any bunnies yet, but as far as the wolves go, I get the crap out of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, you make the Golden Compass sound pretty awesome when you're talking about polar bears and sets of armor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, you don't even know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't read the book or seen the movie yet, but apparently the characters in this story have their souls outside of their body as an animal, and the animal, like, talks in the same voice as the girl in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's confusing because it sounds like the girl's having conversations with herself, and it's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I did play Super Mario Galaxy, though, because I was sick this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did you think of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm still playing it, and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very, very, very much like Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, same kind of setup.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, you know, no red coins.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is pretty much it, I think, from Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's so funny about Saints Row?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, just like you're playing Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still playing some of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We went and tried to beat the second to last level on Inferno, and that's like getting raped by thousands of ants at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not very fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, My Gaming Week...
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't play a whole lot of new stuff unfortunately I've just been very busy I've been watching my roommate play a hell of a lot of Puzzle Quest though on Xbox Live Arcade which is kind of funny because he doesn't get into a lot of video games but when he does he definitely puts he's committed so he's been very committed to Puzzle Quest he's already at level 20 he's gotten way further in the game than I have that's kind of funny yeah so he's enjoying that and other than that I've just been playing the regular World of Warcraft and Final Fantasy XI you know because I just love my MMOs
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went online with Rock Band this week, and I gotta say, I'm just pissed off that you can't do band co-op mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, why did they leave that out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you can do band competitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not even really competitive, but you can do the one song stuff online, like one song at a time, but you can't do the world tour mode online, which seems kind of stupid, because it's not like
[SPEAKER_04]: The Game's Unable to let four people play online at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of like one of the reasons I was excited about Rock Band is I kind of thought you were going to be able to make these bands together with people from far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, Shane, who hasn't been on the show in a long time because he lives in Kansas, also bought the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was thinking, oh, we could have a band and we'd play together.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we do have a band already.
[SPEAKER_04]: A rock band, not a real band where, you know, I play kazoo and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just pissed that co-op mode was kind of missing in that regard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, they did have a David Bowie pack come out this week, and that was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because David Bowie is very awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: He is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like a cover of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a lot else of note.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a lot of new games this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I did play Undertow, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, just not my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't feeling it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to... It was hard to... I mean, it wasn't hard to figure it out or figure the game out, but I thought the tutorial could have been a little better because there were so many different little features in this strategy game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot to mention it last week, and it hasn't really been on any of the websites yet, but they released the Pay the Unlock content for Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or not We Love Katamari, Beautiful Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I bought that, and then afterwards I'm like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did I buy that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did you buy that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an impulse buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought one of those $20 cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1600 point cards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I didn't buy it per se.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got crap that I didn't want and I traded it for a free card.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I can thank a PS3 copy of Assassin's Creed that bought me Rock Band songs and beautiful Katamari download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, Sephiroth1215 on our chatroom says, Rock Band World Tour wouldn't work online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, yeah, you can't hear, I mean, I see Black Lab talking about the vocals in the game, how you don't actually hear the people singing, although you kind of do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you play, but you can have a full band in the, um, play one song at a time mode co-op.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what it is, just quick play or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, you can have a guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually signed on Xbox Live and got a random band thrown together where some guy was on vocals, I was on guitar, somebody else was on bass, and somebody else was on drums.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we could hear the vocalist singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a little bit faint and very, very lagged because it was transmitting through his headset or whatever while he was, you know, singing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but the game itself doesn't support that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it plays the normal backtrack because of the lag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do the vocal parts without people hearing you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, if you just turn your headset off, you can do it without people hearing you.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't hear you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki has a secret desire to sing a little more often, doesn't he?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a secret desire to get achievement points.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, have you been playing anything this week at all?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just WoW, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's WoW been going for you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because, I don't know, WoW's been kind of boring for the past couple months, but now it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because our guild's too small.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we have, like, no tanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't run instances together.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have no tanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of what I think brought me back to playing is that, like, I don't know, some people were running me through instances, and I ran people through instances, and, like, we have a guild bank now, and I'm totally into that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Guild banks are awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, I don't know, it just became fun again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, let's get into some housekeeping tonight, and then we'll get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, DarkSakura is not here tonight, but she will be back next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and I used the Zapper and we played Link's Crossbow Training.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the funny thing that happened is that in the practice round that we played, I fucking wasted Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, my score was ten times his score.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I just obliterated him.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was a practice round.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then when we did it for reals, Loki beat me by a thousand points.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Loki won the Great Zapper Challenge, proving that the Zapper does nothing to enhance the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, you playing the Zapper, it was crap, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say the experience was any better.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the crossbow training game was kind of fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be devil's advocate and a little bit fair here, from what I hear, Ghost Squad, it's really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason why is because they have a good calibration system on it where you aim down the zapper at one corner of the screen, aim down the zapper at the other corner of the screen, and then spot on after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know why every game for the Wii doesn't have something like that in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really shouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be fucking a default thing to have in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, so if they add something like that to all the games, they'll be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one good thing that Ghost Squad has going for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hopefully they'll have the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I assume they'll have the same thing in House of the Dead 2 and 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, I mean, the whole thing is only, what, $25 for the Zapper and Crossbow Training?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's technically $20, but GameStop is ripping everyone off by $5.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're overcharging over retail for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so the Wii Mode itself and Link's Crossbow Training is only $20?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, the Wii Zapper and the Link's Crossbow Training is only $20 retail.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not bad, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_04]: That really isn't a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, the game is probably worth a little more money than... And the game is short.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's something you're going to beat pretty quickly, but I think it's... You know, it's a...
[SPEAKER_04]: We Sports-ish kind of thing where the game doesn't have a lot of depth, but you're going to have a lot of people that want to just kind of pick it up and play it and have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's not like the game was that difficult to figure out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that sucks that Loki won the bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no date for me and Loki gets... Is the wife going to let me take her out or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to talk about that this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can have your night of peace.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, I was going to say for next week, because I have a whole bunch of games on queue to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: A bunch of import stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Quest Swords for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Harvest Moon for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why the fuck am I going to play Harvest Moon?
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking hate Harvest Moon, but I'm going to try it anyways on the Wii for the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Devil Kings 2 for the Wii, which I hear is really fucking good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to try that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then DDR Haas Party for the Wii, the Japanese version, because they have a few different songs that I want to try out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm going to do the All Controller Controller Revolution because it does support the classic controller to do that, which I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll do it that way because I don't want to buy a dance bed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I'm trying to think what else I had.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cruisin', probably one of the worst racing games out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: by, you know, screenshots at least, so I'm going to play it to see how crappy it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then another game that I know is going to be even worse, which is Offroad Extreme Special Edition, is what it's called, and it's another piece of shit that's coming out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll play them so you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: Crappy games can be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I saw today they have the box shots for the Simple Series 3 and 4 coming out for the Wii in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Simple Series 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm also going to be playing Mita de Kart Race, another kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of stuff for next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: When do we get the WiiWare?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that ever going to come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was supposed to come out this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and when I get paid this week, I'm going to import Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_03]: WeFit
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Janai talking about the Wii says, I noticed that Nintendo released a game on Virtual Console that Compile made, so maybe it's possible for Nintendo to release The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I only hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those who have been listening to Orange Lounge Radio for any length of time know that we have a very soft spot in our hearts for the 8-bit classic The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the day that comes out on the Wii, I'm calling in sick to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Odd1 says, the damn system will tell you six ways from Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't kill people with your Wiimote and go out once in a while, you fat fuck, on every game, but they don't think to help us calibrate the things to play the game better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that new warning screen they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: That thing looks like a fucking condom on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the ugliest thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm playing fucking dangerously, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't use the wrist strap, and even if I did, I have the original wrist strap.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, oh, Dillinger's been playing a game I really want to play, Trauma Center New Blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to go out and get that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yes you do, so I can take it from you and play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: My game!
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't take my game!
[SPEAKER_01]: No, yeah, I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to borrow something else on Wii, like Metroid or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not fucking Metroid.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're sure it says Metroid on it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It says old school Metroid, dammit!
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to play no damn 3D Metroid, that blasphemous piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Metroid's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: AZHP says Trauma Center New Blood is the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's okay that you said that, but I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's it for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have a lot else to add, so let's get into some... Oh, actually, one quick thing is that there's like a 90% chance next week, I know I've been saying this for a while now,
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll finally be out in the actual studio for those keeping track.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been in our temporary studio, quote unquote, for like the past three months.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm hoping next week, just due to some things that are going around in the personal life, we're going to try and get out there next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very excited about it, which is why I really want the cam to come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if Op 11 is not back next week, we're probably going to look into either Justin TV or Ustream.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really haven't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thought about what else is a good service.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I kind of liked how Op 11 had the episodic stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyhow, let's get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, the thing that everybody's been talking about this week is a certain GameStop editor was rumored to have been fired for a negative review over Kane and Lynch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, the person responsible for this... God, I can't remember his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just have his last name up here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_03]: and I don't even know how to pronounce that, Gerstmann, I guess?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say it was like a... It was Jeff, I think it was his first name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeff Gerstmann, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so the rumor is, because no one's coming out to say otherwise, the rumor is because of his negative review on Kane and Lynch, Eidos threatened to pull the ad support, because they have the whole fucking site skinned like Kane and Lynch, and because of that, since the ads pay their salaries, basically,
[SPEAKER_03]: Rather than lose them as an ad supporter, they fired him instead.
[SPEAKER_03]: And everybody is just up in arms because now people have finally figured out, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe contributions from publishers and stuff affect scores of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: You think?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, welcome to the real world, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so yeah, tons of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: This guy is... Okay, I'll lie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've totally known about this guy and followed his career for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a good lie?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here's the truth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no idea who the hell this guy was until I read this article on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, he's been some respected game journalist for the past 10 years, but honestly, I don't read a lot of corporate sites, so I don't... There's a lot of independent blogs I read, and maybe some of them are somewhat corporate, because I read Joystick, they're AOL...
[SPEAKER_04]: Kotaku is whatever but I don't really read a lot of the big box sites very often I used to read one up maybe like three years ago I don't really read them a lot anymore either so I had no idea who the hell this guy was nevertheless I can't help but think so I'm trying to look at this like objectively as possible because I can't help but think and this may not be the popular opinion but I actually think there's a bit of mob mentality going on here I don't I think that the gaming scene is jumping to like a lot of conclusions with this stuff when
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of people that really can't talk about what's going on in this situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think there's been quite a bit of jumping to conclusions and things that have probably gotten blown out of proportions.
[SPEAKER_04]: The interesting thing about it, I mean, honestly, these companies involved are kind of screwed because of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of alarming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if anything, from this, what we're learning is that the video game scene can be very sensationalist sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't the first time this stuff's happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, people give him crap anyways because he had that non-10 review on Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen, if I were to review Twilight Princess, it wouldn't fucking get a 10, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, that game is not God's gift to fucking gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, it's just a fucking Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like Phantom Hourglass is a fucking Zelda game, they're good, but they're never great, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I digress, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody's allowed to have their own opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, you know, everybody was fucking, like, giving Zelda a fucking blowjob or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is goddamn just a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it kind of deserved at least a handjob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it was a really good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, absolutely, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was not that great of a game, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wind Waker is a better game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whoa, that's crossing the line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whoa, wow, yeah, no, you did not just go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back on topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, does anyone remember Driver 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: How the whole story came out that Atari was paying for good reviews on that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this isn't the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't the last time this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's happened hundreds of times between those.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just people are finally figuring it out that this is going on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, people don't really know why this guy was let go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just hypothetically, the company, and again, I don't know shit about what's going on in this situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to pretend like I know what's going on in this situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just know what I'm reading out there on the internet, what people are saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hypothetically, in the corporate world, they could have fired this guy because he was late to work too many times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, well, does it confirm that he was fired?
[SPEAKER_01]: He did not quit?
[SPEAKER_04]: He was basically locked out of his office.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, that's all talk, but you feel like there is some validity to that because obviously employees of the company are stepping forward anonymously and saying these things.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'd been at the company for like 10 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyhow, you know, I've seen people in the corporate world work at a company for like 10, 15 years and get fired over a really bad thing or whatever goes on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: This guy could have been like late to work for an entire month or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, I'm being very hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the company could fire him, but the company can't say why they fired him.
[SPEAKER_04]: and if he gets fired over something like that, is he going to say, oh yeah, they fired me because I was late to work too many times?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is he going to let people draw their own conclusions?
[SPEAKER_03]: He probably also can't... Well, I'm not even really saying that... I think he can't actually say why he was fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he has to sign something when he's leaving.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is why, you know, you're not allowed to say... Okay, so he has to sign something or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably actually something he signed when he was... Confidentiality agreements he signed when he...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sign this.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't tell anyone why you're fired if we fire you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted to change wording in the review to make it more accurate as to whatever the changes were between the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 were.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he didn't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he got let go for being somewhat of a difficult person on this and other issues in the past.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that, you know, because the wording got changed, the internet changed that into, you know, the great game of internet telephone, blah blah
[SPEAKER_04]: That got changed into, oh my gosh, he refused to change the article to give it a good score, so Eidos made them fire him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so why didn't they just not publish the review?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why didn't they just say, hey, okay, well, this is not in line with what we're looking for?
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not going to publish it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I know he could just as easily go to his own personal blog and post it or whatever, but that's his own personal blog.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't have jurisdiction.
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is, though, is they use a lot of these reviews as advertising for their game as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's why you see on boxes, you know, GameSpot gave it a 5 out of 5 or 10 out of 10 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, they use that shit in the fucking commercials.
[SPEAKER_03]: They use it in, you know, their press advertisements and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a big deal for them if...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're paying GameSpot a million dollars for advertising or something like that and then all of a sudden they get a shitty ass review out of it and it causes people not to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going to incentivize them to give them more money when they can give it to some other site that's going to give it a more favorable review?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but if they don't publish it...
[SPEAKER_01]: From that particular journalist, can't they just get one of their other journalists to publish a positive review?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but then it's going to come out that this guy had wrote a review on it, and then all of a sudden, oh, wait a second, they didn't print it because this one's more favorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would come out one way or another.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just think that's a little far to be going, like, oh, we're going to fire you because you gave a bad review.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also because they have deadlines when these reviews need to get out there, and they may not have time to
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Raven's Dolphin says, I heard he got fired of the video review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe, but again, this is all hearsay.
[SPEAKER_04]: GZDr4ev says, people canceled their GameSpot accounts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, people are leaving the site in mass over this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, I partially blame mob mentality for why that's happening because people don't really know what's going on yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But people are making up stories that sure seem to make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee says, but if the game sucks, then the players will get the truth out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I think just goes to show the lesson learned here.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you are getting all your gaming news and reviews from one person on one corporate gaming site, you might need to take off the blinders.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're looking for accurate reviews on stuff, don't rely on one website.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go to websites like Metacritic.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got a compilation of scores from all sorts of sites and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that'll give you a good baseline of what the game is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also you can read each review and see what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did Metacritic pay you money for that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: For that endorsement?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just happened to use that site because it compiles reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: FIRED!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get paid for shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you're right about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The truth be told, we actually, because at work we sell Kane and Lynch and stuff, and Kane and Lynch is one of those titles that was kind of a what we call select title.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a title we push because we're getting paid money to push the title a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing is, though, Eidos set our goal so high it was impossible to hit anyways, so that it wouldn't have to pay out any money to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, because the people that make these deals are fucking retarded or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_03]: IDOS was really pushing to make this game big.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing it in little ways I probably wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're advertising and marketing people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little creative ways like teaming up with Playboy, for example, to do that model search.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had interviews with the fake characters in the game in Playboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did reach out to the independent media.
[SPEAKER_04]: They flew a bunch of them out there to San Francisco to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We weren't invited, and we could just drive there, but that's okay, we're not bitter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, sure, you know, because we drive there, you know, that's why they don't invite us or stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, you know, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: But I also think there's definitely a certain type of audience I think this show caters to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, I think we have people from all walks of gaming that listen to this program, but I think people know that we are mostly the one you want to hear for the music, the RPGs.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a certain niche that Kane and Lynch doesn't fit into, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying Kane and Lynch is a bad game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It probably could have been a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played it either, but just from what I've ever been reading and the way it looks...
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, this game's kind of fallen into the same problem that Blacksite Area 51 and some of these other games have gotten in.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're rushed to make it out for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this year, I think also next year, you're going to see a lot of these games that are going to be spread out throughout the year instead of all in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that might help some of these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because like Army of Two, for example, that one was going to be released in...
[SPEAKER_03]: November as well, along with Kane Lynch and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it wasn't done yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so instead of releasing it, they're putting more time into polishing it and making sure that it's a good game before they release it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so now it's coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It missed the holiday thing, but it's going to be a better game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same with Grand Theft Auto 4, Metal Gear Solid 4, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take the extra time and make the game good, and then that way you will get a better score for it instead of rushing this piece of shit out and then having to be broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the other thing that kind of makes me think there's more than meets the eye with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is a 6 out of 10 a bad review?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I realize the way the scale has been kind of skewed over the years by many people, I guess yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I always thought a 5 was average, like right in the middle, you're average.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a 5 is average.
[SPEAKER_04]: So technically a score of 6 is a slightly above average game, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it wouldn't be that bad if it were in a month that was a bit slower with games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is November where you have 60 billion releases coming out and a sixth game may not be played by as many people as say... But here's what you need to do, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're unsure if the game's going to be good... I'm also just trying to take a jab at the fact that most games in this day and age are rated on a scale of 5 to 10, not a scale of 1 to 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: 7 to 10.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but seriously, though, if you're unsure the game's going to be good, rent it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: rent it from Gamefly, rent it from your local Blockbuster, Hollywood, whoever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rent it and see if it's any good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadowslyer wants to give insight on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, on the GameSpot scale, a 6.0 is fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair is not a bad word.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a good word either.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a fair word.
[SPEAKER_04]: There really is no better description.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, I don't even really like scale-based reviews in the first place, because then you just put all your trust, you're like, having them make the decision for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like Loki said, just rent the game if you're so unsure about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if it catches your eye in the first place, read the review, then go rent it, but if not, then I wouldn't even worry about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, god, it's not like this was reviewed by a panel of, like, scientists or something like that, you know, where they had, you know, thousands of people playing this game, and this is the score they came up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one dude, whether he likes the game or not, he may just hate Eidos or something, they may have rubbed him the wrong way before, and now he's embittered, and now it's a six or something, because they fucking pissed him off, or like, you know, if I reviewed Madden or something like that, I don't like fucking football games, one, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's the kind of
[SPEAKER_03]: You're supposed to be unbiased when you're playing this stuff, but, you know, it's... I'm actually kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about the fact that, you know, after all this, the competitors down the street at 1UP did this little protest or something on their lunch, this whole, like, kind of, you know, having the signs, Free Jeff, and whatever all that stuff was.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I certainly have an opinion on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Praise us for doing some good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, other people, if they noticed it or something like that and posted it in their fucking Flickr blogs, then it would be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the fact that they're promoting themselves, look at what we did.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're going to get some angry emails this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeHunter.com Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the motivation is, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to pretend to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do think it was a little premature because, again, I find that a little strange that they would jump in on that mob mentality when none of us truly know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shouldn't they have waited until more news came out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, these guys do represent a corporation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's my only, like, I don't know if that was smart type of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, so it was a bunch of employees from 1UP?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that the reviewers and critics over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Zip Davis or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you can't control what somebody, that's right, they can do whatever the hell they want.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing though, what were they protesting?
[SPEAKER_03]: That they support independent reviews or unbiased reviews or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: So what they're basically saying is that they support that so that
[SPEAKER_03]: OneUp has unbiased reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the impression that you're supposed to get from that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just fucking advertising for themselves is all it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sorry, I don't see it as very genuine at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I see that is is, hey, some manager came up with an idea to have them go out during their lunch break and fucking protest in front of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't believe this shit that they're such a tight-knit group or whatever that they would do that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The few times we have been to these media events and things like that,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always the same fucking people.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think in some regard they are somewhat of a family.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's say that they're a tight-knit group.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I fucking got fired, say that we were corporate or whatever, and I got fired because I wrote a bad review on Kane and Lynch, would fucking one-up be on my lawn protesting for that shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they would be there twiddling their thumbs in their office going, those fuckers that like DDR serves them right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously, that's the shit that would happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not fucking advertising or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just... I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw that and I'm like, oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I read it on every single blog.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, good one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going there less now because of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Going there less now.
[SPEAKER_01]: 25% less because of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, let's see their... I bet you that fucking protest shit's in their goddamn EGM, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much you want to bet that shit is?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, they're so independent and awesome and unbiased.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's put it in our magazine, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look how holy we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I just realized I have Tuesday off work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I should go down there with a sign that says, Thank you for firing him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those fuckers who like DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have better things to do on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm going to see the Spice Girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have much better things to do on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's just, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, the fact of the matter is, okay, we don't know why he was fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: We assume it's because of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this is going on in the industry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big whoop.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, other things go on in the industry, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I don't know, certain media outlets getting to break street on certain news stories and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or no such embargo for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, they...
[SPEAKER_03]: Make a lot of money in advertising, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that kind of stuff happens as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a whole lot of shit you don't see that happens behind the scene day to day, but we all deal with it, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Things aren't going to change, so get over it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And really, in a month, who's going to be fucking talking about this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's going to give a shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want genuine reviews, ask someone that's actually played a damn game, your friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Irene, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do think there is going to be some type of long-lasting effect this whole thing has.
[SPEAKER_04]: because I think people are going to, I think companies are going to watch what happens to the whole rah, rah, rah, my mentality, we hate you GameSpot type thing that goes on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think there's going to be a lot of, you're going to see, I think the big sites post about their integrity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I think you're going to see the competitors like 1UP and IGM make things about their integrity and their reviews and their corporate policies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's refer it back to an old situation that concerned, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: and mishandling or mistreatment of employees at a gaming establishment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, look at, what was it, the EA spouse?
[SPEAKER_01]: How long did we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the EA spouse that was like, oh, my husband's working too long or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lasted about a month.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they raised issues of like, you know, oh, you know, look at them, they're evil and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But people still go and work for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: People still buy their games.
[SPEAKER_01]: No one's really like,
[SPEAKER_01]: EA did not go under as a company.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, no one gives a shit anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they put a hit on her?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because nobody talks about it anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: How the fuck do I know?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think I remember seeing... No, I'm just teasing, obviously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I remember seeing a story like a year ago, like she was unmasked.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we found out who she really was and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll start writing reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the companies can start paying me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I need money.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if I had the free time, I'd write reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't have the fucking free time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then I have a wife that I want to go home and a cat that wants me to play with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, I have to do these things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want me to put a head out on your cat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe my wife.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, that was mean.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was that Freudian or was that intentional?
[SPEAKER_04]: Views and opinions expressed on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room's been lighting up and I've been ignoring them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Odd1 says, I don't know, did I already read this one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the developers give the gaming press more credit than they're worth, especially in the face of the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: The word gets out, we have our ears to the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can get exclusive news from the corporate sites, but the message boards, podcasts, and indie sites are where it's at.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Eidos was stupid enough to push this, seriously, I'd love to see them burn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling, actually, I have kind of a strange feeling that
[SPEAKER_04]: IDOS has nothing to do with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think maybe they were like, they were probably a little pissed, and they probably let GameSpot know that, but, you know, they also probably kind of realized that there wasn't a lot they could do about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling if anybody's probably getting a bad rap over this, it's actually probably them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of what my gut tells me about this whole mom mentality thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't think they had much to do with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they can directly, say, fire this person.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it was EA, maybe, you know, maybe, but, I mean, we're talking IDOS here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what, Tomb Raider, Hitman?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo says, Dear world, go get your own opinion and decide if the game is good or not yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Macman says, I like the idea from all games interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sound effect reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this game is audience laughter out of Mario Jump.
[SPEAKER_01]: Brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw in response to the 1UP protest says, Maybe it's a sign that 1UP would like Gertzman to work for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Odd1 says, Ziff is all about the publicity.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're good with Flickr and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised they videotape almost everything they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't see Eidos pressuring them to fire this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, EA or something, like if they gave Madden a really shitty score or something like that, because they're a big company and have a lot of money to throw around, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: IDOS, I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Would they have come out recently?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomb Raider Anniversary Edition?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... Alright, well, we've spent a lot of time talking about this topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to move on to some other news, but I'm sure we'll hear a lot about this on the Skype line later.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, there always is our mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, more news, and let's talk about the virtual console on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start off with some Wii news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is great news.
[SPEAKER_04]: This makes me think Nintendo finally gets it, what we really want, in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon Snap is coming out on the Wii's virtual console in Japan, and usually this would be no big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, the pictures that you take inside the game, you can now post to your Wii message board and send around on the address book.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you've taken a picture of Pikachu doing a little dance or something, and you think it's really cute, I could send that over to
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you won't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll just delete it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'll defriend you, if that's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I think a lot of us have been shouting from the mountaintops for years, well, at least years, since the Wii came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to see additional functionality in the virtual console games, like online play and things like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the fact that they've done this for Pokemon Snap shows that it's possible, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why did they have to do it with Pokemon Snap?
[SPEAKER_01]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why couldn't they pick a better game to do it with?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, nobody gives a shit about taking pictures of stupid Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I love Pokemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Odd1 says, Message board posts of Pokemon in near sexual positions up 500%.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon Snap has now become Pokemon Slash.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, they're making a lot of money off of Pokemon Snap and other virtual console titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo estimates that they've made $33 million on the Virtual Console alone, and that kind of includes 7.8 million downloads across the service.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's free money, essentially.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can't imagine the Virtual Console takes that much work.
[SPEAKER_03]: All that bandwidth!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's not just that, but obviously, you know, they kind of have rewritten all the manuals in the Wii, because, you know, the Wii thing has their own manuals and stuff, and I'm sure they still have to do QA on all the games and what have you, so it's not like they do it completely free, but it's certainly much cheaper than making a new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this is very, probably very high cost efficiency type thing, cost gains, whatever they call that in the business world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, they sell each one of those consoles at, you know, profit, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, speaking of the Virtual Console, some more titles coming out have been spoiled by the one and only ESRB.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can expect in the near future Top Hunter for the Neo Geo, Puyo Puyo 2 for the Genesis, King of Fighters 94 on the Neo Geo, Baseball Stars 2, Bases Loaded on the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Dynastic Hero on the TurboGrafx-16 and Power Golf on the Neo Geo as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: All must be making their way sometime in the near future.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also just wanted to say really quickly that it's also been spoiled that on the Japanese Virtual Console they'll be getting Treasure Hunter G, which is a game I vaguely remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why aren't they releasing better titles?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Treasure Hunter G was actually a pretty awesome RPG 16-bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of reminisced in a Final Fantasy 6 a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it looks pretty cool, but I mean, the other games, like fucking Power Golf, who the hell played that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Bases Loaded, whatever, that's an okay game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bases Loaded was kind of cool, but Baseball Stars was better.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't play any baseball games on the NES because I don't care about sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually I'm not into sports games either, but I liked, here's the thing, I liked sports games a lot when they were simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I loved NBA Jam so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that game was relatively, I mean, that game was kind of made for, you know, dummies who can't really play basketball but enjoy to watch it, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I liked NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gameplay footage, interviews, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: BoxArt, release schedules for the DS and the Wii, and other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hopefully soon, demos for Wii games as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: But right now they've got some different Touch Generation title demos, and of course the Japanese versions of Pokemon Diamond and Pearl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this seems like a very natural thing that Nintendo probably should have had a while ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any word on when we might get this in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck if I know, but this is something they were promising, what, before the Wii ever came out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: WeConnect24, come on!
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, you might be looking... No, I don't, because I have Wii Connect 24 turned off.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're looking at your Wii at 5 o'clock at night, and you see the weather from midnight that morning, but... Wii Connect 24 doesn't like my mod chip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wows.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Macman says, Everybody's Nintendo channel in America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Nintendo, kill the chibi motherfucking robo team and get to work on it!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an order from Macman in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, stop making chibi robo games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just knock it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not saying fire those guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just put them to work elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying fire those guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, you might have heard earlier in the show I mentioned that I was a fan of the game Eternal Sonata that came out a little earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: TriCrescendo was the folks that made this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're now working on a new game called Fragile.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a new RPG that's going to be coming out for the Nintendo Wii, which is a system that Eternal Sonata was not on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on 360 and going to be coming on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: but Fragile is going to be coming out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we know so far is that the main character is a guy named Set and you explore various cities.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes place in a post-apocalyptic world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of the details at this time are in Japanese but there is an official website up at fragile.nomco-ch.net and there's also a little teaser trailer out there on the internet for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure a lot of people are kind of excited about this because, you know, obviously the first generation of Wii games felt like ported PlayStation 2 games with motion control.
[SPEAKER_04]: So these type of game announcements get people excited for what the Wii can really do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that reminds me, there's another game that's going to be coming out here, Opuna, that came out in Japan, I believe, and it's coming out over here in like February, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to check out the Japanese version next week, hopefully, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I don't really know how much I'm going to be able to play of those games Especially roleplaying games because they're all in Japanese And I speak no Japanese Or at least very little Japanese Anyways, the Nintendo DS in the UK has set some new sales records They have sold 191,000 units in the UK And that's more than any other hardware format has achieved in a 7 day period So that's a pretty good week for them I guess
[SPEAKER_03]: The previous record was held by the PSP during its launch in September of 2005, where it sold 185,000 units.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about we start looking at some release dates?
[SPEAKER_04]: Travel the world and look at games that you can pick up in the UK right now, if you think another game should be selling a lot of units.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, first, before we get into release dates, one thing we promised a few weeks ago on the show is that we would be tracking sales numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: because we have ways of getting the MPD sales numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And obviously one game you guys want to know the sales on is Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's because of the bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you recall, a bet was made on this program that Eye of Judgment, as Loki said, would no way in hell sell a million copies within six months of release.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, if the game manages to sell one million copies in six months within its release, Loki has said he will dress up in a Tingle outfit and dance around
[SPEAKER_04]: in the garage, setting an eye of judgment on fire while playing a game versus Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: All on video.
[SPEAKER_04]: All on video for YouTube for years to come.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, we have to get the game to sell a million units first, and we have an update on the numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how many units are we there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we there yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, at least in the US, we're up to 17,600 units.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will have you know, though, that's just from
[SPEAKER_03]: Launch to December 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't gotten the new numbers yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully, in the next couple weeks, I'll have new numbers for... So that's about within the first three weeks of release.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like two or three, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're 1.7% of the way there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Making good progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep at it, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at the chat room to see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dartetsuya says, that's it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Desgaea makes his way to the PSP
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Blade, Wrath of Fire comes out on the Wii Juiced 2 on the PC Link's Crossbow Training comes out on the Nintendo Wii Myst comes out on the DS I forgot that they were remaking the old Myst games on DS That's what this is, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah That's pretty rad Is that out here in the US?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think on the DS, I know it's on PSP
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon Battle Revolution finally comes out on the Wii over in Europe this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pro Evo Soccer 2008 on the DS also this week on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_04]: SingStar PlayStation 3 finally this week on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_04]: SOCOM on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soldier of Fortune Payback on the 360 and the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic Rivals 2 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple ports of the Golden Compass on PBSP and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomb Raider Anniversary makes its way to the Wii and Ultimate Mortal Kombat on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: and PlayStation 3 isn't left out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uncharted, Drake's Fortune comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're looking for something a little more casual, something mom can get into, Who Wants to Be a Millionaire comes out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word yet if Meredith Vieira stars or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The U.S., we have Alvin and Chipmunks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, she wouldn't because those are the Europe release dates and they have a different host over there, so I look stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: in the US, Alvin and the Chipmunks coming out on PC, DS, Playstation 2 and I believe the Wii American Girl, Julie Finds A Way with I must say the most creepy cover for a game I have ever seen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Ball Z Budokai Tenkaichi 3 Draglade Dragon Ball Z Budokai Tenkaichi 3
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, small little game here called Dance Dance Revolution Universe 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The bundle only is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Universe at War, Earth Assault.
[SPEAKER_03]: When's the game itself come out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we know?
[SPEAKER_03]: January.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to hear something even weirder?
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Hottest Party, the game only version.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not coming out until April now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Godzilla Unleashed on the Wii
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know you're supposed to do that in the regular game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that what it says in the rules?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something my friend told me when I was a kid, so it probably was made up just to make me look stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone's like, what the hell are you talking about, Rob?
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I believe that would be made up, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Viva Piata Party Animals, or as they call it, Atsumare Viva Piata Let's Party
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the Xbox 360, on the PlayStation 3, Conan as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also Pirates of the Caribbean, At World's End comes out on December 6th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also Uncharted, Drake's Fortune.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a brand new USB headset, if you're into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming out on the Nintendo Wii, we have No More Heroes coming out on the 6th, as well as Rayman Raving Rabbids 2, or Rabbids Party Returns.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did they really need to make a sequel to that shitty-ass game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, that game was awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I hear the second one is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: because they've taken over Earth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Namco's putting out a game called, or I'm sorry, Bandai, well, it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mina de Asubo de Namco Carnival comes out on the Wii, which I'm sure is just probably a collection of past games, or it might be, I don't know, this might be some type of Mario Party game, but starring the Namco characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's actually the Namco collection that came out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, with the upgraded games and stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming out on the Wii from Sega, Doraemon Wii, Himitsu Dugoketaisen is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, wait for it, Disney Princess Enchanted Journey this week on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Also another Tamagotchi game, Tamagotchi no Fury Fury, Kajikaiden comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope, I want to play No More Heroes, that looks fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 2, lots of stuff as well, another version of Pirates of the Caribbean at World's End.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another Mahjong game, hooray, Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories finally comes out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And another version of Disney Princess Enchanted Journey, as well as a game called Finalist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's just a price reduction though, it was already a game out there from Princess Soft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doko Demo Raku Raku DS Kakkaibo
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You always kind of worry because they advertise on the box how cheap it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cheap old game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, K1 World GP comes out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you want me to try to pronounce this one?
[SPEAKER_04]: This one's going to be a ton of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a language learning program, which apparently I need.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can special order this game from Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except it probably won't help me because it's probably for Japanese people to learn other languages.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'll be screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also on the DS, Tales of Innocence comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a Namco game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, wow, pretty big week in Japan, I must say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess they don't have the big shopping day like we do here, so they get games right up until Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on PSP, another version of Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Silent Hill Zero comes out, which was Silent Hill Origins here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Minano Golf Portable 2, that's just Hot Shots Golf, comes out over there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so this is actually pretty recent news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Activision and Vividi have merged into one super company.
[SPEAKER_03]: Activision, you'll know, of course, behind the such wonderful series as Call of Duty, Tony Hawk, and the lesser known Cabela's.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Vividi, of course, behind such wonderful games as Spyro,
[SPEAKER_03]: Scarface, and a small little game called World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: They own Blizzard, which is behind World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, this whole merger, you know, it's going to be pretty good, I'd say, for both companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, millions of dollars here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, billions of dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: But bad for the gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: $18 billion deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Activision BlizzCon Activivendi Activivendi
[SPEAKER_04]: Decide which company gets to keep its name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or VivendiVision or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just hope this means we get the level 70 Torrent Chieftain Warrior songs in Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: You already made that joke earlier, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: When we weren't on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't they just call the company World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: They should.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: World of Warcraft for World of Warcraft players.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it will either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Project Gotham Kodo Racing
[SPEAKER_04]: I, I, I, that would be my guess on what's going to happen is that, you know, some of the Blizzard franchises that Blizzard has not had time to pay attention to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero is the new... Activision will make Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody's, somebody's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero is the new class in the next Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that'd be awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: Expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being able to play instruments.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we can come up with tons of dumb ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee says there's no trucks in World of Warcraft, making reference to that commercial from a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a game, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it would be cool to have a role-playing game online that has a bunch of weird shit in it that makes no sense whatsoever, because I've never played a game like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm talking like absolutely like crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, where you can summon a giant jeep to come through and like crash people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just for no apparent reason, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like crazy shit.
Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: So are you proposing that you need to meet with the heads of Activision Blizzard to propose Loki's World of Randomness?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I like the ring of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I might buy that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chatroom, would you buy a game called Loki's World of Randomness?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to attack you with my cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Laser cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll license laser cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ten million right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Giant jelly bean attacks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, zap it with a laser cat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: I summon the truck to run it over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind, forget it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Less QQ, more Mew Mew.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: You should move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The doctor says, I would pay $300.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya says, do want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya gave you a LOL Irene for your less QQ, more Mew Mew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony has just... Talking Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's unfortunately a reference to a book that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony has decided to drop their ad agency of the past 13 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did they decide to drop it now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm guessing probably after what happened in hindsight of the whole PlayStation 3 debacle where the ads were not so hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: For reference, the ad agency was TBWA Chiat Day was the full name of the ad agency.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're wondering, does this affect both the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Europe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were also the ones that created the whole black and white campaign.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that thing for the PSP that some people called racist?
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other like Circus de Soleil one they have going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: This has been kind of a long time coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some might say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, just in case you're worried that Grand Theft Auto might not be coming out pretty soon, well, we still don't know when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they are starting to run some more videos and stuff for it, including a box art reveal trailer, which they elaborately painted a giant copy of the box art for Grand Theft Auto 4 on a giant canvas painting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks pretty awesome, but, you know, your typical Grand Theft Auto game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like every other Grand Theft Auto game I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, your typical Grand Theft Auto one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, people are dissecting it and saying, oh my god, there's motorcycles and helicopters in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like every other game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope the giant air tram can be used as like a weapon or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you can cut the cables to that thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, I wish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, but there's going to be a brand new trailer on December 6th, which is entitled Move Up, Ladies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Move up, ladies!
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: Next Thursday at 3 p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eastern time is when you can expect that trailer, when the internet explodes with it all over the place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but you can expect to see it 24 hours later after the traffic dies down, because you know their servers are going to get killed when the trailer comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, like, didn't they say when the first one came out,
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, that it broke the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But hey, that's good that they're showing trailers because that means that there's more work being done on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least that's what I'd like to assume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some new details have come out for another game that's getting an anticipated sequel next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silent Hill 5 comes out next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some new details have come out about the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The flashlight and radio static is going to be returning to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those kind of features didn't really exist in Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, that's not very surprising because Silent Hill 4 was not even originally going to be a Silent Hill game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Light apparently is going to actually kind of have a pretty major function in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The enemies will respond based on whatever the light is doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also going to be some puzzles that involve an x-ray viewer and nurses that, you know, are doing scary things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like the game, of course, is being greatly inspired by the Silent Hill movie, but I don't think that's such a bad thing, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_01]: I loved the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the other biggest change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silent Hill 5 will not have preset camera angles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: You will control the entire visuals.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's actually... I'm not sure how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That could be a double-edged sword there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the other thing that's kind of weird about it too is the damage system that they have in it now is going to be like Metal Gear Solid 3 where there's just not health power-ups anymore to heal you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to like
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kill a snake and eat it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Break a grenade open and like, you know... Silent Hill 5, break a grenade open and... Like Rambo style or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's gonna be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, there's supposed to be a minigame that has puzzles from like God of War, which were like DDR-ish in a way, button tapping things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh God, like every other fucking game on Earth now with the stupid context sensitive shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, but Konami made DDR, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like DDR, it's just Shenmue did it first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, Metal Gear Solid 4, according to the producer, must sell a million copies day one in order for them to make their money.
[SPEAKER_03]: So with that being released exclusively on the PlayStation 3 right now, that's going to be pretty hard for them to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if the Eye of Judgment could only sell 17,000 in the first three weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: No PlayStation 3 to date has sold a million copies day one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if any of them have sold a million copies at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, granted, if there was going to be a game that's going to do that, I'd say Metal Gear Solid 4 would probably be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we sure this guy wasn't just exaggerating a little bit?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, just because of the...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: but then again also people wanting to draw that conclusion well if they can't sell a million units on the Playstation 3 maybe if they developed it for the Xbox 360 as well they could sell a million units and whatever maybe it'll come out on Xbox 360 someday
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, PC gamers are going to be very happy to hear, especially those that are into first-person shooters blended with RPGs, that Deus Ex is getting another sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deus Ex 3 is coming out from Eidos.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was announced when they were talking about their newest studio in Montreal, which opened up a little earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: The studio hopes to expand to about 350 people in the year 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they just recently have started development on the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just passed proof-of-concept stage, Deus Ex 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will see what develops on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure lots of people are foaming at the mouth because I know this is a very popular game on the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, here's a strange rumor that's coming from a very unusual source.
[SPEAKER_03]: The unofficial Artie Lang site, and Artie Lang, you might know him from the Howard Stern show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, Lang will be voicing the role of a character named Big Al in an upcoming Leisure Suit Larry game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think is pretty cool that they're making another Leisure Suit Larry game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's so fitting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a very interesting way, I guess, that they found out that a new game was coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: No word on when it's coming or what it's going to be, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't think a new Leisure Suit Larry game is going to really be that impressive, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the last one wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, IGN has recently published their list of the OMG Top 100 Games of All Time list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't we get a list like this every couple of years?
[SPEAKER_04]: Every year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metal Gear Solid was number 24.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doom was number 19.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chrono Trigger was number 18.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boo, it should be number 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: 17 was Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_04]: 16 was Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_04]: 15 was Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: 14 was Pirates by Sid Meier.
[SPEAKER_04]: 13 was Ms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: 12 was Star Wars Tie Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that this list included PC games too.
[SPEAKER_04]: 11 was StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, then here's the top 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Resident Evil 4 was number 10 on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, you know, obviously that game got a lot of Game of the Year accolades when it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a pretty great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy III or VI by the Japanese scale was the number nine game of all time, which I believe is the highest ranking Final Fantasy game on the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Final Fantasy VII was not in the top ten, which I'm sure makes fanboys mad, but I think that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number eight was The Legend of Zelda, A Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number seven was Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I love Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which will probably be my number one, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number six was Half-Life 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number five was Super Mario 64, which a lot of people would probably put as their number one, so it's kind of interesting that there's still some more games to go here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number four is The Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's two Zeldas in the top ten?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, the Zelda games are great games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just confirming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, it's two Zelda games in the top ten so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three is Civilization 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: God bless them for remembering the Civilization series because it is a great series.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does deserve to be that high on the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I would have put the original Civilization, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two is Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm, what's number one?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think number one?
[SPEAKER_04]: The number one greatest game of all time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: on the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: The very first original Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That does make a lot of sense because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who doesn't remember Super Mario Bros.?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you play the theme for somebody, who doesn't know that theme and what that is?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Mario is part of pop culture.
[SPEAKER_01]: People know who Mario is.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was a pretty good game at the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Still is.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a different website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also happens to be affiliated with IGN.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing another top ten list.
[SPEAKER_03]: This, of course, is Ask Men's Top Ten Hottest Women in Tech.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll run down this list here real quick, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 10, Wendy Chang, who apparently is, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know her.
[SPEAKER_03]: She apparently does vidcasts on a network, clicknetwork.tv.
[SPEAKER_03]: But she has big boobies, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's Asian, so two points there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bryce Princess has big boobies, and she's Asian.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't do my own video games, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, Blair Butler, who is a stand-up comedian.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know her.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's on X-Play, apparently, or she's a writer on X-Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she also has a reoccurring bit in Tell Geek Out that appears on G4's website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are all these people G4 people?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kristen Holt, Dallas Cowboys Cheerleader, and now she's the host of G-Force Cheat.
[SPEAKER_03]: She also hosts a new game called Shout About Television.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she's working also as a tech reporter on Attack of the Shell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some might call this podcast Shout About Video Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Veronica Belmont
[SPEAKER_03]: Not related, no relation to Simon Boring, then I don't give a shit about her Never heard of her She has, I guess, a, she's acted as a producer and sound engineer for CNET's Buzz Out Loud podcast Let's move it a little faster, Loki Sorry Any guesses?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, Morgan Webb No, this is not number one Actually, here, I'll just skip to number one We'll do a top three here real quick Thank you
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know any other people.
[SPEAKER_01]: and get paid for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what women do naturally.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're so good at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Morgan Webb, of course, she's on X-Play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's at number one, then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one is Amber MacArthur.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never heard of her.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's on G4's TechTV Canada's Call for Help show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I have to see what she looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's not that standout.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's very plain.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know who she looks like?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: The character.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, wow, whoop-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, hey, I mean, seriously, why are they doing a top ten list?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop doing top ten list, people.
[SPEAKER_01]: People that nobody knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room is naming some other people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miranda Cosgrove says Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know who that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Olivia Munn says DJ Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't know who that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's on Attack of the Show, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Diane Miazota.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what Son of Dad says.
[SPEAKER_03]: She doesn't do Cheat anymore, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or not Cheat, Filter.
[SPEAKER_03]: She actually does some... Ranma says that's her name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Courtney Thorne-Smith.
[SPEAKER_01]: Courtney Thorne-Smith, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it a...
[SPEAKER_03]: Makeover show or something like that, like for kids or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a... Not makeover for kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not for kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like... Bam, my kid is ugly, Diane.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like that, like a room makeover.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know, trading spaces, but for kids.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen that before.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not a makeover.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're too fat to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to get liposuction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, they look like little sluts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is a horrible thing to say about seven-year-olds, but who would let their seven-year-old learn these type of dances?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they looked like they were training to become strippers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think, I don't remember who it was that said it, but somebody that I was with said something about like, wow, they look like a bunch of little sluts, and one of the kid's parents was right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're like, they turn around and they're like, yes!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what we wanted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mission accomplished.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl
[SPEAKER_01]: To me, that was a full stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me actually look at the original post here on the dojo.
[SPEAKER_01]: The dojo.
[SPEAKER_01]: About what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, I guess it is the same stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it looks exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they also posted the music from the stage there on the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little bit remixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on the smashbrothers.com website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, gosh, Part A is running long tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're almost at an hour and a half, but we want to go ahead and close out Part A here the way we always do, by paying tribute to the classic games of yesteryear.
[SPEAKER_04]: And DarkSakura is not here tonight to do the classic game of the week, but we've been filling in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last week, I picked a game, Equinox, if you forgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this week, Loki's going to pick a game for us as his classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, classic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I...
[SPEAKER_03]: I was torn on what I should pick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Almost picked Dallas Panic.
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, we'll save that for another episode when she's gone as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week, I decided to pick a wonderful game that I loved on the Super Nintendo and was also on the Genesis as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game called Zombies Ate My Neighbors.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's absolutely awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very cheesy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like a spoof on a bunch of horror films from the 1950s and 60s.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was made by LucasArts, actually published by Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely a game you should check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish it would come out on virtual consoles so we can play it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tons and tons and tons of different levels you can play.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have squirt guns, grenades, all sorts of things you can fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Things from giant babies to UFOs, zombies, you name it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually never played this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I really have.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is one of those games I just kind of missed.
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to go do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then that's why they need to put it out on virtual console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you basically run through the stages trying to rescue people and stuff and collect weapons.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then sometimes they'll have you fight different things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And each one of the stages is titled after a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like a spoof.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they'll have a bunch that are like Night of the Living Dead and stuff like that
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool, he's freezing the zombies in this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it might sound like it's kind of a generic game, but it's really stylized, and it's, like, really fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: You really just have to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really an action game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always hear folks talking about this game, but I've never really seen it in action, so... Oh, there's a little cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, they have cheerleaders, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, wait, by running over them, they're saving him or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think I remember seeing something like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, he bounces on the trampoline to get over the hedge, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can he... Oh, yeah, he's saving that guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, somebody else is bouncing on the trampoline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zombies Ate My Neighbors, your classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Loki...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: All segment long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.