[SPEAKER_03]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to pick up a few.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and unfortunately, I mean, I think there was just so many emails these past two weeks that you're just not going to be able to read them all.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Jamie's having to be choosy this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's open up the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLandsRadio.com, though, if you want to send it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if we don't always respond to them on air, we read them all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I go in there and I read them all every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was one that had a lot of gratuitous uses of the word fuck, so I'm not reading it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm only reading a few of these, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be Robb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Adios Amigos, Dr. Noir Don't move that email out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Save it in there and I'll reply with the address.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, there's a PS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: The plural form of Luchador is not Luchadors, but Luchadores.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the last syllable pronounced S as in Fez, the hat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did want to say, speaking of gifts sent to us, one of our listeners, our lover, Misty, sent a little care package.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see it up on the wall.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a Hello Kitty popsicle there.
[SPEAKER_04]: This little penguin eye dog thing, which I thought was too cute, and lots of rice candy, which is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I ate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: She sent us some candy, but you eat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I eat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of Misty, I'll go ahead and read her.
[SPEAKER_07]: She actually did ask about me talking about the Happy Suicide song.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's Thanatos from End of Evangelion is the one I was referring to.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: The song that's just so freaking depressing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I thought it was the whole end scene where they're dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to read Misty's big email.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was listening to my old OLR episodes and got stuck for some reason on episode 242.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that umbrella song that I ended up ripping from 249, but let's not go there right now, LOL.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess what inspired me to write in again, well this time anyway, was the short text message email that you read in this episode, plus I do have a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I shouldn't necessarily be thinking this far ahead, but face it, ASIN is my other addiction, aside from the station.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know enough not to ask if there'll be a panel, though that would be fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So instead I'll ask this, currently does anyone's schedule work out for ASIN?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's May 16th through 18th this year, but I am to head up to Rosemont on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, should I expect to see Chris there?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't catch her last year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Feel free to insert lame Pokemon jokes here.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I really want to see her in Megzi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I'll leave you alone for now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry if there's a typo I missed, but my typing on the LGNV still sucks a bit anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heart, Misty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would think very much that Chris is going to be there, seeing as how she's relocating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I get to go with her on the trip.
[SPEAKER_07]: AceN probably is not in my future, although a little bit more of my time in that year has been freed up.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love to go, but... I'm not saying no yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not likely right now, just due to the fact that I'm not going to have a lot of free time off work available because I'm going to Mendocino in April.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, never say never because I have found that flights from here to Chicago, or there's actually a lot of direct flights from SAC to Chicago, so, um, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's where ASAN's at, Chicago, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I do believe so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do believe so as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's more favorable maybe than you might think because, you know, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially, I'll tell you what, that maybe is a hell of a lot more likely to become a yes if we can somehow get in on getting a panel there or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got other stuff planned in May and I have to double check my schedule.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I've wanted to go to ASUN now for a couple years.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I want to cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need my costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably all three of us won't make it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at least maybe if one of the three of us can get out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, Loki, trip to Chicago in your future?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wife won't let you go, will she?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, I'm chained to the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like on house arrest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, while I'm still single, I should probably travel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because then
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't leave the room because I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to petition PopCap to make a Bejeweled 3 fast to keep her busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That won't... That's only for like a matter of minutes and then she'll get bored of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: We never did realize just how prophetic that t-shirt would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Game over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get some more emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR, I just wanted to get in my crappy story about the lack of Wiis in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: I live in Sarnia, Ontario, Canada, and at a specific department store whose name I will not mention, there was what you call a midnight madness sale where people will stay up to midnight trying to get the 15-minute only sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, in this particular store, the big grand prize draw was a chance to buy a Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that one gets free or 50% off, but just to have a chance to purchase one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also heard about a guy in Australia purchasing one for $590.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo, make more Wii's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep up the good work, LLR, PKJR92.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only way to make your PC go faster is to throw it out a window.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think what also probably unfortunately sucks for this person who is emailing us, thank you for the email by the way, is the fact that they do live in a pretty remote area of Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: and A, you're in Canada, which is kind of, even though a very important, very large country, is still outside of that trinity of Japan, United States, and the big Europe regions like Germany, France, Britain, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically the big ones there in Spain.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying to leave anybody out, but I'm saying the ones where gaming is more prevalent there in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Canada kind of comes after that sometimes with some things like Rock Band we've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: So unfortunately sometimes they get the short end of the stick with the Wii shipments as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo can only make so many of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: My advice would be though, I don't remember if he said he was trying to get one or whatever, but online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you go to a place like Amazon, they're not going to care if you're in Canada or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of that's the same for US and Canada.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless you're buying toys from Amazon UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is weird though about the whole raffle to get the opportunity to buy a Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know I have to order my UK toys from Amazon Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just thought I'd share that with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft wanted to respond to something he heard in Dr. Noir's email and that is that there are a lot of Wiis unsold in Mexico but that's because it costs almost double than it costs in the US because of import fees.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone import them from Mexico.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is from Mark F. I stand corrected, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sky talked about simple baseball games just to chime in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bases Loaded was way better than Baseball Stars.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the best slash easiest baseball game was simply Baseball for the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fun times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving forward for Robert M. People with your initial names.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello and hope you had a nice break.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully you've ironed out most of the bugs in your new studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I keep getting the podcast feed about a day late.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really like the weird owl for the stupid awards.
[SPEAKER_07]: And just a quick thought on the last show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mentioned Facebook as a verb instead of using it in the sense of friending.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friend went more the head desk direction.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is Facebooking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone would literally entail hitting them in the face with a book.
[SPEAKER_07]: Refreshing and witty comment relating online community sites and physical pain goes here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean like every time I go to MySpace, I feel like I'm going to have an aneurysm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was wondering what your opinion would be on the massively multiplayer online sports games, such as an NFL game where all 22 players could be controlled by online gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hard to coordinate, probably.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to see how something like that would work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brilliant idea, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why it's not out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: People don't know how to work together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, yeah, it's partially that and partially probably that, you know, some people, you know, in a football team, you have your standout stars and then you have the other guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who wants to be the other guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: When you play a video game, you're trying to be something you're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been on the bench.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's why it would be like, what was that game that my husband was playing, NFL Pro or something, where...
[SPEAKER_07]: Your team is all fantasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's some of the greatest players that you've had in sports history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe just that you pick from a pool of players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your team is actually a really big team that you form with friends, and then so many of you play in matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be really hard to coordinate, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the concept.
[SPEAKER_04]: The execution would be a little tricky, but I like your concept.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it can work with a party of more than seven people.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura is having a sneeze fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I will praise Blades of Steel a little more in the great, great hockey game it was on the NES.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I used the Wii gifting feature this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I used the Wii gifting feature to send my friend in New York a copy of Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I tried to send her Mario 3, but the Wii rejected it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the Wii is smart enough to not let you send games your friends already have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see, and I forgot to mention this on our show roll, that Microsoft did the gifting feature now in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: with points.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can give other accounts points now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where did they do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I read it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read it on one of the, like, Joystick or Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that why Xbox has been broken the past few days?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's great for me because, you know, having multiple consoles and, say, if I want to, you know, install, like, a map or something and buy it for each one, I don't have to buy point cards for every single console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, our entire chat room could hear your power sneezes and say, bless you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: My nose feels like a nightmare of pain and suffering.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad you heard me blow my nose, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, any more emails?
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear you sound like a foghorn.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there are emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR crew, I found myself unable to sleep one night at three in the morning and popped on your radio feed on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was able to fall asleep.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I noticed it was playing much more mellow music than normal is the rotation geared more towards slow calming songs at night or did I just happen upon a random anomaly either way it helps me get to sleep so thank you guys keep up the awesome show AZHP you're welcome and you can thank the total randomness because our playlist is the same
[SPEAKER_04]: All day long, we don't do anything special at night Although, maybe we should I am going to be changing the playlist up Because I have a break from work here for another week So I'm going to be working on a lot of OLR stuff And one thing I'm going to be doing is cleaning out the 24-7 show And putting in some more classic game tunes And, yeah, just cycling some stuff in and out So, check it out Alright, two emails left, thank god Alright Because we got a bunch, this is a sample
[SPEAKER_07]: So I updated my PSP the other day and was very pleased with the internet radio edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Given the fact that I listened to your show on my PSP, it would be even better if I could listen to it live on there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be a nice Christmas present, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know how to make that happen just yet, but we have to get on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you gotta figure that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't look at me, I don't know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to basically run a relay through Shoutcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it has to be Shoutcast time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say somebody sent me an email about some Shoutcast stuff, so I will look into that as the week goes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would assume, well, maybe you could probably broadcast on Shoutcast and Live365 at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or we could just leave Live365 and do Shoutcast with as many people as we want on the feed, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything is a possibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can say, I do know you can listen to all games on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did figure out how to set it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if nothing else, you can always listen to our syndicated runs that air on allgames.com on Monday nights and Tuesday mornings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's more to that email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I'd like to note that when I listen to you guys, you always find a way to make me laugh, no matter what kind of mood I'm in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, and I wish you all a very Merry Christmas and many more Happy New Years to come.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy Holidays.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mouthpiece, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to say, TigerClaw says, I can listen to OLR on my PSP using PSP radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess it is possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe share that with everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw, send Loki an email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you like to share with the rest of the class?
[SPEAKER_04]: Send Loki an email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't send me an email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just post it in the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get into it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, then post it in the chat, but I'm not reading it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Sky, Loki, and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to start this out with a true fact.
[SPEAKER_07]: OLR is the best, funniest, and most informative and engaging show in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys, and girl, have done a great job, and for that you should be commended.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, somebody commend us, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: One question, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just got a PlayStation 3 for Christmas, and the only game I have for it right now is Motorstorm.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would be the top three games you would recommend for me to get?
[SPEAKER_07]: Marvel Ultimate Alliance,
[SPEAKER_04]: Sell your PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a gift.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Marvel Ultimate Alliance, Resistance, Fall of Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are actually the three I named right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oblivion, Resistance,
[SPEAKER_04]: Marvel, if you're into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, obviously, Jamie's into that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think if there's something else that maybe was something... It has a lot of awesome... Heavenly Sword.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is probably fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt's recommending Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resistance, I would say probably Uncharted, Drake's Fortune.
[SPEAKER_05]: And depending on how you feel about...
[SPEAKER_05]: Ratchet and Clank, Ratchet and Clank.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Motorstorm's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you bought your PS3, you probably already have Motorstorm.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what he said.
[SPEAKER_07]: All he has now is Motorstorm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then... Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nah, I wouldn't do Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they're going to come out with something new year and buy it, and then all of a sudden, oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, I guess it is cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't buy the expansion, it's like a $30 game, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: and a bunch of Blu-ray movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of the PS3 games are really cheap now and you'll find a lot of them used.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seth is saying Unreal Tournament in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably not a bad pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unreal Tournament and Warhawk, depending on how you feel about online-only multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unreal Tournament 3, if you don't like Unreal really, really fast trigger-happy games, then you might not like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it for emails?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there was more to that one, because people keep interrupting me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sir.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I think Loki shouldn't get the bad rap he does from blasting Sony, because Sony really does leave us gamers out to dry in terms of innovation, besides the PS3, and new hardware such as new peripherals for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: So until they get wise, keep going strong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Canada salutes you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sincerely, Josh G. Well, thank you, Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: I salute Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Canada.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I like this, what's the difference between Windows 95 and Windows 98?
[SPEAKER_07]: Answer, three years.
[SPEAKER_04]: That joke is like ten years old.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, but I think it's great that somebody put that in their email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, now we're done with emails, yes?
[SPEAKER_07]: We are done, and I'm saving, I'm leaving out that one for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get back into some news, and then we're going to get back into the Skype line and go over July and the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Release dates, or lack thereof.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought I would at least open it up if anybody has any release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the US, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not much, and from what I gather, these four games are apparently a GameStop exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for them, I guess, scoring these awesome games, all of which are from a wonderful company named Conspiracy Entertainment, who is known for their extremely high-quality games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, no, not really, but you can get four racing games this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rig Racer 2, which has you racing big rigs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kawasaki Quad Bikes, Monster Trucks Off-Road, and then Classic British Motor Racing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me just save you time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What exactly is Classic British Motor Racing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like an Aston Martin?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's like racing minis.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's
[SPEAKER_05]: None of these games are that great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, they do have a game coming out, though, that's going to be a jet ski racing game, and it looks just like Wave Race 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that has potential, but I would, if you can rent these, go for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're like $19.99, so if you have money that you want to throw away, I can tell you one thing, don't
[SPEAKER_05]: buy monster trucks off-road because monster trucks they had off-road arena or something like that that really sucked and then there is off-road extreme special edition which got like a one on IGN it's like a piece of shit most of these are crap but just kind of know it going into it so that's all you can find this week next week I promise you better games how about the UK Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll give some highlights for what's coming out next week
[SPEAKER_07]: Dancing Stage Universe, Myst on DS, SingStar on PS3, Sonic Rivals 2, and another Yu-Gi-Oh game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll go over the big massive list later.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_04]: And we did get Blaze of Steel here last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so weird the way they've been releasing those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you would think there'd be some pattern to it, but it really just seems like it's just kind of a crapshoot.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the part where I would go over Japanese releases, but there is nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a damn thing I feel like mentioning.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that being said, we are going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to go over with you guys, our listeners, the last few months of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we also want to get your picks for the best game of 2007 and the worst game of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember, if you've never used Skype before, you might want to give Echo123 a call to make sure you sound okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless you're calling over the phone, then there's really nothing you can do to test.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, since there is a little bit of a delay between the live and when the people hear it, they probably don't know it's open yet, so we're just trying to fill in a little bit of time here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later on in the program, we're going to be going over our top five lists of the five most fun games we played this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we'll tally it up, what overall was the best and the worst game of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll give some predictions for 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we haven't forgotten the FUs either.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, a lot of our regular callers are gone this week on vacation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Away for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's where, if you're wondering, why isn't our phone ringing off the hook?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who leaves for New Year's?
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand Christmas, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think people are still gone from Christmas is what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's going to happen if nobody calls?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll do July.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone call us!
[SPEAKER_04]: Or we can do it, we can always play with the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are just being shy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have plenty of people in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's over, almost 50 people in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know what the heck's going on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pick up your damn phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you people have phones?
[SPEAKER_07]: And call us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks are waiting for certain months.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you don't wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: You do this on our terms.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pick up the goddamn phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your goddamn phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, here on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this is the Escapist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Escapist is here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Escapist, how are you, sir?
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing wonderful, yourself?
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little bit of a delay, but I notice you're calling us from Canada, so that's probably why there's a bit of a delay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so I'm going to go through this rather quickly here, and we want to hear your thoughts on some of the highlights of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's talk first a little bit about July.
[SPEAKER_04]: July, episode 237, was when a brain game in the UK was pulled over the use of the word spastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I apologize if I offended anyone by saying that word just then, but we kind of hear in the US go, well, that's not a big deal, but in the UK...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 239 was the week that Mini E3 happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was when Mario Kart Wii was announced for the Wii and Cena was announced for the 360 and the PSP was announced that had a redesign.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just in general, kind of the changed E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, do you think, Loki, the E3 is going to be very similar to how it was this year, next year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you think they're going to get kind of
[SPEAKER_04]: you know, especially since they're moving back to the LA Convention Center, do you think they're going to get a little bit of maybe what they missed?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I think it's going to be about the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of which, you need to talk to whoever was supposed to invite us last year and get them to invite, or this year I should say, and be ready for this next year because I want to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do too, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, anyways, uh, yeah, all I remember from Mini 3 is how disappointed I was with the Mario Kart and, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Zapper announcements.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not necessarily Mario Kart, because Mario Kart's really fucking awesome, but the fact that it comes with a plastic steering wheel, all these peripherals, they were like, God, this is a stupid idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who keeps releasing this crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Nintendo's like, Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: We're gonna do it too!
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes it a good idea, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the Zapper, you know, what we saw was like a pretty cool attachment, you know, kind of like the Nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then all of a sudden, now it's this piece of plastic crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know...
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't all that exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist, did you follow him in E3 news?
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you think of this year's E3, new and improved?
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of really ignored it this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I've never been a big fan of E3 to begin with.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a whole bunch of excitement for a couple months and whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: What makes you not a fan of E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just too much information at one time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get kind of overloaded and overexcited a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Which kind of made a lot of us go, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it did win.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it did end up winning the Emmy, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, the South Park Wow episode integrated the World of Warcraft very well with the South Park kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, the one thing I remember was, ma'am, bathroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bathroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist, out of those stories, the brain game, the price cut, Mini 3, and South Park World of Warcraft, what do you think had the biggest impact for 2007's gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, even though I just undermined it earlier, I'd definitely say the E3 there, just because, you know, it was a whole new year for E3, a new direction they wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still the same kind of information that got released from what I saw, but just a lot less people going to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think even though it is different, I think it definitely was the highlight of the month and the year in some ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the way that they did E3, I mean, besides the multiple hotels and it being kind of difficult to travel from one place to another...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I think works a lot better for me than having to just navigate all around because I end up missing stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said this before on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two years ago, the last big E3, I knew something was wrong when Paris Hilton was there and drawing these big crowds because she had some fucking crappy cell phone game coming out, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: She got the name wrong on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You knew that something was broken with E3 at that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's move on to August, Escapist.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go over the four stories and tell us which one you think had the most impact.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 241 kicked off August and it was another WoW story because that was the week that BlizzCon happened and Wrath of the Lich King was announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, obviously, we even had some folks, I remember Extifer, one of our regular guests, actually went to BlizzCon and came back with a full report.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, a lot of WoW players are very excited about the Wrath of the Lich King expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 242 was the week that the news was breaking that the Xbox 360 Core system was being phased out of stores.
[SPEAKER_05]: The price dropped, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, when Best Buy started to phase them out of their computers and Target was phasing them out of their computers, the systems were slowly disappearing, which kind of made people go, hmm, what's going on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, subsequently we learned about the Elite and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the Elite had already been out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry, the Elite had been out, the Arcade and the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: episode 243 Toys R Us breaks the Bioshock street date Bioshock came out towards the end of August and Toys R Us broke the street date and people were taking pictures of receipts and that stuff was all over the internet and then episode 244 in August was the week we talked about a brand new game Konami was putting out called New International Track in a Field and what made this story stand out the fact that there was going to be a cartoon version of Serial Killer Pyramid Head in the game a little chibi pyramid head game
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the game is not out yet, but we were just talking about the announcement, although I should say that if you saw the Christmas cards that some of the big game companies put out, Konami actually had a little picture of Chibi Pyramid Head in there, and he was opening up a box with new gloves in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: He just reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: My husband's boss gave him one of the Portal Christmas cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Aperture Science?
[SPEAKER_07]: I stole it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a card, but I stole it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, escapists, out of those stories, BlizzCon, Xbox 360 Core phased out, Toys R Us breaking a street date, a new international track and field, or anything you can think of, what do you think had the most impact?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that's a little bit of a tougher month, because it was after E3, but what do you think had the most impact?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, jeepers.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, I definitely have to say the Toys R Us thing was kind of a
[SPEAKER_02]: Big deal there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another insight into the distribution chain there that people are really excited to get their games now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Toys R Us isn't really paying attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of a shot in the head.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited to be on air, that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's a very good point that you're saying there is that, you know, a big chain like Toys R Us you would think would know better, but sometimes down on the lower levels, you know, folks kind of make their mistakes and all that stuff, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: How many people were actually playing Halo 3 before that came out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd already beaten it before it came up.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was another huge one, Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was in August as well, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: October.
[SPEAKER_04]: September.
[SPEAKER_04]: September, almost.
[SPEAKER_04]: End of September.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we get into the next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Escapist, before we let you go, we have a few more things to ask you, and that would be, what, in your opinion, was the worst freaking game of 2007 that should be avoided at all costs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, normally I would go with the obvious pick like the artist, except I actually didn't play it, so that would kind of be a cop-out on my part.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we have to change it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think then?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to have to be annoying and say I didn't really like Call of Duty all that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty 4 never really did anything for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it might be I'm not a true shooter fan or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's because I had a horrible time online playing it, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Adam Montana
[SPEAKER_04]: Hannah Montana was the worst game?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was the best, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was different.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, yes, it was Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody said Gears of War was the worst game that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think it was Michelle from Video Game Outsiders.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd have to go back and listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was so 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: The best game of 2007, Escapist, in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: Last time I tried to avoid the obvious pick, but I have to go the obvious with this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have to be the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably the best gaming value I've ever seen in my freaking life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five classic games all crammed in one bundle, and ignore the Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say I disagree with you, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Orange Box is a great deal, and that right there makes it definitely a worthy candidate for Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you have Portal in there as well, which of course is a brilliant game in itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapists, thanks so much for being on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though we had a little bit of a delay with the cross...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much for having me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you have a great 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, because of the distance there, he was breaking up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to move on to September.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get a call here and talk about September and October.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the Skype line is open at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: September and October.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember, if you don't get through for this one, there is still November and December.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still have that to go over.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see who's on the line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange House Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you were the one that was waiting for September, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You lucked out, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: because somebody else might have beat you to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got September and October.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start with September.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, September was our biggest month.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were five Sundays in the month of September, so we did more shows in September than any other month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting off with episode 245, Neo Geo titles were announced for the Nintendo Wii's virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, a lot of people were like, OMG, Magician's Lair and Magician Lord and OMG, Fatal Fury and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what always surprised me about this was that
[SPEAKER_04]: Fatal Fury is like $9 on the Nintendo Wii, or you can get the souped-up version with the improved HD and online play for $5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you can get the original card for like $100.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think that kind of goes out the window now with Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Jamie, you collect the old-school Neo Geo cartridges.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've paid hundreds of dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you do have some that you've paid hundreds of dollars for, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: The only one that I paid, and I got it for $200 and something...
[SPEAKER_07]: was I got a chance to buy King of Fighters 2000 for relatively cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so that's the one that we've paid the most for.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we've got like Samurai Shodown, Samurai Shodown 2, Baseball Stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think as a collector?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about all this stuff now coming out on Virtual Console for less than $10?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I don't have the money to spend on this crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I did want Samurai Shodown 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would pay the money for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, episode 246 was the episode where Sony was sending out to all the critics out there a review guide for Lair Well, IGN kind of like posted it, but they were sending it to several critics This whole little guide on Lair And they said, no, we're not trying to sway people's decisions But they just want to make sure everybody understood the game And the six axis control, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was a very nicely bound little book.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 247 was the episode where Project Hammer was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if any of those review guides went on the, you know, old eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we never looked.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should have.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could have put one up here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, 247 was when Project Hammer was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a game that looked to be a hell of a lot of fun when we saw it at E3, but apparently somebody at Nintendo decided it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Project Hammer reminds me too much of MC Hammer, and that's like so ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Project MC Hammer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Reverend Hammer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 248 was the week that Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: was announced that it was going to be going online.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, that caused a lot of people to go, Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, later on it was announced that it still has friend codes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the whole...
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole like thing with people just getting in the computer, taking over and stuff Okay, you know what I heard?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, yeah, that's weird I'm trying to get off topic here a little bit Apparently, what was it, not Brothers in Arms Medal of Honor 2, or Heroes 2 Is online, 32 players, and if I remember correctly Does not have friends codes for the Wii Nice So why can't everybody do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Your guess is as good as mine
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was episode 248, and of course it was a five-week month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 249, that was the week that the Sex Pistols announced that they were getting back together to re-record the song Anarchy in the UK for Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: and of course this is big news I think not so much like just the song itself or what have you but just the fact that you know video games and especially a series like Guitar Hero 3 has transcended the music game genre so much that bands that had been broken up were coming back together for the purposes of recording for the game I mean that in my mind is huge especially as an old school music gaming fan so
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my own from episode 247, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one about the New Jersey parents being upset about the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I was looking at that one when I was going through the show rules today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the New Jersey parents being upset about the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you think that was the biggest impact?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, like, 20 years ago, the Wii Zapper, like, I mean, the NES Zapper, I mean, no one complained about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Super Nintendo had a Super Skill.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think anyone complained.
[SPEAKER_09]: And a whole bunch of systems after that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, like, a gun proof on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh, you must ban this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I have a pick for the news story.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Halo 3 is released!
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously!
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone's like, oh my god, Halo 3!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so, that's a big news story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the reason why it was overlooked here is because, you know, it kind of... I know, we don't care about Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, it's not that, because I do care about Halo 3, but just that most of the Halo 3 news was everything leading up to its release.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 246 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is announced that you cannot put the helmets on your cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is disappointing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Biggest news of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Biggest news of 2007, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You okay, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Blink, blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you try to put the helmet on your cat?
[SPEAKER_04]: On Shermie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shermie's too stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, can we put it on the... Can we put a helmet on the ferrets?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we put the helmet on the ferret?
[SPEAKER_07]: We probably could.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we could find the ferret, we could.
[SPEAKER_07]: The ferret ran hiding since Rob threatened to put him down the food trash compactor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Skirgo's the penguin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly the new penguin from Argentina.
[SPEAKER_07]: The penguin is frightening.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is pretty fierce.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's very punk rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's go on to October.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our show's going to go on all night.
[SPEAKER_04]: October, episode 250.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a big week for us because it was our 250th episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was also the week that Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Working episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so excited right now and it's going to be very disappointing when the game actually comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wonder if he's going to kill Hitler at the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be definitely the coup de grace.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the last show we taped in October, episode number 253, was the week that it was discovered that Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3 are not playing nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: The controllers were not compatible with each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you wanted to play both games, you had to use your Guitar Hero 2 controllers.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Guitar Hero 3 on at least PlayStation 3 was not compatible with each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've been using our Xbox ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox, I think, works one way, but it doesn't work the other way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It works with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it works with Rock Band, but the controller doesn't work with Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be better if they made a controller that didn't break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or just that they just would let them both be, you know, a lot of people are like, this just sucks that they can't get along.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I agree, it sucks that they can't get along.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think GS68 was the biggest, or if you have one of your own, feel free to share.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo offering Wii condoms, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: delayed, Capcom announced the Street Fighter 4 and Bionic Commando, or Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3 just can't play nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not too sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not... I don't really remember October too well.
[SPEAKER_09]: But... I would probably guess... I would probably guess 354, the Wiimote gloves, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wiimote gloves?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was pretty big.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me, personally, I would say the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: delay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that seems weird, because then you kind of go, well, that's a 2008 story.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was a game that people were so looking forward to, and especially on the Wii, that really needed some powerhouse games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I guess...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It did pretty well this Christmas regardless.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, so many people were looking forward to that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a real disappointment when that game got delayed.
[SPEAKER_09]: If most of it were to delay, I'd be playing it right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all would.
[SPEAKER_04]: We probably wouldn't be doing this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We would be playing Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's, you know, again, all the more reason why that game's got to be twice as good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, you know, people are going to kind of go, oh, we waited all this time for this?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Given all these delays, I have a feeling people are going to start calling it Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody did earlier in chat, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, GS68, what in your opinion was the worst freaking game of 2007?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't played a lot of crappy games that were released in 2007, but I might have... I'd probably give it to Initial D4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Initial D4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why initial D4?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, mainly because it wasn't programmed so, like, apparently there's this whole speed limit system where if you go too fast on a certain corner, your wheel locks and your acceleration suffers and there's this penalty cancel glitch where you hit the brake to remove the acceleration problem and from what I've read, like,
[SPEAKER_09]: The recent official initial D tournament is the last one they're going to do because I've read that initial D4 is not doing very well in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, over in Hong Kong, for example, version 3 is doing better than initial D4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that is something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a bummer that it really sucked it up on its fourth version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't even really played that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played initial D3, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a fun time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and... Yeah, and what else?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say... Like the tuning system for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like... If you want to... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were going to say another game that you thought was the worst of the year?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to bring up the...
[SPEAKER_09]: whole customizing shop feature instead of
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to eject your card three times just to get to that, so you have to point to another continuous screen, eject your card, and then put your coins in, and then start the game again, so that way you can get to the tuning shop faster.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, it's a way to keep sucking up your money and sucking up your tokens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, that would only be in the case of if you had discounted continuous, like five coins to start and four coins to continue.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, let's move on and stop talking about games that suck and let's talk about the best freaking game of 2007 in your opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the best game in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maximum Tune 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: You must be a real racing game fan because you got both for your best and worst.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why was Maximum Tune 3 your best game of the year?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like what they did with the battle system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of picking a set course, you can now pick the route partway through the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also added new courses, like, you can now race on the whole Wangen line instead of just, like, a six-kilometer stretch, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: The soundtrack was pretty cool, more Yuzuka Shiro stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the Ghost Bell system, like, the whole idea of racing a virtual opponent instead of them having to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've been listening to the soundtrack to Maximum Tune 3 in my car recently, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's
[SPEAKER_04]: And the thing I find about it, though, is if I listen to it too much, I drive too fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I speed way more often when I'm listening to Wangan music than anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's in my CD player like 80% to 90% of the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's music that was designed to put the pedal to the floor, and it happens in my real car.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only unfortunate thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the soundtrack and the graphics are meant to give the game a rave-ish look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Several years ago, there was a game called Wangan Midnight, and the graphics and soundtrack were nothing like Maximum Tunes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it happens that you have a series that's kind of similar, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: There were older...
[SPEAKER_09]: One Good Midnight Games released in 2001, and they were based on Tokyo Extreme Racer.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they looked and sounded nothing like Maximum Tune.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess Maximum Tune was made to be more arcade-friendly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, One Good Midnight was actually... I was finding the stuff on the manga.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it was a manga.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, hey, GS68, we've got to let you go because we've got some more months to go over, but I'll leave you with this thought of us all raving in the car right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's drop some ecstasy while it's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we've got to let you go, GS68, but thank you so much and have a great 2008, alright?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're looking for one more call to help us close out the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up, my friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing much, just waiting till tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Waiting for that ball.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, that ball dropping in that middle of that big city on the face of the earth?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, I've heard of that before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going out to Times Square tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, probably not.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I am getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Legitimately.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not drunk now?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm with friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, but you'll be drunk tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, just going over the year that was 2007 in gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready to go over November with us?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think, I don't know if my memory's still shady, but let's do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll help you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got four stories here to help remind you what happened in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 254... Whoa, we just had a crash here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're dropping the alcohol.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, the alcohol got dropped.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, episode number 254 was the week that Manhunt 2 on the PSP was hacksawed to remove some of the... And target, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Target quickly rushed to judgment and pulled it off even though there's no way in hell you're going to get to it unless you have massive experience in PSP hacking.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Loki, you did it the day this thing came out, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: You had your PSP stripped of the censored stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it worth it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it worth it for fucking genitals getting like, I don't know, you know, basically hurt
[SPEAKER_10]: His network got censored.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weren't the generals, what do you call it, hurt?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Electrocuted, mashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were ripped off with pliers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this game sounds pretty horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 255.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have a lot from this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: NPD withholds sales numbers from the press.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, it is kind of relevant because, you know, obviously it kind of leaves it in the company's hands to be kind of bragging.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you've seen companies kind of stretch these reports out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: They want to appease their stockholders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you at a 7-Eleven or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard a little phone go off.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like the phone's at 7-Eleven.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, my phone just went off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just keep coming quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we say withhold, they didn't withhold everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just reduced some of the information that was going out there and caused the companies to basically be on their own.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus Christ, you got a beeper, too?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we should get another caller.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's got a pimp!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are not putting us on hold.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't believe we got put on hold by a caller.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was only quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Strike one, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_10]: Episode 256 was the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a way to end the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Week number 256, episode 256, that was the week that the Xbox download service was announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360, you would be able to download original Xbox games to the service.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, we've seen this come out now, and you can get Psychonauts and Indigo Prophecy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a way to rediscover Xbox games you may have missed the first time around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, for some people, a way overpriced way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, of course, the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who the hell would put price tags on fucking icons and themes and basically do it against the will of game developers as well when they don't want to charge for that shit, for downloadable content?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, do you agree?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like Epic, for example.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't want to do that shit, but they're forced to because they have no choice most of the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think Unreal Tournament 3 is being held up for the 360 besides the user-created stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's being held up because they can't do cross-platform play between the PC and the... Well, they were doing it... But user-created mods is the other hinging factor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they can worry about that later.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not really a factor to keep it from being released.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jesus Christ, is someone at the door now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just go through the last song, the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero's 80s edition sued because the song is too similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: The romantic sued Guitar Hero 80s edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as we all know, they lost.
[SPEAKER_04]: The judge laughed that out of court.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, out of those stories, Manhunt 2, Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, are you going to give us your best?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you don't answer the phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: You let it go to voicemail.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tony, you're the one that keeps answering the calls from him, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just not cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's nipping in the butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not offended because I think it's hilarious, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm offended.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, the first one, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing December.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me open up Skype, see if anybody else wants to call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's give it a couple minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft in chat says, best call ever, ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: If somebody would like to call us and take Zaku's place, you can call us right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to give it like 10 seconds, and I'm just going to say, Loki, fuck it, you can just do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is DT.
[SPEAKER_04]: Praise be to God, Dark Tetsuya, how are you, my friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think you can do a better job than the last caller?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Manhunt 2, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because people have that much free time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, though, if no one brought it back up, would you still remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: I completely forgot about this, and thank God, because all you need to know is not to trust the bigger sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trust us, because we're awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I stand by what I said before, that there's multiple sides to every story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, oddly enough, you would think me, of all people, would be the biggest critic of GameSpot in this situation, but I actually think people didn't give them enough credit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're too quick to blame the big corpse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just didn't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was getting annoyed at that point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, thank God they fired you.
[SPEAKER_05]: This story's taking too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, there was other news in December.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 259 was Nintendo pulls ads due to the high demand of the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: They basically said, okay, we can't make these Wiis fast enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody still wants one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, maybe we'll hold off on the advertising until the first quarter next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if you're having no problem selling one item, why do you need to advertise it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Advertise for one that may not be selling as well, and they have a little bit more of, so it makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 260, DVR and Internet Radio launches on Sony PSPs in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: and in part A we talked about Akira Yamaoka comes out and says that Japanese development's in trouble and that the American development's where it's at right now and of course Silent Hill 5 is being developed right here in America.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think out of those four stories DarkSakura had the biggest impact on gaming in 2007?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeff Gertzman in the fallout there, Nintendo pulling ads due to the Wii demand, DVR and internet radio hits the PSP or Akira Yamaoka saying that development is...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in America is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Gershman, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think that's kind of a no-brainer.
[SPEAKER_04]: But why do you say that?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think is the fallout that that could have in 2008?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was like back in the day, I don't know if you remember, it was when EGM gave Super Street Fighter 2 poor scores, Capcom full of advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and again, as I do a lot, I compare things to the movie industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, just because Siskel and Ebert might give a movie a bad review, well, Siskel doesn't review anything anymore, but just because Ebert and Roper, Ebert gives a thumbs up, Siskel's, just because Ebert and Roper might give something a bad review doesn't mean that suddenly, you know, they're going to stop advertising in the Chicago newspapers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Siskel, get me out of Ebert's stomach.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been plenty of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not too soon anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want this show to be over.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we need to get to the best and worst games of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya, in your big opinion, what was the worst freaking game of 2007?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hadn't really played all that much, so I guess I'll go with Yaris.
[SPEAKER_04]: When in doubt, Yaris, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: When in doubt.
[SPEAKER_04]: You drive a car with a claw.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, what was the best game of 2007 in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh god, I just rented it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Super Mario Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And why this game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's what Super Mario 64 2 should have been.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of what we got on the GameCube, Super Mario Sunshine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Dark Tetsuya, thanks so much for calling and helping us out with the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya, of course, writes for our website once in a while when there's news to report on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku posted his pics in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: He would have picked God of War 2 for the best game of the year And Kane and Lynch for the worst game of the year Well, haha, you were answering the phone while you were on the phone with us So yours doesn't count, rude person But there you have it, if you were curious Alright, that took us through the whole year What a trip down memory lane, what a long trip down memory lane I don't remember A fucking lot's happened this year A lot's happened this year
[SPEAKER_04]: ManHunt2 ManHunt2 ManHunt2
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: getting delayed?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it Codemasters and the broken Bubble Bobble game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it the lady dying over the Nintendo Wii that so many people wanted a Wii that she drank so much she died?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was Proteus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Proteus?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say probably the biggest story of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, it's the Bubble Bobble thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is because seriously, seriously, how do you do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: How does that happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I would say... Not Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, how many people bought Bubble Bobble?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that affected what, five people?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say probably... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that it's a crime that Activision released three Guitar Hero games this year, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's a crime.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, let me think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that last year or this year?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember when Red Octane was purchased by Activision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about our top five games of the year and our picks for the worst game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get the worst out of the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: The worst game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to tally it up with what the listeners say and figure it out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what in your opinion was the worst game of the year?
[SPEAKER_07]: The worst game?
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually have a list of five.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a list of five.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worst games of the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to say Manhunt 2 was one of them just because, you know, I got sick of hearing all the crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although that was a funny picture with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything with the Bratz franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'll say Yaris 2 just because.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I got warning so I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I have to put this one on here for sauce.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is a quote from...
[SPEAKER_07]: Heroes of Mana is the worst game of 2007 because you need a doctorate in electrical engineering to understand how to play the fucking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to pick that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heroes of Mana.
[SPEAKER_07]: On her suggestion.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn, the Mana games started sucking after Secret of Mana, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish that we had gotten, um, uh, Second Sense 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know in the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Your pick for the worst fucking game of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, too, had five.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, six, if you can't... Jeez, I only had one.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was thinking... I am my... Okay, my number one is not yours.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, number six, Offroad Extreme Special Edition, although I did not play it, but it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did play this game, Counterforce, for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yet another game by Conspiracy Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, my number three would be anything from Conspiracy Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: or actually that'd be number four number three I actually this was the only the first and only game I will ever import for the PS3 Wangen Midnight is a fucking joke on the PlayStation 3 it is poor for a PlayStation 2 game I hated it it was a waste of $60
[SPEAKER_05]: Yaris is number two and the reason it's number two is because it's free number one I paid fucking fifty dollars for and it was a ripoff Transformers the game the worst biggest disappointment of a game this year how do you fuck that up but you did
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and the way it was packaged it just felt so rushed it was just a steaming pile of poo I hated I mean there's not a lot of times I go I really fucking hate this game I hate Fusion Frenzy 2 so much that game was awful
[SPEAKER_04]: Awful, awful, awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's definitely the worst game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I can't believe that's highway robbery that they ever tried to charge full price for that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: My wallet was raped by that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot one more.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an honorable mention, I guess, because it is also free.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember the vision camera from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't the vision cam last year?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yaris definitely runs away with the title of the worst game of 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: SuperMarioGalaxy RockBand
[SPEAKER_07]: because, again, super cool, and Radiohead.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one, Portal, duh.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enough said, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal was just super innovative.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I love anything that messes with physics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would totally be a physics major if it wasn't for all the retarded math.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: GhostSquad
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the most underrated games, at least for the Wii Zapper that's come out for the Wii this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably going to get cheaper.
[SPEAKER_05]: And granted, the graphics aren't that great.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game is incredibly short.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I will tell you, I played that game through like six times in a row.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that you can unlock like 50 different weapons in the game, that makes the games even harder.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know, it was the most fun I had for about four hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's all I've played of it so far but um Ghost Squad definitely worth picking up on the Wii if you like gun games um Rock Band fun um I have to give it props because I bought Guitar Hero 2 and I bought Guitar Hero for the Playstation I played it like once and I said fuck this and put it down and that's where it gathered dust Rock Band I actually played for a lot more than that and it's actually pretty fun um
[SPEAKER_05]: Just wish there was an easier way to be able to play online with multiple people, like, you know, in a world mode or something like that, but definitely a fun game and I really, it's actually one of the games I actually look forward to the download content coming out for it, which, you know, I can't really say that about many other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a great game while it lasted.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought maybe a little bit short.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, not a whole lot of replays
[SPEAKER_05]: Playability, but I had fun while playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That takes us to number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's... Oh, whoops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't count.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number two, Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best thing for a futuristic Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: The most fun I've had in a demo for a game, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely fun to play online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, that fizzles away pretty quick, and the game kind of repetitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Had some pretty good download content for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually went back to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to try to get the five achievements that are in it, Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely the best $20 you'll ever spend.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you find it used, you can probably find it for even cheaper than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: D3 really, really, really needs to bring over the simple series over here because it's absolutely, you know, good money.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the cheesiest, weirdest games you'll ever play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And unfortunately, because they're so weird, they don't end up coming over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I hope that changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Top five games of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised, Earth Defense Force 2017, for you, because you are a guy that's all about fun, and, you know, blowing shit up is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can blow up, you can level entire cities, and then they come back to the next level, and you can level them all over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's, seriously, we've played it for, I don't know how many hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have it logged in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's over 70 hours, I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest was an amazing game that took Bejeweled and just put little twists on it that made a whole role-playing game out of it and a more competitive type of game out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest was an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was my number five game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: My number four game of the year is one of those games that probably most critics aren't even going to put on their top ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for me, it was so great to finally see a true Japanese role-playing style game on a next-gen console and to see what it could do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I thought the story in this game was so amazing, yet kind of depressing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the way that it wove...
[SPEAKER_04]: Real life in with this fictional scenario was just something really innovative and new and that's why Eternal Sonata for me was just a different type of gaming experience that I really enjoyed and had to be in my top five for the year, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say what you want about it getting stale towards the end or what have you or
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: My number two game of the year is all about fun and I did not think that this game was going to be so great because my expectations I guess were actually a little bit low because like I said earlier in the show I was not a big fan of Mario 64 as much as the next guy but Super Mario Galaxy just blew me away.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is so much fun and is really the type of game that I think the Wii was built for.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Super Mario Galaxy is absolutely my number two game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that takes me to the number one game of the year
[SPEAKER_04]: I admit it, I do not like to spend as much money as I do on gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I spend a lot of money on games, and that is why value is so important to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in my opinion, there is no better value out there in gaming right now, period, than the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is one of the sole reasons why the Orange Box is my game of the year, because you get these great, you know, obviously Half-Life is an incredible series of games, Team Fortress 2...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the unique art style of Team Fortress 2 really kind of sets it apart from the other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Portal is kind of like... When you play Portal, you feel like you're starting to play the next great series of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, something truly original has kind of started with Portal that I think is going to kind of continue.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you have all these kind of in-jokes and the whole, like, the cake is a lie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, like, you know, not...
[SPEAKER_04]: Every game, especially its first time out the gate, can kind of create that kind of buzz.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the Orange Box absolutely is the best game that came out in 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not only the best deal in gaming, but just some of the most solid games you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the best 60 bucks you can spend on games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: My top five games of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's tally it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have, let's see, one vote for Call of Duty 4, one vote for Maximum Toon 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: One vote for Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two votes for Super Mario Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you combine Portal with Orange Box, you get four votes for Portal and Orange Box this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to have to say that Orange Box is collectively Orange Lounge Radio's Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did say Half-Life 2 earlier for one of my ones that didn't make the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's part of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of just applied again.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, it's ironic.
[SPEAKER_04]: because I remember when I first heard about this game, The Orange Box, I was like, oh, isn't that funny?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're Orange Launch Radio and here's this game, The Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: I built a computer called The Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's also funny about it is that I remember saying, I was kind of like, oh, these are the, oh, we're not, I'm not really into these kind of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really like the first person shooters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Portal, it's a shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Portal makes me enjoy first person shooters because it's, it's a different, I mean, I think even people that don't enjoy first person shooters can enjoy Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what makes the game so great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well,
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, we are not changing our name to Orange Box Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be no fun at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the Orange Box is collectively our game of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which takes us to 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think is going to happen in 2008?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any predictions you want to make for 2008?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: DS Redesigned Halo Wars Fable 2 Spore
[SPEAKER_05]: Blue and Black DS in February.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, any predictions you want to make for the year 2008?
[SPEAKER_06]: Duke Nukem, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Duke Nukem Forever will fucking come out at some point, and it'll be disappointing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brawl will get pushed again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I keep expecting it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's something that's kind of interesting, and I've actually looked at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been kind of following it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved Saints Row, and we still play it every day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of is holding us over until Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, Saints Row 2 is supposed to be coming out, I think, this year, or 2008.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tomorrow!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I wish.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2008, and it actually looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm kind of wondering, you know, I know Grand Theft Auto 4 is going to be amazing, but
[SPEAKER_05]: Predictions I'm going to make...
[SPEAKER_04]: In the third or fourth quarter of 2008, Sony will redesign the PlayStation 3 and do an effective relaunch, a reboot of the system the way maybe they should have done it the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the reboot will include a playable demo of Final Fantasy XIII that's going to blow everybody away.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Metal Gear Solid 4 will not single-handedly save the PlayStation 3 and that's what's going to want to cause them to really cut corners in the cost and they're going to release this system just as dirt cheap as possible to try and get people to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: somebody will challenge Nintendo to the throne of handheld gaming and it won't be Sony I think in 2008 I think this year this is a very just out there prediction I don't know I get the feeling Nintendo has such a large share of the marketplace in handheld I think someone else wants a piece of that besides Sony but I don't think it's Microsoft I think someone else I think someone we don't know about yet is going to come in and challenge Nintendo for the throne in 2008 um
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of folks in the chat room are insinuating it might be Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their games have not been... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Sega and Nintendo have been kind of working together.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sega also have tried handheld and they failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't say no, but I don't think it would be Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to be somebody that's known for gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be somebody that's known for electronics.
[SPEAKER_04]: is going to try and get in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of like what Sony did when they got into the gaming market.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody who's known for electronics now is going to try to challenge Nintendo for the gaming throne.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: For handheld gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the Wii colors will come out finally this year, and I think they'll come out just in time for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to get the Wiis in the different colors finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think something will happen to address the storage issues on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the color systems are going to necessarily come with more onboard memory.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling they will, but it's not going to be a major increase, just a slight one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what do they have now, 512 megs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, 512.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say they up the internal memory to 2 gigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there'll be a firmware that will improve the SD card support.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see that, because with the price of, you know, flash RAM, I mean, it's going to... This shit gets cheaper every day, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't see why they wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could also see the DS with the onboard storage for downloadable games, virtual console for the DS, so to speak, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see something definitely like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to think what else would be.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation redesign, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Might even see a 360 redesign, especially if they get it cooler and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: and let's see, I don't want to take this on too much longer with just predictions I'm pulling out of my ass, but just, you know, I think there's a possibility some of these things will happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Nintendo, I think the big Christmas game they're going to reveal, I think Animal Crossing is going to be their big winner game, and I think it is going to be an MMO, and it is going to be a bit MySpace-y.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there is going to be a social element to it that no other game has really done yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's going to be their big winner game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I also think this will be the year that Kid Icarus is finally revived.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, call it my gut.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Guardian Legend finally comes to Virtual Console and we all collectively orgasm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see them coming out with some more peripherals for the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, what, the nunchuck and, you know, classic controller?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to fucking redesign the damn remote to, uh, or make a gun thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised someone hasn't hacked the remote yet to figure out how to get, you know, key presses from there, because...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And not to leave Microsoft out, I'm going to make a bold prediction for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say because this latest update has shown that they can do buffering video and they can do it very well, like if you watch the Inside Xbox stuff, that all works out very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Microsoft is going to make a Web 2.0 move this year, and I think you're going to see something YouTube-y come to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to be the reason to get a camera if you don't already have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But this week it's very special because these are the FUs of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So these are the things that have pissed us off the most above anything else the entire year.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off tonight with the FUs of the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess my FU of the year is going to go towards...
[SPEAKER_07]: The City of Citrus Heights for the crap they're doing regarding massage therapist business licenses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because that completely interferes with a year's worth of hard work I've put into making my business happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your FU of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have anything that's really all-consuming for the entire year, but for this week at least,
[SPEAKER_05]: F you at Nvidia and your crappy graphics drivers because for whatever reason whenever I reboot my computer not only does it not save my settings to what screen resolution I have if it did for whatever reason actually boot up in my desired resolution it flashes black and then back to the picture and blacks out again and constantly does that until I change the graphics to a different aspect ratio and then change it back it's fucking annoying
[SPEAKER_04]: and my FU of the year goes to bugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because bugs suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially flies that fly around in the room when you're trying to do a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless there's any last minute things anybody wants to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: In case you didn't catch that earlier when I was talking about it, No More Heroes has moved up to January, or at least the end of January, so it's moved up a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: You get to play the game even sooner in the United States.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there's a thing going around right now where some of the nunchucks that Nintendo has put out recently, I don't know if it's the coloring or something, but they're becoming discolored, like pink.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're less manly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I don't know if anyone saw this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there's a company called Pega, and they're releasing yet another gun peripheral for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one, though, is shaped like a shark.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called the Shark Gun.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, they were actually... They had a whole press release for this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had something... During the gunfighting game, use the Wii Remote, Nunchuck, and Shark Gun together, holding the handle of the Shark Gun and poking the trigger with your forefinger to shoot.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll bring you...
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll bring you a You Are There feeling.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's funny, though, because they have military guys on the cover shooting guns and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although they're not the shark gun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it'd be funny if the military had shark guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's enough news.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can wait until next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week on Orange Lounge Radio, we're back to our classic format.
[SPEAKER_04]: All three of us will be discussing the latest and greatest in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, your calls on Skype, as always.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who knows who might put us on hold next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got one more thing on the shark gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, this is funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one of the features on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: With lively appearance and smooth lines, Shark Gun makes you feel comfortable and gives you a strong sense of shark-like invincible force.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dustcap4
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one more, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a while since we've had a good hearty reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, for myself, DarkSakura, and Loki, everybody please have a happy and very safe New Year's Eve and New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please don't drink and drive, because if you do, you're retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's really it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you guys in 2008 for our
[SPEAKER_04]: Sixth year of broadcasting, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back next week here on Orange Lounge Radio.