[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_07]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: And welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live on this Sunday evening, December 2nd of 2007.
[SPEAKER_10]: The year's almost up.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DivX Support, and Xvid Support.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now we can play all the porn that we downloaded on our computers on our 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, the Xbox Live Arcade hits.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are going to be reduced price games that basically have been released before, sold lots of copies, and now you can buy them cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe some of those Bankshot Billiards 2 is going to be like 800 points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Luminous Live
[SPEAKER_09]: The Marketplace is getting a whole facelift.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to have things sorted completely differently.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, they're going to also have... Are they going to make heads or tails of the movies on there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because trying to find movies right now is not easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about the movie stuff, but they're going to have this kind of thing where you can... I guess people are kind of calling it a cross-media bar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's ways of sorting the live marketplace stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a whole section for free shit, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other things, Xbox Live Originals, of course, is coming up there.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Parental Timer as well, Friends of Friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, the Parental Timer made the front page of Yahoo today.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you saw that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you visit Yahoo, but it's like my homepage.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it comes up and, yeah, it was mentioning that, oh, the new Xbox will limit how much your kids can play games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Friends of Friends functionality where you can actually say, for example, Rob, I have a lot of people that are probably on your friends list that I don't have friended to mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have that enabled, I can look at your friends list, see who's on, and add people off that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, there's going to be a section where you can add a bio to your user tag where you can actually have a thousand words or whatever in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, there's also going to be a section where you put your real name and where you're located and stuff if you want to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I want people to know that about me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, if you want people to know that about you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, what else do they have in there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say I set that functionality to friends only earlier this week when the email went out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it's just a little weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, when are they going to let you... They're trying to turn the Xbox into MySpace.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's exactly what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: In a way, well, I mean, it's smart.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're capitalizing on that whole social networking phenomenon, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not my space.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I remake my profile to look god-awfully ugly in little flash graphics and web bling and glitter graphics?
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a completely... Oh man, we should have brought that up during the break.
[SPEAKER_12]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll bring it up maybe in Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other things that they're changing too, they're going to add a new Xbox Live Blade where it's going to have RSS feeds.
[SPEAKER_09]: including stuff from Major Nelson and other tidbits of information and or advertisements.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, this is all going to be available Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Frisbee says in chat room, chat.orange.com, thanks for the ad.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up, sexy gal?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is it, the...
[SPEAKER_10]: My Say Sexiest Person Alive Award Actually, if you really want to... Copy and paste this to ten people or else you'll be ugly tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, if you do have the Xbox Live Vision camera, you can send wonderful pictures like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You may have to take a picture of your computer monitor or something like that with the image on there, but you could.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or girls can just take pictures of their tits and guys can take pictures of their wangs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I approve all pictures of women's tits sent to my...
[SPEAKER_11]: Not all of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'll redirect the wangs to your wife.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just going to take a picture of someone pooing and be like, this is what I think of you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stop posting this crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Irene's going to send pictures of two girls, one cup to her whole friends list.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can make that your icon, you know, using the vision camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember a while back when Microsoft was banning people for 24 hours for questionable bio lines?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if anybody's tried Two Girls, One Cup fan to see if that gets them banned.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't see why that would be offensive, just putting something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it's not offensive.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, oh my god, you said Two Girls, One Cup.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, we ban you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, moving on to other things that will soon be on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bioshock!
[SPEAKER_10]: We've all been waiting for some more content for the game Bioshock, and a patch is going to be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually going to have downloadable content with the patch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, the patch is going to enable this downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_10]: I assume, isn't the patch supposed to fix the widescreen thing too, or has that already been done?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's going to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see, so that's the whole thing that this patch is fixing.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new downloadable content will, I assume, be a new level or something, but they don't really say a lot about what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, new plasmids.
[SPEAKER_09]: New plasmids, and there's supposed to be a new difficulty in there that's going to disable the Vita Chambers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guitar Hero 3 had a new download pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: This time in the form of some indie love.
[SPEAKER_09]: And included in there are three songs from artists you might not be familiar with.
[SPEAKER_09]: Including you get The State of Massachusetts by Dropkick Murphys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty good punk band.
[SPEAKER_09]: You Should Be Ashamed of Myself by The Bled.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Memories of the Groove by Maylene and the Sons of Disasters.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're fired, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not listening to Orange Challenge Radio anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: You fired Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: He fired me for a better view of download content for Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's one up on my lawn?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do love this show sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other times it sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xbox Live Arcade is going to be getting a classic game
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I thought we already had this game on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chess is going to be coming to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that part of the Spyglass?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Chess Master, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, it's Chess Master, specifically the Chess Master series, which was a huge series on PC, from what I remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, every year there was a new Chess Master game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But all I know is that it isn't Battle Chess.
[SPEAKER_10]: So for that, epic fail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Battleship.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want Battleship in life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Battleship is kind of hokey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you beeping over there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not... My new phone is... Because someone sunk her battleship, apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Chess Master is going to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully it's a little better and a little polished than the Spyglass thing was.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to have lots of different AI opponents of varying difficulty.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Camera support as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say, coming to Xbox Live Arcade very soon,
[SPEAKER_09]: The Sensible World of Soccer
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, soccer fans are pretty rowdy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: The game actually looked kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw a trailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never played this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: As much of a Commodore fan as I was back in the day, I didn't have an Amiga.
[SPEAKER_10]: I only ever had a Commodore 64, so I never really played this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, Sensible World of Soccer.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming to Xbox Live Arcade on December 19th.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Be excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid American.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't like soccer.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya says it looks like a Game Boy Color game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't look like a Game Boy Color game, but it does look like a Super Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an older computer system, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to look a little older.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the games on live arcade look a little crappy because they're old 80s game ports.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, it might play better than Pro Evo 2008.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, because it's sensible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xbox 360 Backwards Compatibility Update
[SPEAKER_10]: that are backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the highlights of games that are now in there, Blitz the League, Blood Omen 2, Burnout 2, Point of Impact, Fight Night Round 3, Forgotten Realms, Demon's Stone, Freedom Fighters, a lot of sports games like MVP Baseball, 03, 04, 05, NCAA March Madness, 05, 06,
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of NHL games, 2K3, 205, 2K... 2K3's on there twice, I think they cheated.
[SPEAKER_10]: NHL 2K3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, there's NFL and NHL, my bad, one letter off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Playboy The Mansion!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure a lot of folks are looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the one game on the entire list that I actually own for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tecmo Classic Arcade is now backwards compatible as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Loki owns this game, this is worth noting.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Guy Game, Worms 3D, Not Playable Still, Good Games, Rising,
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Dance Revolution series, still not playable, backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, I should be clamoring to get an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beyond Good and Evil, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: One interesting thing, the Xbox Live video marketplace is going to be coming to Europe pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is actually coming from one of those prepaid cards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, written on the back in very small print, said...
[SPEAKER_09]: You can access the Xbox Live video marketplace available in the UK, Ireland, France, and Germany.
[SPEAKER_09]: So apparently this hasn't happened soon, but the cards, being already printed, have that information on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So soon you will be able to watch videos and enjoy all the rest of the download content that we have around the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Be excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you saw this hit the internet earlier this week, but there was a video that went out on the internet that... It was kind of a social experiment, I guess you could call it, where a guy whose nickname was XGayboyX signed on to Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Triple X, Gayboy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it Triple X, GayboyX?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: He signed on to Halo 3 and basically got all these people to say, really, now...
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up, gay boy?
[SPEAKER_04]: We should hook up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Friendly Uncle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gay boy and Friendly Uncle coming at ya.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something that should be noted, because you notice, like, that isn't so bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are a few things in here that are not necessarily negative.
[SPEAKER_10]: For instance, you know, but
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows if it's somebody... You know how, like, sometimes jocks in high school would befriend the nerds on a dare type thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't know if maybe it's something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It seems pretty genuine.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, two, punch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope gay marriage never gets passed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun being single.
[SPEAKER_03]: And make it say, single boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're still a faggot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it doesn't matter, dude, because... I'm sorry, you're not a faggot.
[SPEAKER_03]: You give a bad name to gays.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're...
[SPEAKER_03]: A fucking nuke!
[SPEAKER_10]: You're a niggit!
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't worry, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I hadn't already heard all this stuff before in games, like, I'd probably be a little more shocked, but that's still very perturbing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really, like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, in a way, and I'm a little bit torn, because yes, I think these people are really fucked up, and yes, I think it's fucking sad that there's ignorant people like that out there, but at the same time, it's a little bit entrapment or provoking it when the guy goes on there with a name like Gay Boy.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I don't see it that way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why does it have to be seen as entrapment if you have a name like Gay Boy?
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Hetero Boy?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would be interested to see what Hetero Boy would
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, like, that's dumb.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, on the one hand, I'm infuriated.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of, like, livid that people would say that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I heart Jesus or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but at the same time, it's just kind of like, well, you know, successful.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was funny, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is why I only like to play with friends and OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to say, like, Fox News or somebody ran some sort of report on this, and they were talking about, like... I saw that, about the trash talk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there's some other YouTube out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Fox just did a report this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the whole thing was, like, they're all, you know, are you guys surprised that this is on there?
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're like, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, like, I remember reading some comments on that, and they're like, yeah, of course they're not surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're the ones fucking saying that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're interviewing, like, 12-year-olds and stuff, 13-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, the reason why I want to bring this up is that, you know, obviously these things make their way around the Internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if anybody, Microsoft has proven they're very good about kind of staying on top of the Internet buzz and trying to thwomp this mob mentality when they see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, one of their representatives, Trixie, was actually posting on the GayGamer.net blog post where this showed up and just trying to kind of, you know, say, hey, I think these guys are assholes too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when you see this happen, report it because we do follow up on that shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Major Nelson basically kind of says the same thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Major Nelson posts about it in his blog and says, I just watched or listened to the video you posted on your site.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what he wrote back to GayGamer.net who posted the original thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Needless to say, it was disappointing to see how some Xbox Live members behaved.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you know, that's not the type of behavior we support.
[SPEAKER_10]: With over 8 million members, it's unfortunate that some members decide to act like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to point out a few things that all Xbox Live members can do to ensure an enjoyable experience.
[SPEAKER_10]: And reiterates, you know, you can turn off voice from people that aren't your friends, only play with friends, file complaints.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he reiterates, we do act on complaints, so I highly encourage people to file complaints where appropriate.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I play on Xbox Live, if somebody is, like, being annoying, because some people will get, I swear to God, you'll get on Halo 3 and you'll get into some matches and somebody will be doing this the whole time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I swear to God, for the entire match, somebody did that to me once.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of funny, but then if I ever met that person in real life, I'd punch him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I muted the little fucker, finally, so he was just sitting there by himself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe he had a mental problem, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I was going to say, maybe he had a headache.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think the mental problem was that severe because he was kicking my ass in Halo.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other, well, maybe he's like Rain Man or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's really good at Halo, but he just says, meh, meh, meh, meh, a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, like, that could be his thing, but, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what I did, I muted him, and then I rated the fucker down.
[SPEAKER_10]: You go into the little thing, and you can rate.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know how, like, everybody on Xbox Live has a five-star rating?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, not if you play with me in Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll rate you down so fast if you get on there and say something nasty.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I had somebody get on there going, you know, n-word, n-word, n-word over and over and I reported it as abuse.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's just disgusting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, it's gross.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, why do you have to say that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Mommy and Daddy aren't looking and they're acting out to make themselves feel better about themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because Mommy and Daddy bought them an M-rated game and obviously aren't paying attention to what they do and they'll pay for their damn live account because
[SPEAKER_09]: Give Mommy and Daddy a few moments to breathe and make more babies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Frisbee brings up a good point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is he a cat?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh God, I hope I wasn't getting my ass kicked by a cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Laser cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I'd have to quit video gaming forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Man, that must be a stupid cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meow, meow, meow, meow.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't even meow right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up, cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm muting you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, my cat couldn't meow right for a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: It took her time to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I really had to restrain myself from meowing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid faggot cat, stop meowing so fucking much.
[SPEAKER_11]: N-word, N-word cat, jeez.
[SPEAKER_11]: Black Cat, what's that, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sephiroth1215 says something else really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listen to these people, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not really 12 and 13.
[SPEAKER_10]: These people are usually in their 20s.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, those people did sound a little bit older, but they sounded like hicks, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: They sounded like frat boys in a dorm room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gay boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just totally told this guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Man, I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doyle Rules!
[SPEAKER_12]: See, and they all have lame nicknames too.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's usually like, oh, Halo Lover and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or like, I love unicorns or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, how could you make fun of a name gay boy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Master Chief is my butt buddy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, and he really is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: They can't think of anything more creative.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, a more creative way to make fun of someone instead of gay boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you're gay.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you're a boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like,
[SPEAKER_11]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's just, the parts of it that are really significant to me is that people will suddenly jump on there and then they'll be like, I hope gay marriage is banned forever and you're single forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just some guy on the internet playing Halo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that hurt my ego.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't fight back in Halo now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: What am I to do?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then Nintendo looks at this shit and goes, that's why we've got friend codes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Nintendo's so smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kicking you, kicking you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, even more ridiculous news here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, there is a guy filing a class action lawsuit because he believes that Microsoft created defective copies of Halo 3 that are causing Xbox 360s to blow up everywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that wasn't Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, apparently this guy out of San Diego, Randy Nunes, is...
[SPEAKER_09]: Going ahead with a lawsuit against them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, he purchased a copy of Halo 3 from GameStop and was plagued by system lockups and freezes and crashes when he tried to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, where's the explosions?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was being sarcastic!
[SPEAKER_10]: If you blow up the 360, I'm thinking I put Halo, close it, and then suddenly, tick, tick, tick, BOOM!
[SPEAKER_10]: Sarcasm, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be actually kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd buy another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did he try a different copy of the game, return a defective one, the game stopped for replacement?
[SPEAKER_09]: The story doesn't say.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, he was using a 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a bunch of bullshit anyways, because I remember this story came out before that, oh, maybe Halo's breaking systems.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually it's because you're playing the game so much that your system's overheating.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you happen to have that overheating problem, then you get three rings of death or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the fact that this guy's getting sued for this shit, I hope he fails.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, unfortunately nowadays a lot of times these people succeed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, whenever we hear about the frivolous lawsuits, we get a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_10]: and nothing inspires our next segment like frivolous lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's time to bring on the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I guess I would say this is a pre-FU for my work review that's going to be this week, which I'm demanding a raise, which I'm sure I will not get, but I haven't gotten one in three years, and I'm well deserving of one, since I have four times the accounts that certain other sales reps do at my company.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, basically, my whole thing is I'm going to go in there and just say, okay, am I getting a review or not?
[SPEAKER_09]: And if I'm not, then I'm going to be a complete asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, fuck you...
[SPEAKER_09]: Stupid managers at my work that aren't, you know, willing to pay me a decent salary.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm already underpaid as it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I get a fucking raise, then I'll be just slightly less underpaid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go next.
[SPEAKER_10]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that I don't own a house.
[SPEAKER_10]: I rent, but I don't own.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I went to a party last night with William.
[SPEAKER_10]: These guys own this house, and it was just beautiful what they'd done with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The backyard was all, like...
[SPEAKER_10]: FU to cats that can't meow properly.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to, uh... Meow meow meow meow!
[SPEAKER_12]: Shut up, cat!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That does it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was really short.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Usually there's a lot of angst built up for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because we stopped reading chat FUs.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the same way, it got a lot shorter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, that lasted like a minute and a half.
[SPEAKER_10]: Black Labs in chat says, An internet radio will not be getting you a house, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Truer words have not been spoken.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait a minute, what?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Nonbeliever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that a chat name or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: And internet radio will not be getting you a house, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you think.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Geez.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Eidos is building me a house.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to divert our attention real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's the last minute story.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I need you to pull this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gamersreports.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: This better be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has a brand new trailer.
[SPEAKER_11]: for... for... Africa.
[SPEAKER_09]: GamersReports.com?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Gamers with an S, Reports.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aha!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: New Africa.
[SPEAKER_09]: A new Africa trailer for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we should watch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this real or is this something to be seen?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's real.
Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it has a song.
Oh, shit!
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to know what is worthy about interrupting the show with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just... I forgot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we get to find out what the hell you do in this game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't watch the whole trailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see dudes riding a jeep.
I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a retarded cat.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: So basically there's just a bunch of animals walking around.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, this is something I'm sure that's going to really show off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I fast forward a little bit?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully see if we get to the part where the animals get shot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hyena, the unicorn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where's the fucking game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where's the fucking dysentery?
[SPEAKER_12]: Goddammit, this is the most boring game ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hey!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the hippo is saying hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes me think it's Jumbo Safari, like every time I see it and I see the little... I want to be able to hit all the animals with that jeep.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is the only way I'm buying that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to summon the jeep?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, goddammit, that wasn't worth stopping the show for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, it's Africa.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I had to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, that's... It could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm all about games that are outside the box.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just kind of want to know, like, what's the catch with Africa.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_12]: What's the catch?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to be like Manhunt.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get to kill the animals in, like, crazy ways.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you take, like, a, you know... I think it's some type of exploration game, but I want to know, like, what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, stay tuned for more information about Africa.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: In six months.
[SPEAKER_12]: Woop-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Man, I'm waiting in eager anticipation for that time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Metal Gear Solid V. Let's move on to the gaming news, shall we?
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, here on Orange Dawn Radio, we like to talk about the current systems and everything the kids are playing, so that's why this next article is about the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_12]: Radical!
[SPEAKER_10]: And, yes, on the Commodore 64, somebody, with a lot of free time, has managed to make a Guitar Hero 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clone type thing for the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I shouldn't say it's a full game yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still in its concept stages.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's called Shreds 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what they did is they took their PlayStation 2 guitar and basically adapted it so that it can be read in the joystick ports.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, yeah, now they've made it so that, you know, the notes fall and it reads the guitar.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have what's called the Shredocity and the Applause.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the Applause is basically the meter, you know, how well you're doing just looking in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I guess Shredocity is...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Still kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I approve of this project.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I'm disappointed to see that we don't have a Dreamcast game yet of Guitar Hero or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, the Dreamcast has tons of games coming out for some reason, even though... Sure enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, another mod also kind of dealing with a music game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: As you remember me complaining about
[SPEAKER_09]: The drums and how loud they were, apparently a lot of people were looking for homebrew ways of making them quieter.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's a couple different methods that you can use out there, one of which is self-adhesive rubber and self-adhesive colored felt.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you basically shove that on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why does it have to be colored felt?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just so that you know which color, because if you're covering the whole drum, you're not going to know what color is what.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have to.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do all black if you're emo like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I am.
[SPEAKER_09]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's another one I saw also.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a rubber mouse pad, and you glue that on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, though, it works pretty well in reducing the sound, I guess, by 70%.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe the wife will let you play if you can reduce the sound.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way, she bought Rock Band for me, or she gave me a check for it because I paid with it, my money.
[SPEAKER_09]: But she only paid for $100 of it because she says that the remainder of the money would have been for the drum kit, and she's not supporting the drum kit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your wife is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell her we need to, I'm going to take her out.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go to Olive Garden, have a fancy dinner.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Happy Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll take her to Red Lobster if she wants.
[SPEAKER_10]: Spare no expense.
[SPEAKER_10]: BSG Something's getting postponed.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might even be altogether cancelled.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because of this damn strike.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can't cancel Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can.
[SPEAKER_12]: They sure as shit can.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest with Heroes, man, I think that's actually kind of good for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I think Heroes has been just fine this season.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just was slow to develop, like the first season.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the past few episodes have been amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Elle is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I swear to God, if they kill her off Monday, I'm going to be so pissed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: I said two of them are supposed to die.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't remind me.
[SPEAKER_10]: M&L, probably.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: Riders Strike is going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, one thing that they are not striking against is video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the Riders Guild is allowed to write for video games currently while this strike is going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_10]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_10]: did for their European ad campaign.
[SPEAKER_09]: were these two sexy models that were naked to promote the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I approve.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, did you guys see the new Wii commercial for... What game was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where they're kind of, like, sort of parodying Fast Times at Ridgemont High where the girl's coming out of the pool and they're, like, in bikinis.
[SPEAKER_12]: What game was it promoting?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, but, like, Nintendo's using sex to sell, like...
[SPEAKER_12]: What's going on here?
[SPEAKER_12]: Wholesome Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_12]: Putting girls in bikinis?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they finally figured out that sex sells?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Girls in bikinis?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, they're like two girls.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't remember what game it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was a competitive game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because there was like four people in the room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn it, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gosh, you're so good at this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Smarty Pants?
[SPEAKER_12]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Smarty Pants?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: No way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you talking to me?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it's seen it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it's not seen it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it was like...
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was a game that I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: The chat is saying Smackdown vs. Raw 08.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, maybe that's what it was, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they say it's the publisher, not Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that would be a third-party publisher.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's like, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mario Galaxy, now with more nipples.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: You should replace the stars with boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you've ever seen this game, the Nuts and Milk, which is a Japanese game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Nuts and Milk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody turned the game into just nuts, and you were a little wandering penis.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, people do the stupidest stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Irene ruled the world, even the next-gen games, you're going to collect boobies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and pandas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mostly boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boobies and pandas, the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we have Loki's World of Randomness, and Rice Princess presents Boobies and Pandas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it sounds like a good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I need a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you make?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll think about a game a little later.
[SPEAKER_10]: AJ Mix in chat says, ET the Extra Testicle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brilliant testicle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: It could be a penis that, like, gets erect so he can get out of the pit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because remember how you had to, like, extend his neck to get out?
[SPEAKER_11]: You are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, wait a minute, better watch some porn.
Boop!
[SPEAKER_11]: And, like, it'll, like...
[SPEAKER_10]: DrewNami wants to remind us about Magic Penjel, where we already did all of this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boy, Magic Penjel gets brought up at least once a month on this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, we need to go back and play Graffiti Kingdom, where it's basically like a Zelda-type game, but you can draw your own characters, so you could do...
[SPEAKER_09]: All of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Panda Boob Man!
[SPEAKER_11]: Boobies and pandas can actually be a reality?
[SPEAKER_09]: It can be a reality.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, I'm so there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or, you can get drawn to life, which you can do the same thing, just in 2D.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can make your enemies, you know, where it's giant pieces.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just flat boobies and pandas.
[SPEAKER_12]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I wanted flat boobies, I'd go to Africa.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, because every time they show the National Geographic ladies with their boobies, they're like flat and long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not always.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen some big boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: In National Geographic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I'm like, this conversation is not going to a happy place.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's talk about toys and children's toys.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: and that, you know, like all these toys have been getting recalled this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the, what was the, oh God, what was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: The dots thing that had a date rape drug in it apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was something you could use as an ingredient in creating the date rape drug.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, if you eat it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, if you eat it, it has the same effect.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has the same effect.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was that called?
[SPEAKER_10]: The dots or whatever?
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to get a bunch of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: You just want to eat it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to eat it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to make dot creations.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to make the cat eat it and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no, I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't make sure Kitty eat that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it is mean.
[SPEAKER_12]: The cat would go, ma, ma, ma, ma, ma.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's... Aquadots.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aquadots is what they were called.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyhow...
[SPEAKER_10]: According to a recent article in the Los Angeles Times, apparently because of all these recalls, apparently game publishers are seeing a 19% increase in sales because I guess games are safe and they're not going to try to drug your children as you are aware.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll just show them pictures of murder and everything like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pictures of murder, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Murder!
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you remember Manhunt 2 is murder?
[SPEAKER_10]: Murder Sims?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen, we don't need to give Manhunt 2 any more press.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the game's not that good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, this is coming from a quote from Jarek Johnson, who's an analyst from Capital Market, says, There's definitely money leaving the toy sector.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's logical to assume that video games might be viewed by some parents as an alternative.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's an analyst.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why you gotta take this show to the toilet, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just an impulse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: This picture's naughty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you doing over there on your laptop?
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't have to announce it on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, this picture's naughty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, that's real butter.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: Completely off topic here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Space Invaders Extreme.
[SPEAKER_09]: is being released for the Nintendo DS in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: And why should I even mention this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, hey, it's Space Invaders and it's a remake.
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: It kind of incorporates music a little bit to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they have a YouTube video on Joystick right now worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it reminds me a lot of Rez or even like Luminous a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's really cool looking, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, if it comes out over here, I'm definitely going to have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, it kind of changes a little bit of the pace at the end of the game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have power-ups and stuff you can get.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, each ship that you blow up kind of adds beats to the music and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's got a little, like, trippy background and stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it based on also the BPM, kind of like how they did on VibRibbon, like the speed of the stuff coming towards you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about that, but it just looks really cool, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's go ahead and move on to our mailbag segment.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangeonstrater.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to open up the mailbag and choose a few of our favorites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since DarkSakura is not here this week, I will be doing the honors, whether you like it or not.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Email number one this week comes to us from... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't sign it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to say this is from Richard M. Says, alright, I'm listening right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently this person is listening to the show right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm playing Halo 3 and blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to say hi because I haven't listened for about four weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just got an Xbox 360 and Xbox Live and I sent a request to you two, Sky and Loki and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's not there right now, but let her know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll do, but I'm sure she'll see the friends request when she logs in next.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still adding most of the other OLR members, but most are pending right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I would like to know which good games I should get.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I only have Fear, Condemned, Halo 3, and Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give me at least three games you guys think would be great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll play anything but sports games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that wraps it up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Until later, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two thumbs up for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Three games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if you like Guitar Hero 2, you probably should get Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you like RPGs, get either Eternal Sonata or maybe Blue Dragon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, try the demo first because that's getting some mixed reviews.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it's kind of a hit or miss thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how into shooters you are, but Bioshock's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to try a shooter, Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, if you're playing Halo 3, I say get Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're looking for cheap shit, I would say Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's $19.99 now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, you deserve to play that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I understand it's really cheesy and stupid, but it draws me in, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say also, well, these are a bit older, but even Saints Row's not bad, or Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crackdown I liked.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email, shall we?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is from Tensai Noob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Emails us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dear OLR crew, I have a few comments and one request.
[SPEAKER_10]: First of all, the necessary praise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I continue to admire your devotion to the show and quite impressed that you managed to release such a funny, informative podcast each week.
[SPEAKER_10]: This podcast is funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I always worry each week that I'm just kind of breezing over stories and just being too much of an ass and just talking randomness.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even know what I'm saying half the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how much quality I put into this.
[SPEAKER_10]: We start to feel we're slipping a little bit, so thank you for your kind words.
[SPEAKER_10]: It helps our egos.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that that's out of the way, a while ago you were talking about zombie games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that you don't frequently anyway, but ironic considering our game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this was an especially concentrated instance.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you were discussing how it would be great to have a game where you are the zombie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you ever heard of the game Stubs the Zombie, Rebel Without a Pulse?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, unfortunately I haven't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a really crappy game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I tried a demo of it once, and it wasn't revolutionary, but it wasn't horrible either.
[SPEAKER_10]: You control a zombie who can eat brains, turning the victims into zombie minions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take off his hand and take control of others and produce toxic farts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, this game sounds classy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I thought you might appreciate knowing about a game where you actually get to be a zombie instead of always shooting them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you weren't a big fan of that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: It just got horrible reviews.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a bad, bad game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had a funny premise to it, but... Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Secondly, again referring a number of episodes back, I would like to state that Halo 3's story does make sense, but you really need to have played the previous games and maybe even have read the books to fully comprehend it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you need any clarification, I am perfectly willing to help clear up any confusion, as I am yet another devoted Halo fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: On a related note, I completed Halo 3 first time through on Legendary in three days, so I can also provide any gameplay advice you may require, especially for later levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, my advice I need, how do I not suck so bad at it?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's impossible.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like I was thinking about buying Unreal Tournament 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: For some reason I thought there was a single player mode in it, but I'm an idiot because Unreal Tournament does not have single player.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, it does, but it's still fucking Unreal Tournament, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, ooh, I can make mods and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mods are cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm thinking like Quake, you know, back when they had mods like Cujo and the Grappling Hook.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I love Cujo and the Grappling Hook.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I'm weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to buy that game anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, also I want to say about the whole Halo 3 story thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there was a great video floating around out there that was basically Halo 1 and 2's story kind of condensed into a few minutes that was something you could watch to catch up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just haven't watched any of the videos on that second disc.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't you glad you spent all that extra money?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, the only reason I bought the collector's edition was for the video calibration tool.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is the only reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: and ironically enough, I have not used the video calibration tool yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: You tool!
[SPEAKER_10]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email comes to us from...
[SPEAKER_10]: Johnny S, because they didn't sign it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, if you don't sign your emails, I don't know what to call you, so I'll just use your first name and last initial.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm thinking about buying an 80 gigabyte PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to have Metal Gear Solid 4 and Gran Turismo 5, but other than that, is there anything else that warrants my $600?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe Resistance, Fallen Man, and depending on what kind of games you like, maybe Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ratchet & Clank, you know, my friend's been playing tons of Ratchet & Clank, and I've watched him play a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just not that impressed by it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, I didn't play any of the other Ratchet & Clank games, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: He loves Ratchet & Clank, he loves that game, so maybe that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Heavenly Sword, maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Blu-ray player?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Blu-ray's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you like online shooter games, maybe like Warhawk might be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: PlayStation Network
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they get a lot of demos and stuff that we don't get out over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: So do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to check out some of the games that are on there like Flow is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyday Shooter is supposed to be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pain just came up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That might be something I like but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then maybe if you're into Tekken 5 they have the Tekken 5 multiplayer online game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what game I strongly recommend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not playing that game unless I can hit the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only way I'm playing that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I gotta say, despite all the smack we're talking about, the gate looks fucking gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is like a game I could just sit and look at.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and you know what else I can sit and look at?
[SPEAKER_09]: Discovery Channel HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: And porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_12]: Just look at games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like to play them too.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there are a lot of people that do like to just watch other people play games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, we've got to move on and get to some more emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fergatron writes us and says, I know this email is late, but I'm seriously behind my list of podcasts.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's titled Late Entry Episode 255.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a few episodes back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take-Two Interactive had to dish out about $2 million for this hot coffee leak.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm concerned about the programmer or project manager responsible for the original hot coffee feature.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going to happen to them?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did they get lynched, raped, or mobbed by corporate?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We never really heard about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But those type of internal things are company dealings.
[SPEAKER_10]: We never know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I imagine...
[SPEAKER_10]: I imagine there were multiple people responsible for it, and it was probably part of the original concept as it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you think way back to when we were first talking about Hot Coffee, I think the whole problem was is that the mode was never taken out of the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever pointed to the mode, you know, like if you think about programming, the way it works, every game is like a giant flow chart, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically what they did, they took that arrow out that enables something to go to the sex mode and turn it on, and all that cheat did was put that arrow back in, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think one person was solely responsible for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that was part of a larger screw-up, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why the game took so freaking long to come out in its sanitized version, because they had to go back and actually take out the entire thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, if there's some content that's in the game that they leave in there, people will find it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They found stuff in Zelda, like the debug levels, they found stuff
[SPEAKER_09]: Wind Waker, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: They found stuff in pretty much any game that has stuff hidden in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Smash Brothers, hidden characters, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were getting into a talk earlier about, just want to say, before I get back to the email, because now I'm looking at chat room, and we talked about porn earlier, and DMM wanted to remind us that the porn industry actually supports HD DVD, not Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: They support both.
[SPEAKER_09]: They support wherever people are going to buy shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Legend of Zaku says Blu-ray forbids porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's bullshit because I know Pirates, that porno that's pretty funny actually, high production value, is on both Blu-ray and HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: What else did Furgatron say here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sky, you mentioned that you play a lot of WoW instead of other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm in the same situation.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have only a limited amount of time to play games, so when it comes time to play, I end up playing whatever game I can get the most out of, which ends up being WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: What server do you play on and what's your character's name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mine is... I don't know if he wants me to read this on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, if you want to find out more information about the Orange Lounge Guild that we all play on in WoW, it's all on the forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: So check it out, forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice plug, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Go to OrangeLoungeRadio.com and click on forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if my character name is posted, but if you join the guild, it won't be hard to figure out who I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, if you listen to the show long enough, you'll know.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last email tonight comes to us from...
[SPEAKER_10]: Ali, I believe it's Ali.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was listening to episode 255 part B and you just mentioned Logo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my God, I was a beast at Logo.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember me and my one friend had a working Tetris on Logo.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have no idea how hard that is.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, because the language was highly inefficient, it would go wicked slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had this running on a one gigahertz Celeron.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was called Micro Worlds on those machines.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the processor would be maxed out.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fan would be going full tilt to play Tetris.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm a nerd.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, I remember I would make some hardcore art with logo fractals and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: I only ever had logo on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: And for a reminder for those that weren't listening that week, logo is that language where you had a little turtle and you would point, you know, pen down, up 10, right 10, you know, and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was basically how people of a younger age could learn programming more easily.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you giving me dirty looks, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not giving you dirty looks, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just pooping.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, mind your own business, pal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Try not to in the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send us some more email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Skype line will be open very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have about three more stories for you guys before we get there, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: So get your dialing fingers ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, right after a few more news stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Including one talking about Boom Boom Rocket.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: So it sounds like Rice Princess was doing earlier in the corner.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like I incline rock music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I downloaded the five new songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: They are more rock influenced than Synthie, but I wasn't that impressed because they are, again, just classic remix songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: And one other thing I was going to say, I believe that you can also use the rock band drums for this as well, if you are ever so inclined.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're really bored.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, really bored.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really bored.
[SPEAKER_09]: And basically, the five songs are free for right now until December 16th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then afterwards, it's going to set you back 250 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you have a chance, get on live, get the update, get the free songs, play it later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even if you don't think you'll want to play them now, get it anyway while it's still free, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Free is always good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Free is good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless it's Yaris, in which case it's not good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you think about it, a lot of the principles you learn here, you could apply to a lot of different crafts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, who's to say you can make a weighted companion cube out of it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, is that with clay or is that like styrofoam that they're carving or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: It says the materials in it are, I quote, Okay, so it's clay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's sculpted clay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, sculpted clay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's what they use.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you actually, I guess, make a cube out of it and then carve into it and then you bake it and then you color it, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you feed it to your cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or make your cat look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Sculpey, if I remember correctly, because my sister makes a ton of shit out of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: She loves doing that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can use it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can fire it in your oven.
[SPEAKER_10]: Frisbee says that needs to be my Christmas gift.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be actually a fun Christmas gift for people.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about you guys, but I like homemade gifts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they mean a lot more than something bought at Target on clearance.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then I'll poop in a bag for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can make a lot of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys are obscene.
[SPEAKER_12]: Enough for all of my friends.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I know what you mean, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like homemade stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's make arcs and crafts together for Christmas gifts.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to get you a coaster for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't you want one of those?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to make candy with the aqua dots inside.
[SPEAKER_09]: Special Rice Krispie Treats
[SPEAKER_09]: And then another game, as I mentioned earlier, possibly going to import, Wii Fit has come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, there are lines for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of people looking to play this game, including there's going to be a lot of cool stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's yoga, which looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Balance, including they have a skiing game, soccer, ski jump, some sort of like monkey ball thing, and tight rope.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Cardio.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have Hulu Hoop, Jogging and Dancing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game is fucking expensive if you import it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like $189.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why so much?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that just because of the shipping and everything?
[SPEAKER_09]: Import.
[SPEAKER_09]: The import fees can't be that high.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's high demand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Christ.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still might get it though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, you're insane.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why can't you just wait a few months for the version to come out here in the US?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I have bonus money to burn and I can do it that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give me money!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll spend it on a good cause.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you're crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello everyone!
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Rice Princess's other BF, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, Rice Princess's better half.
[SPEAKER_10]: Her other BF.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, other boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, whoa.
[SPEAKER_10]: Competition.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know she poops a lot, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: And fart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't forget that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first thing I want to talk about is the whole GameStop charging more money for accessories.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I've seen them do this on a regular basis because when Beatmania came out, I went over to Best Buy and they had it for like, I think it was $59.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I went over to GameStop, they had it for $69.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, normally the games are known price everywhere else, but when it comes to anything with an accessory, they're known for charging $5 to $10 more for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why you gotta shop around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they price match there, out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because they don't advertise.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus that they do a lot of sales with used games and stuff, they don't price match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's why you want to do your research before you go out and buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, sometimes GameStop may have the best deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, you know, Final Fantasy XII had that collector's edition that was only available at GameStop, had some extra stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, sometimes it's a good place to get games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But sometimes you're better off going somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did go to GameStop to get my collector's edition, but other than that, there wasn't going to be one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have gone to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember when Nintendogs first came out, I ended up going to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to go to GameStop, but that day I found out there was a $5 gift card or something you would get if you bought it at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why that website, CheapAssGamer, that's why that website is so insanely popular.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that's like gamers getting together to share their resources about where to find the best deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoever thought of that, honestly, genius idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Genius idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wish I'd thought of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm jealous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I want to talk about this whole controversy of this guy getting fired over his honest review of Kane and Lynch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to open up into a lawsuit for wrongful termination because I think it's really fucked up that someone gets fired for their honest opinion on something, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, is that fair?
[SPEAKER_10]: But Ranma, like I said earlier in the show, we don't know for sure that's the reason yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: and especially in the state of California where this guy works, we have this whole law about the whole at-will employment where basically an employee can leave an organization no questions asked.
[SPEAKER_10]: An employer can terminate them essentially no questions asked.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of to avoid those types of situations.
[SPEAKER_10]: In order for him to claim wrongful termination, it would almost have to be like they were setting him up in a way or they were like entrapping him into this or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be kind of
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: At the same time, if you're a talented writer, maybe he'll decide this whole thing has him jaded from the games industry and he's going to go review movies or go write for a newspaper.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really up to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there are other states that are like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know here in New York, it's not at Will State, they have to find a reason for you to be fired unless you're like during your first 30 or 90 days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then they can just like, oh, fired, done, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Ranma, do you have any other comments or anything else you want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Last thing and then I'll be on my merry little way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm probably one of the few people in the chatroom that's really against this whole Activision Vivendi buyout thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just really appalled by it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you sure you're not being a little tinfoil hat-ish?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's so scary about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that Activision is like one of the last
[SPEAKER_05]: long-running independent game publishers going back to the 70s they have like this long decorative career of great things that they've done and now boom they're part of some like multi-global unit it's like look at Atari for example they more like a good thing going and then Infogrames bought them renamed it to Atari and now look at them I guess that's true
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess maybe this is just a little bit of fear, but, you know, mergers aren't necessarily always a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, Square Enix didn't work out so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just find the Square Enix merger funny because Square's doing more profits than Enix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enix walks up, I know it, what a big thing of cash.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're like, hi, we're buying you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is that this is not really like a merger per se.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that all the venue has just like a controlling stake in the company.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't said it's a merger or anything, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, we'll see if your tinfoil hat things come true or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope not, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not scared yet, but, you know, yeah, when we start seeing the whole, you know, the orcs and tauren showing up in Guitar Hero, then I will be a little scared.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens, as you said.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, take care, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: We gotta get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1877-GAME-OLR is the magic number to call, or you can give us a call on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is our username on Skype.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Puppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Puppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, Puppy?
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of stuff, but mostly just a lot of rock band issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did your stuff break?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my guitar got that bad strum bar problem that's been popping up with a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you can fix that yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but I'm not that handy with electronics, so I'd rather not risk tinkering with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you're just lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really isn't that hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: You basically unscrew the back, and what it is is the contact switch in there gets kind of,
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess turned, and all you have to do is just loosen the screw, line it back up, and tighten it again.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then you're good to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That doesn't sound too hard when Loki says it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've actually got my thumb away already, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, though, they actually are giving away free games, too, if you have your guitar fixed.
[SPEAKER_10]: You get a free game with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they haven't said what the game is yet, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I read that story earlier and I think it said that people that had put their origin for replacements like a week ago and it was getting delayed because of a lack of stocks and they were getting that free game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I think I heard our old buddy Bobby Blackwolf talking about that because he's been having problems with not just the drums but now his guitar as well and they sent him an email because his drums got delayed but then they told him it was the guitar in the email so he's just all kinds of confused.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was listening to that on his show this week and it just kind of
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I've used my Guitar Hero 3 controller for my guitar My guitar actually started acting up only like 4 or 5 days after I got the system And...
[SPEAKER_08]: It just got progressively worse, and now it's to the point where the downstream doesn't work at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the Guitar Hero 3 controller works on Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_08]: My Guitar Hero 3 controller, my wireless one, does work.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's only the PlayStation 3 version that does not play nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I thought that worked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, maybe I'll get the Guitar Hero 3 controller then, because I do kind of want a wireless controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: The wireless controller is nice, but I like the design for the Rock Band controller a lot better.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the design on the Rock Band controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a bummer that they're having all the problems they are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully by the time they start selling them separately next year, they can fix some of those problems.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really hope so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that would be nice, because having an extra controller would be good for parties and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just that you didn't get Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure there's very few of those people out there at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much, other than the fact that I finished Assassin's Creed and I jumped up and screamed at the ending.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard the ending is kind of shocking a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be very curious about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't want to go into detail and spoil it, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't see it coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't the ending supposedly kind of a trip, too?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the ending itself is really trippy, and the way it's kind of set up is that they basically knew ahead of time that this was going to be a trilogy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the beginning is weird, too, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I first started, I'm like, okay, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_08]: This doesn't look like a game in the Crusades.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It took me a good two or three hours into it before I started to catch the whole timeline of the game, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, Puppy, we've got to let you go to get more calls, but thanks so much for the call, all right?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you have a call you want to get through to us, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio is the username on Skype.
[SPEAKER_10]: Waiting for a call to drop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good evening, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, if you haven't bought Mass Effect, buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the game of the year.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm waiting on Pins and Needles to check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm supposed to be borrowing my friend's copy very soon, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got a free copy from my buddy at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, that is not why I called.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have called because I think everybody who listens to this show...
[SPEAKER_06]: should thank you, Loki, DarkSakura, and everybody else who reports news on this station because we don't get paid to do a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reason I say this is the story that led into the show tonight was Jeff Kurtzman getting fired from GameSpot over his review of Kane and Lynch, which was an acceptable review.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody gave that review the most of seven across the board, and the fact that Eidos...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's the most lowest, unobjective thing I've ever seen a media publication do.
[SPEAKER_10]: But again, do you think you might be filling in some gaps with hearsay, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only thing I'm kind of challenging here is that, you know, yes, we know Eidos pulled the ad campaign, but did they necessarily do it because of the bad review itself?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did they maybe do it because of all this, you know, fallout that happened because of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, I was going on Eidos' forums this morning, and I saw people, you know, telling Eidos, shame on them for doing what they did, and those threads were getting locked and deleted, which means I think Eidos...
[SPEAKER_06]: knows a little more than they want to say about the situation.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just hate the gaming companies being so intimidating.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I recall, we had Beautiful Katamari.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had an exclusive release date, and we were intimidated by Namco to pull that because, I want to say, what was it, 1UP?
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently bought the rights to that, which I think is retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think anybody should ever have to buy news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Money should not be involved only when it's purchasing games and or the gaming review magazines.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that the companies should be in bed with the gaming review magazines ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It creates bad situations like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to blow things wide open.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to make a lot of these publishers look bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eidos has lost my business.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to buy Conan I, Boring Adventures.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm taking my $50 and going elsewhere with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to say, as we referenced earlier in the show, and you do definitely bring up a sore subject around these parts, but it's a fair comparison, so fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, it just kind of goes to show you that there's a lot of shady things that go on behind the scenes, and that's why a lot of this corporate stuff
[SPEAKER_10]: has a very sour taste in my mouth a lot of the times.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm, if anything, you know, I'm kind of very interested to see how, you know, whether it be mob mentality or not, there's going to be a lot of people that are going to open themselves up to getting the news from gamers who aren't necessarily paid to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just kind of, I'm very interested to see, you know, kind of where that takes us, the independent folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I would honestly say if this were to happen to Orange Lounge Radio, the same situation with an editor,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that's just kind of the difference, but we're not, you know, we don't pretend to be a money-making corporation either.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that's why we're not making money.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of the sad thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're making tons of money, you just don't know about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's my cut?
[SPEAKER_10]: I blew all of it on crack.
[SPEAKER_10]: DMN, anything else you want to share with the listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to get some more calls, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's raining like hell in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for the weather report, DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to log you out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was an even better report than the forecast channel, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got more calls ringing off the hook tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: RavensDolphin.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you, RavensDolphin?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just want to shed some more light on the Gershman trial.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not Gershman trial, the Gershman thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, not a trial yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: See what this is?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on a minute, Ravens.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, this is exactly what happens when you play the internet game of telephone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now suddenly on a blog it's going to show up, oh my god, the Gersman firing case goes to trial.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard it on OLR, it's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, no one will believe that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right, no one believes the poo that falls out of our mouths every Sunday night on this program.
[SPEAKER_10]: If the corporate sites are to be believed.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_00]: When does that particular show come out?
[SPEAKER_00]: Wednesday
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the day supposedly he was canned.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's use the word allegedly.
[SPEAKER_10]: That makes it sound professional.
[SPEAKER_10]: Allegedly Wednesday was the day he was locked out of the office and his boxes were thrown out on the curb.
[SPEAKER_00]: That just sounds wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to feel like I'm going to feel dumb if this happens when he goes like, well, it wasn't over Kane and Lynch or he had some...
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, the gaming community would owe these guys one hell of an apology if that came to light.
[SPEAKER_00]: Never gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: DMN wants to know, did the podcasters over on GameSpot sound morose?
[SPEAKER_00]: DMN wants to know, did the podcasters over on GameSpot sound morose?
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Is she a lawyer?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, she is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course she is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: We would never do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, it's just funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's being buried in there now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm surprised she hasn't called in, but she's probably sleeping if she flew back tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, yeah, it's a lot of answers to come next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think this is going to be one of the hot coffees of 2007.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we're going to see this pop up again before we know it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can tell you this, as a person that likes GameSpot, and I'm the person that, I always go to GameSpot for my things, I always reference to them, and this is kind of just, I just can't just go there anymore and trust them anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: I respect them, I respect Jeff for giving an honest review of the game, even though that it got pulled, we don't know until Tuesday, so I respect him for that, and I hope he gets a better job.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I gotta say, GameSpot was one of my more... If I was going to go look at corpse sites, it was probably one of the ones I...
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was better written.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a pretty good written.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was very professional in a lot of the stuff I read.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the corpse sites feel a little unprofessional to me, but that particular one felt professional in some of the things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because obviously when we were in the news a lot because of Beautiful Katamari and the Konami thing, we saw what some of these sites were writing about us, and I thought GameSpot was probably the most fair.
[SPEAKER_00]: They put it in the rumor control instead of the other.
[SPEAKER_00]: They mention your name.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Raven Stolfen, any other quick thoughts?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm echoing, so we've got to let you go here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to give us a call, we'll take a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: 877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, a little special hello from Rice Princess over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like your avatar on Skype, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's some girl with big boobies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, boobs are the win.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think this is going to star in Rice Princess' upcoming game, Boobies and Pandas.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, what's on your mind, Footy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, of course, it has to be this whole thing with games, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's two things.
[SPEAKER_01]: First off, when people are actually looking for reviews, they don't go to one place alone.
[SPEAKER_01]: They go to all of the places, and they make an evaluation, a general consensus of what they think they want to think of the game after they read all the reviews, not just one review.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: and not because of what was written, because I'm sure that what he wrote is the same thing that everybody else wrote.
[SPEAKER_01]: The problem with that is that not only were they an advertiser, but also the number didn't fit with the PR department, which is usually the problem with everything in this gaming industry that we're in.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, like, you know, we're making this sound like, oh, you know, whatever, this is a huge deal, but in truth, it happens every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just so happens that this guy, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone did comment on the joystick story that they wrote on this thing, and apparently it's someone from inside GameSpot, and the guys actually said how the process went, and apparently the management in GameSpot changed, and now it's just a bunch of suits, and apparently this kind of thing is going to keep happening in GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know, but after this huge backlash, money rules everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if it's true that people are canceling their accounts not just by the hundreds but by the thousands, then there are board of directors that are over those suits, and those suits will be out very soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you sure about that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean the thing is that suits are there for a reason.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the reason why they bring them in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Money changes everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember that old song?
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's true that people are canceling their accounts
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to see games go under, I don't, but already they lost credibility.
[SPEAKER_01]: and not the editors.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the editors themselves, if they go somewhere else, they're going to have the credibility back.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if they go, if they stay there like scaredy cats and you will never know if their writing is their honest opinion or something that they're doing just because they don't want to lose their jobs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was going to say, they may not have a choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: They may have families and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: The job market is not that easy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I mean, trust me, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the thing is like we as gamers and as consumers who are about to spend whatever money, okay, not me because I pirate everything, but people who actually pay for stuff, you know, like they want to know what they're paying for.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's not fair for them to buy crap because you don't know if they're lying to you when they're supposed to be telling you the objective truth.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, I mean, for some reason, there's a reason why it's journalism, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a niche, but it's journalism, a kind of journalism.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they're supposed to be objective.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if money's in the way, I forgot who was the caller that said that, but if money's in the way, then forget it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole thing gets screwed, and the only way we're looking at it is everything's going to be Game of the Year material because we never know who's going to be paying for the paycheck at the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more thing, then we've got to wrap up and let you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dr3ev, or whatever this guy's name is in chat, who I can't pronounce his name, I'm sorry, says, FootyMonster takes payola for RPG reviews.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are these accusations true?
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish they were.
[SPEAKER_01]: Trust me, the minute it happens, I'm buying myself a 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just know it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, so far, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: About that, guys, you need to check out The Witcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: Such a good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: What system is this on?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's PC only?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's PC only.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I don't have a great setup.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a really crappy video card, like a 60-bug video card.
[SPEAKER_01]: It works exceptionally good in medium detail, but it's such a fun game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, obligatory plug, check for the review on The Ultimate Quest.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Witcher?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Witcher, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's based on some Polish guy's books, and it's actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've heard of this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: It sounds like a scary game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, I'll check it out, footy.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a scary game at all, but it has sex, which is good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, sex is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm there.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, footy, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye, footy.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's going to do it for calls tonight, because we're looking at two long segments tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess doing a short show last week has made this show very large this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we've got to go around and start getting everybody's final thoughts, but not before we get some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, do you have any last-minute stories for us tonight, by chance?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, that's a first.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a slow week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I mean, there's been a couple huge bombshells, like, of course, the GameSpot thing and everything, and the Activision Vivendi thing, but then, yeah, the rest of it's been kind of a quiet week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, American Idol 2 for February.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: PlayStation 3, 360 Wii, PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very interesting considering Harmonix and Konami aren't in bed together anymore, are they?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could still make it, though, without them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just pooped.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, and Disney Channel Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: When's that coming out?
[SPEAKER_09]: January.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: If at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: It keeps getting delayed.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rice Princess, thanks so much for being here tonight, even if you didn't contribute much besides your poop jokes.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: We always appreciate having you here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, then.
[SPEAKER_10]: You contribute so much to this program.
[SPEAKER_10]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, any final thoughts from you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have a lot of games to play this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably won't get to most of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is I need to charge my iPod so I can listen to lots of podcasts tomorrow at work because I'm writing tomorrow so I want to be able to listen to podcasts and music.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need a new job.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope your employers don't listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think my manager knows how to operate a podcast anyways, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know I have coworkers that listen to this show sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: They like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but seriously, though, I mean, I need a new job.
[SPEAKER_09]: This doesn't pay enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: The problem is, though, in the area that we're at, like, since we don't live in the Bay Area, you know, there's not, like, game companies all over Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Bay Area is a highly competitive job market, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I hear there's a couple job openings at GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's in the Bay Area, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to be an editor.
[SPEAKER_09]: You could take the train over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't write.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can hardly see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you imagine Loki's game reviews on GameSpot?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, this game sucks!
[SPEAKER_10]: There wasn't enough boobs!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I would be objective, but you know, I just honestly, when we're talking about games during our Game of the Week and stuff like that, I can't go into an in-depth review about stuff, because honestly, I don't play a lot of stuff, and I don't have the free time to
[SPEAKER_09]: Review a game every week or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have enough time to play anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: You barely have enough time to do this damn show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I barely have enough time to do this damn show.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would love to do a review show.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the things I'm planning on doing with my...
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyhow, I guess we'll see what the future holds in 2008 for Loki and, you know, all the rest of us here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meantime, thank you guys so much for downloading and supporting independent podcasting by listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you like what you heard, please tell two friends about our station because then when everybody tells two people, slowly we take over the world.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you don't have any friends, I'm sorry to hear that, first of all.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can make some friends on our forums at OrangeLoungeRadio.com, but you can also...
[SPEAKER_10]: Leave us a review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fair as well because we need some more five-star reviews on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: We haven't gotten any in a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: That kind of makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make me happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Leave some more five-star reviews this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you so much for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!