[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of January 2nd, 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy New Year, everybody!
[SPEAKER_06]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio about video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the news that you true gamers really want to know about, because we care.
[SPEAKER_06]: and we want to tell you what's going on in the gaming world, even during a slow news week such as this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope you all had a great new year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope you all had a safe new year.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me as always, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: The world couldn't handle more than one of me.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sober.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were taping right after our live show, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did a little bit of drinking on tonight's live show, so Loki and I are a little tipsy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're safe about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I live here, and Loki brought the fiancé to drive, so we're just having fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make this a little more chatty on these slow news weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, and I'm not throwing up today, so that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we do this before?
[SPEAKER_04]: We've done a drunken podcast before, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've done it before where I haven't thrown up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was that one time that I kind of miscalculated how much alcohol I was consuming.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was sitting on the floor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Over there in that corner, Loki, since I haven't introduced you, but you're talking anyway, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, here I am, 13 shots down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drinking my drink of choice, which would be a screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try to shy away from that next time just because orange juice is so acidic it kind of upsets my stomach if I drink too much of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: My gaming week has been filled with lots and lots of Animal Crossing and a little Popolo Cross whenever I could get the PSP away from Dan.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, he has actually gone back and gotten rid of some of our games like Smackdown vs. Raw and his copy of Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_00]: So for those who had Dan on their friends list, he may as well take them all because he ain't playing.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he picked up Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the joystick, which I haven't used, but I've heard both ways about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hear it's pretty nice, but people have their own preferences.
[SPEAKER_00]: That game, though, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to quote something from my husband's live journal, which I think is probably one of the most accurate descriptions of Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is the quote here.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's dead or alive again with really good backgrounds, bad hair, and 100% more hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, what they did, they've gotten rid of some of the recovery time in that game and you have to be freaking fast to do your counters.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's so much harder.
[SPEAKER_00]: And on top of that, the boss is like naked Liquid Kasumi and it's like she's, you know, scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: OMG, spoiler.
[SPEAKER_00]: So?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, naked.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I needed to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: but it's it's just she's ridiculously hard ridiculous that game is just ridiculously hard but the endings are freaking hilarious so all right uh Loki what about your gaming week my gaming week was also filled with a lot of Animal Crossing just I don't know the game is easy to play for like you know 10 minutes or whatever so I've been actually trying to pay off my
[SPEAKER_04]: Need for Speed Most Wanted
[SPEAKER_04]: And that game is pretty sweet for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very impressed on the graphics for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the storyline that they have kind of going along with it is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I definitely like what they've done with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of very involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very similar to like a Fast and the Furious type of storyline, you know, where your car basically gets...
[SPEAKER_04]: You lose your car in a match and you have to bring yourself back from nothing to winning the top of the blacklist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically becoming the most wanted driver out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's very...
[SPEAKER_04]: Project Gotham Racing 3 Project Gotham Racing 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Project Gotham 3 is very similar to Gran Turismo, whereas this game is a Need for Speed Underground type game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The physics aren't exactly accurate to the cars or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall, though, I've played the game not too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it for about 30 minutes or so today, and I've gotten through kind of the intro storyline stuff and have actually gotten into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty cool so far, and I like the way that they've done, like, they have live actors in the actual game, but they've kind of blurred them out and kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Desaturated the actors so it kind of blends in with the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very stylistic but it's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I played that a lot and of course my standard Grand Theft Auto, Liberty City Stories I've been playing a lot of Grand Theft Auto multiplayer and of course Call of Duty 2 multiplayer which I love those games and seriously if you haven't picked up Grand Theft Auto, Liberty City Stories I highly recommend it for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is definitely one of the games to have
[SPEAKER_04]: for the PSP, and if not anything, just to play around with...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Trainer, which I'll go into later.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week, I've also been playing a little bit of Animal Crossing because I took such a break from it because I was playing Final Fantasy Advance 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also was playing a crapload of H.E.R.O., an old school Atari 2600 game that I was playing on GameTap just because I used to play that game all the freaking time on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: And although the Atari 2600 version really sucks in comparison, it's still one of the better Atari 2600 games and highly underrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the fact that I have the second highest score of all time right now on the leaderboards over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm working on number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just because no one plays it because people don't remember that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm working on number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's within reach.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, with the one gaming site that does the rankings and stuff, you can actually get... Oh, the... I can't... It escapes me right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: We saw them at Classic Gaming Expo and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing actually certificates now for if you...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you are a Nintendo geek when... And then all these lists of Nintendo things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't read them because I'd make it upside down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Press up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that only works on Konami.
[SPEAKER_06]: You spent your summer vacation in Hyrule.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, and actually one of my friends in Animal Crossing has a town named Hyrule.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_00]: When Final Fantasy 3 came out over here, I said that I had the flu and stayed out of school for a week to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this is radio, but she did the 3 with quotes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really 3, but 3 does.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura got me the shirt, but Loki got me a copy of Mario & Luigi Partners in Time for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I finally got a chance to check out this game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very...
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, there's not a lot I can say about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you enjoyed Mario & Luigi Superstar Saga, this is almost the... It's a real true sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very similar.
[SPEAKER_06]: The look is the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: They haven't changed what worked in that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if you're a fan of Super Mario RPG, these games are for you, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's... Even though...
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Mario Superstar Saga, Paper Mario Super Mario RPG
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, they need to have another Super Mario RPG just to come out, because that game was so solid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a really good game overall, even if Square was in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just was an awesome game, and they never really are going to touch that level of gaming ever again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, though, about Partners in Time, and maybe I just haven't played enough into it yet, so I reserve the right to change my mind later, but
[SPEAKER_06]: I think these games tend to get overrated a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they get looked at as revolutionary or something because they're not like your typical RPG because you press buttons along with the fighting to make it more interactive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just fight, monster, go, you know, type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You actually hit the button at the right time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know though, to me...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it... It seems to get a little repetitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like I'm always hitting the button at the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm always dodging the same attack.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it doesn't strike me as so freaking revolutionary as I think a lot of people tend to label this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't lavish all this best game of the year praise on it, but I think it's good, and I recommend the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think there's better RPGs, but it's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I don't want to get hate mail because...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not that I'm afraid of getting a hate mail, I don't care, but it's the type of thing where it's, you know, I like the game, but I just don't think it's outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way, there's some that may stand out Nintendo DS games anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and this is a pretty good... If this was a year ago, I'd agree with you, but now, come on, we got Mario Kart, Meteos, and... Where the fuck else would you see something like Trauma Center?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let me put it this way, okay, this game is good, it's worth picking up, I mean, Nintendo DS games aren't that expensive, you can spend the $30 it is gonna be...
[SPEAKER_04]: To pick up this game, I mean, it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other game that's going to be coming out that's going to be worth picking up is going to be actually Electroplankton, and that's actually only on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be able to find that, because they're only selling it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably because they think it's too collective of a game, so that one's actually coming out in about a week or so from now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get into some news this week and talk about what's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we might as well start it off with a story on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, tell us what's going on with the Walmart and the kiosk and all this crazy 360 stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well Walmart for one, they've actually had a sale that was going on for the first of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were doing their New Year's Day sale and each Walmart was supposed to be getting 12 360 systems, the premiums of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we at the point now where we could actually walk into stores and find these yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because what about this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a story on Dig.com earlier this week where it's like, search your local Best Buys for 360s.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I noticed some were popping up in the area, but I didn't believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wasn't going to waste a tank of gas to go down there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not believe those things were staying.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I did post that in my live journal.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually some in the area that said they had them in stock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, personally, I don't know if you had to go and ask if they had them, because I did not see them on the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking, actually, at their games, because I had a gift card to Best Buy, and I was checking out what they had, and it looked very picked through.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a few 2K games and Quake 4 and stuff, but there's nothing that really, you know, striked me as, like, ooh, I gotta have this, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why, but it's in the best interest for the gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this was kind of a sale thing that they were doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were stockpiling them for the sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm assuming probably they're all sold out now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, however, you still want to be checking back with your GameStop because they're still trying to fill their pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Best Buy, they should be getting some in each week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, they're probably not going to be on the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're probably going to have to ask and see if they have them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I've heard that Sam's Club has a lot of them coming in and Costco, those type of places.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to check and see if they've got them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely, at this point, probably don't pay over retail for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can probably find them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be hard right now because they're still trying to get them out in three different markets.
[SPEAKER_04]: The European, Japanese, and U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they can only make so many.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of tough right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's funny you mention Xbox 360 sales in Japan because I'm actually looking at an article from Nintendojo who ran an article on Japan sales from December 19th to the 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, why is Nintendojo running a story on the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're not.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually talking about, hey, the Nintendo DS is the top-selling toy in Japan this week before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I don't think Christmas is quite the same as it is here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But nevertheless, the DS sold 597,628 units to be number one for the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PSP, 161,332 units, making it number two.
[SPEAKER_06]: But get this, Xbox 360, the seventh number.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most Largest Selling System, is that most large?
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
5,674.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would completely understand that because if you think about it, a lot of the RPGs that are supposed to come out didn't come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Elder Scrolls for one for the US didn't come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not coming out until I think March now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, it is to make the game a lot better because they figured out how to kind of utilize the
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DOA 4 in Japan
[SPEAKER_04]: 3 or 4 big large RPGs that were coming out for the 360 in Japan which is sad because I wish we had gotten some of those over here as well but anyways they were supposed to be getting them and they've gotten delayed and pushed back I think it's probably because a lot of these companies out there that haven't had the 360 dev kits for long enough and they've realized either A they've
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Wash 360 Kiosk
[SPEAKER_06]: Got it hacked somehow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently the disks for the kiosks were rushed so badly that they didn't actually sign them and they weren't encoded.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you can actually get an image of the kiosk disk and download it on your favorite hacker or BitTorrent or whatever site.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that we endorse that, but we're just reporting on what's out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can download that and actually burn it onto a DVD and run it straight on your 360 and
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, that has opened up a lot of things, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, first off, a few things we've noticed on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live game, they had a demo for Hexic HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Shockwave file.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually a compact flash type game that's on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can actually run that in Internet Explorer if you wanted to.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no wonder these PopCap games seem to port over so easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's just running a Shockwave file.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I kind of feel that it's a bit of a rip-off if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're paying $10 for these games, and they're actually Compact Flash.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if it's a really good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, this does open up a lot of things because now you can actually develop applications for it and rename them to these files and run them in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it opens up a huge store for homebrew stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other thing I was actually looking forward to was the fact that
[SPEAKER_04]: These demo kiosks, if you've seen them out there, you can actually bring your Xbox 360 memory unit and download themes.
[SPEAKER_04]: These themes actually correspond with the faceplates you can buy for your 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Rod, Flames, Woodgrain, whatever they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing is, the files in these themes are actually ping files and you can actually replace them with
[SPEAKER_04]: Your own graphics to create custom themes.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is we haven't figured out completely 100% on how to define where these files end or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you can't make your custom themes yet, but it's close.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be coming out with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So tell me this real quick, and then we'll move on to something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because my mind's still back here on the whole rename the Flash thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So possibly if we could get an emulator, and I know they exist already, an NES emulator in Flash.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could run on this, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, a Nintendo game and rename it and put it on a disc with just this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is what's great about this is you can actually create your own CD with
[SPEAKER_04]: just this hexic demo or whatever in it and you can put your Flash stuff on there so you can in effect use this file to create your own homebrew with using Flash programs so you can run Flash on the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it amazing that all we want to do with these new systems is play the old ones like with the PSP?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the thing that's most interesting about this is that the fact that Microsoft was touting that their game system was going to be unhackable and yet they make this
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got this big huge opening where all the simulation is possible and what they're working on is actually getting to run ISOs on it so that you can run the games that they have ripped off the discs.
[SPEAKER_06]: God of War
[SPEAKER_06]: 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Darwinia
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: For PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the game basically... I love a comment on here.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, Darwinia proves that the little guy can create something beautiful even if no one is smart enough to actually buy it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Three, Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really buy into the hype on Shadow of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was a little... It was a pretty game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a very boring game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It didn't click with me, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number two, Resident Evil 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Psychonauts was a good game, but I think it was maybe a bit underrated, but still...
[SPEAKER_04]: Average.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't like, you know, wow, it's completely different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, the whole game involved you using psychic powers or whatever to, like, manipulate different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was also done Advent Rising, which is another game that came out very similar to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a very revolutionary game, but a good game overall.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we might get some letters on that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of letters, you can always email us at togoe at orangeloungeradio.com and DarkSakura will dig through our mailbag with her nails and her claws.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she'll dig out the best letters and read them here on air.
[SPEAKER_00]: With hot pokers.
[SPEAKER_06]: togoe at orangeloungeradio.com is the address to send those emails to.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what are the kids writing in about this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually...
[SPEAKER_00]: Macman has been writing in quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I've gotten more from Actman than I have from Rob.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think he's written in at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe he's on vacation for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_06]: He needs to write.
[SPEAKER_06]: I keep thinking of Mathman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember Square One Teeth?
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerd++!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have gained a level.
[SPEAKER_00]: Minus one charisma.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Minus one INT.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Be better.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just going to quote, and I actually cc'd you on this email.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, Loki, of course, whatever you want to say about Max, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make my day, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: You were looking at porn.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the few fun things to do on a PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Zing!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you couldn't do that on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't like Macs because they're cookie-cutter PCs, as I like to call them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because you... Just, this debate is... This debate is so 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is so 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, Krispy Kreme-y.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who's one of our newest people on our website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Donut.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheesecake donut.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fattening donut.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Said that our mention on the podcast was so cool that he ran upstairs and told his parents.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what to think of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad that parents are involved with what their kids are listening to because this show may not be appropriate for everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just think it's very cool that he's looking forward to the same game I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: We will
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that special game where you do stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the stuff game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: We got an email from Delta One.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's actually a
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to say, pretty insightful as far as the... Okay, where'd the ferret go?
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't resist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Suddenly I'm thinking of StarFox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did I say StarFox?
[SPEAKER_00]: You got that from me.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarFox.
[SPEAKER_06]: The old game, StarFox.
[SPEAKER_00]: On the way up here, I asked, I am Robin, asked if you wanted anything from StarFox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vodka and OJ, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I was thinking of StarFox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was thinking Star Fox because I watched Symphomy.
[SPEAKER_06]: She said Star Fox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, we're going to get that explicit tag if you're not careful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop using that F-bomb.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: He said, you mentioned briefly in your last podcast that the region coding for Japan and the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: will be the same with Blu-ray technology.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you know if this means imported Japanese games will play on U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: systems and vice versa, or does it only apply to movies?
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks, and I enjoy the podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, actually, it will mean that both games will play on the same systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, they probably won't put English language in there, so you're kind of screwed in that sense, but yeah, you will be able to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Couldn't, well, but couldn't they do, because we don't really know what PS3 is all about yet, couldn't we see some type of Sony-enabled protection?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think they really care?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, actually Europe and Africa are sharing a region code, so they will not be able to play any of the American or Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that makes sense because they're TVs, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly, they're PAL.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it doesn't matter if you have an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or a computer monitor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not everybody's going to be on HDTV for five years at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking, though, by this next generation of gaming, we are going to start getting to one unified format for the entire world, which would be nice, because then we'd be able to get the games released at the same time instead of waiting, I don't know, six months to release Katamari Damacy, you know, We Love Katamari or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be until we get to like Playstation 4 and that whole gen of games and whatever else decides to come out around then until we start seeing the more like mandatory HD and all that stuff that you guys talk about but that's years and years away assuming there's not another video game crash as some people are predicting actually they're talking about boom in the market so yeah apparently the arcade market's picked up a bit yeah I don't really just from some of the things I've been hearing you know Sega's getting back into into some of that too
[SPEAKER_06]: God bless Sega for showing some love to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, you know what we need is Planet Harrier on something at home.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I freaking love Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other letters for us this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I actually basically replied the same and got a pretty excited response from that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, we have an email from one of our long-term fans, AsianBuddyPaul.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's he doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just to quote this letter, Happy New Year, Sky, DarkSakura, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just wanted to wish you guys another great year of awesome podcasts and memorable live shows.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have good feelings about 2006 for gaming and everything in general.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh, the announcement.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think this is a quote on here for PS3 Revolution Year of the Dog.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dogs are lucky.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought that was pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both shows will actually be taped live Sunday nights on our station.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're kind of fusing the two shows we have together right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to fuse those shows together so that you, the listener, can actually participate more in our show by calling in, being in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to have a whole new level of listener interactivity that's going to go into our podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're going to hear a lot of those changes starting on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: More information available on OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: We also did get another email from MacMan about having trouble using our site to get into the IRC chatroom.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which, you know, it goes hand-in-hand with what you're saying about us having that interactive level with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm thinking maybe we should look into having some sort of Mac-related...
[SPEAKER_00]: Link off of our website.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have any... Well, I know Java would work on any system, but okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: With any IRC client, hypothetically, you should be able to connect to any other side IRC as the network, other side IRC, and our chat room is Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I warn you guys, outside of our live shows, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday nights, it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Not too active.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of on the dead side.
[SPEAKER_06]: But once in a while we do have our regulars who keep an eye on things and who are policing things that will talk to you if they're there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is more active, though, in our forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: The forums.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, if you sort of want to get an idea of what things are like in our chat room, if you go onto our forums and look at the quote thread under our random chatter, get an idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Such randomness.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else in our mailbox?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I forgot something, but apparently, if you actually try to put in a gamertag that's already been used, like, for example, you'll get a message that says, if you believe someone else has registered with your gamertag, please send an email to support at xboxdiamond.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only problem is that it's actually xboxdiamondcard.com, not xboxdiamond.
[SPEAKER_04]: xboxdiamond is owned by another...
[SPEAKER_04]: and Cybersquatter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you send an email there, you're going to be sending all your personal information to God knows who.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've got to watch out for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently the domain has been changing hands on eBay because I guess they figured out that the Diamond Card thing was going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just basically watch where you're sending your stuff to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely check the URLs if it's not something that you know
[SPEAKER_04]: is part of the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably don't send an email to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, more news going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: One other quick Xbox 360 related story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's a little bit redundant because we talked about this game a lot, but I just want to confirm for you guys, Dead or Alive 4 did come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: December 29th is when it shipped, hitting the streets December 30th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what the hell happened?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why didn't it come out January 2nd?
[SPEAKER_06]: How did they make it out early?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the whole thing was is actually, I guess they pushed ahead their shipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of were overestimating when they were going to have the game out.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they were able to finish it before that and so they were releasing before that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were basically all they were doing was really tweaking online stuff and once that was all done they pressed it and it went gold and got it out a couple days beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean they only really did get it out one day before because
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of most anticipated games, we were talking last week about our favorite games of 2005, and now this week I'd like to ask you guys, what is your most anticipated game of 2006?
[SPEAKER_06]: What game are you looking forward to, and why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, there is so much good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta pick one.
[SPEAKER_04]: PS3, PS4, PS5, PS6
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Kingdom Hearts 2
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so tough because this is a really good gaming year, honestly.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all about the Steamboat Willie level and Tron.
[SPEAKER_00]: Light Cycles, hello!
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about what you've seen of the Japanese version?
[SPEAKER_06]: We see more and more of it hitting the internet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still want Aerith to die again.
[SPEAKER_00]: But having a... Having a...
[SPEAKER_00]: More Cloud is always nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he's actually, it's actually, I don't know if you noticed his outfit.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually Advent Children Cloud.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, this is why I want a new Super Mario RPG because they've done it so well with Disney and Square.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the hell can't they do it with Square and Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just, they've done it so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've really refined the whole RPG thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: P. Diddy said it best, it's all about the Benjamins.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure about that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guardian Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of under the radar.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came out in 2004.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said Guardian Heroes, so I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now Guardian Heroes on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guardian Heroes is freaking sexy, and I have that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, you want to know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: If I am correct, I think it already did get a sequel in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of these technically had sequels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another one on this list here is Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Chrono Cross.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they say that the sequel wasn't really the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: That it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, but... Chrono Cross was a true sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the purpose of this article, they're calling it a spinoff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I know, it's a gray area.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a gray area.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a popular choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's a no-brainer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comics Zone on the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's that mandatory WTF pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skies of Arcadia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_01]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_01]: But with the Japanese music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Grim Fandango, which is another one of those kind of, I never really played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: American McGee's Alice.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need more games in the Fantasy Zone series!
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to see another game in the Mega Man Legends series because I really like those games and I think they're pretty solid RPGs for the Mega Man series.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: A little piece of advice, because, you know, if we just sat around and played video games all day long, we would have no time to come up with new lists.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, here is DarkSakura with her advice column.
[SPEAKER_06]: And DarkSakura, what are you going to tell all the kids out there on Orange Lounge Radio Land about this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's piece of advice is something very important in the post-holiday time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_00]: How to untangle Christmas tree lights.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, this is a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number 1.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unplug all connected strands.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unplug all strands so your tangle is one containing several knotted sections, not one long knotted strand.
[SPEAKER_00]: The shorter the strands, the less complex the knots.
[SPEAKER_00]: Duh.
2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Find a free end.
[SPEAKER_00]: Double duh.
3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loosen all the knots.
[SPEAKER_00]: When the knots are all loose, create a hole through the tangle where free end leaves the mass.
4.
[SPEAKER_00]: Roll or wind the free end through each knot in the tangle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Treat the strands gently to avoid breaking the bolts. 5.
[SPEAKER_00]: Untie each successive knot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Keep the free end rolled to make it easier to work with and reduce the amount of cord to pull through.
[SPEAKER_00]: Six, keep the free end under control.
[SPEAKER_00]: Never pull on the free end.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pulling will tighten the tangle.
[SPEAKER_00]: The knot-free section should continue to get longer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seven, repeat as necessary.
[SPEAKER_00]: But my final piece of advice... Use candles?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Other than you celebrate Hanukkah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, my final piece of advice is just don't let him get tangled in the first place.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop being lazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my final piece of advice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rumors abound that the new World of Warcraft race has been revealed by the February issue of Computer Gaming saying that the new race will be the... And forgive me if I pronounce this wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Draenei?
[SPEAKER_06]: D-R-A-E-N-E-I, I've been three weeks without World of Warcraft and I've been drinking tonight, so forgive me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dry-ni, something like that, dry-ni?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's exactly how it's pronounced, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys, I'm sure you've seen this on most of the gaming websites out there anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just kind of beating a dead horse here, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: But what do we think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this actually legit or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, first off, let me add that Computer Gaming Magazine has come out and said that this source is not official, but it is basically a highly rumored source that this is what the next alliance race is going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I'd like to add my coworker, who is a huge World of Warcraft fan, says that a lot of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Storylines point that this is going to be the next likely race that's going to be for the Alliance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because they're trying to balance the Alliance and horde races.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the Alliance needs some ugly people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, any thoughts on this?
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't played any World of Warcraft in months and I still need to renew my account.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish the Pandaren rumors were more true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, the Chinese are a bitter race.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Legends for PC by Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then three games that are all the same for Xbox, PC, PS2, Rugby Challenge 2006, because it's all about men getting each other bloody.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unfortunately, I don't think that game's going to have any blood, so darn.
[SPEAKER_00]: 31st, Top Spin for Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_00]: Other games that are undated, we have Dragon Ball Z Supersonic Warriors 2, Sega Classics Collection, which is actually a pretty good collection.
[SPEAKER_00]: Space Invaders Evolution, and drumroll, we love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: About time, you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: The US isn't getting too much as far as January releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: The big ones being 25 to Life, which I believe is coming out the third week in January, as well as MVP 06 NCAA Baseball, College Baseball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are the two big games for the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Painkiller Hell Wars is still to be announced because it's been shifting hands from Atari to 2K Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and a lot more stuff to come in February, including my favorite, Full Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: UK and US release dates for your gaming pleasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're winding down here, but first off...
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what's this about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Some cheat thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's a cheat, I know you found it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell's going on here with Liberty City Stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Liberty City Stories, they have this nice cheat program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually a modified save game that you use as a trainer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you actually have a bunch of different cheats you can toggle on and off.
[SPEAKER_04]: This right here is basically what I play when I'm sitting at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually, some of the cheats that they've created so far, Unlimited Health, Heavy Motorcycles, which is my favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: All these different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that kind of opens a huge door to homebrew stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you haven't gotten it already, if you already have Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories, I highly recommend that you download this cheat program for Liberty City.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a save file.
[SPEAKER_04]: You load it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot of fun to play with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you got for us tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: The other thing I have tonight is actually kind of a rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically this thing that Nintendo's kind of trademarked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Nintendo Floor Vision.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of people are kind of wondering what the hell is Nintendo Floor Vision.
[SPEAKER_04]: And obviously the first thing that comes to mind is, hmm, maybe it's something that has to do with the revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hmm, maybe it's something that has to do with the revolution being, I don't know, stereoscopic 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the things that they think on Joystick.com is that it's actually kind of something that we saw at like E3, one of those kind of LCD panels where you can step on it and interact with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Pong Movie in Development
[SPEAKER_06]: I... It is supposedly written by Stephen E. D'Souza, who's writing Tomb Raider... I'm sorry, who wrote... Oh, bullshit!
[SPEAKER_06]: Lord from Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_06]: I... Huge grain of salt with this one, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, um... I know, there's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll say what, if you believe in the Pong movie, I've got some igloos to sell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I...
[SPEAKER_06]: Huge grain of salt with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not exactly going to comment on whether this is a good or bad thing because I don't think it's real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be able to believe it a little bit more if it had Ui Bo attached to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But since it doesn't, I'm going to have the call that this is really stupid and a dumb attempt to make a joke about a movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if it really comes out, you're going to look like an ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, though, I do have to say, though, since they did announce that Pac-Man, the movie, is actually going to happen...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm about to believe anything you write about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Pac-Man the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why the fuck do they need Pac-Man the movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, we had Pac-Man Fever, the song.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had it all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, they said that it might not even be a CG movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be live action.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, you're worried about, you're wondering why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, people are not going to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be like puppets, like Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be stupid no matter what you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd say we're going to wrap it up here with our final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I have 13 shots in me and I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I'm feeling much better and I think I'm going to get a little bit of food now.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: As usual, reject false icons and stop watching TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and I have one little thing to add.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live, if you do have an Xbox 360, a lot of cool demos that they've added lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Condemned and Quake 4, definitely check those out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a really good thing to be able to check these games out before you actually buy them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, show's over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week here on Orange Ledger.
[SPEAKER_06]: The last week of our regular, or I guess I should say old podcast, and then we're going into the twice a week starting January 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio To Go That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update