[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Good evening everybody, welcome to Orange Lounge Radio episode number 170 for this January the 15th of 2006
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, it's our first show of the new format.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've kind of taken our live show and our podcast and sort of combined the two together.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're wondering, hey, wait a minute, when the hell did things go from episode 54 to 170?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's because we here at Orange Ones Radio have actually been doing a live program for the past three years solely dedicated to music and rhythm games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But tonight the show has come together for the first time to allow our listeners to actually interact with the program as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me, as always, say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, what am I not doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, how am I doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fairly decent.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_00]: Fairly decent, I can say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing over there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, our other co-host, Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since we have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Shane Miklatov
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got hit by a blue shell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you playing Mario Kart during the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that don't know Miklatov, since he's kind of new to our podcast listeners, Shane's an old friend of ours that actually, now he works for Konami, but with all those NDAs, we're not allowed to say what he does or what he's doing or any of that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you look at instruction manuals for games, you can totally find out what I do and what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kind of look at it, but it doesn't say Miklatov, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ultramix 3 does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So can you tell us what you did for Ultramix 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: So when people play DDR, you create the steps they dance to?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, we are interactive with our chat room and our Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on Interact With Us to get more information on joining the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, since the show is podcast as well, you guys really can't interact with us if you're listening through the podcast stream.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just incentive to be here on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, you can always drop in there because we have other live shows that go on throughout the week, and it's a good time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is our first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling a little good about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit of a change going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the same time, I'm a little nervous, but I'm hoping you guys like the change.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling good about the change, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you happy with this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, no, I'm just depressed as I can be, and my heart is broken.
[SPEAKER_00]: I feel awful.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm actually pretty happy with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A piece of you has died inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: My soul is dark and empty!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the biggest shock will probably come to people that have listened on the podcast, because we had such a, you know, like, da-da-da-da-da-da, like, we were always just, like, going down this bullet list of things, but now we have a little time to relax, because we're going to be two hours now, so our podcast is broken up into sections, which means you'll get it
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how's your gaming week been?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd have to say it's been pretty lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: All I've played is Animal Crossing just because I'm getting ready to start my next semester.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week, God help me.
[SPEAKER_01]: That and I have a pretty nasty sinus infection so I've been getting motion sick every time I play anything Even Animal Crossing, doesn't that suck?
[SPEAKER_04]: Motion sick playing Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fluid in my head
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that you don't really hear a lot about sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we always see those warnings before we start to play video games, but we never really hear about a lot of experiences.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am one of those people who gets motion sick playing first person shooters or watching them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever taken things to try it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how people get cars to take Dramamine?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dramamine is like, it makes you pass out and it's really nasty stuff and not good for you at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've tried taking Ginger before trying to play Goldeneye back on the N64.
[SPEAKER_01]: Goldeneye is the first video game I've ever played that made me throw up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hardcore, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was watching Dan play it, and I wanted to do the two-person, but also if the screen is split like that with the two-person mode, I can't do it even more, even on PSO.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sonic Adventure made me nauseous.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I love that game and I just sort of push through it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, is there ever a point where you're just like, screw it, I'll just get sick just to play this game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Katamari Damashii makes me very motion sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like how I get sick if I eat really spicy foods, but once in a while it's like, screw it, I want Mongolian barbecue, I want it all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I did actually start to put Beatmania in and then Dan got sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: He turns into such a baby when he's sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's not motion sick, he's like virus sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he's got the flu or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's feeling better.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I did play DDR at Fry's today, and whatever ignition pad, fake pad thing they have there is a piece of ass, as in a skanky piece of ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it was like, right in the middle, you know where you stand?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's where the left arrow was.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We are international!
[SPEAKER_04]: And I shouldn't be giving them free advertising, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting an Intel iMac Jump to a Mac
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, what planet are you from?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can address those cards and letters to Loki at Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to have a system that will run circles around your PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, look at all that Mac gaming out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait, oh wait, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Excuse me, I'm a graphic artist.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a graphic artist.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm glad it can do something.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are so full of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love getting to start off the new show with a good fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jerry!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's because he is holding on to this antiquated idea that a Macintosh is for losers when actually it is far superior to practically any PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: And on top of that, I can install Windows on my damn Mac with my new iMac if I want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breathe in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Calm down.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is this Dell crap popping up on my laptop anyway?
[SPEAKER_01]: See, I won't have to put up with Dell crap popping up on my computer anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dell.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else to share about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I need some rope and a big stick and some fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to roast me a co-host.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a lot of Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know because I'm too lazy to set up game systems to play any console systems or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I played a little bit of Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm more of the single player and some of the multiplayer because it's just fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I did buy more games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought DOA 4, haven't played that yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was trying to... Boobie Fight 2006?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says it has partial nudity in it, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very promising to have a game that has partial nudity in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't some of those costumes just partial nudity on their own, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is kind of disappointing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still waiting for Rumble Runs' XX in a couple months.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game's going to be hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got bears in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be that Final Fantasy XI beta that's going to be in the next official Xbox magazine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that should be coming out in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that already out there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm looking on message boards and I'm seeing... You know how a lot of people are using their little Xbox gamer cards and their signature now?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can see the little boxes that show what accomplishments they've gotten lately?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you seen those with the stars?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I saw somebody who's on a random message board the other day, because I lurk on a lot of message boards out there, and somebody had a Play Online square in theirs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_04]: When did this happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: When did the PlayOnline thing happen, Ari?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it might have already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't really looked to see if the magazines are out there yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe it was the 16th is when the official newsstand date.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well then that would be tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, people get it early still.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess the people that have subscriptions might have already gotten them already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a subscription, but you know how it takes eight weeks and all that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm looking forward to that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But right now, I just haven't been playing too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to really get back into playing more console games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are some games coming out that I want to check out for the PlayStation 2 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I tried acquiring a game for the PSP, DJ Max, that beat Mania Korean Sim type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a little bigger than my memory card.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually remembered one more thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_01]: We were going to break out the Turbo Duo because I now have, thanks to one of our good listening friends, Space Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't that one of those games you kept saying you wanted?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a prototype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I now have Space Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Emerald Dragon, which actually I don't think I can play because I'd need to have an arcade card, which the Duo never had.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had, I think, up to the second card.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that means I actually have to find a DuoRX now to be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else in your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, my gaming week wasn't that exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing a lot of the same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, we don't really get free copies of games from people, so whenever any of us talk about a new game we've played, most likely we have went out and bought it if we didn't borrow it from somebody or, I don't know, Loki hacked something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know for me, I usually buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to add, just real quick, since you mentioned buying games, because I have been the bee in a company that sells games, I can use them as tax write-offs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm writing off $900 worth of games this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop rubbing it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I've just been enjoying old games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been enjoying some of the greatest hits of 2005.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been doing Animal Crossing and Meteos.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually got back into Meteos again and...
[SPEAKER_04]: This dude over here in the corner got me suckered back into World of Warcraft, which I was going to cancel my account.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Miklatov was like, no, you should come play on his server.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I'm playing a Horde character.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's different than the Alliance.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll tell you what I'll do.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I will go ahead and renew my World of Warcraft and I will play with you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll make my zombie chick again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm playing a troll.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm playing on Bronzebeard.
[SPEAKER_01]: My zombie's on Bronzebeard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to say what server, but I'll let you know offline.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care because I haven't touched the game in three months, but I'll play again if you're playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Still cannot find an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been using that Best Buy locator thing we talked about a couple shows ago that you had in your live journal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just driving around to random places, you would think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went Target, Walmart, Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, no one shops at Circuit City anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet somebody's buying up all their Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least in this area, nobody shops at Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a ghost town all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_04]: They told me they wouldn't have new ones until February.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be about right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to get my geometry wars on.
[SPEAKER_04]: This isn't fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you Microsoft for your supply shortage stuff
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I urge everybody out there, do not support the Xbox 360 black market.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are continuing to rob people like me of an Xbox 360 because that's who's buying them is people who wants to put them on eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's harder for me to get upset at the people that are buying them and putting them on eBay mostly because I know some people doing it even though I told them, you make me cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: If people weren't buying them and paying those hideous prices for them,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I finally passed 1,000 wins on Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all we do at work on breaks is play Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than that, I sold Animal Crossing because I don't have time for it because I have Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because you're too busy with Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I started playing World of Warcraft again and City of Heroes and Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm a big nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the listeners would kick my ass because you work for Konami, and I know you have all these non-disclosure agreements and stuff, but I have to ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about this a little more in depth later in the show, but surely you have something you can say on DDR Supernova?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's totally a DDR game that's for the arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bet you didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: In other words, he ain't budging.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have to get somebody from the higher-ups in Konami and Gorillam here on this show to figure out the details on what's going on with Supernova.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk more about DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_04]: I imagine most people, or a lot of people that listen to this show probably started on our music stuff, so they know we're really excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there was a lot of interesting talk in our forums and our LJ community live journal about, isn't it ironic that the week after Orange Lounge says...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to do the Bomani stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Suddenly, doo-doo, we've got a brand new DDR game in arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like we're going to stop talking about Bomani and music-based games at all, because they're still really important, obviously, and we still really love them a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just don't want to only talk about that anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is more to life than to DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is, there is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're gaming fans first, music game fans second, so that's an important thing to remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, before we get into tonight's news, we want to say a big special extra hugs and thank yous to Middyhead, speaking of DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Middyhead created songs, you know, he's been a musician for a while and does stuff for TV and movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he also did some songs that turned out in DDR and some remixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: He also did our brand new intro you heard tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was very nice of him to do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like it a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want more information on his music, you like that little...
[SPEAKER_04]: stuff we had in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: MidiHead.com is his website with more information, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's get into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what's going on with the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of how I can't find one, and they've had these sales goals and all this stuff, what's up with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, first off, basically, it's just been a nightmare trying to find a 360 and that type of stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now they've sold about 600,000 units in the United States.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, that's quite short to their original goal of 3 million in three months, being that we're on month two here, and 600,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, they actually went back on their original announcement that they were going to do 3 million, and now have kind of updated that to 5.5 to 6 million units by June 30th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now it's kind of like, oh, we're just going to put the finish line further out there so we can sell more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the problem is, are they going to make 3 million units in 90 days?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they even going to be able to produce them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the problem was before, and the whole thing that kind of delayed stuff, was that they ran into the problem, of course, with the overheating GPUs and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And because of that, they've had to do more quality control and kind of,
[SPEAKER_05]: Just basically slow down the whole process.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now they've added another manufacturing plant and they've kind of ironed out this overheating issue so hopefully they're going to be up to speed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still don't think they're going to make their goal though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not by a long shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how many of these things have they actually sold since the launch?
[SPEAKER_05]: As I said, 600,000 so far estimated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now there are other sources saying 1.3 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go with the 600,000 though.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lowball it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That way you don't get disappointed.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on in the news, you might have heard this week that Tetris DS was kind of a surprise announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tetris is going to be coming out for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be coming out at the end of March, and it's going to support up to 10-player multiplayer, if you're all in the same room, 4-player Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's still kind of cool that they're taking Tetris Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, they're going to be incorporating old 8-bit Nintendo classics into this somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you see the early screenshots, you can see Mario Brothers and some things like that in the early screenshots.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's very interesting because we don't know yet exactly how that works.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we assume it has something to do with maybe the battle setup or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's just me, but I'm really excited about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, I'm a big puzzle game whore to begin with.
[SPEAKER_04]: So finally having Tetris on the DS is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't think it's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because 4-player ruined Mario Kart Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: 4-player will ruin Tetris Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait, wait, this coming from the guy who just proudly proclaimed, I have a thousand wins!
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but that's not online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Online mode for Mario Kart DS is really stupid, because one, it's hard to find 4-player sometimes, and two, if somebody doesn't get first, they turn off their system, and so then you're down to three, or two, or then just finally one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tetranet Tetranet Tetranet
[SPEAKER_04]: with the item usage and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the fact that it's online, it's that they're limiting it to four players.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: But wasn't Tetranet six?
[SPEAKER_01]: Limited to six or four?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been so long since I played Tetranet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it was more than four, but I want to say it was like five or six was the most that you could have.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's still not much more than four.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, ruin Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't have high hopes for Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, wait a minute then.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're into this local area gaming thing, then doesn't the 10 player... Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just, I'm sad that Nintendo has to go and either limitations on their software or whatever make it for players.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have bad experiences with Mario Kart online, so... It's probably the network.
[SPEAKER_04]: But do you think Tetris is going to suffer from the same problem where people turn off their DSs if they lose too quick and then you have connection error...
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there are some people that are just that competitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they lose, they don't want it to count against their record.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haven't I bought this game before like six, seven times already?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop making Tetris!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't improved anything at all in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't need to have anything improved.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost the perfect game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris is like quack.
[SPEAKER_05]: When are you going to get into a room with 10 people wanting to play Tetris at the same time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I guarantee that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or no, get this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Imagine being on an airplane.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're bored to death and random other people are playing Tetris and you can play Tetris with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the plane crashes because you're not supposed to play those wireless things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you're in the air, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once you're in the air, you can do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's totally true.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fourth time I saw Brokeback Mountain, we took our DSs in the theater and there were people playing Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we played Mario Kart during the previews with people in the theater.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Tetris really could work just randomly anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine like a big sports game or a concert.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet it's the same deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've done PictoChat standing in line.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen lots of people do that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last time I did the massive PictoChat where there was a lot of other people was E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did PictoChat at E3 standing in the line to play Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was doing it in the line waiting to get in, and I remember seeing all these people writing on their PictoChats, OMG, it's Gary Coleman, OMG, OMG.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I looked to my right, and sure enough, Gary Coleman's standing right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, oh, OMG, it really is him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was doing PictoChat and saw a familiar name looked up, and it was Shark's Girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: She was in the other line next to me
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, now, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tetris also launched the Game Boy and was the launch title of the most successful system of all time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more Tetris for any next-gen consoles, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony, hear me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more Tetris.
[SPEAKER_05]: No Tetris on your system.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they come up to you and say, we want to make Tetris for your system, you say, no, I will not have this crap on my system.
[SPEAKER_01]: More Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bring us Tengen Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, remember the Tetris on the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_04]: It sucked because they changed the formula.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of just being the little blocks, they had the little guy that would climb on the blocks and you weren't supposed to kill him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was what, Tetris World?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tetris suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I call it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who remembers Blastress?
[SPEAKER_01]: with the Super Scope 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Super Scope 6 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played the hell out of Blastris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who remembers Hatris?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember Hatris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wordtris?
[SPEAKER_06]: What about Tetris Sphere?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tetris 2, Bomb Bliss?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They all sucked compared to the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Tetris Sphere was awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all about cooperative mode on Tengen Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tengen Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Loki, I find it ironic that you're talking about Tetris on the Sony platform, because didn't you say something to me before the show about Tetris being on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, the first game, of course, that they're going to port using that stupid Grand Theft Auto hack around, you know, is... No, wait, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell me about the Grand Theft Auto hack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, no, there's this Grand Theft Auto cheat device that was created by this guy named... I believe it's in Carter or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Long story short, it's this wonderful device that you can load all these cheats in, basically like a trainer for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now they're using this to port Homebrew to the PSP for firmwares 2.5, 2.6, and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, actually, that's what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first game that's been released right now is Tetris for version 2.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why, people?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, however, one of the things they have done beyond Tetris is they've released a software development kit that they're using for other homebrew over.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're going to see a lot more stuff coming and possibly another downgrader later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's shift gears here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, some folks say that Tetris is a bit of an educational game in some ways because it's a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to think through it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you're making a face.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you making a face?
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris is educational, my butt.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a thinking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the kind of game that your teachers don't get mad you're playing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris is a game of instinct.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get up to, like, I would play Tetris from, like, 1 to 18 to 24.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dr. Mario is the same damn way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's thinking fast in instinct.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's speed thoughts, speed practice.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I was in junior high school, we used to sometimes, because we were such nerds, we would break in our science teacher's classroom and play on the computers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the only times that we would get our teacher in on it is when we were playing Tetris or Scorched Earth.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I had, when I was in the writing class I had to take in college, we actually had those old Macs, like the, not the 2Es, but you know what I mean, the old box crap ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: And my friend installed Tetris on hers during class, and I was playing Doom in black and white on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Back to education.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there's a little article up on 1up.com called You Can't Be Serious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Five famous designers rehabilitate the world's most boring games.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I thought, wouldn't it be more interesting since we are actually more celebrity than those losers?
Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, I see the hate mail coming in already.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no, no, I'm joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have friends over there, be careful.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some pretty cool people involved in that, like they got some of the folks who worked on Ratchet and Clank and different people.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I think we should do our take on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, give me an example.
[SPEAKER_01]: First game, Virtual Leader.
[SPEAKER_01]: It works as a staff meeting without donuts, but it teaches managers how to, I like this, I'm going to quote this, how to squash the hopes and dreams of worker bees.
[SPEAKER_01]: But actually you learn how to keep them productive.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the comparison, the Sims meets Office Space.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in the sense that what this article has is it's got famous game designers saying this is an edutainment game there ought to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is how we would remake it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there should be, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: High school isn't just about learning, like book learning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about social learning, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think there should be a game called Murder the Bully.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't do that, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it says in here, to rehabilitate.
[SPEAKER_01]: This one, this is by Ted Price, who's the president of Insomniac, who did Wretched and Clank.
[SPEAKER_01]: Said, first of all, the employees in the games would be armed, concealed or visible...
[SPEAKER_01]: and then have full body armor and you can shoot your boss for yelling at you, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Each employee should have a unique psychosis.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my take on that would be you would have your mole employee who's actually working for another company working on a hostile takeover.
[SPEAKER_01]: And by hostile, I mean bazookas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a great game based on an earlier job I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is my game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is my invention of a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Data Entry Monkey, the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what you have to do is you have to turn on your... Let's say it's for Xbox because Xboxes have a clock in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's say that you turn on your Xbox and you have to be in by 8 o'clock or the Xbox yells at you and threatens to fire you, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then what happens is that a sequence of like up, down, left, right, and A, B, Y, X come up on the screen and you have to punch them in with 98% accuracy for 8 freaking hours with 30 minute lunch and two 15 minute breaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then when it's done, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: End of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it prepares you for your first office job of data entry monkey.
[SPEAKER_01]: There actually is a Yahoo game where you serve customers and take orders and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Root Beer Tapper?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen, I've watched Iguana Girl playing this.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's amazingly good at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, but, uh, the next game come up is called A Force More Powerful, which is a pacifist game, it's an anti-war game, where you have military situations come up and you have to find a non-violent solution to them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, that right away just sounds really boring, because, you know, the whole world just wants to blow the crap out of each other.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, um, there's a, they talk in here about having, uh, the, uh, uh, it's by, uh,
[SPEAKER_01]: The manager who oversaw Perfect Dark Zero, which I find this hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious what you guys in chat, who are listening to us live, what do you guys think in chat room now?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to hear some good ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com It's the first show, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is number 170.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I keep blaming it on the first show thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it like doing a country simulator with intelligent AIs that you have to convince them?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the game's already been done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Isn't that like ActRaiser or some shit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: The way I would do that is I would not make a game out of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would actually do it in real life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go outside the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be active in real life and stop pretending.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't think that would be a very good game at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have some feedback in the chat room from Tomo Kun.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a game at the McDonald's website where you went through a day at work just clicking over and over and producing Big Macs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw that a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but does the game shoot hot grease at you so you can really get the full experience of what it's like?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: It glamorizes it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it not, you know, penalize you for making really bad burgers or messing up completely?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I forgot the patty.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another game on here is called Virtual You.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'll just go ahead and read this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, you have to either keep your professors happy and keep the football team off steroids and keep the frat boy issues from happening, like hazing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you are being a university administrator.
[SPEAKER_01]: Teaching you the administrative process.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they wanted that to be really realistic, though, the
[SPEAKER_01]: Educators would have to be on both some type of coffee and then lots of booze and be highly alcoholic and have an ulcer.
[SPEAKER_01]: They should actually have school administrator health.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: You have died of dysentery Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Number Munchers was the one I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember Number Munchers?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mario was missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how people thought that was actually a Mario game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I rented it one time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had really good music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the MP3s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know what the one good thing about that game was, though, is that it was basically all of the Super Nintendo graphics on a Nintendo from Mario World.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it looked really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, they put this effort into this game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Excuse me?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, actually, another educational game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that educational?
[SPEAKER_01]: It taught me how to drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm serious!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like how my mom said everything I needed to learn about the birds and the bees, so to speak, I learned from Married With Children.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Jamie, you have a follow-up story here about teachers in the UK supporting games in education.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, there's a project called Teaching with Games.
[SPEAKER_01]: EA and Nesta Future Labs revealed that 60% of UK educators are supporting using video games in education.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a survey that was conducted in November that covered 1,000 primary and secondary school teachers in the UK, and of the 59% who considered using games in education, 53% confirmed they would do so because they are an interactive way of motivating and engaging pupils.
[SPEAKER_01]: 91% believed that playing the games could develop children's motor cognitive skills.
[SPEAKER_01]: Over 60% thought that players would develop their higher order thinking and would also acquire topic-specific knowledge.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I actually, about two months ago, brought up an article I read in one of the psychology journals that I...
[SPEAKER_01]: occasionally read because I'm a nerd, that was talking about how they actually did full lab study tests with control groups to pit the cognitive function of gamers versus non-gamers and that the gamers came up higher in almost anything having to do with a reactive cognitive type of activity.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, when we tell our parents that we're working on our hand-eye coordination, we ain't shitting you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually true.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because the thing is, especially since there are so many different types of games, you have your puzzle games that basically are teaching you spatial relations right then and there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Back to Tetris.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have your games that are teaching you how to basically come to a conclusion, the logic process.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, you have your games that are teaching you...
[SPEAKER_01]: basically how a sport will go or teaching you how to play a game you understand more of the mechanics behind some of these things especially with as interactive as sports games are becoming you really have to know quite a bit
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's actually really terrific and I wish that instead of our nemesis Mr. Thompson going around saying that games are teaching people how to kill, we're so... What was the word this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Masturbatory exercise or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying not to be foul-mouthed in this episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, don't get us that explicit tag on iTunes, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I take that back because no one would want to.
[SPEAKER_01]: They'd be afraid.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't get us sued.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Back to the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do, though, think that a lot of these people who naysay games so much are overlooking the amount of good that there is and all that, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree, I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think it's realistic that someday in PE class we could have video games that supplement the games we're about to play?
[SPEAKER_01]: Schools in Southern California have DDR as part of their gym program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think before we go out and play football for real, maybe learn a little bit about the strategy in Madden?
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly?
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to decide your plays, but that's been there since Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's change gears here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting discussion there on education.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you all ever have any feedback, to go at OrangeLaunchRadio.com is the place to send us some emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll get to the mailbag a little bit later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, we got the Duke from Freeze Pop waiting, so we want to get to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we got a couple stories first.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Loki, what's going on with DirecTV on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the 360, of course, they wanted to be the entertainment console for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: and basically all encompassing and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I think everybody wants in this next gen of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Want some for $400, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what they're doing right now, DirecTV has actually announced that they are planning to bring their service to digital televisions via PCs and the Xbox 360 system.
[SPEAKER_05]: This will basically make it a lot easier to turn PCs and DVRs as well as, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: Making the Xbox 360 awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because now we can record TV to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: How this is going to be implemented, I don't know, but sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you've got a hard drive in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, it's not big, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess anything to reach out to get that Xbox 360 to be the centerpiece in your living room was a good idea for Microsoft, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess, I mean, it's great that they're adding all this extra functionality to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Just when are they going to start making better games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Judgment Day is the one with Tommy Tallarico and Victor Lucas, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing the little, like, you know, I like this game and I don't like this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is, and I'm not sure, I'm guessing just G4 cancelled it because it's one of the shows... Well, because they don't like gaming anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But one of the things is, basically the show will still kind of exist in this...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an ongoing show they have.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do three shows, Electric Playground, Reviews on the Run, and then Judgment Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Judgment Day being gone, but Reviews on the Run is kind of very similar to Judgment Day anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, it's not really gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Reviews on the Run you're not going to see if you're in the United States.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't play it in the United States on G4 or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm surprised these guys haven't gotten into the world of video podcasting yet with their stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if... I mean, they're still doing Electric Playground, so... Take X-Play on, head-to-head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I prefer X-Play personally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Electric Playground's still an okay show, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: They canceled one show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so easy to cancel another one, so... You know, I'm sure they'll just replace it with reruns of Thunder in Paradise or something like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to be nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Coming to G4 TV, Paradise Hotel Because I guarantee you I have some pretty choice things to say about G4 So I'm going to be nice and not say it If you can't say something nice, then shut up There you go Alright, anyway
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Demanded more Freeze Pop Thanks to a relationship with the gaming group Harmonix Freeze Pop continued to rock us with songs in Amplitude, Karaoke Revolution And now, recently crossed over into mainstream hits Such as Dance Dance Revolution and Guitar Hero Now, Jamie, I know you are the queen of Orange Lounge Radio But what do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should we invite some other royalty here on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure Like the Duke from the band Freeze Pop?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, please help me welcome to Orange Lounge Radio, The Duke from Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's everybody out there doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're pretty excited here because we're having our brand new format tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pretty big week for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I know you've been kind of doing a little bit of touring with Freeze Pop lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys were at the GAME Festival in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: How'd that go?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were out there just because a game developers conference was happening at that same time and so there's a bunch of video game related events out there and we wanted to play a show and we also played at the Gang Awards which is the Game Audio Network Guild and at the game event at the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like you guys do a lot of video game related events.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything coming up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, nothing really tied to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: More just like little one-off shows and weekends here in the U.S., and then we're going back over to England in April for a weekend worth of shows, so that should be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if people want to check out your upcoming tour dates, they can always visit your website or your MySpace, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our website is usually the most up-to-date, and that's just freezepop.com, so that's right there on our news page.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you kind of mentioned there that you do a lot of work with these video game award shows and stuff, and of course, I think the way most people know about you guys is that your long-standing working relationship with Harmonix, because seeing a synth band in Guitar Hero was a bit of a surprise, but not to anyone that played Amplitude or Frequency or any of those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did your relationship with Harmonix begin?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, do you want the real truth or do you want the kind of like fake story?
[SPEAKER_04]: We want the real deal here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the real deal is I work there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's the fake story, just out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't work there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, so because you are working at Harmonix, Freeze Pop's not the only name you've done contributions under, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: For both frequency and amplitude, I was initially hired there basically just as an audio authoring person, songwriter, and we knew that we weren't going to be able to get enough artists for the game to especially fill out a bunch of sub-genres that we really wanted to have in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so my job was basically to kind of come up with all the different songs that kind of covered the genres we didn't have, like synth-pop, drum and bass,
[SPEAKER_03]: Electro, Techno, Trance, those kind of genres.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I wrote a lot of music under some fake names for those different genres of music.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it ended up working out really well because Freeze Pop's kind of taken off, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Freeze Pop has gotten a lot of fans from video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no denying that we basically reached a whole group of people that probably would never have heard of us.
[SPEAKER_03]: If not through the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, actually, it was kind of a fun opportunity.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had been trying to get some free spot music into a DDR game for a while, and Harmonix has a long-standing relationship with Konami because we've made the Karaoke Revolution games for them, which there are now four of them out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we actually had one of our, I think Science Genius Girls saw a Freeze Pop song was in the first Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how did this relationship with Karaoke Revolution turn into being a part of Ultramix 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it was basically like any industry.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's based on who you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: The people who kind of like helped the karaoke revolution thing finally got, you know, helped me get in contact with the right people at Tenami and I got some music to them and started talking to them and they were excited about either putting an exclusive Freeze Pop song or a remix or we just, we couldn't figure out like what relationship or like kind of like how we were going to like spin things and so we kind of agreed that they really liked the song Stakeout and I kind of wanted to get them something exclusive that, you know, nobody else had.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking we'll do something more, I hide behind my magazines
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, now the video for Stakeout, the Ultra Mix, is kind of very interesting as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like a Flash animation video.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did the video come about for that song?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was actually done by our singer, Liz Enthusiasm, whose alter ego is actually as a web designer and animator and kind of like an all-around design guru.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she, a couple years ago, you know, when Flash started to become really popular, just wanted to check it out and
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she felt a good way to kind of get into using the program was to make some videos for us, so she made a video for our song Freeze Pop Forever, and then she also made the Stakeout video for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome, well the video turned out really well, so pass on our compliments to her, it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's pretty fun to have kind of like an animated cartoon
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet it's kind of surreal to see that, but that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, is staying in touch with a video game and gamer scene important to you guys as a band?
[SPEAKER_04]: As Freeze Pop continues to get bigger and bigger, are you still going to be contributing to video game projects?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I sure hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd love to stay as close to that community as possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: The kids are really fun, and it's such a wide group.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not just 14-year-old boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: We get
[SPEAKER_03]: People come into our concert, and instead of bringing CDs to sign, they'll bring copies of Amplitude, or maybe they'll bring copies of Guitar Hero now.
[SPEAKER_03]: We played a show in Portland last fall, and this guy brought his PlayStation 2 and had us autograph his PlayStation 2, which was kind of surreal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I hope we get to play a lot of shows that kind of appeal to the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a bunch of other bands out there that are also kind of video game related, like 8-Bit Weapon.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's really fun to play with them and kind of just, you know, our fans who are more of like, got into us musically then find out that they can play some video games and the video game people then find out we have like CDs and play shows and
[SPEAKER_03]: It's definitely a lot of fun all around.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be a little bit of a logistical problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of us bands are pretty up-and-coming and very DIY.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have labels, we don't have managers, we don't have booking agents, so we kind of do it ourselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sometimes a little bit of a logistical problem to get everybody to all show up in the same cities all at once, but it certainly would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true too.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of you guys probably have day jobs like we do here at Orange Launch Radio too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sometimes gets in the way of being fabulous international rock stars.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, now, we've actually heard, because we do a lot of coverage of music-centric video games here on Orange Lounge, we heard of you guys being involved with a new dance game called Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you guys exactly contributing to this project?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just some music, or...?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's kind of confusing, and I don't know how much I should comment on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm friends with the two guys, the two Erics, who kind of have set the game up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, I don't even know what the status of the game is right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neither do we.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said neither do we.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I thought I'd ask.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you know, every now and then I talk to him, and we actually got a chance to meet them finally.
[SPEAKER_03]: They drove up to see a show in Pittsburgh last fall, so we got a chance to hang out with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I know they've had some ups and downs with the games and it would be really great for the games to come out but honestly I actually don't know a whole lot of information about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were slated to put a couple songs in the games and then we pulled one out but we were going to write an exclusive song for the game and I guess we're just kind of waiting to hear if it actually comes out but we would love to contribute songs to it because letting people dance to our music is always like
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and it would be great to just see a new dance game come out in the arcades, too, something to kind of, you know, bring some energy back to the arcades, because the arcade scene's been lacking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, totally.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, I mean, the more people that come out with, like, awesome rhythm action games and dance games and music games, just, you know, it infuses a whole new energy, and you get to see how other game companies approach, you know, dealing with the subject matter, what music they choose, and all that kind of thing, and
[SPEAKER_03]: It's definitely good to have lots of people kind of got their fingers into the mix and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it'll be really exciting to see them get that game out there in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there any other upcoming projects that you can speak about, possibly?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we're definitely, Harmonix is definitely working on some new game ideas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, I can't really talk about them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, of course, we've got some, like, amazing bugs coming off of the Guitar Hero game, and it was, you know, it was really, actually pretty exciting to get a Freeze Pop song on there, considering that we don't actually have any real instruments in our band at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, I mean, we're working on some interesting games, and I think, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there might be some surprises in the future with what we come up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bring up a good point though.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you manage to get a song in Guitar Hero when you guys don't really use guitars in a lot of your music?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you write a song specifically with guitars in mind or how did that work?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, fortunately, we actually had a song that was all about rocking, even though we don't really rock, because we have no drummers or guitar players or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can still rock without guitars and drums, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and it was the song off our first album, and it was kind of funny, because there's kind of a rip-off of Iron Man at the end of the song, and so when the game kind of got underway, and they were figuring out how to deal with all the unlock songs,
[SPEAKER_03]: and they were really supportive about going to a bunch of local Boston bands.
[SPEAKER_03]: A bunch of different Harmonix employees all put songs in the game and so I think the president of Harmonix came by and he was like, you've got to be able to put a song in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if you have no guitar in it at all, I think it would be super funny to have you guys in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I kind of thought about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew which song I wanted to put in, because it had to be a song about, you know, rocking out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was kind of debating for a long time whether or not there should be guitar or no guitar, and would it be funnier to play a synthesizer part on the guitar?
[SPEAKER_03]: But ultimately I went with putting a guitar part on there, and I had...
[SPEAKER_03]: A longtime friend, Izzy Maxwell, who has actually done some remixes for Freeze Pop, and he's a really shredding guitar player, and so I kind of said, Izzy, I need you to record a screaming metal guitar part over this, and he kind of just went to town, and I think he created actually a really fun guitar part to play in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm kind of wondering, you know, obviously Guitar Hero, lots and lots of people are buying this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's doing very well and critically it's doing well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a given that there's got to be a sequel in the works, whether you can say anything about it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think Freeze Pop will be involved with the sequel as well?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh man, if there's a sequel, we've got to come up with... The thing is, we don't even have a song we could use.
[SPEAKER_03]: We may have to write a sequel song to get ready to rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it's like, we got ready, but now we're rocking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not sure what's going to happen, but man, it's always exciting to see if the game is appropriate for putting one of our songs on there, even if it's kind of a stretch.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were some reviews for Guitar Hero with people who were really surprised that we got a song on there and kind of almost gave the game extra kudos for kind of going out on a limb and putting almost an inappropriate song into a guitar game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, it worked out beautifully, and I think it pleases the fans, the longtime fans of Freeze Pop via Harmonix, and I think the folks who were playing Guitar Hero and had never heard of you guys probably had a chance to rock out to the song as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, we're already starting...
[SPEAKER_03]: We're already starting to get some emails from some fans who are like, I never heard of you guys and I saw you in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you go to your website and they figure out who you are and they decide whether or not you think you're a complete idiot or they like your music.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we get our little share of hate mail, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's exciting to know that you've impacted somebody, whether or not you totally rocked their world or you made them completely hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least you made an impression on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We get the hate mail, too, here at Orange Lounge once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting to think that, wow, what you did motivated somebody to sit down and actually write out, Dear Orange Lounger, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, well at least he bought the CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I said.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least he bought a CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was excited because he created a piece of art himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every now and then when we get a new piece of anti-freeze pop email, I forward them that email and ask them to maybe try a little bit harder next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, that doesn't make them super happy either, but you know what can you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to ask all of our guests on the show this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are some of your favorite games to play outside of these music games we've been talking about earlier?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm definitely an old-school person.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, old 8-bit Atari 2600 games are still, like, my favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the thing about games where you have to invest incredible amounts of time to beat the game is a little bit frustrating to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: My interaction with games is definitely more of kind of a transitional, short-time experience, and so I just like to sit down...
[SPEAKER_03]: Play a couple of levels of something and don't feel bad when I want to, like, you know, not sit there for, like, ten hours or have to come back to it day after day.
[SPEAKER_03]: So definitely, you know, I'm big fans of, like, Yars' Revenge and Sub Hunt and kind of old 8-bit games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, you know, like, newer games, I play a lot of them just to kind of see what people do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I worked for a race car driving video game company for a while, so I really got into, like, NASCAR games and race car games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is pretty random, but I like to check those out, and we just got a 360 at Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've been checking out the new racing games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, I'm a huge fan of the games inside the genre.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rez was a huge game for me, and Vibribin, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's great you've named Vib Ribbon because that game didn't even come out in this country.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we know that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we have some Japanese PS2s.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're big fans of a lot of the Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the guy who came up with Vib Ribbon and, you know, Unjammer Lammy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And those games are really super fun to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitaroman is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a difficult game, that's for certain.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know I'm a big fan of Katamari Damacy like I just those games that are kind of quirky and left of center are some of my favorite ones it sounds like we have a lot of the same tastes in games those are games we're always talking about on here so that's that's awesome cool all right so that's about all I wanted to ask you game wise but I want to give you a chance to plug any any albums or tour dates you got coming up that you want to tell our listeners about here's your chance
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, things are kind of quiet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're working on a new Freeze Pop album, and it's well underway.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know when it's going to be done, but definitely...
[SPEAKER_03]: pay attention to our website and we're playing a bunch of shows in March and April we're going to be in Ohio and Indiana and I think we're going to go up to Chicago in March and then we'll be over in England to play in London and Leeds and a couple cities over there at the end of April and definitely just pay attention to our website because we'll probably be out on the west coast as well maybe like in the fall and hopefully we'll have a new album so there you go
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome, alright, so Freezepop.com to stay in tune with all the latest information, what's going on with Freezepop?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're on MySpace too, so come and be our friend there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, awesome, so Kasson, aka The Duke from Freezepop, thank you so much for being on Orange Lounge Radio and spending time with us this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's super fun, thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, no problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was very, very cool, especially the Vibribin mention, because I'm like, Vibribin!
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that guy know how to rock, or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Freeze Pop is now my second favorite band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next to Gorillaz?
[SPEAKER_01]: Next to Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_01]: They even have surpassed Pain.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because we all know Pain is good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Freeze Pop, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally blanked and forgot to ask about Supernova.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the chat room hates me for it, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I totally didn't even think to ask about Supernova.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll talk about Supernova in the next hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'm glad he has a lot of...
[SPEAKER_05]: I still don't like their music.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can just die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't like them.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're probably a really cool band, but nothing I've heard so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like that type of music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like Freeze Pop's music the same way I like 8-Bit Weapon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just the whole...
[SPEAKER_01]: Just the whole little quirky synthy vibe, and they remind me of Berlin.
[SPEAKER_04]: He mentioned 8-Bit Weapon, so I think they're kind of buddy bands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I really dig 8-Bit Weapon.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what else I thought was interesting about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: He said that they have an Xbox 360 at Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Elite on the BBC Micro
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what the hell that is, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've heard of it, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've just not played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it a game system you don't have?
[SPEAKER_01]: I do not have a BBC Micro, and I need to have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wouldn't work on our TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should have to get the little adapter thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I actually have a system.
[SPEAKER_01]: I now have a system so old I cannot play it on my TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: An Odyssey 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, those things are old.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, my TV's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do we have to do these lists all the time?
[SPEAKER_04]: What motivates people to make lists?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so we can talk about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: We can fill show time.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, number nine.
[SPEAKER_01]: My number one cause of motion sickness, Goldeneye 007 on the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was the one game that made me puke, literally.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not because it was a bad game, because it gave me vertigo.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was a really awesome game, and I don't think there has been as good of a bond game since.
[SPEAKER_01]: Goldeneye was excellent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 8, Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming soon to Xbox Arcade.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this was the one that brought you the World Warriors.
[SPEAKER_01]: This set the stage for 2D fighting.
[SPEAKER_01]: For even a lot of 3D fighters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, we actually even have the Street Fighter EX series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, coming up for number 7, Super Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good choice.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and it really...
[SPEAKER_01]: I do agree with this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says it seemed like the worst idea ever but quickly proved itself as the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my college dorm life was Mario Kart like every weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you were in my room, it was Mario Kart because we were the nerd room.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're in the room down the hall, it was smoke weed and drink.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what mine was?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Monkey Island 2, LeChuck's Revenge
[SPEAKER_01]: and, let's see, that was number six.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number five, Legend of Zelda, Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still partial to the Super Nintendo one, but I won't get into that discussion tonight because we're running long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because people don't like it when I say that Ocarina of Time is way overrated.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he lives.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hi, hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glad you could pull yourself a Mario Kart for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk to us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I do apologize.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that was number five.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number four, Pro Evolution Soccer 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are talking about the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The real football.
[SPEAKER_01]: Men in shorts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a really good series, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually kind of want to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, it's Konami.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice plug there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next up, number three, Pokemon Red slash Green, whichever one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still like the Pikachu one best, but still.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will forget that five seconds from now
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart DS Mario Kart on Super Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3, and Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do I know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just some schmo that you downloaded onto your iPod.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number one game ever, guaranteed to piss some people off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Namely, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris!
[SPEAKER_01]: Even better, specifically, Game Boy Tetris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Samba de Amigo Beatmania DDR
[SPEAKER_01]: 65, and this makes me happy, Tempest 2000.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heck, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's too low.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too low.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too low.
[SPEAKER_01]: That needs to be, like, number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Instead of Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is probably my single favorite shooting game of all time, even though I suck at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: R-Type.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game makes me want to do that Linkin Park song, you know, went so long and got so far, but in the end it didn't matter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you can't beat that game unless you're like God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shall I do three shooting games I enjoy more than R-Type?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: And number 99 was Pong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 100 was Hard Drivin'.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I'm surprised Pac-Man wasn't in the top 10 because every top list always has Pac-Man somewhere on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And rightfully so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pac-Man does have a severe tarnish on its name.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Atari 2600 version.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Hard Drivin', I had to mention it because it has significance for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I used to work at an Amco arcade when I lived in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_01]: and you had that swivel out chair and when you sit inside it's really dark.
[SPEAKER_01]: I used to take naps at work in the hard drive and machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and this kind of leads into the next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was watching a documentary on PBS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you guys have seen this, but there's a documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Miklatov saw part of this with me yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's two hours long.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only could watch the first hour because it's like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Old people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, hey, hey, PBS gave me Red Dwarf, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they also have the ABBA special once in a while, if you know when to look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where in the world is Carameldansen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and Square One TV, I know it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So PBS does have some cool stuff, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 321 Contact.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get hate mail from PBS.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some good stuff on there, but let's face it, either you're young or you're old, a lot of people in the middle don't watch it, and maybe... And Reading Rainbow!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sesame Street Do you know why they changed it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Men Porn Games Custer's Revenge
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take a break here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trust me, it was worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back on Orange Lounge Radio, we will talk about DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_04]: I promise we'll get into DDR Supernova because a lot of our longtime fans are dying to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, we're going to open up the Skype line, get some of your calls here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to be our first caller on the podcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to find out very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio