[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight, July 22nd, 2012, has a hugely anticipated title been cancelled?
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft secretly steps up security, and Steam heads to another platform.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is episode number 466 for this July the 22nd of 2012.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're here to talk about video games and the gamer culture, the gamer lifestyle with you guys who are participating live at the VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Live.VogNetwork.com to get in the chat room and chat with us.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, we want to acknowledge the folks listening along in the podcast form as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know a lot of us listen to us on their Mondays to help get through the workday or throughout the week or what have you.
[SPEAKER_10]: So thanks for tuning in and thanks for participating.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You are playing a game over there that you're giggling like crazy over.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to be the guy Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, dear.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember I want to be the guy was one of those like impossible games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just like the look of it now because it's all 16-bit-ish now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's got a lot of homages.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, obviously, the first one had a lot of homages to stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, the first level is it's buying a Capando.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is the appeal of these games that are just impossible to beat?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not impossible, they're just really hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next to impossible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a couple reasons why I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: One, because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's hard, but it's still fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two, because I'm thinking one of two things is going to happen for the next gate challenge for Ready Player One stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to either be a game that's hard like this, or it's going to be a text adventure game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be my guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not good at either one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's time to go back and study up on Zork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much, yeah, because that was one of the challenges in the book was Zork.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You are standing in front of a White House.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a mailbox here.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Open mailbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take letter.
[SPEAKER_10]: You better read up on your FAQs for the old school Zork games.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, also joining us here, since DarkSakura is not here, we like to invite other people to come on and host.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we have our old favorite standby host who doesn't have a choice because he lives here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to Alan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you, Alan?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, thank you for coming back tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like, I asked a bunch of people, I can't get a guest host.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was like, oh, so I'm like sixth choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great to hear.
[SPEAKER_10]: I asked one other person and then I was too lazy to ask anyone else.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just, you know, tap, tap, tap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the other person I asked was Flaco Jones, who, you know, to be fair, was here that night.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's bad luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's me.
[SPEAKER_06]: He makes power go out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it's best you stay away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stay away, Flaco Jones.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: But he has like babies and things.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you have babies and things, priorities and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to our chat room, the always present fourth guest on our show at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft starts us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, the host without a choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: but Tiara and Dan are both two of the big writers at the site Geek Life or geek-life.com and we've done a lot of stuff with them over the years they've been really wonderful in promoting us and we've tried to promote them where we can they got married today geek-life.com a geek wedding happened today in Las Vegas and of course since Jamie and Tiara go way back she flew down there for the wedding so I think that's great
[SPEAKER_02]: What geek theme did they have for the wedding?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know they had like a giant Doctor Who... It's Doctor Who everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's like they had like a giant Doctor Who TARDIS cardboard thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the cake topper is them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it might be Amy and what's his name?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're... Yeah, it's kind of like them as... Because Amy's got red hair and Tiara's got red hair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of like them as Doctor Who characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you can read more about it at geek-life.com because Tiara does a series called Bride and the Geek.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or is it Beauty and the Geek?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I sound like a terrible person because I don't know the name.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's Beauty and the Geek, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's about them setting up and planning their wedding, and I thought it was a really cute series, even if the name escapes me right now because I'm under pressure.
[SPEAKER_10]: But DarkSakura will be back next week, but we can certainly understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: She wanted to go to the bachelorette party, which looked like it was last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think they checked into a chocolate place So, you know, with girls If they're not going to go see the stripper thing and do that What do girls love more than strippers?
[SPEAKER_10]: Chocolate So it makes sense that they would go to a chocolate place Of which I guess there is one in Vegas
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: ImmortalKing in our chatroom says, DarkSakura too busy dodging the bouquet.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, DarkSakura is married.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's talked about her husband, Dan, several times on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe that makes you ineligible to even go out to the floor when they ask, where are the single ladies?
[SPEAKER_10]: Put your hands up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, so DarkSakura would not qualify to catch the bouquet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will point out that I did catch the garter at a wedding a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was when Mel and Mel got married.
[SPEAKER_10]: I caught the garter.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, still waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright, I've caught the garter before too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright Let's see Also in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com TigerClaw says What Sky is trying to say is Tonight's show is a sausage fest Maybe, but we will open it up to callers later on And maybe some lovely ladies will call in Because I know we do have some gals that listen to OLR Or maybe we'll get some emails Or some tweets From all genders later on So we'll find out We'll probably just get Jim Sally
[SPEAKER_10]: Steam sale!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to talk about how has the Steam sale damaged your life or your wallet?
[SPEAKER_10]: Steam sale going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe it ends tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if that means tomorrow at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's done or if that means there's like one last final hurrah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my meta achievement of voting on the community's choice every day of the sale today.
[SPEAKER_10]: That means today's last day.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it says prices through the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think today's sales are going to run through like 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I think it's going to be over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, then it's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there were some like from yesterday that expired in eight hours from when I bought them earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: So probably, yeah, through tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I wanted to go around and see how did the Steam sale wreck your wallet this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, how did the Steam sale wreck your wallet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, before I had purchased Skyrim and Borderlands, actually it was pretty good this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost bought Earth Defense Force, Insect Armageddon, but then I remembered how much I... It was a fun game, but it's not worth owning twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unlike, you know, Earth Defense Force 2017, which I owned a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought Arma 2, the pack they had.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was with Arma 2 and the expansion for like $20.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost considered San Andreas, but I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but yeah, so Arma 2 is only the new thing that I bought.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, uh, I'm looking forward to checking out DayZ, which is that zombie, uh, thing that they've got.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be all sorts of craziness and boring at the same time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't the orange box half, like, every Half-Life thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's Half-Life, Half-Life 2, Episode 1, and Episode 2, and, well, and then the original game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, uh, Portal and Team Fortress 2, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need to play through Portal again because I've played through that a few times.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty sure Alan would tell you Half-Life is the best thing you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really... I play Half-Life 2 and the episodes like twice a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thing is with that is they mark this stuff down all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not like, oh, I missed my only opportunity for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: seriously they mark this stuff down all the time and I'm sure if I go to a GameStop or something like that I'm sure they got a copy of the orange box on PC or even Half-Life 2 just sitting there rotting that I could probably take off their hands for you know nothing let me ask a completely random tangential question because we're talking about Half-Life and you know I know that it seems like Valve is trolling you with Half-Life 3 right Alan
[SPEAKER_06]: either Half-Life 3 or Half-Life 2 Episode 3 whatever they want to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it seems like nothing's ever going to happen, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's now been longer from Half-Life Episode 2 to current day than it was from Half-Life 1 to Half-Life 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you worry that if Half-Life 3 ever does come out at some point that it's going to be like Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: And what I mean by that is I think most people, not all, but most people kind of consider Diablo 3 a letdown for a variety of reasons, be it that auction house or the lack of offline play or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the only reason why there hasn't been Half-Life 3 is because they need to develop a new engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they've been using the Source engine forever now, so it's time that they come out with a new engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_06]: It reminds me of the series Lost and how weird it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the fans were like, they totally know how it's going to end.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other half of the fans were like, they're making this shut up as they go along.
[SPEAKER_06]: Half-Life, I'm afraid the story might get too big for them to rein in.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the story might be weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: But otherwise, it's just going to be a first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Valve's pedigree is very high, so I don't really expect them to drop the ball that much on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameGuru in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com seems to agree with Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Half-Life 3 will come out if and only if they create a new engine for their games.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need a Source 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they are going to create a new engine for their game because it's getting dated.
[SPEAKER_02]: They make good games and the engine still looks pretty nice, but they're going to need to come out with something at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to have to happen because it's going to get dated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because Source as it is, which the first generation of it was 2003 or 2004 when Half-Life 2 came out, it's been updated four or five times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's still the core engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what's running Portal 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Modified Source and Left 4 Dead 2 is also Modified Source.
[SPEAKER_10]: Portal 2 and Left 4 Dead 2, they both still look great.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I understand the desire to... It's the physics and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe Valve is waiting for the next wave of consoles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe at this point, don't make a PlayStation 3 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just need to come out with a game that's just all the source games kind of combined into one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a little bit of Half-Life, you got a little bit of Portal in there, a little bit of Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a mixing of everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit of Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Half-Life 2 Episode 3 was supposed to heavily involve Aperture Science.
[SPEAKER_06]: and because Portal was such a huge hit, it almost makes me wonder if they're like, if they want to keep those worlds separate now because you're supposed to go up to the North Pole or the South Pole to find the ship and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, Aperture Science was supposed to be in Episode 3 and now I don't know if they're trying to write their way around that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because of all the story in Portal 2 about Aperture Science, certainly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that could be an interesting monkey wrench.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, I didn't mean to get us too far on the tangent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go back to how Steam sale wrecked your week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else, Loki, that you bought on the sale?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just those three games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought Civilization V for Alan because just like how I bully him into coming on this show, clearly, I'm going to talk to him about playing Civ V with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't you excited?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I installed it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's progress.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought Civ V Gods and Kings for myself because it was like 20% off, which I figured for a game that's only like two months old is probably as low as it's going to get.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I bought that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I bought a four pack of Dungeon Defenders because it was cheap and I heard it's kind of good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why'd you buy four of them?
[SPEAKER_10]: so that I could give Alan one, and I gave one to Shane.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is Dungeon Defenders anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't decided what I'm doing with the fourth one yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's co-op tower defense, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you not have it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now you do.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's my fourth copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought it for Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did it for you, bro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's one genre I haven't really gotten into, tower defense stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, I guess I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play the stick war games on iOS, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought Skyrim, which I think I talked about on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_10]: My memory is a little fuzzy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I bought Skyrim on PC just because I wanted to be able to mod it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, I had it on PlayStation 3, but it's just not PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I got to say, after installing that high-res texture pack and everything...
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice looking game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all the mods are very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the Steam Workshop, and it's very easy to get that stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Alan, Alan's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: He sent me an email saying like, okay, here are the must-have mods.
[SPEAKER_10]: You need this and this and this and this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he just gave me a list.
[SPEAKER_06]: All quality of life stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the default UI for inventory and spells is shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So here's a mod that makes it pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw who's participating with the show at live.vognetwork.com says can your PC run Skyrim fine?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's running great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it's like the highest highest settings but my video card's fairly new.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's only about a year old and you know I have a fairly powerful PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just very loud.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only problem with my PC is that when the fans are running You should hear mine because it's under the desk.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why it's muted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mine's a beast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your PC's way better than mine and I run games fine so you shouldn't have a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: My PC at home, I need to upgrade everything on it because that was back when the 8800 NVIDIA cards were new.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have a dual 8800 GTS 512s running an SLI and have a dual core because it was a core 2.0 before they had all these i5s, i7s, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's overclocked to almost 4 gigs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, those cards kind of hold it back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Blackwolf, who tapes before us at 5 o'clock Pacific, 8 Eastern at VODnetwork.com every Sunday night, is sending a link.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw your tweet on this earlier, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how I know what this is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the Minecraft mod for Skyrim that actually changes your companion to Steve, the Minecraft dude and all that, which is funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just afraid once I do start modding this is it's going to get weird really fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I'm going to have to get the Macho Man dragon mod.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I got to get that still.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That one also, a quick, I guess a... We actually have somebody in chat too named Macho Man, so maybe you'll get an oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's also, you know, in case you're not a Macho Man fan, they have the Milo Pony ones that turn the dragons into that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the extra magic one is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's just be real.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's for the weed smokers.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have the brony mod for the weed smokers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that there's anything wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to see what kind of... I mean, it's going to look nothing... That's the fun of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I've played Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skyrim's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm still playing it on 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't picked up DLC because I think it's a waste of money right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just want to make the PC version look nothing like the original game and just have it be frigging crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just batshit crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf is also asking in chat, can Alan post his essential Skyrim mod list to the forums?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I've actually been trying to nudge him into doing an article for the site on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nudge, nudge, nudge, nudge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I talk about the Steam Workshop?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_06]: As someone who likes to mod PC games, the Steam Workshop is amazing in how incredibly easy it is to just install a mod.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you don't like it, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a one-click process within Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem that I have with it is that a lot of really awesome mod authors...
[SPEAKER_06]: aren't on it just because they're fine with Nexus, which was the old school modding site.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's a lot of amazing Skyrim mods, especially UI and quality of life stuff, that isn't on the Steam Workshop.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if I make a list, I can say, here's how you install stuff from Nexus, but here's the easy stuff from Steam Workshop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have faith that most of our listeners could figure it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people are intimidated by modding, and the Steam Workshop is absolutely an amazing progression.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very innovative on that stuff, but it kind of split the community up a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because now there's two different sources for mods.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft is trying to share this mod that he says I should get called the Yay Mod.
[SPEAKER_10]: He says, screw the Macho Man mod, get the Yay Mod.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm like, dear God, what is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: And he sent me a YouTube.
[SPEAKER_10]: Usually I don't play YouTubes on the show without looking at them first, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: for yay mod, I'll take a risk Actdeft, don't ruin my show here we go, let's see so the guy's in the dungeon let's see what happens if you don't know the elements of good cheer yet you should try out these cheat codes I don't know what that's gonna do alright Actdeft, when does this get good uh oh, the guy's typing it in let's see what happens
[SPEAKER_10]: This video's only a minute and a half long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing good's happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, you're bringing the show- He should've just gave you a timestamp and said bump it to like a minute five.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm more interested in this because everything's in German right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure dragon shouts in German are terrifying.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just realized it says My Little Pony Friendship is Magic in the title, so I'm a little worried.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might need to smoke a little bit of something before this will actually make sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that the trick?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably a dragon shout that's My Little Pony.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's now a dragon shout that says yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now to the fun part with 10 seconds left in the video.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I give that on a scale of 1 to 10 about a 1.5.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a stoppage of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and Bobby Blackwolf in chat said, Wolf rather, that he's installed mods from Nexus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nexus does have its own little Nexus mod manager app, but a lot of people are like, I don't want to install this 5 meg little weird-ass app.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it kind of has a Steam Workshop alternative, but yeah, I can post all that through the forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and another thing about the Steam Workshop, and this is because I'm a huge pervert, sometimes mods, modders, especially in like the Grand Theft Auto franchise, like to make people naked or make their clothes really slutty, even if you strip them and they still have underwear on, just like cleavage and the big boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not, that stuff's not on Steam Workshop.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want an NC-17 R-rated Skyrim like I do, you're going to want to go to Nexus for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do some good work on Lydia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's a bunch of Lydia mods where it's not appropriate for this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: This show is appropriate for everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: This isn't a Bobby Blackwolf show, Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have some deep cleavage for those characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, what was the damage for you this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I know you went shopping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think from the very first day of the sale, I think it's dinged me collectively for I want to say 50 or 55 bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's 350 here, 899 here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big thing that I got was Saints Row 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: was knocked down to like $7.49 and then that plus all of the DLC all of it I think was like $22.99 so I picked that up just inhaled all that down spoiler most of the DLC sucks actually spoiler all of the DLC sucks
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing I noticed, and you're the one who pointed this out, there's the daily sales that actually last about two hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are the flash sales and then there are the community vote sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those prices have been cycling through every day or like twice a day every other day for the whole sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a genius move on Valve's part because it makes it look like they're putting all this stuff constantly on sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: But all it is, they have the daily sales, and the votes and the flash sales are just the same things as the daily sales, just cycling through at random.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, if the thing that you voted on for the community sale didn't win, it's probably going to be a part of the daily sale the next day or the day after, or it'll be one of the flash sales at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're going to get...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, remember that for Christmas because it's too late now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember when Civ V, I think, was like, what, eight bucks?
[SPEAKER_06]: And people were like, fuck, I missed Civ V for eight bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been eight bucks like three separate times since that you said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they keep bringing those prices back and making us think they're unique.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, so I think we've talked enough about our Steam addiction this week and the stuff we've bought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into a similar topic because it's how we always start the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the Steam sale is just about buying a bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't mean you're going to play them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what did you actually play this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I have to make one more purchase here real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God, what happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just Cause 2 is $3.74.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: for $3.74.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to buy that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Feed Gabe Newell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Feed him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: What am I... See, like, before, like, was it the stupid indie... I blame the humble indie bundles because, goddammit, I didn't have, you know, Steam and all this shit before that and now...
[SPEAKER_10]: And now I'm sucked into this... Alright, well I'm not going to tell you not to do it, but I am going to say pause for a minute and tell us about your gaming week first.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, this week I played Borderlands, because I picked it up on the same sale on PC, so I've been kind of going back and replaying that again since I want to kind of remember a little bit of what happens for the sequel, so that I can bust that out when it comes out in September.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, I went ahead and modded it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been a while since I've actually played that game, so they've patched it a few more times and you can't do some of the really cool guns that you had before.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's still some pretty awesome ones in there that you can mod.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have some of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a pistol now that takes people's heads off and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Mario World World Select
[SPEAKER_02]: and I don't like the fact that you can't stop moving in that because it's you know you push left to right and your guy just keeps walking and there's a spot where you have to kind of sit still before you know you do something um so it's a little annoying but I'm sure it's on like that on purpose
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3 Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
[SPEAKER_02]: My class that I'm going to be using for the tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I mentioned last week, I'm going to be entering a Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3 tournament almost a week from today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Driving down to Stockton.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, just, I think that was about, oh, I had been selling some stuff on eBay, and I guess I must have bought something on eBay not too long ago, because I had like $6 worth of, it was like $6.60 in eBay bucks that they have, you earn like, I don't remember what the ratio is, but you earn like free money, basically, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I was bored one day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, okay, I never really spend these.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to find something that's gaming related under $6.60.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to try to find the best value for my money.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I was searching around and I actually found a digital copy of Child of Eden for $6.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I picked that up because that's a no-brainer.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully I'll get back to playing that on the 360 again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's all I played this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll go next because I didn't play a lot of new games this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I talked about most of the stuff in the Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't play enough Dungeon Defenders to really review it yet, so I'll come back to that next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did play a little bit of Civ V, Gods and Kings, but you have to really book out a chunk of time to play that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I started playing it, and I didn't really have a whole lot of time, and I was playing sloppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: For some reason, I decided to go for a military victory, and I never do military victories.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I was spreading myself too thin on all fronts so I was getting my butt kicked on like an easy level and I was like forget it stop delete I'll come back to this later so yeah didn't really get to do a whole lot there played a little bit of WoW
[SPEAKER_10]: Played a little bit of Mass Effect 3 online on PC, and I gotta admit, I'm a little disappointed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm left with a bad taste in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_10]: You all know... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say it double fold.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's two reasons.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, one reason for me, two reasons for you on why it's shitty and why you're not gonna play it anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I'm threatening not to play it anymore, but I think we all know somebody will be like, please come play with me.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'll be like okay but I'm just I'm really frustrated and a lot of it has to do with connection issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: Origin and I hate to say this because I know people that work at Origin but it's not good like I'm sorry I can't I'm really frustrated with it and a lot of it has to do with connection issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm consistently having an origin and this whole
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go in.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can play our own separate matches.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can do co-op with two public pugs that we let in through the public match.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Origin, its network kernel, can only keep track of one IP with two sessions on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can't do it for another IP with two sessions on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when we try to play with our friends who are in the exact same setup as us, the third person could get on.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when the fourth person tries, they time out.
[SPEAKER_06]: or if the match is already in progress, it will time out the person at their house while the fourth person tries to get in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this makes no sense at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, TLDR, it's shitty.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's shitty and it's peer-to-peer, which is why it has this problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: XBLA and I think PSN is all server-based.
[SPEAKER_10]: so the matching service on Mass Effect 3 is peer-to-peer and that's why it has all these problems and let me tell you what I've had to put up with to play what is otherwise a great game again I don't get into online shooter games ever but Mass Effect 3 which isn't really a shooter but it kind of is like it has defied that trend but what I have to do to play this fucking game on Origin log into the game wait while it connects to Origin
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, game is connected to Origin.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now the menu's up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait while it loads my Galacticness Ready readiness rating or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, now select multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait for multiplayer to load.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let me connect to my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait to connect to the friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: It takes like four minutes to get into a freaking match.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet what it's doing for those first two big lags when it opens up the Galacticness Ready, I bet that's all like the DRM Origin security stuff going through.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's gotta be.
[SPEAKER_10]: which is ridiculous like it's stop like do it once do it once every 10 connections just stop bogging my game down because it's really ruining it for me and then what really just set me over the edge was that we played a game the other night it was me you and our friend Tim we were three manning some bronze maps which we can do to full extraction and we were playing those online we played two matches and I got about 30,000 credits I leveled one guy to from 19 to 20 and another my engineer from like one to six and
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, lost all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: After I disconnected from the match, lost it all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rolled back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wrote EA customer support.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please give me back what I lost.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got a reply back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, can't do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you can do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't want to because you think I'm trying to, you know, get it from you or steal it from you.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is ridiculous and I'm kind of over it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xbox has its share of connection problems too, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because with Mass Effect 3 multiplayer, aside from the galactic readiness and the first player part of it, there's the challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then, aside from the challenge of shooting shit, you get credits and you buy these goody packs and you unlock new characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why people play Mass Effect 3 multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because they want to play as a Vorcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: They want to play as an Asari.
[SPEAKER_06]: so if you're not getting your credits that's that's why you're playing is to buy unless you want to get Bioware points but which I refuse to do yeah so and then I have saved up for so many of these packs and then this gets into a little bit of like you know it's not fair the game's not fair I have yet I've unlocked two characters out of like the and the way you unlock stuff is ridiculous because it's all RNG you you buy a goodie box and then pray you get the shit you want in it and it's totally random and
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Osfer says in our chatroom, just calm down and play the game on 360 after the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll have a proper multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can play it on PC, you can play it on 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe, I mean, I'm not saying no to like playing games on 360, but like all these issues, no matter what platform, I'm kind of like over Mass Effect 3 multiplayer and I'm ready for a new game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm ready for some single player content.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why we're going to play Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Civ 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: you realize Borderlands 2 you can play split screen on one Xbox 360 system and then also with that split screen play against other people we can do co-op and you can both play on the same TV
[SPEAKER_02]: Come to the Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to check out Borderlands 1 again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I only played it a little bit before and got distracted.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I'll definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, that's my little Origin rant.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is setting EA as a company back.
[SPEAKER_10]: But of course, EA is doing it to themselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've ran it enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, how about you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mass Effect 3, we already talked about that plenty, so I'm not going to get into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Noire, which I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm almost near the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of want to beat it, not because it's boring, but I am using a FAQ so I can get everything the first time through and just follow the narrative of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And with the FAQ, that game's kind of boring, whereas other games, if you follow a FAQ, you still...
[SPEAKER_06]: Have the mechanics of it keeping it fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a shitload of L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to the Steam sale, it was dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I got it for like 10, 12 bucks with it and all the DLC cases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enjoying that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was playing Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on the mission where you parachute onto the top of the building and Kanye West is playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like an hour or so in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Played a lot with the character creator in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have that game on PC, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You might check Gentlemen of the Row.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a lot of cool enhancements and stuff for both Saints Row 2 and Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I installed a game that I hadn't played in a couple years Postal 2 for anyone who remembers that it's actually it's a really it's incredibly vulgar and offensive in a lot of ways but it's a first person shooter it's you know dated seven days of the week I got the expansion so I was playing Postal 2 for some reason I'm like I just want to play a really offensive awful first person shooter I think oh um
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I'll make this a part of my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I decided to check out my PSP, my Slim, which has got custom firmware on it, just to see if there are any custom firmware updates up to date, maybe check out some of the UMDs I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I noticed when I turned it on that there's this weird spotting discoloration splotches around the border of my screen, and I googled it, and it turns out this is a known issue for older PSPs.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't live here.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Sacramento, it's like 102 degrees outside right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't live in San Bruno anymore where it's foggy, but this is a known issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's mold under my LCD between the glass and the backlit portion.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a slight discoloration.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Jamie was here, I'd have her take a picture of it and put it on the Flickr stream.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw someone else but I guess yeah this is a thing you get mold under your it's when I'm actually playing when I'm actually playing like a bright game like crap of the rapper really any game it's the the colors and the movement doesn't really notice I don't really notice that much but on like just the crossbar the menu screen I'm like this sucks
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's mold, though, because it's almost like just the LCD screen just kind of going out or something, because you can see if you turn it, it changes the colors and stuff of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks...
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's, ooh, it's all splotchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looks like a disease.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like your PSP has shingles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to put it down.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, I've heard people say like, not that this is a fix for it, but someone, I was reading a forum post and someone was like, what if you put it under a UV light for like a day?
[SPEAKER_06]: Will the UV light kill the fungus under there?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, I'm not doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's, if you have a PSP and it's been in your closet for a year because you don't play PSP anymore, turn it on and see if it's got,
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird splotches under it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got 2000, haven't really powered it on in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: My PSP has crud.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It needs antibiotics.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could just get a new screen if you wanted.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, it's not like you leave that thing in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, like in the bathroom you might expect it to get moldy because you know the steam from the shower and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been in the living room on our shelf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when I last turned this on... It's dry here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not even humid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I turned this on last around Christmas and it was fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's something that's happened within the last six months.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm worried about my PSP now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because it's been years for yours.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we need to turn on the Vita every couple... You're still watching Netflix on the Vita, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if that's it for your gaming week, let me get into housekeeping real quick and then we'll get into the news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some quick housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, the Summerfest for PlayStation Home is next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can read more about that at the VOG Network's website, vognetwork.com, but we will be live in PlayStation Home, kind of being there exploring in the Aurora space and meeting some people virtually as well as broadcasting at the same time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't worry though if you don't even have a PlayStation 3, nothing's going to change for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just, you know, you won't be able to participate in going into home, but you're not going to miss anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're still broadcasting the way we always do and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just kind of like we'll have a
[SPEAKER_10]: and some listeners that want to come into the home space.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, that's happening in the Aurora space during next week's Bobby Blackwolf show and our show.
[SPEAKER_10]: For more information, there's a story right in the feature bar at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, please don't forget to add us on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we are also on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a giveaway tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to do a giveaway in part B. And tonight we are giving away, thanks to one of our listeners, and I really appreciate it, Boshka.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of our listeners is giving this away.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can tune in to his blog.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe it's CritCraft is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I want to credit his blog for providing this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a beta key for Ravaged.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ravaged was a Kickstarter funded project and it's now in beta.
[SPEAKER_10]: All you need is you need Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're going to give this away to a random listener in part B. If you want to win this, you have to be in our chat room and
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel like I'm forgetting something, but if I think of it, I'll come back to it later.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's get started with tonight's news in the meantime.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm sure this is going to come to a shock to a lot of people, but there's a rumor that Final Fantasy XIII Versus is dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shocking that, you know, a game that we haven't seen much of for six years not coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: but uh yeah and this is coming from some inside sources um that apparently Kotaku is talking to and they're saying that you know it's officially canceled but I mean I don't know if it's officially canceled or if it's just gonna be retitled they haven't made a statement right there's no been no PR bulletin or anything okay
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's the last thing I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're almost done with preparing our latest info for the game because of a totally unrelated reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are circumstances in which that info cannot be released.
[SPEAKER_02]: so info for that game maybe it's now no longer versus because honestly 13 versus it still didn't make any sense to me why it's called that because both games you know it looks nothing like Final Fantasy 13 at all and there's nothing so far that they've shown us that's led me to believe that's even in the same universe as 13
[SPEAKER_10]: I think some of the mythology is supposed to be the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the whole LaCie and the Falsie and all that I think is supposed to be like a constant.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say it was a trilogy but there was the main story and then the two guidance side stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: One for the PSP and then Versus 13.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's supposed to be some common thread no matter regardless of how thin tying it all together.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy Agito, or whatever it was called, excuse me if I'm butchering that name, it just became Final Fantasy Type-0, so why wouldn't Final Fantasy XIII Versus just become something else?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which folks are speculating, including me on this show a couple months ago, I think I said, why don't they just make it Final Fantasy XV at this point?
[SPEAKER_10]: It would make a lot of sense, because we're starting to get into the next cycle of consoles, yet we're supposed to get, I mean, you know, again, Square can do whatever they want, but historically there has always been
[SPEAKER_10]: Three Final Fantasy games on every console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1 through 3 was on the NES, even though 2 and 3 didn't come out here in America.
[SPEAKER_10]: 4, 5, and 6 was on the Super Nintendo, even though 5 didn't come out in North America, but it did later.
[SPEAKER_10]: 7, 8, and 9, PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: 10, 11, 12, PlayStation 2.
13, 14...
[SPEAKER_02]: 13.2 13.2, yeah and technically 14 isn't out on consoles yet, although it's still slated it'll eventually come out, I mean 14 or we should say 11.2 because it's basically the 11 characters with their names changed so they could very well, instead of saying Falsie and Lussie or whatever, they could be like they're the we're just going to go back to Espers they're Espers now, or they're Summons, or they're I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's make up another name for summons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they could just... It's Final Fantasy blank.
[SPEAKER_10]: They could think of a name for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, just like there was Final Fantasy Tactics.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't really a Final Fantasy game, but kind of in that universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Dui Decium.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a great game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck was that kind of a name?
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can't count 13-2 really as a game in the... I mean, because then you'd have to count 10-2, and then you'd have to count Dirge of Cerberus, and it throws everything off.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are all spin-offs.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess we're going to have a definitive answer come, what, September 1st?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because there's supposed to be some... Probably a Tokyo Game Show, at least by then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Square's doing some type of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like they even said, what is next in the Final Fantasy XIII universe on September 1st?
[SPEAKER_10]: And so either that's Versus has a new name or it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: or all of this is proven false because, again, it is a rumor.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you know, it's not like everything Kotaku's ever said has turned out to be true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's also a possibility, and a lot of people are saying, well, what else could they do but Final Fantasy XIII 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't that be something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is weird because... If it's true that there's a Final Fantasy XIII 3, which would make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think XIII 2 did pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It probably wasn't as expensive to make because they made it on the same engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had all that DLC for it, which I'm sure made them money too.
[SPEAKER_10]: XIII 3 actually makes a lot of sense for them to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's weird because...
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy XIII was supposed to be three separate games and now Final Fantasy XIII might if these theories prove to end up being three games that are all just 1, 2, 3 Final Fantasy XIII, 1, 2, 3 It's kind of weird how it transformed like that
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think the reason why a lot of people are invested in this story is for those who don't follow Square Enix that closely, the crew that, like the director and the main crew who did the Kingdom Hearts console games have been working on 13 versus 13 for however, five, six years.
[SPEAKER_06]: So for it to become vaporware maybe would piss a lot of people off because...
[SPEAKER_10]: depending on how tinfoil hat you want to get the Kingdom Hearts console team has been working on it so they need to have a product out so they can work on the next Kingdom Hearts I just can't see Square just throwing it away I could see where Square has decided Kingdom Hearts 3 needs to happen now
[SPEAKER_10]: and so maybe they've said, you know what guys?
[SPEAKER_10]: You've had this game for too effing long so we're taking it away from you and giving it to this other team and we're going to put it out under a new name and you guys go work on Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, anything is possible in that regard.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not beyond throwing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although some things that they should really throw out, 14, they just don't and they hold on to.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe they're realizing they need to rush 15 because they need to erase 14, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is still getting relaunched.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I also saw speculation that the reason why there's no press release saying yes versus 13, this is what's happened to it, whether it be canceled or whatever, is because their last year fiscally was so bad because of 14 shedding the bed that they're just not putting out negative press releases anymore because of damage control from 14.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's kind of, I don't...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to drag this out too long, much longer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to get to the next story, but I do want to kind of throw this idea out there because somebody on Facebook had said this and I was like, hmm, that's a good point, is that, well, if they canceled Final Fantasy XIII Versus, why did they just release the theme song for Theatrhythm?
[SPEAKER_10]: because Theatrhythm has that song as a downloadable song.
[SPEAKER_10]: So why would they release that if they just canceled the game and teased this Final Fantasy XIII versus?
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, this could be the case of Square Enix being a giant company.
[SPEAKER_10]: The left hand hasn't told the right hand Theatrhythm DLC team what's going on, but I thought it was an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Avatar Famestars
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, a trademark for the game had turned up earlier in the year, but now we're starting to see this actually appear in games, such as Wreck-A-Tier, not to be confused with the game that's on Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Wreck, like Wreck-It Ralph, Wreck-A-Tier.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is part of Microsoft's Summer of Arcade series, and it is including this Avatar Famestars.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_10]: Avatar Fame Stars is a new program from Microsoft Studios and is part of a select group of games that delivers new and exciting ways to play online with your friends and compete for social recognition, according to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess this is supposed to include in-game challenges, and this sounds like kind of like rebranding of shit that's already been there, because if you do these challenges...
[SPEAKER_10]: or I thought Achievements.
[SPEAKER_10]: In these Avatar Fame Star games, you get rewards based on your Fame Star points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, so like rewards for my Avatar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doesn't that technology already exist on the 360?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I could swear that if you play like Super Meat Boy, you get a T-shirt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's tons of that type of stuff in games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm trying to figure out like what is this?
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess what they're doing is instead of it being game by game by game, this is one gigantic pool.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if a game is participating in this pool, then you get the points and the achievement points towards a common unlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the difference, which is a little weird, but that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the rewards cross from game to game, as does the points total.
[SPEAKER_10]: Avatar Famestars is locked to your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're saying it's possible this is something that could spill over to Windows 8, Surface tablets, Windows phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: Other games that will include Avatar Famestars support, Full House Poker, World of Kieflings, so games that already exist.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be kind of patched in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fire Pro Wrestling, Home Run Stars, Avatar Motocross Madness.
[SPEAKER_10]: we don't know when the already existing games will have it patched in or when all these other games are coming out but I guess if you're into collecting avatar awards there you go
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about you guys, but pretty much every avatar on my friends list is all wearing Mass Effect carb Not me though, I actually tried to make my avatar look like me I was a sucker and I spent like 120 Microsoft points to get a stupid hat for my avatar that looks like a hat I would wear out to a club Because I am a sucker Anyhow, let's move on with some more news
[SPEAKER_06]: So Valve is always trying to do great and interesting things with Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a gaming store and application.
[SPEAKER_06]: They brought Steam to Mac and Apple platforms, and they also invented Steam Play, which is where if you buy a license for one game on PC, you get it for Mac and vice versa.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now they're bringing Steam to Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's going to be a Steam client.
[SPEAKER_06]: For Linux, they are using the Ubuntu distribution.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for people who aren't familiar with Linux, there's different revisions of it based on which company wrote that build of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's Red Hat and Corel and Ubuntu.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, that's what they're going for because it's sort of the popular make of it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first game that they're porting to their first party title that they're bringing to Steam Linux is Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've been working on it since last year, 2011.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be an internal beta of Steam on Ubuntu in the near future.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've announced that it is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Left 4 Dead 2 is the first title they're bringing to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If other developers want to port their games over to Linux, Valve is making the distribution model for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ran a Linux box for a while, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a FreeBSD box.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a long time ago, back when I was trying to host my own domain name and be a super nerd.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask this question.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to take it back a huge step here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to ask this question because I seriously think a lot of people don't know the answer to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think sometimes the hardcore computer people, super nerds, don't realize that a lot of people don't get this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or maybe they do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But why would someone want to have a Linux machine?
[SPEAKER_10]: What does Linux do for you that Windows doesn't?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uptime.
[SPEAKER_06]: A well-made Linux install.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just have your computer on all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't lose any performance.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can put... The terminology, I haven't touched this stuff in seriously like 10 years, but when people think Linux or Unix, they think of sort of like MS-DOS prompt, like just a text terminal, but that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: Linux has visual Windows-ish interfaces now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, but if you're into independent software, like really independent, Linux has got a huge community, people making apps for each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just all about the...
[SPEAKER_06]: If you do have a good internet connection, you want to host your own email, host your own domain names, host your own web server, blah, blah, blah, you're going to be running some flavor of Linux on that box if you want to do all that in-house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at all these nerds in our chat room, and I say that lovingly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blackwolf says, I've had a free BSD server up for over 1,000 days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Up time.
[SPEAKER_10]: My home box was up for 400 days until I rebooted it recently.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw says Linux is commonly used to run servers, especially for online games.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameGuru says Linux is generally more secure than Windows.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that, though, because just less people use it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it's kind of like the whole, well, Apple never gets hacked because there's less people on, you know, those systems than there are on...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there was a problem in the early 2000s where certain distributions of Linux, if you just put it on a machine, would have its email relay turned on by default.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if someone found your IP address, they could just spam the shit out of everybody using your server and you would never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you don't know what you're doing, people can do nasty things on your Linux box.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then that's your problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's you being an idiot, not the software being, you know, built...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Technus says, I like Linux.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate the elitist community that comes with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: FreeBSD versus Linux, or just the StarBSD versus StarLinux, that's some Star Wars, Star Trek shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's switchblades, and people get shivved in alleyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very brutal.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Steam on Linux, do you think that would be well received by the community?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or do you think it'll be like, ugh, commercialism?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they would have to run, if they really wanted to play Windows games on Linux, they would have to do, I think, it's called Wine, which is kind of like, I think, Boot Camp.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people on the internet wine very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: it's like boot camper parallels I think on Mac where you can run Windows through it so if people wanted to play PC games but they just I don't want a PC box in my house I don't want a partition of a hard drive god damn it this will allow them to do that for at least for Left 4 Dead 2 anything else if they don't want to have a Windows box or a Windows partition they're going to have to mess with it
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf says very clearly, Wine is not an emulator.
[SPEAKER_10]: It basically implements the Windows DLLs on Linux.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little correction.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because remember, Linux, elitist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm giving him a hard time.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameGuru says Left 4 Dead 2 is a good choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a rather complex source game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you can get that on there, then that opens the door to a lot of other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, before we go on to the next story, Loki, I want to... Wine actually stands for wine is not an emulator.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I actually knew that, but I'm so far removed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ten years, just saying old age.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to go back to a comment that came up in chat earlier, because this is a very important clarification to something I brought up a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Osfer in our chatroom says for the Theatrhythm DLC for Somnus from Final Fantasy Versus XIII it labels the song as just from the Final Fantasy series but not which one maybe that's a sign of the name change that they don't want to reveal yet that is huge that is a big deal I think that's worth stating so thank you for saying that Osfer I think that is if they didn't label it as Versus XIII then yes a name change is coming or question mark question mark
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, back to news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so let's talk a little bit about Fez.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fez had an issue with one of its recent patches where not a lot of people, but some people were having issues with their save games being obliterated.
[SPEAKER_02]: and, of course, because of that, Polytron pulled back the patch that they put out and they were going to release a second patch to fix that problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, they said no because it was going to cost them $10,000 to get the game recertified by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, so they're just saying, well, you know, if any players have an issue with the game, um, you know, your saves being deleted since you're only like 1%, um, kind of tough luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just got to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, so of course, you know, they made the comment, you know, had Fez been released on Steam, we wouldn't have this issue because updates are free.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I believe the designer of Fez said it's not a PC game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't want it on PCs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they said no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, does that mean a Steam version is in progress?
[SPEAKER_02]: Only a few months left for Xbox Live Arcade exclusivity, they said.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft, of course, responded saying that Polytron and their investors, Trapdoor, made the decision not to work on an additional title update for Fez.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft Studios chose to support this decision based on the belief that Polytron and Trapdoor were in the best position to determine what the acceptable quality level for their game is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And while we do not disclose the cost of title updates, we did offer to work with Trapdoor and make sure that wasn't a blocking issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were mainly huge fans of Fez.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know if that means, okay, we're not going to charge you $10,000, but we'll charge you $7,500.
[SPEAKER_02]: Discount!
[SPEAKER_02]: Discount.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't really know what the issue is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently Microsoft patches are available in the Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, it is a closed system, so Microsoft can charge you wherever the hell you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when you make your game, you're well aware of what those costs are going to be before you make your game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they probably thought, okay, well, that's no problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to have an issue with this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then some bugs went through, and so they released a patch, which obviously they did not test well enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if it's only happening to 1% of the people all the time... See, I don't understand how a save game problem can only be happening to 1% of the people because...
[SPEAKER_02]: that's you're basically running on systems that are all the same you know I don't understand how it can affect one and not the other but whatever so they released a patch that they didn't test well enough and now they're complaining that they would have to pay more money out of their pocket to you know fix the game and I understand this developer is not as big as like Activision who releases like 13 goddamn patches for Call of Duty and
[SPEAKER_10]: Indie Game, The Movie, Surely They Must Be Rich
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if that's the case, but maybe $10,000 is too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're kind of like opportunity costs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can either fix it for the 1%, but are we really going to recoup this money in additional sales, or do we just leave it as it is, and hopefully it doesn't affect that many more people, and we'll just keep the money where we're at.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's kind of where they're at, is that they want to spend the money.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a tricky issue, though, because on one hand, I'm like, wow, that's kind of fucked up of Microsoft to charge so much money, but on the other hand, I'm like, well, it also really encourages people to get it right the first time, so I can't blame them.
[SPEAKER_02]: because as it is games are patched left and right anyways and you know I think that it's a good thing that they do charge that kind of money because it does discourage them from like going well fuck it we didn't really test this game so we're just gonna release it out there we'll see what kind of bugs people run into and then we'll go fix it I should be able to get a refund when their game is buggy as hell although it's not granted it's only affecting less than one or whatever it is one percent of people but if I'm in that one percent I should be able to get my money back don't you think
[SPEAKER_10]: You'd have to make the argument with Microsoft Welcome to the world of digital distribution Yeah They just take customer service right on out of the picture
[SPEAKER_02]: But to be fair, it's not necessarily Microsoft's fault that that game doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just being hosted on their service.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the developer and publisher that decided, hey, we don't want to pay money to fix this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're going to have to go ask them for your money back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but it's on their system.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's only on their system.
[SPEAKER_10]: They kind of own it a little bit too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, whether they want it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not their fault though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like saying, oh, that game is like
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is buggy, and just because it happens to be on Xbox 360, I'm going to blame Microsoft for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't make any sense, because they're just providing the system that it runs on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their system's not causing the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least, I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well let's move on to a different topic that apparently is causing a big problem in the iPad world, or iOS, but this particularly is for the iPad, and Alan, I'm pretty happy that Maruko in San Rio, your cats...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm incredibly against decline cats because they actually remove like it's part of the bone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're taking off like half their finger.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you don't have a declawed cat, why is it pining your iPad?
[SPEAKER_06]: It costs like $800.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think the glass scratches that easy from cats scratching it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, like my cat scratches our LCD TV and... I wouldn't want to take that chance.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I look at the sofa and I'm like... Well, that's the sofa.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where you've got material where the cat's claws are getting caught in.
[SPEAKER_10]: The cats have already fucked up the bed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but we're talking glass.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're talking glass that's meant to withstand quite a few scuffs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, dropping it on something or scraping it against something sharp might cause a scratch, but the cat claws aren't strong enough to cause a lot of scratches.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's folks in the chat saying Bobby Blackwolf says their claws don't scratch the screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've tested.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plus, I hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't believe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, the bottom of their feet are nice and soft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So whatever scratches they put in there, they buff right out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: When a cat bats at something playfully, it doesn't have its claws out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when it's trying to fuck up a chair, it's trying to clean its claws on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, its claws are out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not going to do that on an iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: It, like everything else in the Apple world these days, has DLC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Double dippin', right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Charge you up front and then, hey, you want more levels for your cats?
[SPEAKER_10]: 99 cents for a new mouse level.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's the real surprise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cats bought it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, there's this epidemic where cats are inadvertently buying the DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: And people are complaining...
[SPEAKER_09]: That the design of the game fooled cats into buying it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because there's probably some little mouse that says buy more on it that runs across the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the next one is yes to check out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, real hard stuff to code around.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I thought that they had to put in passwords in order to, you know, get that stuff purchased.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can save those, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I can't do that on my iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you can save your password so it never prompts you for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: We let our cats watch the TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is it stupid?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like, okay, this is basically like saying, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: My cat likes the outdoors.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to buy it a car so it can drive down the street because it fucking likes the outdoors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tootsies is real.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it the benefit of the doubt and say that I can see someone having a little swipe, you know, a little game visually for the cat on an iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can believe that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I can't believe is someone going, hmm...
[SPEAKER_06]: Mittens was really into that game a week ago, but now she just doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she needs the DLC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she needs a new stage for her to be interested in again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, cats don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: and they're like, I gotta get that light.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta get the light.
[SPEAKER_02]: The light's delicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eat the light.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light.
[SPEAKER_00]: Light.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chase the light.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The light.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on my paw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, so close.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where'd it go?
[SPEAKER_02]: That can also be a dog too, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dogs do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to love that because I'd play with the laser pointer on my dog and you'd see her just like twitching out for like an hour afterwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like, what, what, what, what, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're coming for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: To answer the folks in chat, Hiccup is the company behind this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And an artist named TJ Fuller, who did the artwork in Games for Cats, said, quote, We got in a lot of trouble.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, they have implemented a human check to fix the issue.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to hold four fingers on touch points without moving them for a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because a cat would never have that type of attention span to hold in four spots for a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless it's standing on top of the iPad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So just like you have to monitor your children when they're playing with the iPad, maybe you should monitor your cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because let's be real, you're not buying the app on the iPad for the cat's enjoyment, you're buying it for yours to watch the cat play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get the cat away from you so they would stop bothering you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma in chat says, this all reminds me of the Smurfs village fiasco.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Ranma, but those were children.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: They still have like 13-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that those Microsoft purchases were real money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the name of the really, he's really old, he's got the sunglasses, the fashion designer, Margaret Cho had a bit about him.
[SPEAKER_10]: Carl Lagerfeld.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: His cat has a personal assistant and a Twitter and its own iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just put that out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Carl Lagerfeld's cat has its own iPad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that maybe that could be, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What have you done with your life?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the story reminded me of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a real thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you put on your resume?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was a personal assistant to this cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my last... The cat fired me because I... Tunes is the driving cat.
[SPEAKER_00]: The cat who can drive a car.
[SPEAKER_00]: He drives around all over the town.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tunes is the driving cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tunes is the cat who can drive a car.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't just look at me!
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's be real, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two Exes did a good thing by making sure Victoria Jackson was in that car.
[SPEAKER_10]: Agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: And poor Phil Hartman.
[SPEAKER_10]: Poor Phil Hartman.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rest in peace.
[SPEAKER_10]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio on VOGnetwork.com, use the passphrase, kitten.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me, I'm eating popcorn.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony is shutting down the online servers for two of its MotorStorm Muddy Truck games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specifically, it's MotorStorm Pacific Rift.
[SPEAKER_06]: which came out in 2008 so that is four years old and it's PSP counterpart MotorStorm Arctic Edge so if you like to connect to PSN and do races co-op or whatever with the matching service that is all going away.
[SPEAKER_06]: as of, I think, October 1st is the last day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I guess September 30th is the last day you have to enjoy that because October 1st is going down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least I gave you a heads up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that was nice then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are any of these games online pass games or are we not there yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we're not yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't even get into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I was bitching about Mass Effect 3, by the way, I didn't even get into the online pass thing and how my $10 isn't paying for shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, I'll just let that argument write itself, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a really short story.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Motorstorm Pacific Rift and Motorstorm Arctic Edge, which is a PSP title, losing its Sony-provided network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the PSPs are molding over anyway, so that one's not so bad, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and see what games we can buy that will have their servers shut down in 2015.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if any of these games are going to have their servers shut down, but there is not really much coming out this week because it's kind of falling along the lines of...
[SPEAKER_02]: July, the month with no game releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this week we do have, if you're feeling that you've got to get in shape to wear a bikini, maybe not this year because you've procrastinated too long, but for next year, they've got the Adidas MyCoach for PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 Move and Connect.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's tons of pre-orders for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Myst on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: because there's actually people that were born well after that game came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Prototype 2 on PC finally making its way out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was quite delayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also I guess they have a Move Essential bundle for the PlayStation 3 with Just Dance 3 thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that is out in Japan this week on July the 26th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alice Madness Returns gets a price reduction on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also on the PlayStation 3 this week, Shin Sangoku Musou Multirade 2 HD version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that tells me this is a remake HD version.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a remake of a title that was already out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to see if this is a game I recognize from here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like...
[SPEAKER_10]: DYNASTY WARRIORS
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing really of note on the Vita this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some accessories, a new AC adapter, but that's not that exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So lastly on the 3DS this week, Cave Story 3D makes its way to Japan this week, as does a new pen in cobalt blue.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, ah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That does it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: UK and Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Prototype 2 on PC is coming out July 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 25th, we have Wizorb, which I would recommend very much if you're into 16-bit retro sort of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's 2D, but it's an RPG, Arkanoid Breakout mashup game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's got the Super NES graphics, and you're a little wizard.
[SPEAKER_06]: playing Breakout, and it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have that on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's also, check out the Steam sale before it goes away because I got it a couple days ago for like three bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on indie games for Xbox if you don't have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's specifically on the PlayStation 3, PlayStation Vita, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wizorb also on July 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Recketeer which is the game we were talking about earlier July 27th we have Inversion on PC and Pokemon Conquest on DS and then finally for this week on July 28th Freaky Forms Deluxe Your Creation's Alive which is a very silly name I don't know what that is
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, just a few more stories for you guys before we get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura may not be here to give the classic game out, but SalaciousPop will fill in, and we'll figure out what he picked in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: For now, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may remember a few years ago there was a class I mean, there's always class-sashing lawsuits when it comes to Madden and NCAA, but there's one that actually went to court, and they finally settled, so
[SPEAKER_02]: EA has reached a settlement in a class action lawsuit that started in 2008 for $27 million.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, part of that, they will not be able to renew their exclusive agreement with the NCAA, assuming that the court upholds that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, because of that, those who were affected by it, who purchased a
[SPEAKER_02]: EA Sports NCAA game will be entitled to anywhere from $6.79 per game on the GameCube, Xbox, and PlayStation 2 and $1.95 for the Wii, Xbox 360, and PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they're saying that also EA has agreed to stipulation on future license agreements as part of the proposed settlement they will not make any exclusive licensing deals with the AFL for five years and they will not renew their current agreement with the NCAA and also they won't be able to enter another exclusive licensing agreement with the NCAA for five years and the exclusive I guess well the trademarks for like the NFL and stuff are not affected by it because this is only the NCAA
[SPEAKER_10]: but uh it's still interesting yeah I was gonna say I don't follow sports titles as closely you know I think that's pretty obvious if you listen to the show for a while but obviously these are huge money games I know EA's had a lot of they've taken a lot of shit for their exclusive agreements in the past this kind of seems like a big deal here I mean granted the the refunds that people get aren't that big a deal although I heard that whatever people don't claim will go to child's play which that's great but
[SPEAKER_10]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it sucked because it didn't have those licenses.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't have as big of a budget.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it sucked as just a game, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to say they couldn't pull something out, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then the other thing, too, is that they have to wait on approval from the court, which is going to happen on September 27th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is all, right now, the settlement, but the court has to say, okay, we agreed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The settlement's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll just have to see what happens there.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we should say again the NFL trademark is not it's not affected no this does not affect Madden at all so um but I just think it's funny though is our arena football is also I mean they haven't had an arena football game in forever although I didn't remember they did try that for a while they had an arena football game for like two years what about the XFL game I'm just kidding
[SPEAKER_02]: The Lingerie Football League
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm telling you, that's a real thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I might play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know the problem with those lingerie football leagues and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the people watch you because they're hoping that a top gets ripped off, and it never fucking happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's my problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not adult enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need an adult...
[SPEAKER_06]: I need an adult.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's only so much plausible deniability on why you're watching it before it's like I could have looked at so much porn in the time that I've been watching this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to take it that next step further.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm watching this because I think they play really good football.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one's believing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're reading it for the articles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm watching this for the articles.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what would make  getting away from sexy women for a minute, you know what they should license into a game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've already done that because you see  Get out.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Puppy Bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: But remember, there was the  God, who was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't Joe Montana.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Jerry Rice Dog Football.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out on the Wii last year, about a year ago, actually, because I remember... Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the problem is that was Joe Montana, who's kind of, you know, he's long... It's Jerry Rice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Jerry Rice also kind of, you know, it's not that hot-ass ref that they had on the Puppy Bowl the past couple years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really, you know why I failed?
[SPEAKER_02]: No kitten halftime, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Jerry Rice and Nidus Dog Football was the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they have any  I have a  the talk about chicks and football and all this has me thinking about one of my good friends and I follow her on Facebook and all this.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's getting really into roller derby lately.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are there any good roller derby experiences on consoles?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I want to say, I thought there was a roller derby game, but probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think there is a roller derby game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, perhaps... There's quite a roller derby audience, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's got, like, a trading card and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps, you know, they will come out with one because, you know, there was... There's been plenty of games for, like, what was it...
[SPEAKER_02]: for lacrosse and for rugby and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe we'll see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am seeing, though, there is... Yeah, Jam City Roller Girls was actually a game that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on, I think, the Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: Stan in our chatroom says, you mean Asuka?
[SPEAKER_10]: She was the girl that was on the tester who was on the show about six months ago at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: I follow her on Twitter, but not Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I forgot, she does Roller Derby too, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, this is a different friend I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, WeWear.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on WeWear, Jam City Roller Girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is an authentic, well, I don't know how authentic, but it is a roller derby game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they do have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is, you know, they should have more than one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks decent.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to go to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to put this out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, Alan, I'll wait for you to make some smart-ass comments so you get ready, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even really want to plug the website by saying its name, but I'm going to have to.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I want to just preface this by saying I ain't endorsing this shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just have to report on how ludicrous it is, all right?
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a new website out there, and it's basically, from what it sounds like, it's kind of like Adult Friend Finder, but for gamers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's called Shag-A-Gamer.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's launched in the United Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't imagine that's in the United Kingdom with it being called Shag-A-Gamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't believe anybody uses the phrase Shag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every time they see Austin Powers, they want to say Shag.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Austin Powers featuring a British spy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's some current stuff there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Current material you got working there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Austin Powers, a franchise that hasn't been around for years now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is what they're calling the number one adult site for gamers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we're number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, who's their competition?
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're offering their services to thousands of single gamers who want nothing more than a quick shag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: For just 19.99 a month, you get full access.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a quote, quote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Full access to young, old, exciting, sexy individuals wanting no strings sex.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're apparently coming soon as a Shaga Gamer TV as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I do want to say, and this is important in their quote, they do not mention female gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be all dudes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All dudes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So technically, yes, there are young, old gamers that want to have sex with no strings attached, but they're all dudes.
[SPEAKER_10]: The site continues, quote,
[SPEAKER_10]: and out of all those thousands of people that are hooking up, they have 56 followers on their Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe the OLR Twitter has something like 700 or 800 followers.
[SPEAKER_10]: So would it be fair to say that if suddenly we said, you know what, we don't want to be just an internet radio show anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to be a place for casual gamers to find a fuck.
[SPEAKER_10]: We would be able to say, now we are the number one company.
[SPEAKER_09]: So suck it, Shagga Gamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a problem with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alan?
[SPEAKER_06]: This just makes me curious as to how many hookups happen at E3 or PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do people get laid at those cons?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: PAX, there's been articles where people will post Craigslist notifications.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a meetup for an orgy, basically, at PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Anime Cons.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's a lot of geek sex going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything with a furry crossover, then yes, obviously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dragon Con?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think all the guys from VOG are going?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mean stuff that's set up like that on Craigslist, but just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, hey, I see you at the Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm in that hotel, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Room 4?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got some wine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they have a phrase for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, a fool and his money are easily parted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't be a sucker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, there are not sites like this that are, there's just tons of hot gamer girls just waiting around for someone to just fuck them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are there any guys here that fuck me, me, Mrs. Attractive Gaming Loving Girl with big titties?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that does not exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anywhere!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, all these sites that want to charge you money and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, for example, there's a perfect, what was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the gaming one where you would join up and you'd play games with hot gaming girls and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they would, you know, have video cam time with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they may undress somewhat when you're playing Battleship or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, Alan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might shag that gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: That image on their splash page is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I can't tell if it's just a really cheap stock image photo that they just photoshopped the Shagged Gamer thing on his shirt or if that's an actual photo shoot.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because she has it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: She has it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I could shop that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's a photo shoot that they had.
[SPEAKER_10]: About as hard as that might be right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: What am I pointing at, Alan?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look how well defined that is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, she's lifting his shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think that's a photoshop.
[SPEAKER_06]: at his junk, I guess, but you don't need to lift his shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what's going on in that picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then they show some of the actual users of the site, and like, you know, Paula, 25, she's waiting to get shagged.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, here's my question, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is so gamer about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, is it like, you know, you want someone to fuck and then cuddle and play Skyrim with after?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't you just go on OkCupid and set gamer tags as your match?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, only show me people that have this filter?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or even if you're looking to date somebody, there's even that Geek2Geek site, which I hear is okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you're better off with something like an OKCupid or Plenty of Fish or something like that, where it doesn't really cost you anything to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because these sites, they basically, oh, yeah, it's free to sign up, free to sign up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you sign up, and then you're like, oh, I want to talk to this person.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to send them a message saying, yes, I would like to fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry, that's going to cost you money.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not a premium member.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you become a premium member.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry, you're not blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need more money to do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: These people that they have, the models that they have here are not on their fucking site, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: really tiny, really
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we've spent far too much time on this topic yeah just don't give them your time I mean that's basically the moral of the story just go to Craigslist but be careful like there's some real freaky people on Craigslist Craigslist is just weird freaky people let's go to a time when games were a lot similar
[SPEAKER_10]: Back when we were innocent and we weren't thinking about such pervert things.
[SPEAKER_10]: The classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week, DarkSakura goes into the vault and finds a classic game that she deems worthy of you to revisit all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: But since she's at a wedding, Alan's here and he dug into the shoebox to find the classic game that he thinks you all should play this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Classic Game of the Week is a LucasArts game on the Scum Engine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Came out in 1993.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is Maniac Mansion, Day of the Pinnacle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got any audio for me?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting some up right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Made a poop sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: This amazing intro.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, this is the sequel to a previous Classic Game of the Week, Maniac Mansion, which came out in 1987.
[SPEAKER_06]: You play Bernard, who was one of the cast members of the first game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are called back to the mansion by...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally blanking on his name, Dr. Fred, because the Purple Tentacle has drank some toxic sludge that made him super smart, and he's going to take over the world, so you and your two friends have to go back in time to prevent him from drinking the slime and becoming super smart, but something goes horribly wrong with the time machines that are made out of porta-potties.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're modified porta-potties.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen to the audio.
[SPEAKER_06]: they fixed the engine that they used in this for Salmon Max Hit the Road which was the other game I was debating using tonight but yeah so you've got give, pick up, use, push, look at, open and you just click that you click on your verb and then you click on what you want and you interact with the puzzles that way
[SPEAKER_06]: Bernard stays in present day, his sort of overweight rocker friend, very hair metal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hoagie goes into the future, and then she's kind of a Daria Morgendorfer, Ally Sheedy and the Breakfast Club kind of spazzy girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: She goes back in time to the colonial ages.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy Edisons forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do I have that backwards?
[SPEAKER_06]: I forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: She goes to the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hogi goes to the past.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I haven't played this game in years.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's super awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They went and looked at a bunch of Warner Brothers cartoons for the visual, like how they wanted to do the art direction.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also a lot of the sound effects are taken directly from the cartoons as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, it's got Thomas Jefferson and George Washington are some of the cameos that Hoagie has to deal with in the past.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has a great endgame when it all comes together and all the three characters are joined again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: this game also was one of the first few CD games for one it was a computer game that came out on CD-ROM and also had full voice acting which at the time I think King's Quest 5 the Sierra game which came out I think in 91 also had voice acting but a lot of it was really bad the voice acting in these LucasArts games even though for the early 90s are phenomenal
[SPEAKER_06]: Amazing voice acting considering that it was new technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because when this came out on PC and PC were just getting talky video games, we were playing the Super Nintendo for about a year or two because that came out in 91.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just show the timeline of how the technology was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I actually installed, I still have this, I have the original instruction booklet and the disc, and I installed DOSBox on my Windows 7 machine so I could play this in Salmon Max.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does this come on LucasArts' pack that's on Steam?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good old games has it, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember there was some type of LucasArts mega pack of adventure games that was on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that's how you could get loom and shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for people who are into emulators, DOSBox is just... You still need the game with DOSBox, but if you have SCUMM, SCUMM is also an emulator specifically for LucasArts games that run on this engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft clarifies, nope, it isn't on Steam at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it is not a part of that pack.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also some other comments on this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Burr says, Day of the Tentacle is the best adventure game ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dungeon Buster says, this was LucasArts at the height of awesome too.
[SPEAKER_06]: This and Sam & Max, I don't want to try to put one over the other, but both of those games together are just phenomenal adventure games for that era of PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to say about Maniac Mansion Day of the Tentacle?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the funniest games I've ever played aside from Beavis and Butthead Virtual Stupidity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, I'm sorry, Mike Judge wrote the script.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a hilarious game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll have to pick that next time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I want to say... There's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say that I'm trying to find the actual site for this rumor, but I think it might be Telltale Games, but someone somewhere wants to put out an episodic franchise that exists in the same universe that references Day of the Tentacle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could see that, because, you know, as much as people love this game, nothing ever really came after it, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, Maniac Mansion 3, do you think we'd get?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, LucasArts has been all about, literally, Star Wars games for what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much since, once this era ended, they've just been about Star Wars, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Grim Fandango was their last big splash in PC adventure games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, super awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: People should check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Maniac Mansion 2, Day of the Tentacle, or just Day of the Tentacle for short.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Alan, good pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: A good PC adventure game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break, but don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have plenty more show when we come back, including Rapid Fire News, and we're going to revisit Xbox Security again, but this time it might not be as much ranting as it's been in the past.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll find out when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, live on Sunday, July the 22nd of 2012, with episode number 466 of our show.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: She is at a wedding in Las Vegas, the wedding of Tiara and Dan from geek-life.com, and we want to once again wish them a very happy wedding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see the pictures are starting to show up on Facebook, and all I can say is, aww.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I promised a giveaway here in Part B, and again, this is a code generously donated to the show by Bashka, and you can visit his website, critcraft.blogspot.com, if you like World of Warcraft stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even if you don't, he tends to have some other little gaming things that sneak in there too, and the types of stuff that a lot of OLR people, I bet, would be really into.
[SPEAKER_10]: What we are giving away, once again, it is a beta key for Ravaged.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can play this little gameplay trailer here that he sent me there on the Facebooks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess there's some gameplay in this trailer here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a first-person shooter that is set in a world ravaged by a polar shift pitting scavengers versus the resistance.
[SPEAKER_10]: So as soon as this ad finishes playing, I'll play a little clip of the gameplay trailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: and we're going to give this away right now to somebody that is checked in at vognetwork.com and in our chat room and of course wants the code because I'm going to send them a private message and be like, are you going to use this code?
[SPEAKER_10]: And if they will use it, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they don't, then I'll give it away to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looks like a lot of... This is the game that was supposed to be like Rage.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how rage is supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, you know, like fighting in Doom Buggies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lots of like Doom Buggies, planes, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Might want a pretty decent computer in order to play this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's see who we're going to give that away to.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to do this live right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: What I'm doing right now, I'm pulling up the list of people that are currently checked into the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so I need you, Loki, you checked in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you trying to win this too?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I just check in all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, pick a number between 1 and 30.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, pick a number between 1 and 30.
[SPEAKER_10]: 23 23, so that's 31, 39, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3 I want to see if that person is in chat right now Hopefully they have a similar name or I might not be able to identify them I think you can just Google a random number generator and put in the 1 to 30 It's more fun if I ask you I'm looking I don't see that person in chat right now I'm looking one more time
[SPEAKER_10]: Just making sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, yeah, that person isn't in chat right now, so give me another number.
12.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty sure this person's in chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me see if he wants it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to be the guy, Gaiden
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll have to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's three levels long and you can check it out on GameJolt has it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just go to GameJolt.com and look in their freeware section and they've got, you know, I want to be the guy Gaten.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty easy to find.
[SPEAKER_02]: or you can go to Kaylin's site k-a-y-i-n dot p-y-o-k-o dot org slash i-w-b-t-g I want to be the guy so there you go you can find all the information on that and it's pretty cool so check it out this is kind of funny you know the game Tokyo Jungle the one that's basically a bunch of animals surviving in a post apocalyptic Tokyo it looked awesome
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they're even making it a little stranger.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're adding Japanese businessmen to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's DLC that's coming out that you can play as a salaryman.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, businessmen can be pretty savage, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can play the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hope you don't have to mate them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yes, so that'll be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to the game when it finally makes it over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft in chat says, isn't it being localized for the US?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ray Deer at live.vognetwork.com says, I want to be the guy, damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure that's what a lot of people say playing that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Manos, The Hands of Fate Manos, The Hands of Fate
[SPEAKER_02]: How bad is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've fallen asleep twice trying to watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once, both times with Mr. Science Seeker 3000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh wow, and it was still bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was still so bad that I fell asleep.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's move on to some other stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: First up, Rock Band Blitz finally has a release date.
[SPEAKER_10]: They said it would come out this summer, and we're already about halfway through summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we finally have a date for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: PlayStation, August 28th, Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: A day later, August 29th, it's going to cost you $15.
[SPEAKER_10]: And some more songs were revealed for the game that will be in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool and the Gang's Jungle Boogie, My Chemical Romances Sing, Fun's We Are Young.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's like the song that won't go away off the radio at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Avenged Sevenfold's So Far Away also there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a lot of people very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It uses all the DLC from Rock Band that you might have built up on your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you're like me, you have a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: An anonymous tech at NASA laser engraved the space core on a part that is going to be flying on a resupply craft to the International Space Station.
[SPEAKER_10]: Valve posted about it on their official portal blog on Friday.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't know who did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was an anonymous tech at NASA.
[SPEAKER_10]: NASA did not endorse this, but it's happening because they actually laser engraved this little Wheatley in space.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Wheatley.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a core.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wheatley Zemo about it and then there's the other guy in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been a little while since I beat Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I beat it when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you're going to kill me because I gave a little spoiler there, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Game's been out a year and it's been on sale for like five bucks lately.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I'm thinking you haven't played it at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, lastly, EA gets a lot of hate, but they did something that's pretty cool this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: They joined Microsoft, Viacom, Google, Zynga, another company that gets a lot of hate, and eBay on this that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a amicus brief that declares opposition to DOMA, the Defense of Marriage Act, which legally defines marriage between a man and a woman.
[SPEAKER_10]: and EA in a press release said quote DOMA presents a number of problems for businesses like EA as it creates regulatory tax and discrimination complications for employers and that's why we're standing against it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The underlying lawsuit impacts all employers no matter how big or small and no matter the industry and we encourage other businesses to join these efforts.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: EA's been pretty supportive of LGBT causes in the past.
[SPEAKER_10]: They actually marched in the Pride Parade in San Francisco and in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've done their own It Gets Better campaign video that's available on YouTube as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So a little less evil doing the right thing and standing against DOMA, which obviously we here at OLR also think is kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's move on with some more stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Los Angeles Comedy Club Laugh Factory, which is world famous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the first stand-up comedian that ever performed there was Richard Pryor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dave Chappelle has done like six-hour sets there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yes, world famous.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a charity to help kids and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are coming out with a streaming channel for PS3 on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: PS3 only from this story $3 a month if you're a stand-up comedy nerd like myself and you listen to stand-up comic podcasts like Greg Proops and Aisha Tyler like I do you might like this I know stand-up comedy isn't really as relevant now as it was in the 90s but yeah Laugh Factory Los Angeles Club $3 a month both pre-recorded and live performances from stand-ups no real schedule yet on the content but if you're a comedy nerd
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got three bucks a month to burn.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although you can get it for free through some of those other podcasts you mentioned.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also the Dreamcast Classic Jet Set Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a very funky, amazing, cel-shaded game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming to iOS and Android this summer to complement the PC and Vita versions.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I remembered the Dreamcast one, the original, and it was an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It eventually got too hard for me to like, I think by the time I unlocked the fourth or fifth character, it just got so hard I couldn't do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: The learning curve for the controls was when you got it, you got it, but it took a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I cannot imagine how this is going to play on a touchscreen unless they really tweak the controls.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, funky Jet Set Radio goodness coming to your phones this summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you looking?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, don't just say something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't Google it.
17.
[SPEAKER_10]: 17.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if Ragenator was 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know that person's in chat and I know he'll respond.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is VXJasonXV is number 17 to check in tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Buy me a little time here, guys, while I send Jason a private message.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we're going to get into the Fugle question of the week here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week we ask you guys a question on our Facebook and our Google+.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put them together and you get Fugle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have the music queued up this week, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: We read some of the responses here on the air.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think we'll get through all of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a lot of responses tonight, and there's no way I'm going to be able to read all of these.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please, please check out our Facebook community at Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio and our Google+.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a few responses over there, too, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have a URL for it.
11094.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not going to read the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just go to Google+, and search for Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll find us there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the question of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of a tricky question because obviously there was a lot of really tough stuff that happened over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, just a lot of really unfortunate events.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when tragedy like this happens, unfortunately people like to point the finger at video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: and so I wanted to ask this question to our Facebook and Google communities and that is sometimes when tragedy happens commentators on big news channels are quick to blame video games for a person being so deranged what if anything can we do as a gaming community to stop this reputation and show that there are far more good people playing video games than bad you know because when that
[SPEAKER_10]: Incident happened in Aurora over the weekend, which was terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: They splashed that guy all over the news, as the news tends to do, which is really unfortunate because they're just making him famous by doing that, which I hate.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should be the victims we should be remembering, but anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: They always bring these commentators on because everybody wants to know, why'd he do it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why'd he do it?
[SPEAKER_10]: What was going on in his head?
[SPEAKER_10]: He was a quiet kid and he went crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why'd he do it?
[SPEAKER_10]: And somebody always inevitably says, video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem with playing video games is it's as common now to be playing video games as it is to watch TV, so you can blame TV now too?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was that rock music he was listening to, it was those comics he was reading, it was the TV he was watching, it was the movies he was watching, it was the drugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: and some people blame Batman because he said when he got arrested or whatever that he was the Joker.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the goddamn Batman.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know who is to blame?
[SPEAKER_10]: Him.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a fake article that circulated on Tumblr the night that it happened saying that he was arrested in like Joker cosplay and which of course is full of shit not true but it's like why are people photoshopping fake
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like talking about him, but I will entertain that there was a picture of him with crazy hair that was on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, anything can be photoshopped, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it was on his adult friend finder.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it's those sexual deviants!
[SPEAKER_10]: Look, no, it was him.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was his fault.
[SPEAKER_10]: He did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, two words.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck him.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get to, though, how do we keep the bad reputation off of gamers?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because there's far more good people playing video games than there are bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me go to some of the answers on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: RedTheHaze starts us off.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first thing we should do is not get online and attack the people who blame video games because it just proves them right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Think before you act.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to bring ourselves out there and show our positive side and drown out the negative noise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make a YouTube video or write up on how we are productive members of society.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just don't be an asshole on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's as simple as that.
[SPEAKER_10]: or don't watch those news programs because they're sensationalist to get people to watch them Ronnie B says usually it's the news media so I'd ask them how is their constant coverage endorsement of graphic stories 24-7 any less likely to drive someone mad than a video game even if the results of a tragic event is inspired by a video game what can you do when the person is a grown adult there is already the ESRB in the US so I don't think you can really blame video games anymore and I think that's the best argument
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: And part of the reason he did it was he said, I want to be famous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know I'm going to be plastered all over the news.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be famous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be the most famous.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, in this interesting, ironic twist, that all happened on September 10th, 2001.
[SPEAKER_10]: so he wasn't famous for very long because the media hopped right on to something else well he got his 15 minutes I mean and it's just like I'm not trying to be funny it's just this really hugely ironic thing and it just kind of points out I mean god I hate using that word in conjunction with such tragedy but you guys know you know what I'm getting at it's that he you know was driven by fame
[SPEAKER_10]: Attention whores, that's what they are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, right here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clover N responds saying, promote all the charities connected to video gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Acidic Vampire says, nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a waste of time trying to educate our tards who scapegoat.
[SPEAKER_02]: The End
[SPEAKER_10]: WhyNot18is9 responds and says, Parents, it's not the only solution but a start on knowing what your kids are playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: If there's a problem with the kid's brain, then a video game might be the start of stifling the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could be wrong, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great show, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Picaruno says,
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're really interested in how TV really works from an insider's point of view, I urge you to watch Charlie Brooker's Screen Wipe, News Wipe, and Games Wipe on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting comment from Picaruno, kind of from the inside.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last one from Facebook, Cody T says,
[SPEAKER_10]: So in conclusion, there is no good or even great way to get media to stop blaming it on video games because media is media and at the end of the day, true gamers know that it is not true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Complicated issue.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before I go to Google, Alan?
[SPEAKER_06]: With all the, you know, with Chris Hardwick's franchise Nerdist and all this stuff, the progress that gamers have made with like PAX and just crossing into the mainstream and being more of an accessible thing for, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not as niche as it once was, but the reality is that it's still considered for the people ages 45 and older who watch the news, who get really into this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still a part of the counterculture, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still something that a lot of people can't relate to.
[SPEAKER_06]: That makes it a magnet, like Loki was saying about the sensationalism.
[SPEAKER_06]: If he was a huge sports nut who was a jock who got super late in high school and he was just a big sports freak and did not...
[SPEAKER_06]: even own a console, they wouldn't pursue that angle because that's considered normal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They would pursue it as he was a sexual deviant because he had an adult friend finder profile.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they would say, okay, well, what's the first thing we can find that's even a little bit not as bland and as mainstream as possible?
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games is often that thing because a lot of people over a certain age don't understand it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask this question, and I'm taking a devil's advocate angle, because I think a lot of this sensationalism happens because we just want to understand, as a society, why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did this happen?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did evil, there's no other word to describe it, why did evil happen?
[SPEAKER_10]: Where did we as a society fail to allow this to happen?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the other thing, too, is they keep saying he operated on his own, but how'd he get in the theater?
[SPEAKER_02]: He bought a ticket.
[SPEAKER_10]: He had to suit up though, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear what they got up to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is he going to hide an AR-15?
[SPEAKER_10]: Regardless, I mean, I believe I had heard something and read online he used an emergency exit to go to his car and propped it open so that he could get back in the theater.
[SPEAKER_10]: Regardless, the guy had his house booby-trapped to the nines to try and kill some policemen too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, he was clearly deranged in all sorts of ways.
[SPEAKER_10]: He thought of a way.
[SPEAKER_10]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, but again, let me go back to the devil's advocate question.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's wrong with wanting to know where did we fail as a society?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's the difficult question.
[SPEAKER_06]: The easy question is to just say, this terrifies me and I'm confused and hurting and this is a horrible story, but the media is saying that it's video games and I'm old and I've never played those and I don't know anyone who plays those, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I can sleep better at night knowing that it's that evil yucky thing that's influencing people to do this it's the quickest way to get people to like they need to associate something because they just they don't understand it and it's unfortunate that video games is often used because it's a billion dollar industry it's everywhere people will pay attention if you obviously lie and say bullshitty things about the industry that aren't true because people that play games know that it's not
[SPEAKER_06]: and hope it doesn't happen to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: you know because already people talking about well was he mentally ill had he tried to get help before and then he was denied help you know there are all these existential questions about what drives a person to do this but people need like they're like oh shit this like I'm terrified this is a horrible story if they can just make that mental association of oh he was influenced because of this maybe and that's scary and weird because I'm old and I don't know what that is they can get that they can pin their terror to something
[SPEAKER_06]: and because I think there is a youth angle to video games, that's...
[SPEAKER_06]: A good go-to for the media, if I'm making sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Osfer in chat says, Me and my mom went and saw the midnight showing of The Dark Knight Rises.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of people told us that they were glad that we were okay, but I just shrugged it off.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not going to let one guy ruin my movie-going experience.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's also funny how now when I tell people they should see the movie, they tell me that they don't want to get shot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely ridiculous, which I agree with.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, what short-term memory...
[SPEAKER_10]: Those people have because it's really unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Evil people killed people while they were working.
[SPEAKER_10]: on 9-11.
[SPEAKER_10]: Evil people have shot people on college campuses and on high school campuses.
[SPEAKER_10]: Evil people have gone into fast food restaurants and shot people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it doesn't matter where you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's just the sad reality of the situation.
[SPEAKER_10]: To blame the movie and say, I'm not going to go see a midnight movie because I might get shot is incredibly ignorant and disrespectful of all the history that came before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: We still strive as a society to figure out where were the warning signs so we can catch it before this happens again.
[SPEAKER_10]: How do we stop it from happening again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, going to Google Plus quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wendy S on Google Plus says,
[SPEAKER_10]: Ridiculous point in that millions play Skyrim or WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to agree with Mike, which I'll read in a minute here, that acting like ladies and gentlemen online and not accepting people being jerks will help as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let me go to that comment from Actdeft that said, well, for starters, stop acting like dicks on online games or when gaming other people in general.
[SPEAKER_10]: Second, stop acting like you're a badass know-it-all just because you play first-person shooter games, though this applies to other games too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, educate the other people that aren't playing video games and pretty much state to them that video games do not cause violence, and especially to parents.
[SPEAKER_10]: Proper education stops this kind of action.
[SPEAKER_10]: Luckily, most people have stopped blaming video games for this type of situations, at least in a general sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: A couple more comments quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: says,
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, Marilyn Manson then is on the warpath now.
[SPEAKER_10]: he's been charmed there's a whole nother thing Marilyn Manson has basically made a career off of attention grabbing and it's the same thing many people have done in our culture they've made millions off of grabbing attention Alice Cooper, Madonna Gaga
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, lastly, last comment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Preston Evans says, blame graduate studies for the shooting.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was studying neuroscience.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would do that to anyone's psyche.
[SPEAKER_10]: In reality, there is no current way to stop ridicule of one small part of our society for one great event.
[SPEAKER_10]: When all parties have a part in it, it's too hard to fix that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just throw one to the wolves instead of all taking the slap on the cheek for your part in the grand plan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I know that's a tough topic, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, again, on CNN, and this happened on CNN within hours, there's that pundit on the TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what we have to put up with as a culture.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, some different ideas from our listeners on how to stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's try to lighten the mood up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get back into video games, talking about some less serious video games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or in this case, I guess this is something a little serious going on on Xbox, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been secretly tightening their security.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this started, I guess, with the spring update that we just had, the one that prepped for the fall update, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now it says they are encouraging people to check their security information, update their passwords.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, the update they said built on security enhancements for the near future.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I guess they're working.
[SPEAKER_02]: There might be something that they'll announce for the fall update or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My thing is though, I understand that they're going to be secretly doing this stuff, but why go such a secret route with it unless, you know, maybe they're worried that if they said, oh yeah, we're updating our security, people would go, ah, so your security had issues that needed to be addressed and you just wouldn't admit to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, when they do it secretly, it kind of makes me wonder, they really did have issues that needed to be addressed, and they just didn't want to cop to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So either way, at least they're making a step in the right direction, I guess, but they didn't really say what security measures are being put in place that weren't in place before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can understand the secrecy behind it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, as critical as I've been of Microsoft on this whole issue in the past, I can understand why they don't want to give it all away, because they don't want to give the people that are hacking the accounts hints.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I can understand why they're being very vague about it, and I'm strangely okay with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad they have finally come out and said something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that they have said that they've taken the measures to stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I honestly think that hackedonexbox.com and their whole little report about that they were working customer service, I think that is directly to thank for this finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then here's some of the details of stuff they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: We increase notifications to members whose accounts may be compromised to add proofs, update their passwords and if necessary contact Xbox support.
[SPEAKER_02]: This helps our team lock down an account quickly, investigate and restore the account.
[SPEAKER_02]: to his rifle owner.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've taken legal action to pull down online posts of gamertags, usernames, and passwords gathered from malware phishing schemes to help protect our members.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our live spring update included many behind-the-scenes improvements that help us build on security enhancements for the near future.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're sending unique codes to security phone numbers and secondary email addresses provided by members to verify authorization for Xbox.com purchases, account change attempts,
[SPEAKER_02]: Not staying from members trusted device.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can vouch for that for a fact because we've had to recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know how much of a pain in the ass it is to stop their auto-renew?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we had some other co-workers I've created accounts for on my old PC, but since I've worked at the company that I've worked at, I've switched PCs, and so they're asking me for a second verifiable thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Problem is, though, is you can put any phone number you want in there, and they'll just call you with the security thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that doesn't really help you, but granted, it will give you a phone number that they can send that to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or text it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the other thing too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of free texting programs out there that you can get a disposable number for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an extra layer, but it's not foolproof.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have they finally programmed it in on the Xbox where it asks you for your card security code whenever you make a transaction?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I know that's available on Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why don't they do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would have helped in so many situations because the hackers would not have all those card codes and only let a person do it like three times and then it removes the card from file.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would seem super easy.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it wouldn't be as convenient to purchase stuff and that's...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, too fucking bad because it's the right thing to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the right thing is not profitable.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, we're working to reduce market incentives for criminal activity, engaging in identity theft, trading, and stolen accounts, and committing credit card fraud are illegal and violate our terms of use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those involved in these activities, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they get banned and blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reduce market incentives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last I remember, I believe Madden now started selling those cards, too, that FIFA was so popular for.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, those...
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, moving on to another news story here, and this has to do with the Wii U. We haven't talked a lot about tonight, but there's still some rumblings going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's always new rumors every week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this time it's about Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Gearbox, actually, the co-founder, Brian Martell, came out and said...
[SPEAKER_10]: Good things about the Wii U. Quote, we really like the Wii U. I think it's a really cool platform.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like what they're doing, obviously with the touchscreen, and it will be interesting to see what Microsoft does with their approach to that idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of those problems of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only people who have ever made a lot of money on the Wii is Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Borderlands 2 was on the Wii U, the thing I would most be excited about is inventory management.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be amazing on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would just be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think the artwork would look really good with the way they can deal with the resolution and textures.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a really good console.
[SPEAKER_10]: So a lot of people are jumping ahead and saying, confirmed, Borderlands 2 on Wii U.
[SPEAKER_02]: well of course they want to port it to any system they can and if it's easy to port it over then cool but once again it's kind of running into that same issue with what did DS do all the time oh well put the pause screen stuff the inventory stuff on the bottom screen instead of you know having to be a separate screen so do I really want to buy another system so that I don't have to pause my game to change my inventory I don't fucking care I'll pause my game to change my inventory and not have to buy another system for $300
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's assuming, you know, you're a person who doesn't end up buying it for some other reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, though, you know, all those inventory things at the bottom screen, you still have to look away from the screen to do all that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also in related news about the Wii U, another Wii U game, this one's called Rise of the Guardians, has been given a November release date, November 23rd for the 3DS, DS, 360, PlayStation 3, Wii, and Wii U. So this is another game being released in November.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Game system to be out by November 23rd.
[SPEAKER_10]: Christmas, Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I really need to... Yeah, I'm going to do it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: November 18th!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming out fucking November 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know that for sure, but it's coming out November 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because everything points to November 18th as the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't wait for it to not be that day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to play that clip on repeat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Within seven days, November 18th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Would you care to make a bet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a costume.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have a costume.
[SPEAKER_02]: That does not exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: November 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: $249 to $349 price range because of three different SKUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We already covered this on another show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go back in the archives and find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Alan, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: In the silly and weird lawsuit department, there's this story that's come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: A company based out of Texas, excuse me, a tech patent collector, Unilock is the name of the company, has filed suit against Mojang.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mojang, as some people may realize or remember, is a Marcus Persons company.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's the developer and creator of Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this company, Unilock, is suing Mojang for... And this is a typo in the thing that was put out to Mojang, the notice they're being sued.
[SPEAKER_06]: Minecraft with a D. So there's a typo in the claim that gets the name of the product wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specifically for the Android version of Minecraft...
[SPEAKER_06]: The patent that they are accusing Mojang of infringing is a system and method for preventing unauthorized access to electronic data.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that a password?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I'm kind of ignorant about this patent.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't read the whole thing because it's very dry.
[SPEAKER_06]: but specifically the filing references claim 107 of the patent which covers a computer code executable on an electronic device to prevent unauthorized access to electronic data stored on the electronic device so I don't know if it's the certain system or style that Minecraft is doing this on the Android but they're saying oh yeah we did that and only we can do that so they're suing it and Notch
[SPEAKER_06]: has said, unfortunately for them, they are suing us over a software patent.
[SPEAKER_06]: If needed, I will throw piles of money making sure they don't get a cent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Software patents are plain evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: Innovation within software is basically free and it's growing incredibly rapid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Patents only slow it down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unilock is seeking damages compounded by both pre- and post-judgment interest as well as ongoing royalties from Mojang.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah and it's not not Minecraft the PC platform but specifically the Android one for whatever reason and not just saying lol at you all right um this does sound a little patent trollish to me right yeah it's just me because they got the name of the product wrong in the in the suit wow
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, good luck with that, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are really trying to get me to wear that Tingle suit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, you lost your opportunity.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should have bought more copies of... What was that again?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember the name of the title.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brown Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, let's talk a little bit about Ouya.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Ben Wattaweek.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, of course, you know, they've been doing updates on the Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the updates that they did to kind of get people to trust them a little bit more, they let them know that one of the people on the production team is actually the guy that helped launch the Amazon Kindle line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mufi Gadali, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Godly?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how you pronounce his last name.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was in charge of the Kindle line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, his purpose there is to make sure that the system launches.
[SPEAKER_02]: My job at OUYA is to ensure that we meet the needs of gamers and developers and
[SPEAKER_02]: They're trying to get out the software development kit as quickly as possible to prospective developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, they're hiring engineers to join their team as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some other announcements that they made regarding the Ouya is that they're going to have an exclusive game to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Robert Bulling's Human Element is going to have a prequel on the system Human Element is going to be a zombie game that's going to be coming out on consoles in 2015 that's a long time
[SPEAKER_02]: and he's going to have a prequel that's going to be launching on OUYA first actually at the launch of the console and it's going to kind of follow the events that lead up to the actual Human Element game of course also you may remember Robert Brolin from his new studio Robotoki and he originally was one of the developers for Call of Duty Modern Warfare and
[SPEAKER_02]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, he also donated $10,000 to the project as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, they've got lots of, you know, they have people sign on.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a lot of indie developers that are kind of jumping on board as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of them actually have kick-started projects as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, at least there's going to be some games on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they've been trying to answer questions and whatnot from the community regarding why we've seen a controller and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now that they have a game finally to talk about, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it sounds like a cool game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what kind of a game it is, though, but there's a lot of other, like, you know, people that are in the Kickstarter, you know, world there, like, that want to bring their games to the console, like, one they're going to be talking about pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very soon is another Shadowrun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're thinking about bringing that to OUYA as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of games there right now saying, hey, if we get this game out, we're going to put it on OUYA as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got support.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's just really early still in the development stage as far as the design.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they haven't finalized a controller yet, but they're going to have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a beta kit running or a prototype, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I'm going to move on with another story here, but first, we finally gave that code away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead of doing it to just somebody random, and unfortunately twice we hit people that weren't around, I finally put a call out in chat and I said, look, if you're going to use this code and you want the code, send me a private message right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I asked Alan to pick a random number, and the winner was Osfer, won the code, and yes, he's going to use it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, congrats.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry that contest was a little bit of a mess, but I thought we'd do something fun with the new website registration.
[SPEAKER_10]: But oops, I guess people were checking in and then leaving to get dinner.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least we know it's going to get some good use because it was an opt-in thing that time.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think this is a little bit of a follow-up from last week because I remember we brought the first part of this up because I remember it was about that game on the iPhone that was heavily borrowing, quote, quote, assets from Torchlight and Torchlight was pissed.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they, you know, I guess they went and they went on a Twitter rampage and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: The company, EGLS, actually came out and made a statement about
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess, oh gosh, where is this here?
[SPEAKER_10]: EGLS went to Touch Arcades and said, we hardly agree with Travis Baldry from Runic Games, who judged that EGLS wholesale stole most of the assets from Torchlight.
[SPEAKER_10]: EGLS is Entertainment Game Labs, by the way, who is the developer behind this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only based on the similarity between several small monsters.
[SPEAKER_10]: The judgment is simply untenable.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, except there's a little more to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: EGLS employees say they are, quote, both crazy game fans and ecstatic movie lovers.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the comparisons are an accident at best.
[SPEAKER_10]: Arm Heroes, the last time they checked, was still available on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's free to play with purchases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what ended up happening a little later?
[SPEAKER_10]: EGLS did come out and say, all right, we'll remove some parts of the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they talk about that they are going to make some small changes to the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Runic Games really wants EGLS to admit that they just stole it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually stole even the audio from the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there were some unused audio clips, like a certain sword or something like that, that they have in Torchlight.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the audio files were named exactly the same as Torchlight.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like even stuff that they didn't use.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said, I also downloaded the app.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can unzip them and look at any iPhone app.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there was a sound manifest that listed all the sound files in the game and they were verbatim all of our sound files including our own misspellings.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, they stole them.
[SPEAKER_10]: yikes now armed heroes online is now down i guess runic filed a complaint and finally it got taken down but it took a little while that was on when did it finally get pulled july 19th that was thursday when it finally got pulled and we reported on that last week i wonder how many people uh grabbed that game
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says they're in China, so there was nothing legal they could do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they can't sue the company, but they can fight them through Apple.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they did, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can also reinforce stereotypes regarding China.
[SPEAKER_10]: What, that it's thieves and gold farmers and all this?
[SPEAKER_02]: MMOs and all this, or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They copy and counterfeit stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: hmm but it's gone now and let's I wonder if Apple actually like really hammered the band hammer on them because you know Apple usually when shit like this happens Apple will just say you've lost your license done you're not getting to put publish anymore but most of them just come back under another name you're not gonna publish anymore until you pay another hundred dollars to buy a different license under a different name exactly
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, every week we invite your emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and DarkSakura, she usually dives into the mailbag headfirst to read some of her favorite emails, but in her absence, she's loaned the hazmat suit to Alan, who will dive into the email bag.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to state this, we received a lot of emails this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there's a bunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's weird because usually we're sitting here with one or two going, send us more.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you sent more this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But here's what we're going to do because we don't have enough time to read, especially after some of the other segments tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't have enough time to read all the emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to have Alan read the first half of the emails that came in.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to roll the second half to next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: First email is from Robert M, subject 3 questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Robert M and I just had 3 somewhat quick questions, or rather 2 and an observation.
[SPEAKER_06]: First, have you guys had the chance to check out Spelunky yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw on a preview of the 360 version that someone did a Mac port, so it's one of my Steam shortcuts now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reportedly, Steam may be getting a version of the game with the 360s graphics and extra modes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Secondly, if you're too... I haven't checked it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blame the rest of the Steam sale on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I haven't checked it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Secondly, if you're too busy with Minecraft based on what you know, do you see updates for the iOS version falling by the wayside with the Android version?
[SPEAKER_10]: because I don't really follow the Minecraft forums enough to I haven't played the iOS version at all it's kind of like for iOS game it's kind of expensive which is ridiculous because I have like $19 credit on my iTunes account right now thanks to gift cards but I don't know I just I've kind of avoided it for some inexplicable reason but you have it don't you Matt have what Minecraft on iOS uh I have it on Android oh you have it on Android
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think that, I mean, Minecraft on PC is so popular because it's pretty, it's like limitless, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: The world just goes on forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think you can do that on the phone, and I think the 360 has really taken off, so maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: The phone's really limited what they've got in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of, like, there's object types that aren't there, and there's a lot of things that you have unlimited supplies of because they don't have a waste.
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah technically the 360 version is limited too but there was a story that came out this week they've sold 3 million copies of that it's one of the biggest Xbox Live Arcade titles ever crazy finally going back to the email finally not a question I came across a banner ad for one of those free to play Empire building games with the mandatory woman in the image being Anna Williams as in literally the Tekken 6 character art weird I'm almost certain Namco has nothing to do with this FTP keep up the great shows it's probably from China
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to refer you to that story we just read.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to say, just rewind the podcast 10 minutes and go back to that last story.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's probably what's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless it's an Amco game, but I kind of doubt that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anna Williams, by the way, was an amazing tech and character, just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved her.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one I'm not going to read because I think that's an admin question for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't read that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is one we can screen out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next email from Jeffrey Help!
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there a support group to help me stop buying all of the games in the summer Steam sale?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe a transdermal patch to slowly meter out old video games that I will probably never play.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you came to the wrong place.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've picked up a couple indie bundles the THQ pack and a few other odds and ends I most likely won't touch half of the games included I'm just interjecting my own note here for all of the games that I bought this weekend or on this week under the sale I don't have the hard drive space to install like half of them at once so yeah it's very easy to have hundreds of gigs of games in your library
[SPEAKER_10]: I most likely won't touch half the games included now I see what happens to old people when they watch QVC that shit is no joke my mother is addicted to QVC and she'll never admit it and she'll hate me for telling you that's a very prescient and terrifying observation and it is 100% correct oh my god Steam is QVC without the host but at least QVC has like Marie Osmond and shit
[SPEAKER_10]: True story, you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I've mentioned this on the show before for the new listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: My mother owns the complete Richard Simmons doll collection from QVC.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're all old lady dolls, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: My mother loves Richard Simmons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doll form.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, she legit loves him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please give me some tough love.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we need like a Scared Straight program for Steve Sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, seriously, it's just like spending money I don't have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please give me some tough love.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell me to stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could also accept encouragement, but that would be detrimental to my wallet.
[SPEAKER_06]: As always, love the show and thanks for the years of entertainment, Lab Rat, Y2K.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, I'm going to say you came to the wrong place because you probably heard the first 30 minutes of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what I would like to see happen a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: To help offset the whole buyer's remorse thing, I would like to see more of an organization of certain gaming nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, hey, let's all play Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_02]: We bought it, let's go play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, hey, let's play some Armored 2 DayZ or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, hey, let's play this together so that it's not like, why did I buy this game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did I buy Borderlands?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, to play with other people that have the PC version, but I'm not actually going to play with other people that have the PC version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lab Rat, Y2K, let me just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you can't beat them, join them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Join the VOG Network community on Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also an Orange Launch Radio community, but we're trying to kind of push people more to the general VOG one now so we can be even bigger.
[SPEAKER_10]: And more information is available at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know this one's long, but it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll read it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you mind reading it?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a long email.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's it from first?
[SPEAKER_10]: Read who it's from first.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tonic Vision.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now you can read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to address this in the chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Technus in chat says, Richard Simmons scared the shit out of me when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did his nut fall out of his shorts?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's harmless.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to admit, that guy takes a lot of shit, and he really is just trying to be a good person.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a healthy dose of fabulous.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's absolutely nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clearly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, Alan?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's what's making him so spunky at age 60...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need more.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am being completely real.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Travis, you play this clip over and over on your show if you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make fun of me.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need more people like Richard Simmons in the world.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, there is nothing wrong with Richard Simmons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Richard Simmons is the antithesis of the evil we were talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: What is wrong with Richard Simmons?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, Tonic Vision.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got a chance yesterday to go check out the Wii U in person.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are doing a Tensity Tour and inviting Club Nintendo members and wanted to share my impressions with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: To preface, I would just like to say that I don't consider myself to really be a fanboy of any particular system.
[SPEAKER_06]: and don't really have a vested interest in one over another because to me they all have various strengths and weaknesses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I own basically every current system including the 3DS and the Vita and am generally excited enough by next generation hardware to be a consistent early adopter.
[SPEAKER_06]: With that said, I really cannot find any way to get excited about the Wii U even after hands-on play with each and every launch title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: For me, it is because of the following three reasons.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this guy got an exclusive invite to some top secret come play the Wii U in an unmarked building type of thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, I may actually have an impression of the Wii U after this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our Ubisoft guy may be bringing a Wii U to our game conference thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's probably for Just Dance 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there a Rabbids game on Wii U?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there is.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is.
[SPEAKER_02]: May or may not.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's trying to get a Wii U dev kit out, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Item 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: The name sucks, plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is this a big deal?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a big deal because it's indicative of the fact that Nintendo has become a little too comfortable.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is still a Wii, folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it has a new controller, and yes, the graphics are prettier, but it is still a Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you bought on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: You take a PlayStation 3, and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sequels to consoles are fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess my whole point's invalid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen the light.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think he's saying that aside from the graphics hardware, I mean, the Nintendo to the Super Nintendo was a huge step in audio, visual.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mode 7 fucked your shit up.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Rob, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's games on the, like, okay, the jump from the NES to SNES, so you have Zelda and Mario Brothers, and then you had Super Mario World and, you know, Zelda 3, Links to the Past.
[SPEAKER_02]: which are two of the best games ever fucking made.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those were amazing fucking games and look at how much better they are than the previous system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we seeing that with the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like we have a new Mario game that's exactly like the fucking Mario game that's already on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they came out with a game that's like holy fucking shit that's
[SPEAKER_02]: Goddamn amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so much better than the previous Mario game where, oh my god, look at this Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so much better than the one in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then maybe it'd be a different story, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are the same fucking game, slightly prettier, but basically the same.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is hard to argue with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only thing I could say is that the Zelda game wasn't a launch title, but granted the Mario game was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the best is yet to come.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just telling Alan last night we haven't ordered pizza in a long time and he's like oh you want to go to Papa Murphy's get a take and bake I'm like fuck you no I want bacon sausage that's right we are going like we're gonna call Straw Hat and we're gonna get it delivered in a box can you put a Christmas ham just right on the pizza when I worked at a pizza place I never got sick of pizza I could eat pizza every goddamn day and I would be happy eating pizza every day
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand the point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Item 3 The technology isn't new.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have played games on a touch screen and I've played games with motion control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Putting them together is not innovative and really doesn't bring anything terribly exciting to the masses.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playing through each and every launch title I can say for a fact that not one of these really do something unexpected with the marriage of these two technologies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps a year or so after launch there will be a handful of third party titles that will push the envelope and do something daring.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly Nintendo certainly won't be leading by example.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all of these, excuse me, for all of these reasons, I really find myself at a loss when attempting to justify this purchase at launch, or maybe at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry for the rant, but that was the feeling I was left with after two hours with the Wii U. And this, I mean, this guy's an Uber Nintendo fan because you had to be to get in the click to go see the system, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he said that he doesn't really stand for any console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Enthusiast enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then he's kind of like any of us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I like Nintendo, but I like Sony and Microsoft too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some days.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just depends.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's pissing me off this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: on a separate note I wanted to share with you another preview of some art that will be showcased at the upcoming video game power-up art exhibition this will increase your X attached here are some pixel sculptures we've created one of which was recently featured in your classic game of the week enjoy we encourage all OLR listeners in the Chicago area
[SPEAKER_06]: to come out and see the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It opens Friday, August 3rd from 6 to 10 p.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: at Gallery 27 at 1833 Halstead and will be open every Friday throughout the month.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can also check out the show online at all one word gallery27chicago.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll paste that in chat in a second if you can't make it in person.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks and I hope to see you there, Tonic Vision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, none of us are in Chicago, at least here in the room, and I won't be through the area, but I know we have some listeners in Chicago, we have quite a few actually, so I expect a full report, tap tap tap
[SPEAKER_06]: One more?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll do one more, and that's just going to leave three left over.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll figure out what we do with those emails later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Roll them over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is from Nasty Canasta, Evening OLR Crew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Among all the discussion about theatrism's pricing on your show, Bobby Blackwolf's, and around the web, I thought it was interesting that nobody considered to bring up the Square Enix tax.
[SPEAKER_06]: There have been instances where RPGs and related titles published by Square Enix, especially re-releases, have a price that is artificially raised above the norm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take Squeenix's PS1 Classics catalog, for example.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas most games are priced at $5.99, Chrono Cross, Chrono Trigger, all Final Fantasies and Xenogears are worth $9.99 to purchase.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know why that is?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you'll pay it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, there's really no other way to say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any Square fan is going to be, this is my own commentary, any Square fan is going to be cuckoo bananas about those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're legendary.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be fair, aren't they larger games too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know Xenogears was two discs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Final Fantasy VII was three discs and Final Fantasy VIII was also three and nine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it was four and two.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, so I mean, yeah, but I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yes, I understand what you mean.
[SPEAKER_06]: In this day and age, that's kind of a weak argument.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oddly, Front Mission 3 and Vagrant Story do not have inflated prices despite both having RPG elements.
[SPEAKER_06]: And those were more sleeper hits, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or cult hits.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: For them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those were also one disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure the tax also applies to titles available from Nintendo's Virtual Console service, at least in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nasty Canasta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that name, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And wasn't when Secret of Mana was ported to iOS and put on the Apple Store, wasn't it like really expensive?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it was four or five bucks, which was outrageous for what it was, just a port of the SNES.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say those games on Nintendo and Super Nintendo Virtual Console were like 100 Microsoft points more.
[SPEAKER_10]: or excuse me, wow, 100 Nintendo points more.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm losing it tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I was distracted because look who came to say hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look who never comes out in the studio to say hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look who's here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Maruko.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kitty, kitty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kitty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have a comment, Maruko?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's sniffing the microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how is your cat, by the way?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sanrio is doing much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: She just needed a day to have it, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: She gets constipated.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when she has a really bad hairball and she's plugged up, it'll tweak this nerve in her stomach.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it completely, like, knocks her out for a day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where she just, she can't eat.
[SPEAKER_06]: She gets dizzy.
[SPEAKER_06]: If she walks, she'll stumble and fall down.
[SPEAKER_06]: She just needed a day to get better.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Kitty can't poop, but she can poop now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry for the TMI.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really scary to see your cat completely out of it and you don't know what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and a really good friend of ours had to put down their cat this week, and I know that's really difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was a long time trying to get them better and figure out what was wrong with them, so they finally had to.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_06]: We get really attached to our pets.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I love my kitty, and I'm glad that she's better, but I need to make sure that doesn't happen again, because I don't like seeing her like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's it for emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Logi.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to people that change lanes without signaling.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of you out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why people do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, FU to the Steam sale for... I guess I should blame myself, but I'm blaming the Steam sale for having me spend way more money than I wanted to on this Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: And buying games that I will probably play, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Right away, and it just adds more games to the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, you want to go?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, on Friday night, I have this gorgeous 25-inch Hewlett-Packard monitor for my PC, the Pitchron.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on Friday night, it started to flicker, like there was maybe some EMF interference from a nearby appliance.
[SPEAKER_06]: or maybe the backlight of the LCD was starting to go out which was terrifying because I don't want to buy any monitor right now so that sucked but I replaced the I took it off HDMI cable and I plugged it into my video card with a DVI cable and now it's fine so the HDMI cable
[SPEAKER_06]: went bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, F you to shitty $8 Amazon HDMI cables that make you think your monitor's dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you should have got a $60 monster cable.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're all the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just buy the cheapest possible cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was a Belkin on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It lasted two years, but I guess the HDMI cable went bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, F you to heart attacks that, yeah, over technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cablewholesale.com, they're damn cheap and it's one day shipping to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I get cables when I happen to get cables.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did they pay you for that app?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next time they should.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're SoCal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, no, they're not SoCal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're somewhere in the Bay Area or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so it's only a day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really have a lot of angst.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things are going pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a lot going on, so F you to being really busy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm kind of obligated to something over the next couple months that's going to really cut into my weekends, which really stinks because I really need to get back to San Francisco and see Grandpa Warcraft and some other people over there and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: And F you to the fact...
[SPEAKER_10]: That the annual showing of Showgirls, which we must go to, is the same day as another theater thing I have here.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I've got to make sure I can go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I love movie Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's so bad, it's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't know shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, one more news story for us and then I've got something.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then that's the part where we get to taking your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: But after two more stories here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can't go to both of those events because they're at different places, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm happy you made a Showgirls show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen Showgirls one too many times.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was only because I wanted to see the boobies.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really the only reason to watch Showgirls more than one time anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: so let's talk a little bit about kickstarter because why not we we always talk about kickstarter because it's in the news all the time so a couple new games shadowrun online i'm kind of excited about that because shadowrun's pretty awesome um but they're starting a kickstarter they're looking to raise half a million dollars by august 14th so you can go check them out at kickstarter um
[SPEAKER_02]: DefenseGrid 2 DefenseGrid 2
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3 quarters of a million, you get a level editor, and then 1 million you get a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of lame, but that's how they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then last but not least, if you're looking for an alternative to Kickstarter, the website GamesPlanet has launched a new service called GamesPlanet Lab.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically a crowdfunding service.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: which is kind of cool because it's not US only because Kickstarter is US only so you have to have a way to pay via Amazon on that but it's based in Europe and they will have projects from around the world and already they've got a couple games on the service that you can fund one's MagRunner it's a title from 3AM Studios and
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's like a first person puzzler game and then they've also got Day One which is like an adult themed point and click adventure game Like Leisure Suit Larry?
[SPEAKER_02]: They say it's heavily influenced by the Devil's Dictionary.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't really say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe the difference with this service as opposed to Kickstarter, because I think one of the reasons people are kind of like, I don't know about crowdfunding and stuff, how we know we're actually in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they have a process that they actually kind of review these games before they
[SPEAKER_02]: and allow them to be on the service.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, it's only going to be games on this service since it is Game Planet Labs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat, I guess, if they have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so that's the alternative if you want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, I believe, at lab.gamesplanet.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Want to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, lab.gamesplanet.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, since you just did a bunch of Kickstarter-esque stuff here, this one is kind of another Kickstarter-inspired thing, but like it or not, Kickstarter is now kind of a part of pop culture right now, and that's probably one of those things that we'll look back on in 10 years and on the next VH1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the 2010 decade special.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll have someone there talking about how everybody was into Kickstarter and the other stuff it inspired.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nino Kuni, Wrath of the White Witch, Wizards Edition
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now they're expanding this for the US based on the number of pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it doesn't say though what they will keep adding to it when they hit different levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm going to the page right now, which you can get at ninostarter.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't say exactly what you will unlock, but apparently if you hit these different pre-order goals, they're going to add stuff to the collector's edition, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, here it is, the first one.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first item is a set of five Ni No Kuni prints.
[SPEAKER_10]: So little crappy little postcards, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, if that's, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah all right I think it'd be better if it was like the regular game and you know the more people that pre-order the game like more free shit like they upgrade it for free like do a special edition or something like that and have crap that they throw in there yeah that'd be a little bit better because collector's editions that's really a niche niche niche audience you're you're not going to niche game with a now you know collector's edition that's going to be even more niche than that
[SPEAKER_10]: It's $99, too, if you want that collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, see, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Believe it or not, I'm tempted, because I really do love the Studio Ghibli stuff, and the game looks good, but I feel really weird taking that leap of faith when I don't really know if the game's good or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I could go look at some Japanese.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, but just because it looks pretty good?
[SPEAKER_10]: Come on, what have we learned?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sometimes games that look good don't really end up being very good or lasting a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I do think that doll is really cute, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the DLC, might as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, anyhow, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see if I get on board or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, you have until August 31st to do this, and they even have the little countdown clock there on ninostarter.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says right now 2,683 fans.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that mean that many people have pre-ordered, I'm assuming?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: But little trailers available there and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a cute little idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to give us a call and talk about anything we've talked about tonight or maybe there's a story you think we've missed, the Skype line is now open.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll get to last minute stories in a minute, but I also want to read some of the tweets that have come in at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm going to start off tonight with a tweet from Dave Falcon tweets us and says, a few days ago, I picked up Duke Nukem Forever at GameStop for $4.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: My How the Mighty Have Fallen and Fallen Quick
[SPEAKER_10]: Would you buy it for $4.99?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gearbox made Borderlands, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand that, and it's really sad what they had to work with for Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that was kind of one of the things, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like they lost a lot of credit with that, but Borderlands 2 looks really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let me go to the phones because we are getting a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, X-Link, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing really too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, Loki, I'm also hyped for Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so happy that Ashley is actually going to have a role inside of it playing as Tiny Tina, which is absolutely great because I love watching, hey, Ash, what you're playing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I thought she was great doing those.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be kind of intriguing to see how all that works out after they bring everything to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's good to know too that they actually have the game already done so hopefully they'll patch up any kind of bugs or anything within that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: This hype train has me very interested.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a big fan of the first one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have the first one with all the DLC and actually I would like to team up with some people go through the arena part and get the rest of the achievements.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did the first arena by myself but the other ones are just
[SPEAKER_10]: I swear I will try and play the game soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had to remove it from my hard drive because I needed the disk space.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it'll be back.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really, a couple things real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chaos Rings from Square Enix is $12.99 actually on the iOS store.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the sequel, which came out not too long ago, was actually $17.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: So those are really expensive compared to...
[SPEAKER_01]: to Xenogears and the rest of those for $9.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd rather get those anyways, at least that way, you know, I would have a copy I could always play compared, you know, because, you know, stuff happens, you know, discs can break, you know, get scratched really easily.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, they're very hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those are games also that are very hard to come by, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: You look on eBay, you're trying to find them.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were going up to $50, $70, $80 a pop for some of those games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So just to say, oh, well, you know, they're trying to, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Galza Price.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, 10 bucks is a very simple price.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd rather pay 10 bucks than...
[SPEAKER_01]: 50 or 60.
[SPEAKER_01]: The same thing with the Steam sales.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought the Dungeon Seed Collection for $7.49.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was like 75% off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought Brink for $5.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that's a crappy game, but I like these little first person shooters from time to time after having a rough day at work, coming home and shooting something.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really great to have some of those stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then of course I bought for my girlfriend the Secret of the Magic Crystal for $1.25.
[SPEAKER_01]: So
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you can't really beat those prices for the sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking at my iPad right now at the store, and yeah, I mean, Square really does charge a premium for some of their games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy Tactics, $17.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chaos Rings 2, just like you said, $19.99 on the iPad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'll pass on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can get Imaginary Range for free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I have my 3DS that can play some of those games just fine, and I'd rather do it on something like that than worrying about paying 18, 19 bucks on an app that when I'm in the middle of doing something, like you said, basically for Mass Effect 3, it's going to crash upon me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I pass on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, so it's absolutely 100% bulletproof and it's not going to crash or anything?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe, but even then, that's a considerable amount of money.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a big chunk.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially since I have most of those games anyways, and if everyone gets the same thing, I really don't feel like paying $15, $18 for it again.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: And also about these shootings, and, you know, they always, you know, every time when some of this happens, you know, they're always blaming the media somehow, whether it be video games, movies, you know, music.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: They never mention books.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, what kind of books was a person reading?
[SPEAKER_01]: What kind of reading was a person doing to get to maybe even this frame of mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, because books are just as dangerous as anything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no moving objects or anything within books.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some people still blame books.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, I'm getting a little historical here, but Fahrenheit 451 was a book, ironically, that was kind of all about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we still have in this day and age people that try to ban books from the public library.
[SPEAKER_10]: What, Catcher in the Rye always comes up on that list because it's smut.
[SPEAKER_01]: Harry Potter, no, but... Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, what we need to do, too, is also look at the good stories.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at the things that are done, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody saved, you know, a family or something from a building building, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe try to twist out, you know, not really twist it around a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe try to see if that person is a gamer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say, hey, look, this person was a gamer.
[SPEAKER_01]: This person just saved a family, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: He...
[SPEAKER_01]: Just because these people are gamers doesn't mean, oh, I like Halo and Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't go around decapitating people, shooting people in the head because I'm seeing this in the game and I'm going, okay, I think this is okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about all the good things, gamer?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love that lyric when he goes
[SPEAKER_01]: they blame it on Maryland and the heroine where was the heroine and look where it's at and you know it's kind of funny because those little things it's kind of like looking for that little niche looking for that little thing to to basically saying you know if these weren't here this was you know this would have you know would never happen in the first place though it would and it's unfortunate too because it you know happened in such a closed area but you know like I you know like you said before
[SPEAKER_01]: Even after seeing these stories, stuff happens, I'm still going to go to libraries.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still going to go to grocery stores.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still going to go to the movie theater to watch my movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: We should let these little things affect our everyday life.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if it doesn't, then congratulations, they win.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's that simple.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very well said.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to let you go to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_01]: But thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anytime.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go ahead and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meanwhile, Loki, do you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do have a couple of the tweets here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just going to comment one more time on the Games Planet Lab thing because that's kind of vague on what exactly they do different than...
[SPEAKER_02]: The Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they actually have 10 commitments that they're going to make.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them, you know, a quality label designed with gamers, DRM, the gamers experience before all, secure payments, respective IP, clear timetable, a guarantee for delivery rewards, virtuous funding solutions, real selection work, project holder identity, and clear information.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically just kind of providing more information, more...
[SPEAKER_02]: Commitments.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me go to the phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have another call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Osfer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm happy that I resisted the newel, as Bobby would call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, but you ended up winning a Steam code, though, so... Yeah, I mean, it's good that I won that, but, like, all my friends are like, oh, I have no money, and now I've been, like, using all my wallet funding on these Steam sales, and I'm just like, I only bought one game, and that game wasn't even for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I bought Mass Effect 1 for a friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: So have you been tempted by any of the Steam sales?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just sort of looking at games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_10]: Say that again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did we lose him?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we lost him.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't hear you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Plug the mic back in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it says internet connection problem between us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we just dropped.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did we drop?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, don't take that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, don't, don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a hiccup because we are still... Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: He called right back.
[SPEAKER_10]: We probably lost all the listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: There went the feed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully, it'll come back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you still there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we can hear you.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're taping.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go ahead and keep going with your question for the podcasties.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're offline right now, but the podcasters are still hearing this.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: I had asked you if there was anything that you were wanting off of Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was, like, looking at, um... I'm tempted by Amnesia and Alan Wake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, Alan Wake won because I heard it's kind of Silent Hill-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I might like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Amnesia actually did... I watched a group play through it, and I played, like, a little part of it myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, like, there are some bits and pieces I missed, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I should really get the full game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game made me terrified at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually a video of me playing through it at one point, and I'm just screaming when I do something blatantly obvious that hurts me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, you're saying there's this video like it's out there on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you need to give me the link.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a video of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: A bunch of people in my group down at college.
[SPEAKER_05]: We all get together and we play games late at night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it just has all the screams.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you film your antics and put them up on YouTube for your adoring public?
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, it was the guy who was in our group.
[SPEAKER_05]: He brings in his desktop.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't even know this, but he has a microphone sitting behind the desk that we're playing at.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's just recording everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so he takes the scream and then he slows it down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's pretty hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well while you're looking for that link for me, is there anything else you want to call in to discuss tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing else other than the fact that I might regret getting my friend Mass Effect because if he gets really into it, then he'll eventually get to Mass Effect 3 and then I'll be like, oh, I want to play with you online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I have to get the PC version now too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll never be able to connect.
[SPEAKER_10]: So just, you know, don't get your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Enjoy that beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, no problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank Boshka.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: While I still wait for that link for the video of...
[SPEAKER_10]: Osfer screaming at the amnesia because I think amnesia reaction videos are really funny I love the one that Alan put on my wall on Facebook of the guy playing through amnesia where it just starts and like the first door opens he's like lol nope and quits it's like a 10 second video
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's go to the phones again and hope the phone doesn't drop during the call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you are on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're such a hater about the Mass Effect 3 PC game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_10]: How can you not be mad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the Xbox does the same exact thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you haven't, no, Xbox hasn't robbed me of credits yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It robbed you of playing it on PC, and that's a far worse offense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Surely you didn't just call to complain.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else did you call about?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, actually, I was all complaining.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm mad you didn't play Jack Levin's theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: during that F-Zero break when it's clearly the best song in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The folks listening on the podcast don't even know that we played F-Zero music during the break.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not special.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't get to hear F-Zero music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Views and opinions of Shane or Shane's.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Making sure the podcast listeners know you're a jerk.
[SPEAKER_08]: There, you know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: and now I have to go find my copy of F-Zero because I may need to play it even though my flipping people off finger is so badly hurt right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you cut your finger before the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were posting pictures on Facebook and they're really gross.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do people do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't need to see your wounds all over Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: My finger is kind of like the current model 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has three different layers now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got the fingernail and then the finger and then the huge flap that's left over where my finger got cut.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: The picture you posted of your dog was much better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he was tuckered out from all the blood.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, look, did you have anything else you wanted to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to complain.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was kind of bored.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I'm going to let you go, hater.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not if I do it first.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he hung up.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Shane, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, let me... I want to go to one other... Okay, this is the YouTube that Ossifer was... Oh, this is a six-minute long video.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: He linked me right to the right part.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good job, Ossifer.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's loading.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to have to wait for that to load.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's buffering.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meanwhile, we'll take one more call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: What up, guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Xenocore from the OKC.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_10]: How you doing, Xenocore?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, no, staying employed.
[SPEAKER_10]: In this economy, that's a hard thing to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I've been playing a hell of a lot of the Streets of Rage V5 remake that got pushed out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did Sega succeed in getting that pulled?
[SPEAKER_04]: It already escaped to the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no stopping it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They may kill their own personal link, but it's out in the wilds now.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what made you decide to play this remake?
[SPEAKER_10]: You just love Streets of Rage?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, they did rearrangement of Yu Suzuki's music.
[SPEAKER_04]: What version do you need?
[SPEAKER_04]: You thought F-Zero's music was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You put that stuff on with real instruments and everything behind it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to put it up in the club and just play all night.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the soundtrack alone is worth checking it out for.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I ripped the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already on my phone so I can listen to it in my car when I'm driving.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it's actually a pretty faithful remake.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all pixelated and everything, even if you make it full screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost like playing on MAME or something else like that, but it's all custom.
[SPEAKER_04]: It did quite a good job with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I understand why Sega might want to squash it, because it's almost a better version of what they've been putting out for their games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's better than what they do to Sonic in some ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, what else is on your mind this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Steam's taking care of everything, but they still can't lure me to Skyrim until I get a game of the year version so I can get all the DLC at once for one price.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is no DLC on PC yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe the Vampire DLC comes out when?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's got to be really soon, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but sooner or later it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did pick up the Arkham City DLC for $3, so I played my two hours of that and was like, ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a big thing that was on sale during the week, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, almost all the DLC has their own little mini sales.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just got to go into the game to see them if they're not currently running on the front page.
[SPEAKER_04]: So y'all got, like, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: 30 minutes, one and a half hours to go and check out all the DLC that you want so you can get it at a worthwhile price.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You better hurry, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's all I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good show, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Xenocore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Appreciate it, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's about, sadly, all the calls we can take tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm very sorry we didn't get to everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: The phones were actually blowing up tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm loving the participation, though, you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for emailing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for calling.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry we couldn't get everybody, but be sure to, like, you know, send us more emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: Participate on the forums at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can also tweet us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will do one more tweet here.
[SPEAKER_10]: That video won't load.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to have to try after the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It must be just our internet connection is kind of jank tonight, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, let me read this real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is a link from Tigerclaw, and I love this story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Microsoft had to apologize because a programmer hid the phrase, big boobs in company software.
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, apparently there's a string in the hexadecimal computer language that says, in hexadecimal, Big Boobs, if you can figure out how to read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The code was spotted by programmers and caused controversy within the community because, of course, they want to distance themselves from being just an all-male pig-headed club.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Big Boobs is harmless.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Big Boobs is funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even women like boobs, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Jamie were here, she would say yes, trust me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they say, oh, it's childish humor.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just boobs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, that's all I have for the tweets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, do you have any other last minute stories you want to read?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, just one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a new Operation, because you know there's Operation Rainfall.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now there's Operation Zero, which is trying to convince Nintendo of US to bring Fatal Frame 2, the Wii edition, to the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they've got a Facebook page you can go check out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just search for Operation-0 and they're going to have a letter writing campaign starting this week, July 25th through the 27th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I finally got Osfer's video to load.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did that scream really come out of the same guy who called us a minute ago?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I haven't installed that game yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I have it too, but I'm afraid if I play it, Alan will be there with a camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see you making that noise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to make that same noise.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I'm not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so that's it for Last Minute Stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it for Twitter topics and that means that is it for the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are about on out of here but not before we get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alan, thank you so much for sitting in on the show tonight in place of DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: A pleasure as always.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good job and thanks for your insight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully we'll see you again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't be a stranger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully you'll have more Sunday nights off in the future if your boss is listening.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you like making the money too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have any final thoughts for listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hamburger Helper helps your hamburger make a great meal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's very deep.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's insightful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is next week on Saturday I want to play some serious Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the week from that, or week from Wednesday, I want to play some serious Ritter Player One.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of stuff on the line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Win a DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought tonight is Nutter Butter.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate the support.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it is an ad-free show.
[SPEAKER_10]: All we ask you guys, if you enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell people about vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Check out some of the other great shows on vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: We just added two new shows last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Critical Myth and British Invaders, both really great shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: But check out
[SPEAKER_10]: Pod Culture, Under Station Live, Girls Gone Wow, Anime Jam Session, and yes, even Horde House 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Check out all the great shows at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Blackwell, of course, I always plug his show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there's lots of great stuff at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, thanks you guys just for being here and staying up for three hours with us and being entertained.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we'll see you next week when we'll do this all over again with another episode of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_03]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_03]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next week!