Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
Dark Sakura,
Sky and Loki
Tonight July 8th, 2012
Sony purchases Gaikai
What does this mean for retail?
Microsoft securing a domain name leads to speculation
and a court in the European Union
makes a huge decision on reselling digital games
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice
it's Orange Lounge Radio
We are live as we always are
Sunday nights at The Voice of Geeks
or VOG Network
www.vognetwork.com
Sunday nights 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
right after Mr. Bobby Blackwolf
and his fantastic show
also on the network
If you are listening to us live
get your butt in our chatroom and participate
so we can read your comments
live.vognetwork.com
We always appreciate you guys
participating along with our show
I said your show, it is your show too
it's all of our shows
We do like to bill ourselves
as the show where every gamer has a voice
This voice you're hearing right now is Rob Roberts
I'm one of three hosts on this show
along with the absent, sadly, tonight
Dark Sakura
Dark Sakura sadly called in a couple of hours
before the show tonight
She's not going to be able to make it
She's recovering from being sick
and she said
Garris
But joining us here in studio is tech master Loki
Hello
How are you doing, Loki?
I'm doing good
Yeah?
Yeah
Alright, it's all good?
I'm full now because I've had like a liter of root beer
That is a lot of soda
What did you think about
not to get all political on this show
but since, you know, I know a lot of gamers
and I know a lot of gamers that drink soda
there was a lot of feedback to that whole New York City law
that they were talking about
where they were going to ban
the super-sized drinks and all that
What did you think about that?
Buy two drinks and
That's exactly
Like, I just don't understand
What am I going to do?
I can't get a large soda
I mean, the large soda, I understand
it's twice as much as the small soda
but how am I going to get a large
Buy two of them
I mean, I don't even understand why that's a problem
I somehow knew in my mind
that's exactly what you'd say
Maybe having done this show with you for ten years
and knowing you about us long is probably
I can predict these things
I just, it's, it's dumb
What they need to do is
they need to just charge, you know
Hey, I'll tell you what
We'll charge you, uh, you know
half price of a large for two
or, you know, each of the smalls
and then we'll give you a large cup for free
How about that?
And then you just pour it in there
and, you know, loophole
For ten years and knowing you about us long
feedback, sorry
Ugh, I am not with it tonight
I'm hosting the show tonight
I'm not with it
I forgot to enable the live check-ins
over at vognetwork.com
and everybody in chat is screaming
Man, turn it on, turn it on
We're having two hosts tonight
Alan, I know we talked last week about
It's his birthday
Happy birthday, Alan
If you're out there listening from work
where he's at right now
I was going to forward you a picture
but I couldn't do it on my phone
I'm totally off topic here, but
No, that's fine
Help me fill time
There was a killer tattoo that I saw
that was a Golden Girls tattoo
What? A Golden Girls tattoo?
A Golden Girls tattoo
I was like, man, Rob would have to get that
What was it of? Be Arthur?
It was of all of them
All of them, and it said
Thank you for being a friend underneath it
It was great
I like that
It was on Facebook
But yeah, that was hilarious
So, um, yeah, lots of soda
See, I was almost gonna, I left early
I was like, okay, I'm gonna go get something
I normally get because, you know,
I have this extra time now
So I thought about, well, I could go to In-N-Out
But I really don't like In-N-Out that much
I mean, everyone loves their fries
But I think they taste like crap
They taste like a little, I don't know, it's
Not crispy enough, I guess
Not enough salt
They're very natural with their fries
And I don't like that
I want it to taste artificial and salty
Alright, live listeners, it's all better
You can check in now at vognetwork.com
Sorry about that
Things are gonna be a little broken tonight
Because to hosting it, we kind of have to
I don't get as many little breaks while
Dark Soccer's talking or whatever
And we couldn't scrounge up a third host fast enough
As I was saying, Alan worked today
Although, to be fair, it was his choice
Because his boss said, you know, you want the day off
It's your birthday, whatever
And Alan was like, oh, no, I want to make money on my birthday
Sounds good
Sounds good to me, right?
So there you go
Which, I don't know if I'm supposed to say this
But I'm gonna
His boss, you know who his boss is?
His boss is Jessica Harper from Understadation Live
Really?
Yeah, they work together
Isn't that funny?
That's awesome
I know, it's like the VoG family at work and online
So that's pretty funny
I don't know if I was supposed to say that
But oops, I have a big mouth
Sorry about that
Happy birthday
Alright, anyhow
Usually we get into talking about our gaming weeks
But I want to do a kickoff topic beforehand as we usually do
And I want to kind of address the pink elephant story in gaming
You know, we know we're not breaking news to you here on Orange Lounge Radio
But one thing we like to do is kind of present the news
Put it on the table and talk about it a little bit
One of the big things that has everybody talking this week is
Gaikai, right?
Because Gaikai got bought by Sony
And, you know, I know there's some more with that
That's gonna come up a little later in the show
But let's talk about kind of that first step there
Because Sony has bought Gaikai
Why, Loki?
Why did Sony feel they needed to buy Gaikai?
For streaming games, I mean, that could be useful
They've got a lot of, you know, Sony is an electronics manufacturer
They have laptops, TVs, tablets, phones
So they want a way to stream the Sony or PlayStation brand
To all those devices at the same time
Maybe somehow make them connected more with the PlayStation console
Or just tying everything together
I think that's a good way to do it
Is just, you know, with a streaming platform
You know, I think I've made this comparison before
And I may not have said it on the show
But I totally thought it, which counts on the internet
And that is that the whole
Sony has been doing a little bit of that streaming
With the whole PlayStation 3 to the PSP
Even before the Vita technology
Where you could, you know, remember
I've brought this up on the show before
But if you're a new listener or whatever
It's one of the best hidden features
That will really surprise you about the PSP
Is that that whole Wii U technology has existed
I'm not dogging Nintendo
I realize Nintendo is going to try and perfect that with the Wii U
That's fine
But that technology to stream from your console
Has kind of been there with the PlayStation 3 and the PSP
Granted, you're not streaming the full PlayStation 3 game
That is not what's happening yet
Although maybe this guy kind of purchases
Well, and it's also not just
You could stream like videos and other things
And it's also not just Sony stuff
I mean, you could stream it to pretty much any platform
That would be connected to the internet
So, I mean, you could really stream it to like
Android tablets or an iPad or whatever
And so that's kind of, I could see them being interested in that
Or, hey, they could even be just improving their streaming technology
So that they can stream more sophisticated things to the Vita
You know, maybe PlayStation 4 type graphics or whatever
Not necessarily graphics, because obviously you can't push that through the Vita
But, you know, more intricate games that are going to have complicated graphics and stuff
To those devices
A little easier than you did with the PlayStation 3
And you can also do that PSP PS3 integration through the internet
If I remember correctly
You can actually, like, I could be at a friend's house
Get into their Wi-Fi, turn on my PlayStation 3 at home
And get whatever I need on there
Although that's really limited to, I mean, video
You know, I wouldn't try to stream a game off of there
Like a PS1 game or anything, because the lag would be crazy
Can you imagine trying to play, like, Umjama Lamy over to that connection?
Nope
Although that might be a fun challenge
But, I mean, just the fact that I can, like, look at my home setup
On my home PlayStation 3 and my crossbar
Is kind of cool
Like, it's a nerdy, whoa, Keanu Reeves meme moment, you know?
Yeah
So, I'd be very curious of PlayStation trying to perfect that technology
What about, you know, one thing I've been kind of thinking about is that
PlayStation Plus, they like to do these demos
The 60 minute demos of the games
But right now you have to pretty much download the whole darn game to your drive
In order to just play 60 minutes of it
I mean, for some people, depending on your connection
It takes longer to download the demo than it does that you actually get to play the demo
Maybe they're looking into Gaikai technology to stream demos
I mean, that would certainly be a great use for it that they could probably implement ASAP
Uh, it's possible that they were looking at doing that
I mean, they could do a bunch of different things
I just don't know
I don't know, I don't know what they're really doing with it yet, I mean
How do you, and let me pose this question to chat as well
And I'm behind on some chat comments
In fact, let me read a couple right here even though they're on other topics
But I don't want to ignore our chatroom at chat.
Excuse me, live.vognetwork.com
But AcidicVampire says
I don't drink soda much, water or iced tea
You know, there's a lot of people that
You know, when you drink soda a lot
It's kind of like one of the first things you kick
When you decide you're going on a diet or whatever
And it can be effective, like, I stopped drinking Mountain Dew once
I lost like 10 pounds alone
Yeah, I could do that, but I'm not
ImmortalKing in our chatroom says
Give yourselves credit, you've made a lot of exclusives
Well, alright, maybe a few here or there
There may have been some like a week or two ago
Regarding a new console or anything
Perhaps, perhaps
But we don't talk about that kind of stuff
Because everyone's going to forget it anyways
And BobbyBlackWolf saves the day saying
chat.vognetwork.com, which I almost said
That will work too, so you can use live or chat
It's the same darn thing
But let me pose this question to you and pose this to the chat
Going back to Gaikai a little bit
How would you feel if they came out and said
And I know this probably is not going to happen, disclaimer
But how would you feel anyway if they came out and said
And on the Playstation 4, we're not going to have discs anymore
You're going to buy your games in your virtual library
But you'll be able to stream them on demand
And we hear that that's your option for the next console
It's basically a Gaikai slash on-live slash whatever console
How would you feel about that?
Would you still be on board with gaming or would you be out?
Absolutely would not be buying that console
Because I don't want to have to fucking deal with that shit
And when you say fucking deal with that shit
Is it just you're pissed because you won't be able to
Rampantly mod things like you've been able to do before
I mean, it kind of puts the kibosh on all of that
No, not even at all, it's just I have to stream stuff
I mean, I have an internet connection one day
Or, you know, who knows?
I mean, the internet's not always reliable
Or I should say your internet connection's not always reliable
That's very true, we ran into that a couple weeks ago on the show
So, I mean, I don't really
I mean, it's fun to play, you know, let's imagine a world
That this actually is going to happen
But it's never going to happen because they built a monster
That exists out there, that is their market share
And there's no fucking way of getting rid of it
Because honestly, you know, if they decided
Hey, we're going to put out a console
It's only going to be able to stream games
You're not going to be able to buy it at the stores
Then games will be like, who the fuck's going to sell your console?
Your accessories, your points cards
Oh, that shit, your video cables
Oh, oh, oh, oh, now you need us?
Oh, and you're not going to give us any of that software money?
Well, fuck you guys, good luck selling your console on your own
And that's honestly the situation that's going to be in
Because there's no money to be had in
Definitely no money to be had in consoles
And definitely no money to be had in
At least not much money to be had in accessories
So it's got to come all from the games
And even though the profit margin in games aren't that great either
But still, people trade in stuff
And there's no use market
So that's basically going to be taking away the money from
The largest retailer for video games
And I'm sorry, but they kind of control what people do
And so as much as all these companies want to go all digital
It's not going to fucking happen
Definitely a lot of negative reaction to my question in chat
Which I kind of expected, I think we all did
But a lot of the reasoning focusing on the maintenance of your connection
That you can't always trust your internet connection to be stable
Which I can definitely support
AcidicVampire says, if it's streaming, what if your net connection slows down
Therefore your game stutters? Yes
Reginator says, I want systems with optical storage
If only due to backwards compatibility
Reimu says, suppose you can't connect to the internet
GameGuru says, screw that, I'll just stick with Steam then
Interesting point about PC gaming
I mean, streaming's been available on PC for a bit now
And it certainly hasn't killed Steam
Not by a long shot
They can do that as another option
To say, hey you know what, you can either download your game
Or you can stream it instead
And that's cool that adding options is not a bad thing
But completely removing all other physical options
Because you want to have control over the content
And make sure that there's no piracy
And also making sure that
I don't know, whatever other reasons it has
So that they have all the money, profit from it
It's just, it's not going to work
Let me read a couple other very strong comments from chat
MegaBoyX says, I will never buy a system
Unless I can own physical copies of the games
Which, you know, some people want that type of control
You technically don't own those, but you know
Yeah, we could get into that whole thing
But I mean, Alan, remember I plugged DBA
Or Alan was here on the show last week
And he plugged Zebay's auctions
And I plugged them on Twitter and stuff
He made decent money off those sales last week
I mean, they were old Game Boy Advance games
But apparently some of them are very hard to come by
Especially in other countries
So he did pretty well off that
So, you know, being able to resell your games
When you need a little cash
I think is something we all kind of like to have
That kind of investment there
I guess maybe it's like leasing a car versus buying a car
I don't know
Let me read the most blunt comment in chat, though
I want to talk about this for a minute
Blender at live.vognetwork.com says
They do that, Sky, and I'm done gaming
That's probably the bluntest comment I've seen
But I can't say I blame him
Like...
Go ahead
Okay, I just...
Not to sound like real, like, disastrous
Or dramatic or whatever
But I've often wondered if that's what's ultimately gonna cause the end of OLR
Especially when I see these stories about, you know,
Xbox will prevent used game sales
PlayStation gets Gaikai
And maybe will stream only
Although they probably won't
And all this other stuff, you know, I sometimes wonder
I wonder if there's gonna be another video game crash
And we're just gonna stop being fans of gaming
And that's ultimately what's gonna probably end the show
No, that's not gonna happen at all
And here's why it's not gonna happen
Because, you know, all that's gonna mean
You know, just because a console fails
Or an idea fails
Doesn't mean the whole industry's just gonna go belly up
I mean, look at it
Let's say the PlayStation 4 actually
Let's say Sony is stupid enough to actually say
Okay, we're gonna make this console streaming only
Well, you've got other console manufacturers
That don't necessarily have to follow that
And, you know, we know that the Wii U's not gonna be that way
So, I mean, that's just stupid right there
So people just won't buy the PlayStation 4 instead
Let's assume that all of them are really dumb
And they all decided to go that way
Well, hey, you know, you don't have to give up gaming
I mean, hello, there are how many generations of fucking game systems
You can't tell me you've played every single fucking game that's in existence
I mean, there's plenty that keep you entertained until you're dead
I mean, seriously, you don't need to
That's true, it's very true
You don't need to buy brand new fucking games
And, hello, you could go play on a PC
Because none of that bullshit's there
Or you could just... indie games
Yeah, indie games
I mean, there's a ton of shit out there that you can be playing
You don't need to be relying on
Well, all these new systems have to be successful
Yeah, you won't have these really great games that are on consoles
Because you don't want to stream everything, which is fine
Because I don't blame you
And also, it's not going to work anyways
Because why am I going to stream all this content to my system
And then hit my bandwidth caps for my internet providers
We're just not in a world right now where it's viable to do that
Hey, Comcast is up in that cap to 300, apparently
Ooh, let me put it this way, okay
I could be rampantly pirating for an entire month
And I wouldn't hit that cap, okay
I mean, it's a large cap, but I haven't ever done, like, streaming constantly
With, you know, gaming and stuff
And honestly, I don't want to do that
I haven't tried it online, maybe I should
GameGuru in chat says
I don't think there will be another game crash
If anything crashes, it will only be the console industry
Save Nintendo, who lived through that shit
And I think...
Nintendo didn't really live through it
At least not in America
I mean, I can't speak to really Japan
But they definitely didn't live through it in America
Because the NES wasn't really out when the bottom fell out of the market
I mean, that was mainly the Atari 2600 and just the oversaturation of games
Especially the quality and the price that really drove things down
But, I mean, I could...
If it's gonna happen, it's gonna happen in this next cycle of consoles that's coming out
And it will be bad decisions that cause it to happen
But, anyway, don't run around crying, you know,
Oh, OLR threatens to end, no, cause funny enough
I arrived at a similar conclusion that
Well, we could always talk about classic games and food
There you go
There's never gonna be nothing that we can't...
I mean, just because, you know, it's...
I mean, let's say the industry crashes
What are we gonna have?
Just real quick, Black Wolf clarifies
The arcade games were out before the crash
So, like, Donkey Kong and stuff was out around that time
There's plenty of stuff to talk about
Anyway
There's plenty of stuff
When I all of a sudden go,
Well, I can't buy a new system
I just hate games now
I'm just gonna leave
We would just have to change the format again
But, anyway, I don't...
Let's not go further down that road
Cause that's not gonna happen for a long time
And there are, you know, there are...
I'm sure by the time the next E3 rolls around
And we actually get to see these consoles and the offerings
There'll be a little more excitement
At least I hope to hell there are
If not, we'll talk about the Playstation 3 and the 360 a little longer
They're not gonna go streaming only
It's just not gonna happen
Alright
Live.vognetwork.com again if you want to participate along with the show
And offer up your chat comments
Let's get into our gaming weeks
Going back to the present a little bit
Or maybe games, classic games that you've been playing this week
Dark Soccer, if she was here, she told me to say this to you listeners
She would be talking about Garrus and more Garrus
She has been playing more Mass Effect 3
I think she's about, she's at least halfway through the game
From what she'll be
She got to the romance, she did get to romance Garrus again
In part 3, I know that
Her femshep and Garrus went on their little date
And I think she's, it sounds to me like she's about half to two thirds way through the game
So hopefully by next week's show
Since you know cause she ain't here
And she's at home recovering and resting her voice and all that
She's playing Mass Effect
She'll probably have that stuff beat by next week
So we can ask her about the ending
Anyway, so I know that's Dark Soccer's gaming week
Let's go to Loki's gaming week
Well I started off by finishing up playing
Ultimate Collector Garage Sale
Which is the game that's tied in with that Ready Player One contest
Fucking hated that game
Ever fired my body so I
Wanted to get that out of the way
And I did, I finally got the DeLorean in game
Got my, you know
Leaderboard position
And have the new website for the
Last challenge which will open up on Wednesday August 1st
Well actually technically Tuesday night
Cause it's Eastern time
Which I've already made plans on how I'm going to tackle that
Including staying up all night if I have to
Cause that's the one that's actually gonna count
Cause right now it doesn't really matter what your position is
Even though it was number 14 for the second challenge
I was gonna say
I heard that you placed like 14
So does that mean you're number 14 like overall right now?
It doesn't matter, it's just for fun
The leaderboard is just how fast you completed the second one
But it's really the last one because
It's whoever completed the first two challenges
And whoever finishes the last one first
Is gonna be it
And they said it's really hard the last challenge but
I mean we'll see
I bet it's gonna be something like
It's gonna be like Super Meat Boy Hard
Or like the Impossible Game
Or VVVV but like even harder
I hope it is something like that
Cause I've actually played quite a bit of that stuff
I bet it's gonna be one of those style of games
That's gonna just make you wanna poke your eyeball out like
I don't care that'd be fun
And you know what I'd rather have it be that
Than wanting to poke my eyeballs out
For playing that stupid Ultimate Collector thing
Which is so goddamn boring
There is a trick to it I mean
You just have to get a lot of friends on Facebook
That are playing that
And so I did that and
You know I was able to
Cause you can send energy to each other
And that's how you can do it without having to pay anything
I have to play this a little bit
Cause this is a link that
Alan sent me on my Facebook this week
It's off of Tumblr and it's credited
The source is KidXForever
I have no idea it's Tumblr
I can never tell how this works and who gets credit for it
But here you go
It's somebody playing the impossible game
And giving their commentary
And this is what I picture Loki is gonna sound like
During that final gate competition
Oh it says Achievement Hunter
Oh yeah it's that Rooster Teeth thing
Oh okay then there you go it's Rooster Teeth
So here you go
Let me play a little bit of this here if I can
So they're hopping along to the bricks
He'll fuck up here in a minute
That looks pretty hard
That's probably the type of thing you're gonna have to play
FUCK!
Holy shit this is way harder than the original
This is like two seconds
This is the beginning of the fucking level
And it's like double spikes, triple spikes
Fucking shit you gotta jump over
It's fast as fuck too
Damn it! Come on you fuck, come on you fuck
JUMP- GOD DAMN IT MOTHERFUCKER
I always fuck up that last part
By last part I mean the end of the very first fucking-
Okay the video goes on like that for like five minutes
But that's totally gonna be you that night
Playing that game
GOD DAMN IT
They just fucking did this so they don't have to fucking give the DeLorean away
Mother fuckers
First that fucking Facebook game and now this shit
On top of the DeLorean thing
Let's just, you know
Let's say I won that thing
I'd have to still fucking drive to L.A.
And pay the taxes
And pay whatever goddamn registration
Insurance
All that shit
It sounds like a big pain in the ass actually
But I still wanna win
Cause who doesn't wanna win?
Who doesn't wanna win? Exactly
Speaking of which, that reminds me actually
There's a Call of Duty 3 tournament down here in Stockton
One of my customers is actually having it
And I need to find someone to play with me
Cause none of my friends wanna go
And that kinda sucks
Anyone that listens that's in Sacramento
That happens to be somewhat good at
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3
Hey, you might be interested in
And that ain't me
You know, interested in going down
See, cause I thought my old coworker might wanna do it
But he has his kids, you know, they're divorced
And they're shared custody
So he has his kids on that Saturday
Cause we'd fucking tear that shit up
Wait, so you have to have like a partner?
Yeah, so I think it's a two on two
So if you wanna team up with Loki
You gotta be local though
You gotta be local
And don't be scary
Yeah, Stockton's scary enough
We don't need any scary people
Meeting me down there
At least that's what I'm thinking right now
I haven't really discussed with the wife yet
But you know
Well, cause I wanted to see if I could even get someone
Cause you know, what's the point
Me just going down there
But it might be fun
There's cash prizes involved
Don't know if there's that many people
Anyways, so other things to play this week
Minecraft
Playing Minecraft a lot
I finally got the achievement for On a Rail
Cause my rail system goes really far
The other thing though
Is I'm not sure how
Bobby was talking about that he got that achievement too
And I was wondering in the back of my mind
He did not
Cause I didn't know he was building a big rail system
He has an underwater rail system
I actually saw there was a Minecraft thread
On the VoG forum that I saw his thing
No, but mine actually goes really
Like all around the world
I'm gonna get the achievement by just going to Loki's world
That's fine, come on in
I'm redoing the whole mine cart thing
Cause before I used to have it where you push the switch
And it would call the mine cart
It just doesn't work now
I was gonna have the mine carts just traveling around
But I ran into a problem
Where I accidentally
I was trying to get into one of my mine carts
And it caught one of the powered rails
And just kept going
So I'm like, oh that's fine, I'll just catch up with it at the end
And it never appeared
So I'm like, does the game just lose track of these mine carts
Cause that's gonna fuck up my entire system
If I have these mine carts going around they just disappear
Because, oh it's too far away
That might be a problem
I don't know what I'm gonna do there
That's an issue
But yeah, it's been fun playing that
And a little bit of Modern Warfare 3
Let's play a little bit of that
Bobby says the one that he built was actually above ground
He couldn't get the underwater one to go long enough
So there you go
Alright, anything else you wanna share with your gaming week?
Ah, that's it
My gaming week, I've actually still been playing
More Final Fantasy 11
It's kinda what I've been playing instead of WoW
Cause there's really nothing to do in WoW right now
Unless I wanna level in alt
So I'm really kinda just burned out on it
Playing with friends a little bit has been Final Fantasy