Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loku
Tonight, July 29th, 2012
Will one new non-MMO game require a monthly fee?
Game developers speak up on Windows 8
And could used digital games soon be a reality in the US?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello, my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
It is the show where every gamer has a voice
It is episode number 467 for this July 29th, 2012
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
To talk about video games, gaming culture, you know, our community
And cool things, and off-topic things
With my co-hosts, say hello to the one and only
Dark Sakura, or Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you? Welcome back
How was the wedding? You were in Vegas last week for a wedding, right?
It was very lovely
Yeah
And very Jewish
Congratulations to Dan and Tiara once again
Even though we said it about five times last week
Yes
There was an open bar
Was there?
Well, then you had a blast at the wedding
I had many, many amaretto sours and raspberry vodka with cranberry sauce
Cranberry juice
Cranberries, gross
And mudslides and other things that people just put in front of me
And said, here, drink this, and champagne
So you'll drink anything someone puts in front of you?
No
Oh
People that I know and trust to put liquor in front of me
Nice, nice
It was very good, it had a very good time
And it was good to see everybody
And get my nails did
So, yeah
Awesome
Alright, say hello as well to Tech Master Loki
Hi
How are you, Loki?
I'm doing good
Good times
I like your shirt, by the way
You're wearing a shirt that actually says, Loki Charms
Yes, it was the ripped apparel shirt from a couple days ago
I like it
Or actually about a week ago
Oh, yeah?
Yeah
Alright
We have a special guest joining us tonight here in studio
And some of you old school Orange Lounge Radio fans might remember her
Because she has been on the show before, but it's been a very long time
I am so happy to welcome back to the show
Marissa
Hello
How are you, Marissa?
I'm great, how are you?
I am fantastic
Thank you so much for coming back to Orange Lounge Radio
Great to be here
For those who don't remember
All you need to see are her boobies
They are very nice breasts
And I don't mean to sound like a pig or whatever
But, I mean, seriously, girl
They entered the room before me
Don't forget to talk right into that microphone
Because it's not very sensitive, unfortunately
So they can barely hear you
It's not nearly as sensitive as Rob
I mean, I have to do it because it's been years later
Why am I not, I'm not here
Is the mic on?
Testes one, two
I don't know, it's like very quiet for some reason
Why don't you just pick up Loki's mic?
Hello, hello?
Hello, is that better?
Much better, now I can actually hear you
Alright, how are you Marissa?
I'm great, thank you
Despite the technical failure
Why don't you tell the boys and girls listening at home
And in PlayStation Home, which I'll get to in a minute
I haven't forgotten you guys
Why don't you tell them about yourself real quick
Well, I'm a music geek
Singer-songwriter and, you know, collector of vinyl
And all sorts of music
And I also, as far with regard to gaming
I'm an adventure game geek
You know, Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis
And King's Quest and, you know, things as such
I'm not really that up to date with the modern stuff
But there have been some recent, you know, not that recent
But, you know, adventure games
You hear a little blip about them every now and again
They're having a nice little renaissance
Thanks to, kind of, a lot of the stuff that Telltale's been doing
And the indie community especially has been very big on this
Like, I know there was the King's Quest fan thing
The silver lining, which was really awesome
And, you know, the fan community's just great for that stuff
That was great
So, actually, I came up here specifically to see this band, Prilosis
And if any of the buddies in Sacramento, I highly recommend that you check them out
They're a metal band
They're also actually hilarious
They have a great YouTube channel
It's P-R-Y-L-O-S-I-S
And that's also Prilosis.com
And for anybody that's into metal music, I just had to recommend them
Because that was a lot of fun and they're fantastic
But that's more music geekery for me
That's no problem because now the network is about everything geek
It's voice of geeks
So, a little music geekery on our show, it's A-OK
Especially for metal fans
You know, I'm not even actually a metal fan by nature
But I really enjoyed it
They're really melodic
And it's just amazing, though, how one can expand your horizons
Especially when it involves people that are really musically gifted
But you do a lot of music playing yourself, right?
I do a little bit of singer-songwriter stuff
Bitching about ex-boyfriends with an acoustic guitar and stuff like that
So you're like a Lilith Fair, basically
Not that bad, but
I'm doing a lot of jazz covers recently
I have a guitar player and it's been a lot of fun
Hanging out at this place called Kulak's Woodshed North Hollywood
And they webcast actually live all their shows
Nice
And it's kind of a singer-songwriter deal as well
Very cool
Well, welcome all the way from LA
Appreciate you stopping by tonight
So happy to see everyone
Speaking of live webcasting, I'm going to transition to this
This is going on tonight, a little special event
The VOG Network got asked to be a part of
PlayStation Home Summerfest is going on right now, live
And I know we have some new listeners tonight
Because of the PlayStation Home Summerfest
I will say this is an unofficial event
It's not something that Sony is really sponsoring
But I bet they're really happy it's going on
Because there's lots of people
It's fan-organized and lots of different communities
Be they gaming communities or PlayStation Home specific communities
And so forth are coming together
To basically put on a week-long event of
Hey, let's get a bunch of awesome people together
And, you know, dance, have contests
Talk to each other, kind of get a chance to meet new people
And I spent all of the last hour during Bobby Blackwolf's show
Because he's before us live at vognetwork.com on Sunday nights
5 Pacific, 8 Eastern, right before us
I was in PlayStation Home during his show
And just kind of really seeing the community
It was almost like watching an episode of Cheers
Where people would show up
Norm!
Everybody seemed to know each other
I thought it was really cool
In a way I felt like an outsider
But everybody was super welcoming
It was like saying hello when I was talking about VOG
And people were actually pretty receptive
During Bobby's show he got a caller from somebody
That had never listened to VOG before
But was listening because of PlayStation Home
And I just thought that was a great cross-promotional opportunity
So if you are listening live
And you are in PlayStation Home
I do want to point out Bobby Blackwolf is in there now
And he's going to be feeding me comments from PlayStation Home
To possibly read during the show
He just got there
So give him a big hello
And be sure to shout out hogwash for him
So he can see
That's become the rally cry of tonight in PlayStation Home
I noticed that during Bobby's show earlier
Of course if you want to do things the old fashioned way
Nothing wrong with that
I'm not going to ignore you guys
In our always present chat room
Live.vognetwork.com
Is where the traditional IRC based chat room is
If you want to join that and chat along with the show
You can also check in to the show at VOG Network
As we are live here and get your VOG points
And maybe a little bit of loot
Alright
Stan in our chat room
At live.vognetwork.com starts us off tonight saying
Rob is there a way to stream the live podcast
On PlayStation Home
Cause I'll switch if I can
You know sadly I don't think that's something that's possible yet
Because I don't think you can really do
Like streaming music or any of that yet
We should all let Sony know that's something we want in the future though
Cause how awesome would it be if in that VOG Network clubhouse
We could actually have like a VOG Network feed
That would be like the best thing ever
So who knows anything's possible in the future
So BlackWolf is reporting that
From PlayStation Home
That the club channels just died again
Our party is crashing the servers y'all
Do we know how to party or what?
Alright
Anyhow so yes again a big hello to you guys
At PlayStation Home who are listening tonight
Let me throw out some names I remember from before
Manda Panda
Jay
Steven
Junebug
That guy who had the 91 on the back of his shirt
That made me feel insignificant no just kidding
But yeah I want to say hi to all you guys who are
Listening right now
Alright
And also some of the
OL Army and VOG regulars
Are in Home Summerfest right now
I saw Tigerclaw in there earlier and I saw
Spaznators and some of the other people
So that's pretty cool there's kind of the cross
Promotion stuff going on so that's what it's all about
It's just promoting community and
And cool people meeting other cool people
I know PlayStation Home
Has had it's share of you know
Some people still don't get it
And I even admit I've sometimes
Been a little critical of Home on the show
But that has nothing to do with the community
That's only about the software
That sometimes it can be a little slow
And tough to connect to things but
It really has changed a lot
Since that first beta
So if you haven't checked out PlayStation Home in the past three years
Seriously there's like a million mini
Games now tons of prizes you can
Get for your avatar and just like cool little
Knick knacks it really is worth checking
Out if for nothing else than just to
Meet some of the awesome people that are on
The PlayStation Home community
Alright
Before we get started with
Tonight's show I wanted to do a quick
Kickoff topic which I think might have
Been just saying hello to Marissa and
Interviewing her a little bit
Let's see Marissa
So you like adventure games
What is your favorite video game
Ever?
It really does have to be Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis
I really just love that game
Do you have a thing for Harrison Ford? Let's be real
No but I have a thing for fedoras
I really do
Damn I left mine out in the car
No true story
One of my other passions besides internet radio and video games
I have been a member of like live shadow casting
For midnight movies like Rocky Horror Picture
Show especially right for like
12 years well lately
I've started doing stuff with Repo the genetic
Opera which is you know one of this
Yeah that's kind of I hate
Calling it the new Rocky Horror because it's not
It's just a new
Cool phenomenon that also happens to be
At midnight
Exactly it's kind of like the shadow casting
Thing of the now and last night
They did the 80's repo show
And I got to do Indiana Jones in a
Special cameo which was awesome
Did you bring your whip?
They did a joke
Where the Paris Hilton
Character Amber Sweet is kind of like a dominatrix
So they did a joke where I came out
As Indiana Jones
And she stole my whip
That was kind of the joke which was super cute
But the audience cheered
And I felt hot
Awesome
It was a good time anyhow
Let's get to video games
Speaking of games I know where to start
This week Loki I want to talk to you for a minute
Alright so you've been talking
For weeks about this
Contest this competition you
Were going to be at this weekend
Let's hear about it how did it go?
It was terrible
Ok what was this that you went to?
Ok so I went to a Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3
Contest it was going to be 2 on 2
And you know for a while I was trying
To find someone to go with and I had my
One of my friends brothers was going to go
With me and so everything sounded
Cool because he plays a lot of you know
Call of Duty I play
Quite a bit and you know
The rules were a little weird
It was basically custom classes
But there were certain restrictions on what kind
Of loadout you can have and that was fine
I practiced with you know the loadout
That I could
Work with in the
Rules of the
Tournament and so I was kind of ready
I had everything set up
Ok so here comes Friday
You know the Friday before
The tournament
Literally about 2 o'clock
My co-op
Partner drops out
So I have no one to go with
So I'm like fantastic ok
So I you know I
Call my friend Sean I'm like hey
Does your other brother play
Because you know and he's like yeah he plays
Let me see if he can go
No he's got things he's
Doing ok fine
Alright that's fine you know
I'll just find someone to play
With when I go down there or
I will just you know
I'll play one against two
That should be ok with you know I'll take them both on
Exactly with the loadout I had
So I drive these guys are gonna all be what
16 I'll take them all
So I drove down there
Like an hour and a half down to
Stockton and
So I'm
At the shopping center where this place is
And I can't find it at first so I
Look up on Facebook because
This plaza is actually
On both sides of the street I'm like oh that's probably
On the other side of the street let me just look up where it's at
So when I go to look it up
I notice that there's an update in the events
Oh by the way
We changed all the rules
Oh how convenient thank you
How convenient so they're all oh by the way
Now we're not doing custom classes we're just doing
The standard classes that are there
And with no restrictions I'm like
You gotta be fucking
Kidding me I drove all I'm like fine
You know what I drove all this way
I'm gonna play at least
So I get there sign up and everything oh by the way
Now we're gonna not do kill streaks
So it's like what the fuck
So ok so fine whatever I'll play
So I got hooked up with somebody else
And then it was just kind of it just kept going
Downhill from there oh yeah
We don't have headphones for
Anybody so you can't really hear what's going on in the game
Oh um
The person that we
Put you with he doesn't even
Really understand what kind of tournament it is
And he thinks it's a free for all tournament
First and then finally figures out
It's a co-op tournament so at this point
I'm like there's no fucking way we're gonna even win
One round and that's exactly what happened we played
First and we lost both of our rounds immediately
Because it was just a clusterfuck
I guess I had been practicing
With a certain class all week long
Per expectations to the tournament
And then they fucking switched it all up on me
So I'm like god damn it I don't know what fucking class I'm gonna play
And did they ask you, you mad bra?
Oh no oh it gets better than that
It gets better I'm like ok so what the hell
I mean why did you guys change the instructions
Oh well it's actually supposed to be standard classes
All along but that's what we've been telling everybody
That's been coming in here you know the past few weeks
Oh the past few weeks so you've known
About this shit and you've been telling everybody
Oh but you fucking failed to update it
On Facebook so that you know people that were
Coming out of town would know anything about it
Well I don't know I'm just
I'm just working here
It was a big fucking mess
So yes I didn't enjoy
Myself but at least you know what at least I didn't
Spend that much time in Stockton
I played for a few minutes
I got to meet with my customer and devs
Down there and I left and that was it
Dungeonbuster in our chat room at
Live.vognetwork.com says the rage
Gauge is nearing critical
DJ Morpheus is counting the number of F bombs
That you're dropping I do want to
Because we do have an influx of new listeners
Tonight thanks in part in
Large part to the Playstation Home Summerfest
I just want to remind everybody it is a mature
Audiences show so please put the kids to
Bed or put headphones on
Let's be honest I mean come on I mean there's
People that I've been to video game tournaments
Before you don't go to a tournament
That changes the fucking rules
Nah that's messed up like 10 minutes before the
Tournament starts like back in the day if it was like a
DDR tournament like oh man
That tournament would have been smeared on DDR
The next day yeah it's just it's
The next day the same day
The same day it was ridiculous
We couldn't we didn't have live blogging back
In that day but we had laptops at
Tournaments there was but see no one else was
Pissed there except for me because everybody else
Everybody else there was local and so they
Had been in the shop at least a couple times
Before you know tournaments started so they
Were aware of the the change in the rules
But no one fucking mentioned it
At all it was just
It was really annoying but whatever you know what
I I even like
I contemplate I'm like do I really want to drive down
Stockton since it's just going to be myself you know
I do want to point out Wicked is in our
Chat room right now saying yay Loki
Was in my neck of the woods
So you are bashing one of our listeners
Hometowns right now but let's be real
Dude bro you live in Stockton
You know what though
Your city's bankrupt
Let me put it this way it at least
The tournament was in a
Seemed like a good portion of Stockton like the
The shopping mall was actually pretty
Nice I mean so
A compliment from Loki everybody
The mall was nice
Was it by the S Mart?
I don't know where the S Mart is but
But there you know in the game
Store was nice it's just I'm unfortunately
You have an idiot running your goddamn tournaments
That's the only problem and I don't know
It may very well be that this guy
Is new to running tournaments because I hear
That their fighting game tournaments run okay
But then again I'm sure they're not switching up
Rules you know it'd be funny
Hey let's go play
Marvel vs Capcom 3 tournament
Oh and the reason too
The reason that they changed up all the rules is because
Oh well we didn't want someone to say
Oh well the only reason you won is because you got this kill streak
And the helicopter killed me
Too fucking bad you can get the kill streak too
Damn it that's what I was planning
Exactly too fucking bad if you get killed by something
Or a certain gun or something
That classes have
You have all of these guns available to you
And you're playing by the same rules
Why can't you fucking just suck it up
That you just sucked instead of
Forcing these people
Which I say to just succumb to their peer pressure
To change the rules at the very last second
Because
Oh we don't want to hear someone bitching wine
Well you know what you're fucking hearing me bitching wine about it now
Because I had to drive 90 fucking minutes
To your stupid tournament
Which I will
Oh and by the way
I love my customer but
I'm like so are you coming back for Stockton Fest
I'm like no I'm not fucking coming back to Stockton Fest
I am not driving to Stockton ever again
When I drive to LA
I will drive around Stockton
The last time I went to Stockton someone stole my Xbox
This time I went to Stockton
Fucking tournament sucked
I'm not coming back to Stockton
There will not be a three strike law here
This is two strikes we're done
I'm not going back to Stockton
Wicked in our chat says
Trust me if I didn't have to live here
I wouldn't
Hey trust me
I'm sure it's just
It has nothing to do with Stockton
This could have been run in Sacramento and had an idiot running tournament
It doesn't matter
You don't fucking change the rules
At the last second
Okay if you're going to change the rules
I can understand if it was like
Hey you know what you guys
We said all these restrictions
Are in place
But we're just going to lift the restrictions now
Okay that's not so bad
Because I can still play with the class I had
Or I can change it up a little bit
Instead of oh by the way now you have to stick to one of these
Six classes
Oh and you know that sucked
And you can at least get some killstreaks and stuff
But we're going to take those away too
Wicked in our chat room says
Aw you won't come back to Stockton
Not even if I bake cookies
No
Sorry
I'm going to vomit all over the entire town
We're going to have to broker like a Loki Stockton
Peace Summit in like Lodi or something
I don't know
We're going to have to figure that one out
Alright look we're too many local jokes
It's a worldwide show
The rule I mean just
The lesson to be learned here is
You got to be I guess you have to be aware of how the
Wherever local stores
Are running a tournament
How they handle things
Because I mean honestly no one should be changing the rules
And I noticed they deleted the event
On Facebook so no one can comment
On it or anything
They must have had a few
Angry people
Who won?
I don't care I wasn't going to stick around
Who cares like I felt bad for the guy
That was playing with me I'm like well
Like is it like the second game
Basically it was
Oh and that was the other thing they changed too because it was single
Elimination first and then it was like oh best two out of three now
I'm like is it best two out of three or single
Elimination well it's best two out of three then
If you lose once then you're out
Okay fine
That doesn't even make sense
Whoever loses the best two out of three
And then or wins the best two out of three moves on
Then the loser is done
So
They so we did this
So we lost our first round because it was like okay
Let's try to get ahead and we were doing alright
I mean it wasn't like we lost by a whole
Ton
It's still you know quite a few
Points but it wasn't like you know
We had 100 points and they had
2500 or something it was pretty decent
But
You know we had already lost our first game so that put us at a disadvantage
For the second round because the second round it's like well
We have to come to them because they're not
You know in order to
Win this and so it just unfortunately
We had the advantage there
Alright we have a comment coming out of Playstation Home
The man Bobby Black Wolf is in he does
The show before us Sunday nights
On VOG Network he is in Playstation Home
Right now feeding me comments because I can't
I can't see the TV it's too far away
I'm in there doing the running man I can see everybody
In the circle doing the running man which was
Cracking Marissa up when she walked through the door
But I can't actually read
The chat because it's too far away
But Black Wolf says the spasinator
In Home says if Loki vomited
All over Stockton he'd probably
Improve the place
A circle of running men just sounds
Dirty too
Alright
Let's talk about our gaming
Weeks and the other actual games
We've been playing this week hopefully not at
Tournaments in Stockton that caused us to rage
Dark Soccer we'll start with you tonight
How was your gaming week?
It was Mass Effect-y
That was really about it
Because that's really about all I played that and
Some words with friends
Ewww Zynga game
Whatever Judging you
Whatever No I know it's popular
It's real popular I don't care if it's popular
It's addicting I've been playing a really
Addicted game I mean I'm like cutting and talking
About something in my week real quick but I've been
Playing well no this is important
I've been playing when don't I ever
Make a topic about me Dark Soccer
Even over what 10 years alright
More than that
There's a game on iPhone called
Song Pop I think is the name of it right
Now and it's really fun it's like guess the song
As fast as you can like it's like
Name that tune yeah yeah right
So you gotta check this out but here's
The problem we're all just looking at our
Watches counting down how long before
Zynga buys them
How long before Zynga buys them
Well Zynga's already getting burned because I think they're
Starting to realize that's ooh
I heard there's like all this I don't think it's
In our show tonight there's like all this scandal
Like the guy sold his stock like the CEO
Sold like a bunch of his stock like two months
Ago and then they had the report
Like you know insider trading
Investigation since you interrupted I'm gonna
Interrupt you as well that's cool since we're talking
About Facebook games and stuff
Let's talk about Facebook real quick
Facebook in case anyone
Hasn't fucking noticed
Is a little broken right now
Because you cannot
Unsubscribe from people's comments and likes
Or updates by games
I try I don't fucking care about
Your stupid song game or whatever
I'm trying to hide that shit but Facebook
Does not want to let you know what's funny I thought
I set all that shit to private
Like are you seeing my song song other people
Oh okay Bobby
It's alright and you know I don't mind
That kind of stuff it's mainly people
Commenting on other people's like cat photos
I really don't care if you think that's a cute cat
Or not but it's it's up
It's Facebook's problem because all that stuff
Was hidden before and now it's not
I just want to make it known that this is an
Issue so everybody can also make it
Known to their friends that this is an issue because
It no one seems to be fixing it
It's been like this for a week I think the real
Issue is that I heard this one into
Place a couple weeks ago like if in group
Let's say you're in a group and you make
A post in that group now
You can see when everybody
Read that post uh-huh
I kind of think that's like a privacy violation
In messages surprise
I want to be able to stalk people with
Impunity
Exactly I can see that too with
Messages direct messages that you send to people
On Facebook you can see if they've read it or not
Whatever happened
To good old fashioned anonymous ignoring you
It's just like those emails with read
Receipts and stuff like that I love deleting
Those before they get sent
It's terrible well actually
I mean I have to
Bitch about Facebook too because they're totally
Fucking over page owners right now
I mean I would I understand
That you know that they're a for profit entity
And they have to make money but I operate I operate
Several pages myself for musicians
And one for a venue that I work for
And you know it's very important for our
That mic is cutting in and out sorry about that
Live radio kids hello love ya
Okay burning with fire
I know um
Yeah I operate several pages for musicians
And for venues and for a venue that I work for
And um I completely
Understand that Facebook is a for profit
Entity and they need to make money
So I'd be happy to pay for extra features
However to pay for just
Basic exposure that would normally if you were
On a friends page would just go out to all of
Your friends is bullshit I'm sorry
On Facebook you pay with your
Soul this is true
I'm not gonna how do you like your Farmville
Now
I completely agree
But yeah I mean page owners if you didn't know that already
Your um your posts
Aren't getting Zuckerberg is watching you
Masturbate Shalom
I'm allowed
To say that
For the record
But yeah
I mean if you
For any page owners that didn't know this earlier
Unless you're you know paying for their extra services
You make a post to um on your page
It's not going to reach your whole audience
At all Marissa we really just need
To show on vog where we giggle for an hour
This is true
Giggle time
Oh dear what have I started
Tickle fest
Yay
Alright
Oh yeah this was Dark Soccer's gaming week at one point
Well fuck all that I'm looking up
Mass Effect t-shirts
I was not familiar with Mass Effect
And Jamie did introduce me to that character
Glorious Baritone he is lovely
Oh he's a lovely voice
The guy that was his voice actor was on
An episode of Buffy as like this real douchebag
Who was like this horrible character
Oh really? Yeah it was in season 7
So it doesn't count
Can you celebrate your heart?
He has a very nice lower register that's all I can say
Well then Marissa I'll ask you about your gaming week
It sounds like you got exposed to Mass Effect
A little bit
My new wallpaper by the way is the
Citadel smooch
That's it? Watching other people
Play Modern Warfare and then getting
Yelled at for stealing their bandwidth
Has pretty much been the rest of my gaming week
God dammit are you on the internet
Sorry
That's like Sunday nights at OLR
When Alan mistakenly
Downloads BitTorrents God dammit are you getting porn?
Trying to do a show
I'm trying to
Hack into our neighbor's connection
His connection's name is Mr. Touchy's
Uncle Touchy's puzzle basement
But I haven't been able to figure out his code yet
It's a Patton Oswalt joke
As long as it's
You won't wear a shirt and you'll cry
You can hack it pretty easy
I can send you the link
Lifehacker had an article on it
Alright
We'll go move on to Loki
Loki how was your gaming week besides Stockton?
Hey Stockton just was unfortunate
But this week
I didn't even finish mine
I thought you were done
Fuck you fuck everybody
I'm bi
Alright you're done
Okay so um
No no no no no hold on
I had to walk away so I wouldn't time out of home
You said and I quote
I've just been playing Mass Effect
I might have played other things
But when you say
I just played Mass Effect
Well I did just play Mass Effect before we left the house
That is true
She made it sound like
Oh forget it I'm not having a grammar war
With this woman
Fine lady how was the rest of your gaming week?
Uneventful
She is a level
She is a level 50 grammar knight by the way
She's a level 50 bitch right now
No Rob 69
I'm sorry bitch it's a subclass
You need to put a B in a circle on the back of your shirt
When you go into Playstation home
Alright Loki how was your gaming week?
Now do I have permission to move on to the show?
Carry on carry on
Thank you
How are you enjoying hosting the Olympics your queen?
All these countries used to be mine
No I have to do
I have to do the proper
All of these countries used to be mine
We are not amused
May the odds be ever in your favor
Okay alright Loki
Now you may proceed
So this week I played well Call of Duty
Of course
Also played a little bit of Borderlands
And a little bit of Just Cause 2
Had to stop playing Just Cause 2
Cause my computer felt like it was gonna melt down
Which means I had to
Make some modifications
It ended up that my cat apparently
Was using the inside of my
Or the heat fins for my
Cooler inside my
Laptop as a lint
Collector and so there was a
Nice layer of cat hair in there that I
Found when I
Disassembled everything so
Thankfully that was easily remedied and then
I drilled holes in the bottom of it
Because
These Asus laptops, the older ones
Just had really piss poor
Cooling so it's actually helped
A lot and um
It doesn't feel like I'm shooting fire
Out of the side of my laptop right now
Um and then
I got
It's never good to have a hot laptop on your crotch
Because then you really get fire crotch
Well then you have
Roasted sausage
No no I used to
I have a cooling pad
They put on there but yes before when I
Icy hot?
A metal
Metal pad with fans in it
Anyways um no but when I had
Before I had all the
Cooling modifications to it I would burn my
Legs playing games on
My laptop so yes that's
It is possible to do that
And it got so hot too that
Like I was burning my hands not
Touching my laptop on top of
My keys it was just getting that hot
I'm like okay starting to smell things
Burning probably should cool it off
Wow um so yeah
So I think we're good we're in a good spot
Now because all the other spots that I haven't
Drilled holes in don't really have any processors
Underneath them so it's probably not
Necessary um and then
Played Minecraft a bit more of that that's
Kind of fun we just started kind of exploring
The area and the new
What was it uh
Octocock Minecraft
Scene um
It's actually a very boring map so
I might want to start another one
Um and then
Um what else
Oh I have a beta key
For the little big planet carding thing
I haven't gotten a chance to try yet
Thank you Loki by the way
No problem um
And
That's pretty much it I just have a lot of stuff
I'm you know a lot of it was just
Hinging on cooling my laptop down so I can play
More Borderlands again because it was just getting
So hot I'm like I don't want to break anything
In there alright
Talking about my gaming week um I played
Borderlands a little bit I was really
Busy during the weekend because of the shadow casting
Events going on this weekend but um earlier in the week
I played Borderlands like a little more
Seriously this time I mean not
A lot a lot I only probably got to like level
10 or 11 which you know is is
Change in the scope of things but it gave
Me enough time to get a better feel for the game than what I
Played of it before and I like it it's
Kind of like I think
The description of World of Warcraft
As a first person shooter is somewhat
Accurate except it's not really an MMO
But you can play the multiplayer
That was the only thing that felt a little
Disjointed for me and like this is gonna
Sound negative but it's really not like I do really
Enjoy the game you guys but I kind of thought
It was weird that like it's the same you can use
The same character in your single player
And in multiplayer I know
You can use different too but it was
It just felt a little disjointed like here I
Am doing some quests in single player and then here
We are multiplayer and so
And so is kind of off doing this and so is off doing
This and kind of like we're all completing quests
I'm not able to really follow along I'm not
Able to get into it as easy so it's kind of like
I feel the need to play through this game
Once single player just
To like know the story
And know everything and then go back and do
Multiplayer and
Okay for real GameSpy
Is the multiplayer client like what is this
But
Okay I realize the game is a few years old
I'm not gonna I'm hoping Borderlands
I'm hoping Borderlands 2 uses
Something a little more modern
That just kind of surprised me I'm like
You know I'm missing origin
Right about now Maybe it runs really well
Because no one uses GameSpy anymore
Maybe maybe maybe that's the secret
I don't know but yeah I mean
Borderlands was it's fun I mean
It's more of an actual
Like shooter than like Mass Effect
Which I was talking about before that
You know remember I said I was playing a lot of Mass Effect
Multiplayer and it makes me want to play a first person shooter
Because I'm really enjoying Mass Effect
And the most people suggested I play Borderlands
I think it was a great suggestion
It is a little more first person shootery than I'm used to
And I was surprised I couldn't dumb the difficulty
Down because I like to play my shooters in
Easy noob noob mode
But there is no difficulty
Yeah you gotta hax it though
You gotta hax it
I didn't want to do that
I'm doing alright so far
Multiplayer kicked our butt
Like because the enemies get so much stronger
And now it's not just one guy running around
Not knowing what they're doing it's three
This is me and two buddies of mine
We can certainly play later on
I know Bobby's got it, Allen's got it now
Lots of people in the Borderlands
Otherwise for me I've been playing
A lot of the same stuff
Otherwise not a lot of new new stuff
This week you know World of Warcraft
And all that good stuff
I'm eagerly awaiting
Thanks to Loki I got a beta test code
For the little big planet karting
Super excited to try that out
Play it as quickly as possible because it ends like Wednesday
Oh no I'll download it tonight
Play it Monday and Tuesday night or something
Let you guys know my impressions on that next week
That ought to be of interest to the Playstation home folks
Because that's a Sony exclusive
We got some codes that we can give away too
You say we have extra codes to give away?
Yeah we do
Maybe we need to do a giveaway tonight
In the Playstation home clubhouse
That'd be fun
I think like three extra codes
We'll think of a way to do a contest
I don't want to ignore the folks in our live chat room either
Maybe we'll give some codes away in some different places tonight
Guess Marissa's cup size is the contest?
I can guess what it is
I told you
I don't know about that
Alright
I gotta keep it
We might be a mature show
But I want to keep it somewhat
PG-13 at least in home
Out of respect to the community
Keep it a little PG-13 there
Too big is the answer
Alright
Shane is messaging me
Going I want a freaking code
Well Shane that's what you get for bragging about
The Playstation all stars
Network battle
Royale thingy that you were in the beta for
And I was like let me play
You know what his answer was? No
Alright
Let's move on
I think we covered everybody's gaming week
Yes yes yes alright
Housekeeping
I want to talk about this
This is something a little special
No this is serious for a minute
A little special and unique on the VoG network
And I think this is really cool
And kind of shows some of the different stuff we can do
So next week after Orange Lounge Radio
That's right after Orange Lounge Radio
I think we've been doing this show like 10 years
Have we ever had another show follow us?
Like usually we're the last show of the night right?
Because it's like 1am on the east coast by the time
We're done sometimes
Well next week there is going to be a special
Show following us
At VoG network.com
I know it's very late
I know it's a long time to stay up
But this is very cool
Travis Donovan from Understation Live
Is going to be doing a special live
VoG coverage of the Mars
City Landing
So I think that's really cool
Like Travis if you listen to
Understation Live at all which is on Saturday nights
At VoG 7 o'clock Pacific
He loves space
He loves NASA he loves the space program
Is he the best at space?
He might be which by the way before I forget
Rest in peace Sally Ride for real
Sally Ride
Not just all the stuff that came out afterwards
But just Sally Ride
I was around 5 or 6 when she first went into space
And I don't
I don't even know
How to put this like at such a young
Age you're like even so happy
To see like a female go
Into space like
And you kind of wonder as a kid
Like on one hand you wonder why is it
Such a big deal but on the other hand
You're like you feel like a lot of like happiness
And pride for kind of like that equality
I remember feeling that at a young age
And I'm not even a girl like I guess I was a feminist
At 5 years old who knew but
Anyway Sally Ride
Amazing inspiration to men and women
Everywhere
Out of current events I didn't realize
We had set up another
Like
That's just a one time special
No not that I'm talking about
Sending something to Mars
I didn't even realize that we had
Sent anything else to Mars
I thought they were like ahhhh
We fucked up that last rover
We're done
I mean that's cool
Well you know what you should
Tune in to Travis' special
Next week you might learn something
Makes sense that now they have all these Mars landing games
Like who cares about landing on Mars now
I mean that's like so old
And what the hell is the world turning to when I'm learning things
From Travis Donovan
Love you
Alright
So I did want to plug that
Of course I want to plug our Facebook community
Facebook.com slash OrangeLoungeRadio
We are on Twitter as well
You can follow us at at OLR
Or you can follow the voice of geeks network as a whole
VOG network
VOG network did grow in the past couple weeks
With a few new shows
Critical Myth and British Invaders
Want to give them a shout out
Great great television and discussion shows
They're both fantastic shows
And so happy to have them on the lineup
And of course one more shout out
To the folks right now doing the running man
Or just hanging out whatever they're doing
Playstation Summerfest is going on right now
Looks like it's thinned out a little bit
There was a lot more people in there during Bobby's show
But you know it's getting late
On the east coast
Some people got to go to bed sometimes
Alright moving on
Let's get into some gaming news
I think we're just on the other side of the camera
Oh was the camera just facing the wrong way?
Oh my god someone made
A chibi garris plushie
I see from back here I see it
Junebug says thank you everyone very much
Awesome job vog
Thank you Junebug!
She won a $20 gift card during Bobby Black Wolf's show tonight
For Playstation Network and she called in
And I thought that was amazing
Shout out Junebug
Loki starting us off tonight
With exclusive news
Maybe?
I don't have all the details on this yet
But it was interesting
It's a test that they're doing
Apparently it was that new
Nike Plus
A fitness game for Kinect
That's coming out this fall
Is going to require a subscription
Service
In order to play the game
Now I'm not sure exactly how that works
Because I was asking him some questions
He was basically
The rep we had at Microsoft
Was kind of using this
Hey we can sell some more points cards using this
I'm like aren't people going to be kind of pissed off
That you guys are charging 400 Microsoft points a month
For the service
I guess it's for stat tracking
And something like that
Now he said
Because I don't know too much about this game
He said that the game will not work unless you pay
This monthly fee
So I'm not sure what exactly
Is entailed there
If it's just going to not track your progress
That's what the monthly fee is for
Or if it's just
Going to plain straight up not work
Unless you have like
A pass or something
If you don't pay us
You will get fat
I don't know
See my thought is
I was just kind of
Why
Why are you guys doing this
Aren't people going to look at this kind of negative
Because I even brought up the typical things
I love that you called him out on it
You guys
You have your gold service that people are paying for
Aren't you guys kind of worried that
This might look bad
They're charging a fee
On top of this
It's just a test right now
So I don't know
This is a test
This is only a test
That's me sucking money out of your wallet
We'll have to see what
We'll have to see what exactly this is
When it comes out
Because I'm sure that he didn't have all the details
Trust me, I know reps for companies
That don't know what the fuck they're talking about
When it comes to product
And so
It's very possible that he got some stuff wrong
Or just wasn't clear on things
Maybe it's just this whole
Stat tracking thing that's extra
Or something
But I still don't like the fact that a game
Is requiring you for a monthly fee
For something that should be
In my opinion included with it
So
We will see when this comes out
And if it does require this
That kind of sucks for them
There's plenty of fitness games out there
For the Xbox 360
This has to be something super special
The Nike Plus has
That whole
Will it integrate with the shoes?
It's going to integrate with that stuff
Maybe that's what it is
I don't know if Nike Plus
As a service
The one with your shoes
If that requires a fee
Maybe it's something like that
All I know is they're saying
So
Yep
Five bucks a month
I wonder if that will have to be right
There on the front of the box
That they're going to be charging that
It won't be
That's scary
Then what are you getting?
I can see if there's a premium club
I guess that's no different from Call of Duty
That's what it's going to be
Maybe
If you subscribe to this
And you're out of it
That would make sense to me
It would be a huge mistake
To say this game requires
All this DLC
But that's how he phrased it
Maybe it's just
Him misinterpreting
The information he's been given
It's possible
But I'm just reporting
What I've been told
400 Microsoft Points a month
Some people have mixed success
Rates with those fitness games
Brad is talking to me in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com
Right now and he says
Talking about fitness games
Christina got a
Your shape game
And while doing one of the initial
Setup scans it told her
Straighten your back
And they cracked up because she has scoliosis
So her response was
Good luck with that
Marissa you're...
I can imagine Marissa playing
The Your Shape game
You seem a little top heavy
I can't straighten my back either
I have thighs
Put down your groceries
Stop carrying that baby
Please put down the watermelons
Please
I'll do ooches braziers later
Alright
Anything else on this topic
Low key or can I move on
One more thing I forgot
I mentioned this week
I played Dead or Alive 5
The near final build of that
That's kind of cool
But I don't play Dead or Alive
So it was button mash fest
I didn't do very well with that until I switched to Ryu
And then I fucking kicked ass
He apparently is pretty conducive for button mashing
It looks pretty though
Is Dead or Alive
I made a huge faux pas by the way
Christina is a girlfriend not a wife
My bad
Awkward
Sorry guys
Back and away
Did I mention what a great show pod culture is
And you should all listen to it
So that I can be forgiven
Monday nights 6 o'clock
Awkward time at the dinner table
Rob is red now
Don't worry it's just like when people say
So Alan's your roommate?
Well yeah we do live together
In the same room
And have mating practices
Alright hey let's move on to Windows 8
Marissa it's going to turn into the giggle show
She's over there making like she's digging a hole
Let's talk about someone who's almost as awesome as Brad from pod culture
Gabe Newell
And he's talking about Windows 8
He's not a fan
You know Windows 8 is coming out towards the end of the year
I believe it's been a year
I believe it's been officially dated for October 26
And it's going to be coming out
And a lot of people are excited about Windows 8
But one of them that is not excited about Windows 8
Gabe Newell
He says quote a catastrophe
He just straight up called it a catastrophe
And that's according to all things D
I think Windows 8 is a catastrophe for everyone in the PC space
I think we'll lose some of the top tier PC OEMs
Who will exit the market
I think margins will be destroyed
For a bunch of people
If that's true then it will be good to have alternatives to hedge
Against that eventually
And that is a follow up to Steam being on Linux
That is actually
Now that you kind of hear that
You're like damn that's genius
That's a proactive move by Steam
Just in case Windows 8 is a gigantic fucking bomb
That it turns people off
That's a pretty big risk in a way
I mean I'm sure the Linux folks are happy
That's crazy that all of a sudden old versions of Windows 8
Just disappear and become Windows 8
That is a little interesting but
I mean gee what's going to happen to all those computers
Running those older OS's
And people not upgrading
Oh I guess everything will work as usual
That's odd
Alright
But hey I guess you know you've got to be prepared
For the apocalypse
I want to come back to what Gabe Newell said in a minute
Because he said something else
That was really fascinating
And I definitely want Jamie to hear it
But in the meantime I want to talk about Blizzard
You know the makers of World of Warcraft
And Starcraft, Diablo
You might have heard of these games
They're kind of big in PC
Just if you haven't heard
They have a new game coming out this year
Pandaria right
Ok so
Blizzard is kind of on board with this
It was according to Twitter
And a comment from game designer
Rob Pardo
He said on Twitter
Nice interview with Gabe Newell
I think Windows 8 is a catastrophe for everyone in the PC space
Not awesome for Blizzard either
Now keep in mind
This is one guy at Blizzard
But when he is a game designer
Yeah
So there you go
Not some good early feedback
I'm hoping this isn't going to go over
Windows ME or something
Or Windows Vista
Even Marista
The non-gamer is sitting over there going
Oh so cold, so cold
Wait give Marista the mic
Marista you are not a fan of Windows ME
No I've actually had it in many offices
I've been the legal secretary
At many points in my life
And attorneys are very cheap
I've had to try to work with Windows ME
I still have nightmares
Alright
Let me go back to the Gabe Newell thing in a minute
Alright Jamie listen up
I know this is software that is a big part
Of what you do
Because Gabe Newell kind of alluded
To programs like Adobe
Like Photoshop
That causes us to have conversations
With Adobe and we say
The next version of Photoshop
Should look like a free to play game
And they say
We have absolutely no idea what you are talking about
But it sounds really bad
And what he means by that
Is that he is saying you know
People make money on things like
Team Fortress
Team Fortress 2 excuse me that are free to play
One steam user apparently making
$150,000 a year selling hats
In Team Fortress 2
So he sort of goes to something like Adobe Photoshop
And says what if your platform
Was free
But you sold the little bits
That's at least what I am reading into this
You sell the little bits and pieces
You sell the advanced filters
And all of that
How would you feel if Photoshop looked like that?
Dark Sakura?
Well there are other programs that look like that
And that's why I don't use them
Oh really?
Yeah I mean I could use GIMP
I love GIMP too
But I want what Photoshop does
So I use Photoshop
Let's have real talk for a minute
Aren't there a lot of people that just pirate Photoshop
I mean isn't that what
Isn't that what Newell is kind of
Trying to get at
Well people are
Pirating it anyway
So why don't you just make it free for everybody
And then add the features
Because that's not going to work
There's plenty of companies that are still going to
Buy the official ones for their
Designers
At a design firm
There are plenty of professionals who are going to have licensed copies
Because they can't produce
Work for a profit situation
If they are using a pirated
Version
They have to have licensing
Even free to play stuff
Sometimes has that pay tier
Like a lot of MMOs
Like Star Trek Online or DC Universe or whatever
Yeah it's free but then if you pay the monthly fee
You get your Uber access or whatever
Yeah Marisa
I would be happy to pay
If it was a little more reasonable
For those of us who aren't using it under a professional capacity
Well that's what surprised me about
Windows 8
The price, you know a lot of people are shocked about
Windows 8 price but some people
Infer that that's coming from the Mac side of things
Where you know I think the latest Mac upgrade
Was what 20, 30 bucks
Don't quote me on that because I don't have a Mac to upgrade
Right now
But yeah a lot of people are saying that
Windows 8 is a cheap upgrade because of that
So interesting counter move
I like 7
7 does what it needs to do
And it
I just think that
And this is the whole reason why more and more
People you know basically are leaving
The PC and Mac universe to
Head over to Linux because they want
To have the control over what they install
In their systems like I love
Linux because if I want my
System to be optimized for graphics
Over like say sound
All I have to do is install a new kernel
That's optimized for graphics
Done
Or optimized for system speed
Done. I can switch between the two
If I want to
You know I have all of my programs
I can download them through one place
Yes but they've been tested and
Worked for my system I can still
Go through other means to download the programs
That I want. I love Linux
I'm running Linux Mint right now
On my netbook which
You know was half the size of the Windows
Install that came on it
And it uses I think
A third of the memory resources
That Windows does
But is it efficient for porn?
Yes I can watch porn on it
He's efficient for porn
Hey porno box I love you Linux
I just got done
Looking up a bunch of mass effect porn
I mean
You mean deviantart research
Whatever
I'm
I'm doing
Work
If a computer from
Back in the 90's is efficient for porn
Which mine was
They're slow let's be real
A netbook can easily look up porn
I mean Loki I know you were the kid
Like me who dialed into all the BBS's
To download porn? It took time
That was dedication because if that picture
Because if that picture
Sucked then oh my god
You've just wasted a good like
30 minutes
And we were thankful back in my day
Pornography
Was logging onto the local
BBS to see Snow White
Gangbanged by seven dwarves
Animated gifs
They
Weren't even animated it was just
A regular gif
And you what you know what
You were lucky if it was in 256
Colors because look at those boobies
In 16 colors and you'll like it
Two miles uphill in the snow
Go find an old abandonware
Archive somewhere and download an old
School strip poker game from like 1984
For what was called
Now kids I know you might not have heard of this
But for what's called a CGA monitor
Does anybody know
What a CGA monitor does
And then we had EGA
Okay I have a dirty
Porn story
My favorite
Safe for your audience though but it's funny that you mention
That you know with you know with the
Internet and internet pornography it's amazing
Actually how much of a backlog
And you know things that run on VHS
That are on the internet I found out
That a friend of mine
Had a
A gentleman had done
Porn and
I was there for this this was funny
She found out while she was here
Yeah and um
The Wii came out
Now I understand why when we were doing
The whole cute little like find out your porn star
Name game now I understand why he thought that game
Was so funny
Now I understand like he didn't
Yeah well I managed to
Look it up and uh
I found it it was like 94
I also found out that he hadn't changed his
Comforter and I had house sat for him once
And I was grossed out
Because they shot it at his house
Did you run and take a shower immediately?
Yes
He had a chair it was just so comfort
I slept in the bed I was watching his house
And I took a screenshot of his own face
And I sent it to all his friends
Wow
That is a cunty thing to do
Oh my god
I'm sorry if that word offends you
Alright I didn't want to go there
That is like drag queen level
See you next Tuesday
That would be the truth
But the problem was Rob
You sent a picture of his own face to all of his friends
I had dated him
And he did not tell me
Okay
I didn't want to
I didn't want to have to make that confession
But yes
I have fucked a porn star
Congratulations
Yay
The things we learned on Orange Lounge Radio
In retrospect his technique
Makes a lot more sense now
Now I look back
Oh
By technique meaning
That he uses the same techniques that butchers use
For like tenderizing meats
Or perhaps that you're like
Man were you like a butter churner
In your past life or something
I just want to give another hello to the Playstation
Homers joining us for the first time
At the Voice of Geeks Network
These are the things geeks have to say
Who knew? Well you know what
There's a comment coming from Playstation Home
From Manda Panda 1979
Snow White banging the seven dwarves
Hot!
It really wasn't that hot
But yet we were 13 and loved it
One of the days of the pornos he was in
Was called Country Western Cuties
Nude pie eating contest
And he
Bob is on the floor literally
He was actually
A country singer songwriter
That's how I knew him
Okay for the record
I had just broken up with my boyfriend
It was a very dark time for me
And now I
So how about video games?
That email actually said to all my friends
Had said I have a present for you
And I had the
Screen cap of Zo face and in
Porny font it said you're welcome
It's a pie eating contest
I'm
So sorry
Oh yeah and by the way I actually had asked
A bunch of my friends to tune in
This evening
Who were not aware of the story
So now they know a lot more about me
Than I never cared to have them know
I'm surprised that that's the title of it
That's actually pretty
You know
It's not bad for a porn title
I mean there's
No we're talking like actual pies
And not like pies in the
Pornographic sense
That's where my mind went
I've been literally rolling on the floor laughing
So hard
You're welcome
I apologize
I'd like to take this moment to apologize
Can we get to the games please?
Maybe
Chigurh says
That I'm going all Anderson Cooper right now
Rob was
Literally on the floor
You know what's funny is I had some people
Come up to you during the game summit thing
That we had at our work and everything
And they're like hey so I have some libraries
And stuff that might be interesting in podcast
And I'm like did you realize this is a pretty adult podcast
Like we use some colorful languages
And they're like yeah that's okay
Are you sure you know what you're getting into?
Well if Catcher in the Rye is at the library
I mean
They're not my customers
Okay
Monty Boggs in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Says I'm so glad this is
The OLR live I get to
Come back to after so much time away
Please don't put this on the wiki
Somehow
Windows 8 led to that
Discussion
To register
Participation for this week's episode of Orange
Lounge Radio on vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase
Olive
So DarkSakura
Why don't you try to bring us back to games
Here with another story
More porn please
No not that
Square
Is saying that
Versus 13
Is going to still be out
And they still are not showing shit about it
But they are watching porn
No
There was basically
A statement by
Yoichi Wada saying that
Someone was spreading a rumor about Versus being
Cancelled
They said that he just left a regularly scheduled
Meeting for Versus and quote says
If you were to see
The city
Etc presented today
You wouldn't be able to stand
From surprise
Because everybody thinks the game is dead
Yeah
Could it be though I mean okay
Cancelled but weren't there a lot of
You know kind of rumor I mean granted this is
All rumors or whatever that it could be a different
Name now
I don't know they just said that they're still
Running it under the luminous engine
Well I know that's a lot of what we talked about because when the story
Came up last week we were here but
We hypothesized
It doesn't say anything about it
Final Fantasy 13 a sequel
Reborn
I see what you did there
We'll come back to that
Dark Sakura what do you think of Final Fantasy 13
Versus does it look like something you play?
Given that I didn't play the first 13 more than
The level then I kind of
I'm not interested in it
Well keep in mind Versus is more Kingdom Hearts ish
In the way it plays then I play Kingdom Hearts
I mean seriously
I'm kind of spent on the Final Fantasy
Franchise I kind of don't care
About it anymore
14 didn't help but we'll get back to that later
I didn't play 12
I tried to play 13 and I thought it wasn't
Great and I'm really not
Invested in the universe so
I think honestly between
13 and 13
Versus is pretty much just like
Joel Schumacher Batman and
You know
A different Batman Final Fantasy 14
Was kind of the Batman and Robin of the series
Right now it's kind of like
We had to hire
Who's like a big
We had to hire Steven Spielberg to redo
Batman and Robin like that's what's going
On in Final Fantasy 14 right now
Alright let's move on with
Some more news while I get a drink of water
Because my face still hurts from laughing so hard
Damn you Marissa this is why
You haven't been on this show because you kill me
Every time
I'm trying to take
I'm on the Facebook app right now
I'm trying to take down the leak I sent all my friends
Inviting them to listen in
Not all of them knew that
It's okay though it is funny
I love you so much right now
I can't even
Alright so what was his porn star name?
No
Everybody's gonna
Google it now
Let's move on
Games, video games, gaming culture
That's what we do here at O.L.R.
Alright
So let's talk about Ouya
Ouya is that you know
Wonderful 99 dollar console that's being
Created through Kickstarter of course
And they made some announcements
Including that the streaming service
OnLive will be coming to the system
As well, not a big surprise since
OnLive runs on Android and it's an Android
Device so it makes sense to me
That it would be on there
But of course OnLive has been
They committed that they will deliver a full console class
Experience and bring hundreds
Of top tier games for more than
80 publishers, more marketing speak
Marketing speak, marketing speak
And then of course at the same time
They also showed the second half of that
Concept picture for
The Ouya controller and
Yeah looks like the second half of the controller
What do you expect
And of course everyone's like oh I don't like that d-pad
Well everything's still not finalized
It's just a concept picture
But now you have your second half and wow
It looks like what you thought it would look like
The Ouya, the OnLive
Everything is a really interesting back door
To get the big games on
Ouya because you remember a couple
Of weeks ago we were you know kind of having our
Skepticism chat about should we fund
This or not and we were talking about
You know how they're doing this poll to see what
Games people want on Ouya and it's all this
First party stuff is what people really want
It's like dude this box is not going to be powerful enough
To run you know Mass Effect 3
Or something like that but
Thanks to OnLive technology
I mean you could play Assassin's Creed
Or you know whatever the games are
That are on Ouya
Borderlands is one of them I know that
And I don't believe
A publisher can say
No we don't want our game pushed to
Such and such I don't think
Yeah so that is
I gotta say that's a really
Smart partnership
Because you're using a technology
That's gonna be able to
You're using
A technology that your system can accommodate
To kind of use those
Big games and I think that's a
Really brilliant idea on their part
Yeah and then of course
I think we may have mentioned this last week
That they're getting the prequel to
The human element
Is gonna be an exclusive thing on there
Considering that that game doesn't come out in 2015
I don't even know how
Why would you even announce a game that's gonna come out that far
From now I mean
Cool you got a game coming out in 2015
I won't remember by the time I get to 2015
Tigerclaw in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com
Who earlier told me they were
Feeling ignored because of all the
Attention I'm giving the Playstation home tonight
I'd love you guys too
At the regular chatroom live.vognetwork.com
Tigerclaw says
On live is on Android
So it coming to Ouya was a no brainer
Well if you said that last week
Tigerclaw you would really look like a
Games analyst but now
I mean
I'm not surprised because even if
It wasn't on there they could have easily
Just you know side loaded it
On there and game guru reminds us
On live already has
A set top box you know so it's
Already available out there
True I think their set top box is like 50 bucks
Too but at least
This you'll get a set top box that'll
Do that and other
Things it'd be cool
If it's compatible with the on live controllers
I'm hoping that it's going to be compatible
With any bluetooth controller because then
I can use my PS3 controller
Which isn't getting a whole ton of use right now
Except for
You know browsing porn
On the PS3
What else do we use
Our devices for alright
Before I get into the next story I have some
I'm sorry home this is
These comments are a little bit delayed
But I think you can tell what segment of the show
These comments are from
PSV J style
In the Playstation home
Chat room Aurora 1.5 space
Tonight during summer fest says
Are you listening to this
LOL and
Fizz Liz says giggle time
So apparently
Now it's the running man and giggle fits
In Playstation home summer fest
Awesome
Are you going to do the Carlton next?
I don't think the Carlton is one of the
Dances it might be
You know what's great
Tangent time you ready for a
Random rob tangent
They upgraded the lotus notes system
At my work yes my work is one of the few
That uses lotus notes as opposed to
Outlook the other one right
So we use lotus notes and one of the huge new
Features is
Customizable emote icons
So now when you do the
Instant message you can have like your own emote icons
And one of the most popular ones right
Now that has been passed around
At the work place that we send to each other
Is the Carlton gift
When something goes well
You can add any animated gift
To the emote icon system which is amazing
Please tell me you added the table flipping or something
I don't have a table flipping
But I have a cat jumping out a window
It looks
It's a safe cat don't worry
It looks like a great distance but it's not
It's just like jumping into the backyard or something
But it's funny
Some things
Coming to
I feel bad that on the Sony Playstation home night
We have all this Microsoft news but
We do have some Sony news coming up a little later
But
This is an interesting experience on the Xbox
There's some new TV experiences
Coming later this year
They are Connect Sesame Street
TV not to be confused
With the game that already came out
And Connect National Geographic
TV which I think they're just calling
Nat Geo because I guess that's what the hip kids call it
Nat Geo
Alright
They will be $29.99
That's 2400 Microsoft
Points for 8
30 minute episodes
Apparently they are interactive
TV shows though
They will be available at retail
And Xbox Live under the
Season Pass
I don't know how the interactive
Episode works but I imagine maybe you will like
Sesame Street like they count along
You interact with Connect stuff
Like Elmo will tell you
Hey toss me my
Teddy bear and you make the motion like you're tossing
The teddy bear and if you don't it will
Still play on as well
It's like optional
I gotta say if I had kids that
Does sound pretty rad
Have you thought about something like this for Josh?
I've definitely thought about it
I may pick it up
How does Nat Geo work?
You point to
I want to see the topless natives point
I think it's animals
Not topless natives
It's more like
Can you spot the
Giraffe or something like that
Given a thing you have to find
I found it right there
Trivia and stuff like that
The other thing too is those are also
Rentable
I was going to get to that
For five bucks
That's 400 Microsoft points
September 18th is when this all starts
That's the purchase
Renting them is 240 Microsoft points
Each
That might be worth checking out
You should definitely put Josh
To the test there and see if it happens
It's hard to say
He probably won't know what to do
He's still a little young
If they tell him jump up and down
Sing a song
Sit there and eat a cracker
He's like no
I'm not going to do that
Skullking in
PlayStation Home says
Will this Sesame Street game be like Dora the
Explorer? If so I'm down
That's kind of how
That show works
A little bit
But it's for real
Maybe that will be the next thing that comes to connect
If these do well
It's all about how well these do
As iconic as it is
I imagine it's got to be pretty cheap
To reduce
Since this is all PBS programming
Fuck Dora the Explorer
She's on Nickelodeon
You know what it's all about?
Fucking Carmen Sandiego
Ghost writer on there
No
Reading Rainbow
I want LeVar Burton
To read to me on my
360 and that sexy sexy voice
Ah PBS
Mr. Rogers neighborhood
I know Mr. Rogers is long gone
Maybe a live interaction with King Friday
And what was that lady's
name? She was kind of a bitch
The lady that had the
museum or something, the carousel
Yeah you lost me
Somebody with me here, come on
That's Sharon Lewis and Bram's elephant show
We were listening to the theme song
yesterday
Two elephants went out to
play upon a
spider's web one day
And
where the hell is my god damn
Bob Ross painting game that I was promised
at the launch of the Wii
Huh? Please tell me you heard that new
Bob Ross remix Yeah it was alright
It's nice
Alright
Lady Elaine, thank you DJ Morpheus
I knew somebody in chat
would know it Lady Jane
Frisbee gives the full name
Lady Elaine Fairchild
That was it Lady Fairchild
She was
kind of a bitch
What do you want?
In the land of make believe
I would give a fuck
Make believe I'm gonna kick your ass
I made believe you weren't talking to me
Hold on sorry dead air but I'm trying to look
up right now on
the YouTubes
If I can get a clip here
Oh fuck yes here we go
Oh damn it that's like a song or something
That's a creepy puppet is what that is
It had a picture on it but
Is she a creepy puppet?
She was a creepy puppet
Alright forget it
Although maybe if that pop song is any good
I can put that in a vog network rotation
Anyhow let's move on with some more stories
Dark Sakura
Well how
about a survival
game called Pulse
It's free and it was put out
by the Vancouver film school
Well because you know students
student work has often played
into many a modern video
game like
Portal
You know
Anyway this game called Pulse
is a first person survival suspense
game so you play as a blind
girl who has to go through
a cave by throwing around
four sprites
Splat!
And the sounds
they make help her see the world
around her kind of you know daredevil like
So she has sonar
She has sonar by throwing fairies into the wall
I like that
And it's done by Pixel
Pie Team and it's
very artsy, colorful
cartoony
but it's very very grim
and actually
they want to
expand it beyond the free version
but for now I think
if you want to get it you can go to their
official site
which is Team Pixel Pie
as in 3.14
.com
I'm going to get it when I get home
Very cool, I'm glad these students
had time to produce this you know
And the site is really pretty
I love the color scheme in this
It really is just very
different
Well congrats to the folks at the very original school
Well there's another one too
There's one called the Mask of Key QI
which is a third person platformer
that has a master flying squirrel
and it's done by
Team Kronk and it's another
freebie
Alright let's travel around the world
and check out release dates of some more
traditional retail games coming to a store
near you this week. Loki?
Not a lot of big things but
a couple big games that you'll probably be interested in
starting off with Risen 2
Dark Waters on Playstation 3
Xbox 360
and I believe PC
and then for 3DS owners
finally getting your copy of
Kingdom Hearts Dream Drop Distance
in 3D
on 3DS
You don't say? Yes I do say
and
I think that's pretty much it
I mean at least those are the big ones this week
Well the Kingdom Hearts game is kind of a big deal
so that's cool
Yeah that'd be it
Let's travel- Oh Grow Lancers
Grow Lancers way far over time
Forgot the Atlas PSP title
Alright moving to Japan
and checking out the release dates over there
The Idolmaster 2 gets a price
reduction this week on the Xbox 360
That's not a new release but
if you like to save money that will be going
into effect this week. On the Playstation 3
things are a little more exciting
when you have Tales of Vesperia also
getting a price reduction and
Tales of Graces F also
Troy Musu getting a
price reduction as well as Idolmaster
2. There's lots of price reductions. Oh
Battlefield Bad Company 2
It's like a Playstation 3 sale but
sadly no new games to report on either of those
systems this week in Japan
Looking at the Playstation Vita
there is a game called Momo
Daisensu Gen Daiban
comes out this week in a regular
and premium edition that's a game on
the Vita. I don't know if that's
based off an anime or what
but it's from SystemSoft and
it kind of looks like these
I don't know, one chick kind of looks like an army girl
and another kind of looks like Sailor Moon-ish
but she's got like a microphone
so I'm not sure what this game is all about
there is no description
about if it's based off a series
or what have you. I have to randomly add
that Chris always compliments your Japanese
pronunciation. He's always
impressed by it. Don't listen to early
episodes of the show because it was a hot
mess. Never had a class
Well I did have Jamie sitting over here
to slap me on the back of the head when I'd get one wrong
I can't do it right now. You put the embosses
in the wrong syllable
On the 3DS this
week, more exciting
games like Smile Pre-Cure
Let's Go Marching World
that's what it's called. Madagascar 3
and Wan Nyan
Dobutsu Buyan 2
Sorry that's not a Nyan
cat game, it just happens to have that in the name
but there is a cat and a dog in it
I think it's like a pet dog
Wan Nyan
Midnight Maximum Tune
or something like that
A crazy drift racing
Nyan cat
Starring Tunes is the driving cat
This actually looks
super cute. It looks like a pet
hospital kind of game because the front cover
has all this guy
and ladies in lab long white
coats that you'd see veterinarians wear
and it's all kitties and puppies
and that guy in the back
Oh my god this is perfect
Shane if you're listening you need to see this
Dude in the back with blue hair holding a corgi
That's like
It's Shane personified right there
I'm going to send him a link to this in case he's listening
Alright
Moving on
I'm sorry I'm busy calibrating
Who are you? Garris?
Let's do UK releases
Okay well in the UK
I'm going to have to reload the page but on the 30th
we have Orcs Must Die
and now I have to go back
to the top of the page and load it next month
So
They freaking changed how
their things work so whatever
Um
Where's fucking August
Fuck. Okay August
I can't help it
Stop judging me
Okay on August 1st
Deadlight and Puddle
On August 3rd Risen 2
Dark Waters and then that's all and if there's anything else
I don't care
Sorry
folks overseas but Dark Soccer doesn't
care. No that's all that
Eurogamer told me there was
Alright a couple more news stories
I couldn't be bothered
A couple more news stories for you guys and then
the classic game of the week we're going to take a trip down
memory lane and revisit a game from the past
that you should check out
because Dark Soccer told you to
but first a couple more news stories
In this case because Dan told me to tell you to
Okay. Alright so apparently GameStop
CEO Paul Rains
He made a comment regarding
the possibility of a used
digital
downloads
format. Basically
the whole
lawsuit that happened in the UK
kind of set an interest
well it didn't really set a precedent but it was interesting
that they kind of favored
towards that that you should be able to get
refunds for used games
when you're done using them
Basically calling and saying
interesting. It's not a
meaningful business yet
Right now we're not seeing
that as a huge market but I think
we're on the leading edge. There are a few companies
a few startups out there that we
talked to that are doing this
and of course they just purchased
Impulse which is
originally from Stardock
and they kind of have a similar service
on there where you can
use it as
goo to create used
PC licenses for different
games
and they say no we don't see
a lot of interest in the model from our publishing
partners
but definitely something
that they're interested in looking at when
that time comes. I guess it makes sense
if everything is going to go digital and stuff
and they do eventually have a
way to revoke licenses which would be
pretty cool. I mean especially some of the
stuff I have on like steam
and stuff if I could sell some of the
things that you know I'm not playing
and I got in some of these indie bundles that would be
kind of cool
to trade it in for
other things
but of course you know if it
has anything to do with used game sales they're probably
all over it. Do you think this could
work? It could work but
it involves all the
publishers having to agree on that kind of thing and that's
kind of basically green to
having a used marketplace and isn't
that what they're kind of trying to get rid of already
so that's
I don't think that this is ever
going to
hit full force
anytime soon. There's a part
of me that thinks a system like
this is just begging to be hacked
like I kind of
think they might try to implement well then again
I don't know steam works alright like
they haven't been able to hack steam right
but I don't know something like this
just seems like
it's begging to be worked around
there's ways to hack game not that I'm saying
you should do it but it definitely is one of the
things that's got to be giving publishers pause
I just think a lot of these systems are
going to be closed and then the
other thing too is like say I
have a PS3 game or something like that and I want
to trade my digital copy in for something
what if I want to get a 360 game with that
or am I going to be able to do that? The system is going to be
separate and you have different rules I mean there's a whole
lot of things going in
going on there and it's just
that's probably why this isn't
they're trying to get rid of used game sales they're not
going to try to all of a sudden say hey
yeah we're going to go digital but we're
bringing used games back that's not going to happen
I mean come on they're doing this to get people
to buy new games in the first place
they're not going to all of a sudden
flip a 180 and just say hey
by the way used games are awesome
no it's not going to happen
alright one more story for you guys here
before the classic game of the week and it has to do
with Final Fantasy 14
yes we do want to do a little
reporting on Final Fantasy 14 because
you know very interesting
MMO this is a I mean
it wasn't that great when it came out
let's be real if you played it on PC especially
when it first came out it was a really
crap game there have been
improvements since it first launched
and they're promising even more before
the big launch on Playstation 3
later this year well they now
are officially calling it
Final Fantasy 14
A Realm Reborn that is
the version 2.0 of the game
that's going to be coming out later this year
I don't think it's coming out later this year
oh really? yeah
I have a TBA 2013
date right now for it really
well they did put out a trailer
this week I haven't even watched this
trailer yet but I'm told there's no
gameplay in it it's just CGI
really Final Fantasy trailer no gameplay
in it I know right but color me shocked
apparently a lot of this has to do
with like
it's basically Final Fantasy
14 Cataclysm to put
I mean look you can see we're watching
the trailer here and you can probably hear a little bit of the audio
coming through the feed but we're
looking at you know missiles flying from the
sky and basically destroying
things you see all these like warriors
suiting up and putting up shields but it's
very obvious the world is being hit
so that tells me that's their
you know just like they did in World of Warcraft
that's their way to
change the look of the world and so
forth but I gotta say you know
the CGI heavy or not
it looks great
of course the original trailer for 14 looked
awesome I remember that original
trailer at E3 gave me chills
just because I spent so many years with
Final Fantasy 11 I was like legit that
excited and then when I played the game
I had different type of chills so cold
so cold it's so bad
why is this allowed to be released
he touched me in a dirty place
but see that looks pretty rad doesn't it
I don't know
I'm just looking here at the end I'm trying to see if there's actually a date
nope coming soon
I don't have a date coming soon to PlayStation 3
and PC December 31st
2013 is what the placeholder
date is right now which means
TVA 2013
if it's TVA 2012 then yeah maybe later this year
Akuma JP
says Meteo maybe
that's a reference to what you might be seeing
there in the trailer very interesting thought
Monty Boggs says Final Fantasy
the new 52
in parentheses online players
via PlayStation 3
I see what you did there
yeah Akuma JP is putting it
together saying there's a red meteor in the sky
so he thinks it's gonna involve Meteo
I gotta say
Final Fantasy 14 at least the look of it
fits in very well with the series
it's just kinda you know
the game was kinda crap
Final Fantasy 11
a game report into Final Fantasy
version 2
alright look let's take a step
back to a time when games are a lot more simple
they weren't so flashy
there was no CGI trailer for this game
we're about to talk about and if there had been
it would have been all kinds of awesome
Dark Sakura
is gonna step into the vault as she always
does and she'll go
this is crunchy
and this will say Dan
game
and get a classic game of the week
suggestion Dark Sakura what is this
classic game of the week? Roadblasters
good pick
yeah I know
it's an arcade game that came out by Atari
games in 1987
when I was still in
middle school
basically
it is a game where you drive
a sports car through 50 different
rally races and you have to get to the end
without running out of fuel
so you have to complete all 50 of those
races
you can basically have as many vehicles
as you want to complete the rally
but you have to have gas
in the arcade
the Sega
and the Lynx version
you could start the game
at a higher rally and get more
opportunities to jump levels
and you can continue the game from where
you left off but you only have
one chance to complete the 50th and
final rally
so you have four ways that you can get in this game
by green globes, red globes, a checkpoint
and the rally point
green globes are on the road and they fill
your main tank, red globes
are getting by shooting enemies
on the road and after
you complete the rally you get an extra
fuel reserve depending on how many
enemies you destroyed
so you get fuel by blowing shit up
each consecutive kill shot increases
your multiplier one up to ten
and this lowers your multiplier by one
so whatever your multiplier
is that when you cross the line
you get
that much fuel
so
excuse me, I just finished my coffee
wow girl, shut up
it's your coffee
like I said you have
a checkpoint, a midway point
where
when you cross that line you actually get
the amount of fuel in the main tank restored
to what it was at the beginning of the rally
but your reserve
tank is not restored so it's just basically
like you get a quick
fill up, quick fill up
so you've got different cars in there, you have the stingers
which are orange, command cars
which are purple, they have bulletproof bumpers
and must be killed by a cruise missile
or an electro shield, you have cycles
rat jeeps, they come in from the left
stop it and swerve to the right, so basically
they're like knights in chess
gun turrets, you have mines
on the road, you cannot destroy
them but you get alarms that let you
know where they are, and toxic
spills, you get special weapons
you get the UZ cannon
it's a rapid fire gun that does not
deplete your multiplier
but they have limited ammo, you have a cruise
missile which kaboom you get three missiles
a nitro inject
which increases your speed from 210
to 298
kilometers per hour
electro shield
which lets you drive through the enemy
unharmed for a short distance and you get three
to a pack
they wanted
though, now this is a little bit of
information about the production which actually this little bit
I did not know
the creators wanted to have an electronic
version of Mr. Sandman
to play on one of the levels
but they never put it in
that's kind of weird
no, this is weird
it had a promo with the original arcade game
where you can send in your score when all 50 levels
are completed to get a free road
blasters t-shirt
it had a toy tie-in by Matchbox
so you get die-cast cars
that can be customized with armor
lasers, machine guns, rocket launchers
and jet engines, there were the
turbo force and the motor boards
during the gameplay you would get
a slightly robotic sounding female voice
that gives you advice
and it has different phrases
including hit it and eat
lead road hog
and when you use your nitro inject
you get, now that's cruising
a guy with a last name that I can't pronounce
I'm guessing it's a Polish name
Stan Szczepanski
holds the
official Guinness World Record
for roadblaster
at 2,216,120 points
if you beat this
we'll give you some air
and that's it, roadblasters
alright
good classic game of the week, I remember
many bowling alley trips to play
roadblasters, among other things
alright, let me shut up
ok, be quiet roadblasters, we're done with you
for now, alright
we're gonna take a quick break guys
we're not done, we're just gonna take a little break
to rest ourselves, bathroom break
and what have you, more coffee for dark soccer
no, break or whatever she might need
garris break
we will be back though in about 6 minutes
or if you're listening to us on the podcast
we'll be back in like 6 seconds
with more of Orange Lounge Radio
and of course we got the rapid fire news
we've got your phone calls
your tweets, your emails
and lord knows what else
from Marissa
in just about 6 minutes
here live at the VOG
network, the voice of geeks network
we'll be back after
this with more of Orange Lounge Radio, don't go anywhere
welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge
Radio, the show where every gamer has
a voice, we are live here on
July the 29th of 2012
with the 467th episode of our show
already in progress
big night tonight
I was laughing so hard
in part A that it hurts, if you have no idea
what I'm talking about
I guess you'll have to tune in to the podcast later
which Marissa will not be plugging on her Facebook
just for the record
but Marissa is in studio joining us tonight
and hopefully above all else
having a good time, I hope so
not just
Marissa having a good time with our show
but the folks participating in
PlayStation Home Summerfest
the fan event going on
right now, we are in the Aurora
1.5 space, but to make sure
you're in the right instance
you do want to make sure you follow somebody
there, I think Home Event Bot
is no longer in there if I was looking
correctly earlier, but you could
follow Black Wolf, he is in
there right now, and so
am I
Green Sky with IE
at the end, you can follow either one of us
into the appropriate event space
there, it looks like Tiger Claw is in there as well
so hopefully you can follow a friend
into PlayStation Home
it has thinned out a little bit
it is getting later and later on the east coast
some people have some other things to do tonight
but to all of you that are still there dancing
and chatting along there
a big thank you to staying up
late with us here at the Voice of
Geeks Network and listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Black Wolf is in
VoG chat and he's
in the PlayStation Home space right
now saying, they are bubbling me in Home
now, I don't want to know what that means
what about bubbling somebody
isn't it? I don't know
is it what the floor was doing?
no, the floor makes those pretty effects
alright, I'm being told to pick a number
between 1 and 100
and say it on the air for another
Blender giveaway, he was awesome enough
to give something away during
R
the letter R will not work
he was awesome enough to give something away during the Bobby Black Wolf show
and he's giving something away now, who knows what it could be
but I will let the lovely Marissa
she's here tonight, pick that number between
1 and 100, Marissa what's it going to be?
3, she's low balling it
alright, 1 and 100
please don't make any references to balls with me after the first one
balls Marissa?
Marissa, 3 balls?
really?
alright, 3 it is, that's the magic number
good luck, hope it's you
I don't know what that's
going to pick, but Blender will let us know
alright, meanwhile
we're going to get back
into some rapid fire news
and some quick news stories
and then the FUGL question of the week
and I'll explain that for those that are new to the show
I do want to once again welcome any new
listeners who you might have this week because of Summerfest
or whatever, if you don't know Orange Lounge
Radio, we've been around for 10 years, believe it or not
we started the show back in
2002, in June
of 2002, it was back
then, a show we created
in support of the
music gaming community
especially games like Dance Dance Revolution
Beatmania, Bust a Move
or Bust a Groove, depending on what country you're from
that whole series
everything music game related
especially DDR was the big arcade game
Dark Soccer, Loki and myself
all met playing DDR, if you can believe it
at a place called Golfland
or, you know, sometimes we'd
go to the bowling alley, or we'd drive all the way
to Stockton, Loki, remember
we'd drive all the way to Stockton Golfland
to play DDR Fifth Mix when they had that
but as the years went on
we decided, you know what, yes we love DDR
but we love all video games as well
and our show became about all video games, especially
the community, because the style of our show
has always been
you know, we would do these arcade
nights where we play DDR, and then we'd go
to a restaurant called Brookfields
a local place here afterwards, and
just have dinner and talk shit about things we
liked and didn't like, and that's kind of
the atmosphere we bring to the show
is we literally sit around a big table
and talk some shit, but you guys get to
talk with us in the chat room
via Skype, via the mailbag
and all of that good stuff
and we really do care about what you guys have to say
and that's why we call it a show where every gamer
has a voice. Anyhow
alright, after that little reintroduction
just for the folks new to our show tonight
let's go to some rapid fire news
and talk some shit, Loki
I'm good at that, you know, talking
shit and stuff, so let's talk about
one of my games that I'm very
happy about, Grand Theft Auto 3
coming back to the
Playstation on the Playstation Network
has a downloadable title
and it will be coming this Tuesday
and that is the first
of the kind of
Playstation 2
Grand Theft Auto games, so pretty awesome
it's gonna be 10 bucks, so check that out
if you can
or if you're like me, just buy the old copy
because I have an original Playstation 3
rub it in, rub it in, rub it in
so I can play my original copy of
Grand Theft Auto San Andreas
with hot coffee
can't wait, you know what I'm waiting for
speaking of Grand Theft Auto, aside from 5
where the fuck is Retro City Rampage?
I want that game now
supposed to be this summer
question mark
and then completely
off topic
I watched some video in 1080p
from our Activision rep for
Black Ops 2, I need that
game now
that is a sexy game
we went and saw, I didn't talk about this during my gaming week
because it's not really a game, but we finally went and saw Batman
on Tuesday, and they played a
trailer for that, they played
a video game trailer before the movie, which I thought was
interesting, it wasn't like a
you know how movie theaters do this now
I'm sure every movie theater in America does this now
like you go to the movie and
before the trailer starts, there's just the
20 minutes of basically commercials
that they call like, what is it, First Look
or the 20 or something where it's just
it's just commercials
get here early and see our
ads, yeah you consumer whore
and they were
showing a trailer for that Modern Warfare 2
and Alan
leans over to me and goes, this looks bad
this doesn't look good, and I'm like
it's a shoot em game, honey, you wouldn't like it
it's a great game, he doesn't know what he's
talking about
no seriously, the new one's actually being
kind of ties in with Batman because it's being written
by the guy that did
yes, I was in the ads
it looks good, there's some new
stuff that they're adding
it'll be the first Modern Warfare game
that I'm actually going to get at launch
I'm finally caught up
except it's not really Modern Warfare
I mean it's Future Warfare
anyways, so let's talk a little bit about
arcade games, and I actually have
Double Fish on my arcade cabinet
I haven't really played a whole ton of it
but I have it emulated
and it was a game
that was on Sammy's
Autonomous Wave
Autonomous Wave arcade
hardware, they had a lot of other stuff like
Dolphin Blue and stuff
and it was a fighting game, it was pretty awesome
well, Dimps
the company behind it
I guess, picked up the rights to it and now
they're going to be re-releasing it on
consoles
not consoles, I'm sorry, arcades
and they're bringing Rumble Fish 2
to arcades
which was
in 2005, and now it's coming back
and I guess
it's on this new
Nesica Live
or Nesica Cross Live
it's a
not a streaming platform, but it's a
platform where arcade
owners
can actually download
games to cabinets
digital download of arcade games
I'm surprised
that's only just now becoming a thing
because that makes an awful lot of sense
I forgot a shoutout I wanted to do at Start A Part B
I'm so sorry, this is so important
I'm so pissed I didn't get to go this year
I mean, I just, juggling priorities
California Extreme
was this weekend, and I got
sent pictures and video
and apparently they had a full on
Chuck E. Cheese animatronic, I don't know if it was Chuck E. Cheese
but one of the likes, animatronic band
that would sit there and creepily play songs
cause I got sent a video of one
that's awesome, so I mean
you never really think of that cause there's a lot of Chuck E. Cheese's
that have closed down
or just upgraded and stuff
I hope I didn't get that wrong
but it's that style
I would love to have the old
Bullwinkles stuff
maybe that's what this is, I don't know, anyway
I'm gonna hand that to Marissa, hit play
so that Loki can see it too
that way you guys can kind of check that out
that's why it was sent from California Extreme
and they're singing
Total Eclipse of the Heart
that is pretty amazing
I was sent
Neil sent that there
I would just put that out in my front yard
all year round
he had a animatronic band
it's Halloween, put a fucking
pumpkin in front of them
it's Christmas, put
Santa hats on them
so shout out to California Extreme
I'm so sorry I couldn't make it this year
the shadow casting was this weekend too
it would only make that thing better
if they would fucking just
totally get some
brick rolling going on there
never gonna give you up
oh boy
anyway, so we're at
Rebel Fish
I think it's pretty cool that they have arcade hardware
you can download games for
if it wasn't so expensive, I'd buy some
arcade hardware I could download games to
well, I have arcade hardware I guess I could download games to
not entirely legally
but you know
still, that's a cool idea
I guess
alright
and then of course, this is kind of cool
I know a game that we kind of liked
a while back
Puzzle Quest, they put out a couple games
and kind of disappeared
but now Puzzle Quest is coming back
apparently this is kind of
because
Firemint, the company that
put out the game
I guess they
or they just
Firemint is now
putting out the game because they purchased
Infinite Interactive, which was the original creator of the game
and so now it's
coming back
Puzzle Quest 2 is pretty awesome, it was on like every system out there
and I'm not talking about the galactic one
that didn't do so well
but Puzzle Quest 2 is really good
Puzzle Quest is a pretty cool game
I wasn't a fan of the galactic one but
I would be, I'd be down for more
of the old Puzzle Quest
heck yeah
alright I got a few stories for you guys as well
or Puzzle Pirates, I'd be down for that too on consoles
Puzzle Pirates, Puzzle Pirates
you can do Puzzle Pirates on Steam
for what it's worth, it's free to play MMO right now
you didn't know that?
yeah, it's on Steam
yeah, but no one's playing it anymore
they will play it if you will play it Logie
we will be Puzzle Pirates together
alright, I got a couple stories for you guys here
first one is about
Super, or excuse me, New Super Mario
Brothers 2, did you know I had a
working title called New Super Mario
Brothers Gold, in fact that was
supposed to be the name, and you know they've kind of
been saying this a lot, this is, even at E3
when they were talking about it, what does Mario
love more than anything? Gold coins
and this new game's all about coins
well, apparently
it was about
excuse me, it was
it was so much a part of the game
that it was originally going to be
called New Super Mario
Brothers Gold, but
yeah, they went back and called it New Super Mario Brothers 2
but they were worried too many people would think it's just
you know, a cheapy, or a cheap
cash-in on the first one
of the first one, yeah, but hey, switching
out gold and putting two in there, that totally
you know, gets rid of the whole
thought that it's a cheap cash-in on the first one
it's now about, it's all about the coins
now, Loki
oh yeah, it's all about that, it's totally
different than the last game
alright, a
comment from Crytek is our next story
about the Wii U
you know, we've been getting more and more developers commenting
on this, producer Mike Reed
mentioned that
Crytek is talking about working with
Nintendo, a version of Crysis 3
for Wii U should not
be ruled out, he would not
confirm if it's in development
or not, but it's sounding pretty
likely, and here's a quote
from ComputerVideoGames.com
I wouldn't say there's no chance
I wouldn't say no chance, I mean the Wii U
still doesn't have any kind of release date
attached to it at this point, who knows what the
future will bring with it, I can definitely say
that we are working with Nintendo, and that's about all
I can say on that front, I wouldn't rule it
out, but there really has been no official releases
associated with the Wii U yet, and
given that we're releasing Crysis in an 8 month
time period in February of 2013
we can't play off of what their
schedules are, I wouldn't rule it out, but you know
it's a possibility.
I mean come on, their
hardware is pretty much
on par with the current consoles, it's
not that hard to port that over, I mean
they're porting other games over, so
yes, of course there's gonna be that
I think what the stipulation is
gonna be, you know, what's Nintendo require
from these people putting out stuff
for their platform, are they making them
hey, you gotta have some unique gameplay that
involves their tablet, and
them figuring out, well, how are we going
to
fit this
tablet gameplay into
Crysis 3?
One more story about
the Nintendo Wii, with no
U attached to it,
apparently some retailers are out of stock
right now on the Wii, GameStop,
Target apparently reported some of them
have the console back ordered,
some Best Buys and so forth are just now
getting stock in again. Here's the thing
though, most people are drawing from
this that either Nintendo's about to do a new
holiday bundle, so they're trying to get rid of what's on
shelves now, or this is
in preparation for the Wii U, they
might be trying to clean out the old stuff a little bit
to make room for the Wii U.
Loki, any insider thoughts
from your perspective?
I haven't seen a lot of demand for the systems,
I would think if they're trying to clear out
the stock that they wouldn't be on back order,
they would be in
plentiful supply because they're trying to
get rid of them. I don't think that they
have a problem with, I don't think Nintendo's sitting
on consoles right now,
it could just be that they're
just switching production from
you know,
who knows how long, I'm assuming
that they've got to start producing these consoles,
so maybe they're starting to switch
over some of those manufacturers that are doing
the Wii to making the Wii U
system instead, just to get prepared.
Before we get to Dark
Sakura's stories, let me talk
some comments from our chat room at
live.vognetwork.com
Tigerclaw says, you know with all those gold coins
Mario has collected, you think he would use those
coins to build a high end security to protect
Princess Peach?
Gameguru says, why isn't Wario the villain here?
He loves coins.
And we have an update from Bobby Blackwolf at
PlayStation Home Summerfest, going on right
now in Aurora 1.5 space,
saying that the random
number contest ended up being
that you had to use the random number
action, and whoever hit 3,
Marissa's number first, won a
gift from the Lockwood gift machine, and
the winner was GTIVW1975.
So congrats!
A clap for you.
Golf clap.
Golf clap. Golf clap.
Alright.
Let's move on, Dark Sakura.
Well we have a few goodies.
What we have is Little Big Planet 2
getting Disney Princess
edition, where they all look
kind of bizarre.
But I think everything in Little Big Planet
looks bizarre. So there's two different
DLC packs. One of them, like I said,
is the Disney Princesses.
The costume pack one has
Aurora, Cinderella, Jasmine, and Snow White.
And then the second one is Belle,
Tiana, Rapunzel, and
Ariel. Yay.
Then,
we have some information
about Dance Central 3.
We have
the songs
that are going to be out on it.
As some of these people
I really do not know who they are.
I'm assuming some of them I do.
To anyone, whoever the fuck that is,
I am the best. We have Alice DJ,
Better Off Alone, fucking love that song.
Backstreet Boys,
JJ Fad,
Lil Jon,
Eastside Boys featuring Nyan Nyan Twins,
whatever.
LMFAO, Lost Del Rio,
we have
Maroon 5 with moves like Jagger.
I actually really like that song.
We have Ice Ice Baby.
We have Vicky Sue Robinson,
Turn the Beat Around, and Village People
YMCA.
Whatever happened to Alice DJ?
That was like my college
years right there. Alice DJ is Better Off Alone.
Apparently.
And then, last but
never least, the Nintendo 3DS
XL UK
price.
This is going to be $179.99.
Again, that's in
pounds.
Tesco's, however, will be offering
the device for
175.
So, you want it cheap, get it at
Tesco's.
Game, one more,
has a trade-in deal that for $79.99
you can trade in an old boxed
3DS and
get the 3DS XL.
So that's it.
Not bad. Not bad. Not bad.
Alright.
Moving on, we have a segment
we always do here on Orange Lawns Radio
called the Fugal Question of the Week.
You might be asking yourself,
what the hell is a Fugal?
Put Facebook
and Google Plus together
and you get Fugal. That is what it is.
We ask a question each week in our Facebook
and Google Plus communities
and you guys answer it. Here's this week's question.
There's a couple betas
going on right now, including Guild Wars 2,
Little Big Planet Karting, and
Sony PlayStation All-Stars Battle Royale,
just to name a few. Have you
ever made a decision whether or not
to buy a game based off the beta?
Considering that betas are
unfinished products, do you think that
it was a fair decision
or should a company not put it out there
if it's not ready to be judged?
I thought it was a good question
not just because I thought of it.
So let's get to some of these comments
here. I want to
start with Google
Plus tonight.
And yes, there are people posting on Google Plus.
My quick impression of Google Plus.
Hello! Hello!
No, we have
two comments from Google Plus
tonight. There's
at least two people using Google Plus.
Some weeks we get four.
All right, Reddertainment says
no, but I did buy
cakes prolonging the magic after
listening to Alpha Beta Parking Lot,
which I...is he plugging something?
I don't know what the...
had nothing to do with the question, sir.
However, Flaco Jones responded
saying, I knew after playing all the
starting areas in the Final Fantasy 14 beta
that it wasn't worth buying.
I do think that was a fair decision
since the game came out a month later
and was reportedly as bad as the beta
was. Yeah, that was
a beta that ended up being pretty accurate
I gotta say. Good reminder
Flaco Jones.
Going to Facebook for some of the comments from Facebook.
Amanda, Amanda R says
I've played in betas that were out only
a couple weeks before game release
and by this time, these are mostly
finished products with only minor tweaks
being made. I have made the decision
to not buy a game when it came out because
the beta was just not fun and with
that close to the release, not
enough changes were going to be made to change the game
in any significant way.
Cody T says, I've played betas of
a million games and I think I've bought
most. I think betas are more for the
developer than for the consumer. It's a cheap
way to see exactly what is wrong with the game
by the best judge, us.
And it's a way for the gamer to be involved in the actual
development of the game.
Nick M. responds
saying, I believe a public or
large closed beta is the only responsible
decision for game companies if their game
relies heavily on multiplayer
due to the large number of, excuse me
large amount of problems that will often
otherwise show their head on launch day.
However, more often than not, betas
talk me out of buying games that I'm already
on the fence about.
Boschka responded
and said, yes, the only game
I have ever done it for is a game that's
actually free when it comes out.
Path of Exile. Think Diablo 2 and new features
and updated graphics. I donated
$10 not only to get a second beta
key for a friend, but because I love
what they're doing with that game. If I could get more
I would. Blizzard just take some
notes on how to make a good action RPG.
Ooh, sick burn.
I think it's fair. People
have to learn what a beta is for. It's not
a demo. You're testing buggy code.
You're testing builds that are normally
four to five builds behind what the devs
have. Some games basically require
betas based on the sheer size. For example,
in the Mists of Pandaria beta
they changed one ability for a
boss fight and the next thing you know there's an
elevator coming out of the ground on another continent.
If the company says before
that it's not a demo, it's a beta, I think
that is completely fair. If you don't get the
difference, you're not the type of tester they want anyway.
A long but good comment from
Boschka.
Let's see.
Wicked says, I believe betas are an
integral part of games development.
It gives the fan base an inside look at
what is to come and also gives
the developers instant public feedback to
work out any bugs the game may have.
However, game companies should be wary
about using open betas as it sometimes
gives the gaming community expectations
they may not have had before, positive
or negative.
Sometimes the game does not live up to the
over-hype that sometimes follows certain
open betas or some good games
could easily be overlooked due to
negative reactions to betas. So
while betas can easily help a game's
development, it could easily skew the game's
anticipation in the public eye.
And lastly, Chiggers
responds saying, I've bought games based on
the demos. Does that count?
Kind of. Demos
are a little different than betas. I think
kind of going back to the other points, like betas
are put out there
because they're not supposed to be demos. They're
supposed to be tests for the developers. But
kind of where I was trying to go with the question
is that a lot of people look at betas as
demos in this day and age. Is that fair?
Or should the developers be real
and realize that's how most people
are going to view it? Anyhow,
thanks for all those answers on Facebook at
facebook.com slash orange lounge radio.
I didn't read them all
so please go check out the post to read
some of the other great insights from
this week. Really appreciate it guys. Sorry
I couldn't read them all, but it's only
a three hour show.
Alright.
Oh, by the way, XLink
giving me the update in our chat
room at live dot vog network dot com.
Here's what happened to Alice DJ.
Quote,
after the group went their
separate ways, Prank decided
to move on to other ventures by putting her
music career aside to become a makeup
artist and beauty fashion consultant.
I remember
the video. She was a
very hip looking gal. I remember
that. They actually had like two
videos for that song, Better Off Alone.
Anyhow, well, I learned something
tonight about Alice DJ. Who knew?
I've learned about pornography
and I've learned about Alice DJ. Who
knew? Marissa's
hiding her head. This is adorable.
Loki,
what do you got for us next in
other gaming news?
Alright, so let's talk a little
bit about
you know, rock band. And this is kind of funny
because I don't know
if you guys remember, a couple months back we had a
scare where, hey, guess what?
You know rock band that you purchased
on IOS and stuff like that?
It's being delisted. It's being taken away.
And you know that game you just
purchased? Well, now it's going to be completely useless
because you're not going to
be able to get anything anymore for it.
It's just, it's going to be gone.
Well, and you may remember
that they came out and said, oh, no, no, no.
That's not happening. That message was
sent in error. Well, the error was that
it was sent two months early.
Because now, yes, they are actually
delisting the game.
Well, I don't think people were mad
that the game was being delisted. I mean,
whatever. People are pissed if it wouldn't
work anymore. That was the
original, like, scare campaign going around is that
haha, you just bought this game and none of
your DLC or anything is going to work anymore.
LOL, bye. You know,
but that doesn't appear to be the case. I mean,
if they're just pulling it from the store, then whatever.
Well, they're pulling basically the
rock band, um, IOS game
and rock band reloaded IOS game
and all the, um, I think
all the DLC for it as well.
Yes, you will not be able
to purchase any more DLC for it.
So,
and that's supposed to happen effective
July 31st.
So, a couple days from now.
Well, yeah.
As a musician, like,
yeah, um,
which, I'm sorry,
I'm actually just being unemployed.
But,
with regard to the, um,
the music games, it's actually, especially
guitar players, like, games like Guitar Hero,
especially at the time, it was at its height,
really enraged.
You know, musicians, they got so angry,
especially since a lot of people were misinformed
and they, you know, you,
I even heard a lot of people
ignorantly at GameStop believing that it could teach
you how to play guitar. However,
um, I ended up, um,
my friend's mother ended up winning a free copy
of Rocksmith, so we played it.
And, um, that was actually one where you, uh,
they gave you, you know, an XLR cable, and you actually,
you could actually plug in your guitar to the Xbox.
And that actually was a pretty good game, and then
actually, I mean, you plug in your own guitar to it, and that actually,
um, I had
guitar players play it, and they actually found it challenging
and interesting, and it actually, you know,
accurately, you know, presented theory and things like that.
You know, I'm glad you said that.
And you don't, you didn't
know this before you said that, but I usually have to
refrain from comment on that game, because
a really good friend of mine knows somebody
that's a big part of the development of that
game, so I usually don't try
to avoid the topic on the show because of
conflict, but, uh, I'm glad you said that.
I'm sure that'll make somebody very happy to know that.
Yeah, I didn't get that far into
the game, but I mean, I enjoyed it, and I think
that, um, you know,
it's not gonna turn you into a virtuoso,
but I mean, um, you know,
if you're too cheap to go, to go get lessons
immediately, it's a good place to start, just to get, like,
a very basic foundation, and it's fun.
Yeah, I understand that game does
have kind of quite a bit of, like, a cultish
audience, I don't know what it sounds like, but, like,
a lot of the makeup of, I
think, who's into that game is kind of like people
who are rediscovering
getting into music maybe at a later age.
Like, it's not like kids and teenagers
and so forth playing it that rock band
tends to skew towards, like college parties and stuff,
but, like, Rocksmith is, like, 30-somethings
who always wanted to learn to play
an instrument that never did.
I wish that they had, um, I guess it didn't be
That's my impression, it's not, like, just my impression of it.
I, um, I guess it didn't, you know,
my understanding is, you know, it didn't
blow up, necessarily, but, I mean, I wish
that they had a, um,
a wider, um, library
of music, you know, it started to when it came
out, they started releasing stuff all the time, but I wish it had
more, you know, but, you know, that's just selfishly
excited, you know, it'd be fun to play.
Well, they do DLC pretty regularly.
And you're in luck, because they have Rocksmith
and Bass, or Guitar and
Bass coming out, uh, this October.
You don't need a game
You don't need a game to teach you bass, no.
I'm kidding.
I'm kidding, actually.
It does require
talent. Just not a lot.
You don't have to be a
retarded monkey.
No, actually, though, I have friends like
Freebo. I have friends who are excellent bass players.
And all the running musicians joke, making fun of
bass players. Good times,
good times.
It's just, are you a fan of Green Day?
Like, I like Green Day,
but let's be real, a lot of their songs are kind of like
the same chord over and over, and it cracked
me up, because he was sitting there, he's
gonna be the guy that's lead singer in the band
is gonna be one of the, not like a judge,
but like a mentor or something on The Voice.
But he's working with Christina
Aguilera. And I don't know why,
but I found that to be like the funniest thing I'd heard
all week. Okay. You're not gonna
appreciate this, but any other
musicians listening to this
and the
band that now
knows my embarrassing past that I've told
to tune into will appreciate this.
Green Day is
kind of like the Creedence Clearwater
of their time.
I know that sounds obtuse,
but there's always this joke that like
Creedence Clearwater songs and John Fogerty's songs
only require three chords to play.
And that is essentially, I mean, there is
something to be said about, you know, Green Day's later
artistic merit, you know, and there are things
to be appreciated about it, but
do I think that they should be
held in that high of a regard?
No. Well, I'm not a member
of the cult though, you know.
I appreciate some of the things that they've done,
but I'm not a cult member or anything.
You know, and it's amazing where they've come, you know,
singing songs about acne and masturbation
to
guitars that were out of tune.
To like commentary on President Bush and so
forth, and that Broadway play.
They've come so, oh god.
Rissa, you alright over there?
I feel like, you know, like
Green Day songs with, you know,
Fosse moves.
Uh,
Stan in our chat rooms, you are
spurring some music discussion in our chat rooms.
Stan says, same with Hansen.
Bop is only three chords.
They didn't even have three hits.
They had like 30
babies between them all though.
The girl in Hansen's
pretty cute.
No, they're actually all from evangelicals.
That means Justin Bieber
is like the Hansen of our
time, basically.
Justin Bieber has his own video game now too.
Oh god, I hope not.
People don't understand. Teenage girls
are stupid. I said this is
a former teenage girl.
As one who was once
a teenage girl. I was there, I was there.
I have authority on this subject.
I do. I mean, granted,
I never had bop posters on my wall
or anything. No, no, no, no, no, dear.
This is what you get for being younger than me.
I had new kids on the block.
Everyone can shut up.
I was, the kids
in my school called Victoria.
So,
so I was very much the
anti that, but the thing that people don't get
about this, and of course, yes, it's interesting
how the media will exploit everything when it comes
to a tween star like this, including
the areas of video games and apps
and all this crap, but it's just
just, they just
found a boy to fill
the slot of cute teenage boys
singing songs to seduce, it could
have been anyone, you know. They just,
you just put him in the spot and they put the marketing
movement behind him and done.
It could have been anybody. It had nothing to do with
who Justin Bieber is. Nothing.
Sorry. It fascinates me at what musicians
get movies, too.
Like, Justin Bieber
gets his movie at like the Megaplex and so forth
and then fucking Katy Perry
has this big,
uh oh, uh oh.
I just opened Pandora's box.
If Katy Perry
gets her own movie,
I should have, you know,
my own, you know, like quadruple
sequel and then mini
series and TV shows.
Let's face it, she got the movie
because of her titties, okay?
I mean, she has some cute
songs, blah, blah, blah, but mainly it's because
she's beautiful, you know, and people
like talking about her boobies, apparently.
So, that's why she- And Elmo.
So, I deserve my own series.
You should be a Star Trek next to that.
You should be like four TV
series, what is it, like
nine movies and fanfic.
If her movies alone get her
a movie, I deserve so much more.
But then, here's
what fascinates me, like, yeah,
Katy Perry has some catchy songs, whatever.
When you're drunk at a gay bar, you
don't care. Oh, Katy Perry, I love her!
You know? She's a big marketing team
too. But, I mean, she's kind of a tool.
But then, you have, like,
LCD sound system had, like,
their big, you know, farewell thing and all that
and like, what did they get? They got
like, they got a Fathom event.
They got like, their movies
like one night only at the local
cinema.
Life is not fair. Before the Metropolitan
Opera, you know, movie theater
night, you know?
Poor guys. Alright.
Anyhow.
ActDeft in our chatroom says, Marissa
the movie 2, electit boobaloo.
That should be the name of your next album.
Alright, moving
on.
That's how Katy Perry sells shit, I can do it too.
You just,
you gotta get out of the little affair
and get into the pop music.
All I need is some vocorder and some autotune.
Just whine about a boy who broke up with you
years ago or something, you know?
Just sing about Dave Coulier.
You know?
Insult the women that actually are gay
and can't help it and pretend to be a lesbian
and, you know, to amuse men.
It's great. Get in a
pillow fight, braid somebody's hair.
Oh my god!
Free someone's bra. We used to do
that dip of bra and orange juice and put it in the freezer
for the first girl who fell asleep.
Yes.
That's hot. Keep talking. Alright.
Moving on.
Okay, this is bad.
Because we're going to go from such humorous, happy
discussions to really unfortunate
situations.
I'm about to Debbie
Downer the show a little bit.
And talk about some layoffs.
Stop laughing, Marissa.
Stop laughing, Marissa. Inappropriate.
No, this news really does
suck. Maybe we should skip
this story.
Read it already.
We need variety.
Uh oh, Marissa's choking.
Alright.
Serious face.
Microsoft laid off a
small, as they put it, number of positions
at their Vancouver based development
studio. This is because Project
Columbia, whatever this was, we
don't know what the real name was, it got
cancelled. It's off the
books now. It was supposed to be an educational
Connect title. It was going to educate
young people. It was going to pair books with
music and illustrations. I guess
it had something to do with the Sesame
Workshop as well. That doesn't necessarily
mean it was a Sesame Street game. But it
sounds like it was something that was kind of geared towards kids.
Or the like.
Wonder Book Connect.
And then they saw the Wonder Book presentation like, wow.
That looks like shit.
And then they're like, woo. Scrap that.
Perhaps. But layoffs are
never good news. Especially
also when they hit Warner Brothers. Seattle
also had some layoffs hit them this
week. They were currently working on
Lord of the Rings Guardians of Middle Earth.
And if you might be thinking to yourself, God, they're
still making Lord of the Rings games? Well,
there's a Hobbit movie coming out at the end of the year. You might have
heard of it. It's a big deal. So yeah.
Moolah moolah. Unfortunately,
not enough moolah, apparently.
Layoffs hit the studio once back in
November that was supposed to be 60 people.
And a statement from WB
says, quote, due to shifting business
imperatives, Warner Brothers Game
Seattle has made staff reductions. The
group will continue to remain an integral part of
Warner Brothers Interactive Entertainment.
Yikes. Now,
since I would like to end with a little bit of a positive,
id Software,
id Software, you know,
they made like Doom and shit.
They are actually hiring
right now. They are
hiring on their website for a
UI programmer job for, quote,
an unannounced game on future
generation consoles.
So could it be something that
is a sequel to one of the past
franchises? Possibly, because the listing
actually says, quote, familiarity with
id Software games, characters, brands,
and universes. So who knows?
It could be a new Quake. It could be a sequel
to Rage. It could be a game with
Space Marines versus either
demons or
aliens. It could be Commander Keen
6 or 7 or
whatever they're on now for all we know. So
there you go. Anyhow,
that's it for
that story. Let's move on. Dark
Soccer. Okay, well, in other
news, how about
something about that PlayStation
All-Stars crap that's coming out?
Oh, you think it's crap?
I don't know.
We're gonna, actually, we're gonna have Beta, somebody
we know very well has been in the Beta.
We're gonna have Beta impressions in a little bit.
Well, I'm not necessarily going to call it
crap. I'm gonna call it potential crap.
So, um,
there are some, uh,
people who have gone through the data
files for PlayStation All-Stars Battle
Royale and has nine
stages, eight characters, and a bunch of other
stuff. So what we have
is a Bioshock Infinite stage,
um, Sir Daniel
is it Fortesca Fortescue
from Medieval?
Dante from Devil May Cry, Spike
from Ape Escape, Raiden from Metal Gear Solid,
um, Nariko
from, uh, Heavenly Sword,
and, um,
we've got David Hayter saying he's
recording dialogue.
So, and he's, um, sorry,
he's Snake, so.
I believe all the characters that you
mentioned, but they're new characters that haven't been
released yet. Well, yeah. Well, I'm gonna go through the whole list.
This is the, the new stuff, okay?
We have Dante, Evil Cole,
um, Nariko, Raiden, Sackboy,
Ratchet and Clank, Sir Daniel
Fortescue, and Spike.
And then for items,
there's an Atomizer,
the Balmusu Axe,
Boots of Hermes,
Freeze Missile, Golf Club
from Hot Shots Golf, Gravity Shield
from Wipeout, Hedgehog, um,
Grenade, uh, the Dovat
Laser Designator,
Leech Beam, Murder of Crows
from Bioshock, uh,
Railgun, Razor Claws,
RPG, Scythe, Spear,
Sonic Rift, and Sackbot.
And then, supporting
characters, as in minions, Captain
Quark, Kai from Heavenly
Sword, Kat from Devil May Cry, Kia,
Monkey from Ape Escape,
Nyx, Pierre from
Doko Demolisho, um,
Sackbot, and Sam
from Metal Gear Rising.
And then it says, there's, like, just a bunch
of modes, but as far as stage goes,
Alden's Tower, Black Rock Stadium,
Columbia,
uh, Franzia from Locoroco,
that actually looks pretty neat. Um,
Is it Franzia boxed wine as well?
No, that's Franzia. This is
Franzia. Well, my bad.
Marissa's, Marissa and I
think alike. Paris, tip it!
Tip it, Kathleen, tip it!
We think, like, old 50-year-old. I'm sorry, I think of
Kathleen Griffin.
I do too. I have San Francisco from
Resistance, um, Stillaways from Uncharted,
Time Station from Ape Escape.
So, yeah, I'm most excited about Locoroco
stage, really.
And all these were from, hacked from files
from the beta. Yes.
Hackers gonna hack! Exactly!
People should know that by now.
Hack like what? I'm looking forward
to playing as Parappa. I think the
game looks fun. Yeah.
I, I heard, I'll let the,
the person who's gonna review the beta in a minute here,
which we just talked about, you shouldn't
do that, but hey! And that is, I believe,
against the, uh, end-user license
agreement, or the, uh, was it the, um,
confidentiality agreement?
This... We ain't the
ones gonna get sued out for it!
Ain't our asses! It's not me! It's not me
playing it! I got a special tipster.
We'll, we'll break out the,
the voice, uh,
disguiser, and the shadow,
everything for, so they aren't
identified. Well, tech,
this person's using someone else's beta.
So, it's even, like,
I know, right? A woo-woo!
Anyhow.
Um,
moving on. Loki.
I wish I was in a
beta test for that game.
Looks awesome. I try,
I was like, give me, give me the logon
and password so I can get into.
Um,
so there was a hack that was, um,
demonstrated by a Russian hacker,
uh,
using, uh,
basically a way to spoof the
iOS, or the Apple Store,
um, servers
to allow him to make
free in-app purchases.
Pretty much, um, they say,
uh, you know, he
enabled, I guess, 8.4 million
fake in-app purchases.
Over 115 games were affected,
including, um, you know,
all the big stuff, Angry Birds, Fruit Ninja,
Infinity Blade, Plants vs. Zombies,
uh, that kind of stuff. And,
um, apparently, Apple, though,
is, of course, gonna fix this. They say
the fix will check whether in-app
downloads were valid, and
fake purchases will be wiped from the
device. In other words,
it's gonna slow everything down.
So, thank you
for ruining it for everybody. Appreciate that.
Of course, you know, um, it's gonna require
that, you know, these people that publish
these apps are gonna need to update, um,
their apps with a new API for it.
Um,
I don't know how they're gonna, how's that
really gonna work? Like, say, for example, I
use that glitch or whatever,
or that exploit to purchase
a bunch of tower bucks or something in
Tiny Tower, and then I spend
all of them. How are you gonna take
that away? I mean,
I don't see how it's gonna work. I don't
think you can at that point. I don't think
for consumables like that, I don't think you can
actually do anything. I see, like,
okay, if I purchase, you know,
songs from Rock Band or something like that,
make sure that I actually purchase those
and then go from there,
but...
Maybe the game could break?
Like, if it takes you into negative tower bucks
or whatever, it just says, fuck you,
I'm out. Then the game stops
working or something. I don't know.
From what I'm aware, though, the hacker, I don't think
has released, um, the method
of how that's done, although
it's just being done, like, um,
somehow, I guess, he just spoofed
the, um, response from those
servers. Very interesting.
Hmm.
Alright, well, moving on to a different topic, this
has to do with Sonic and All-Stars
Racing Transformed. This is that Sonic
game that has all the really interesting characters,
like Danica Patrick is, like, a playable
character, and then we talked to Wreck-It Ralph,
uh, last week. Well, um,
apparently, there is, uh, an interesting comment
that was made this week. Uh, this was
by the digital, or, excuse me,
the executive producer, Steve
Lysette, who's with Sumo Digital.
Uh, he's basically implying that the
characters could be different
depending on which platform you purchased the game
on.
Why is this? Well, some platforms
have characters that are unique to that platform.
I'm not gonna say which, that's part
of the fun of the reveals. Some are
Sega characters, some are not.
Don't bother asking.
This has a lot of people speculating
that maybe the Wreck-It Ralph
will end up being a Nintendo exclusive
guy because of all
those, you know, stories about how
the Nintendo characters are the ones in the movie,
and apparently, the Wreck-It Ralph
official game is only gonna be on the Nintendo
consoles. It's kind of leading people down
those lines. We won't really know until
the rosters are revealed for all three platforms,
but, interesting speculation.
And I believe the reason why,
uh, well, the reason why it's
exclusive on the Nintendo platforms is also
they're kicking in some money for marketing as
well, um, for the Activision
game, so, it makes sense.
It does, it does.
Alright, well, let's
take a look at our
mailbag.
Music
Every week, Dark Sakura dives into the
mailbag head first and reads a few emails
for you. Mailbag at
OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Now, Dark Sakura, when you weren't here last week,
there was, like, eight emails sent to the show.
So, we only read half of them,
and we saved the other half for you. Well, there's
three that I saw.
These might be the leftovers from last week, I know.
Well, this is July 22nd, so.
Um, greetings, OLR.
It's your friendly neighborhood turtle. I just wanted to
share how much I love Steam sales, and boo
to Origin. As someone
who doesn't need many games on
release days, I always wait for the
Steam sales. I can't wait for this holiday.
If you want, please share the damage
that Steam did, um, to each of you.
Your loyal turtle and Philly series turtle.
And I think I just bought, uh,
Borderlands, that's all. We ended up, uh, actually
talking about the Steam sale last week a little bit,
so I'll, uh, kind of point you back
to that show, but Dark Sakura, that was the only
damage they did to you, was Borderlands?
Yeah, pretty much. Oh, we'll have to play together sometime.
I have to actually install it.
Marissa, you ever use Steam? I know you're not,
you're not a huge, huge gamer girl, but you,
you like the adventure games. I gotta say, Steam is
a good place to look for some of the newer stuff,
if you're into adventure games. I don't know.
I have not, but I probably should, because I have had
the same recommendation as well. Yeah, because some
of that stuff goes on sale, like, dirt cheap
sometimes, and it's like, if you, they actually
have a Lucas Arts pack. I
don't, something's missing from it, it was just
probably, oh yeah, Maniac Mansion, because that was the Game of the Week
last, or the Maniac Mansion sequel
was the Game of the Week last week, and,
um, because we let Alan pick when you were out, and he
picked the Day of the Tentacle, and that was one of the
Lucas Arts games that's missing from that pack.
But you can get, I think it has, like,
Loom and some of the other things that Dark Sakura's picked
in the past. That's one of the big things on there,
so, yeah, pretty cool.
Alright.
Oh, yes, next email.
Um, the theme,
the subject is Garris.
And it starts off, Garris.
Hello sentient creatures. There is a media
event that I'm sure you are aware of. This is something
that people have been eagerly anticipating,
and have been looking forward to
for a while. I'm also sure that many of us
out there saw this media event.
However, there are some of us who haven't seen
the media event, or have
yet to see this media event in
its entirety. It is for this reason
that I email you today. Please, for the
sake of all of us who haven't seen it, please don't spoil
the British Open. Stay black,
redertainment, Garris.
Or the Olympics. I think the joke
might have been Batman, Dark Knight Rises.
I saw it.
It wasn't bad.
It had some really slow parts,
though. It did have some slow parts,
but I was okay with it in the scope of the
big picture. I'm not gonna spoil.
I'm not gonna do that to you guys. I have one question
from that movie. What? Why did Bane
sound Belgian?
Is it just me, or did he sound Belgian?
I do not think you should talk about
his voice in a negative manner.
He sounded like Count von Count to me.
He sounded Belgian.
He sounded...
With that same pleasant
Belgian... I liked his
voice, even if it was a little silly.
He sounded very pleasant. I'm glad
they changed it from that trailer, though.
Like in the trailer, Bane sounded
like this.
Okay, Tom Hardy.
Tom Hardy is...
I'm just saying this.
As your resident gay gamer,
I'm just putting this out there. Tom Hardy
is so fucking hot. Like, I can't
even. I can't even.
He's no Bruce
Campbell, I'm sorry.
He wasn't that hot as Bane.
Oh, the movie. The movie, can I just say?
It wasn't as good as the last
one. I didn't say the last one. The Dark Knight
will probably be the best comic book
movie they ever freakin' make.
But, I honestly
think Dark Knight was better than Avengers. Don't get me wrong,
I love the Avengers, but Dark Knight was off-manning.
DC fails.
This new movie was pretty good, except
the tw...
I liked Catwoman. There was a twist.
I was pleasantly surprised with Catwoman.
Anne Hathaway is a goddess.
Let's just be real. Anne Hathaway deserves
to have statues built of her. The ending twist, I should have seen
coming because I saw the casting.
But, it still threw me.
Even though I knew!
Couple twists, and one of them I
saw within like five seconds of the character
showing up. I'm like, oh, not
that. That's the one I probably
should have seen coming because I knew better. Anyway, yeah.
Okay.
So, next email. I don't want to spoil anything.
Hi again, OLR. Well, Rob,
I wrote in last week requesting all your knowledge
on Final Fantasy XI as we ventured
into Van... Van...
Vanidel is how he wrote it. I guess it's
Vanidel. Oh, Vanidel. Whatever.
To say stepping foot
back into that world again was fresh
and very nostalgic. I was greeted with many open
arms and more than a few people to help me
get my gears back in line to play.
Although, after playing for about
six hours in between two days, I found myself
wishing there were more wowish things
about it. Oh well, I guess
all other MMOs
were the gateway drug to the ultra drug
wow as we know it. As a sucker
that is on the annual pass plan,
I guess I'll go roll a new
toon and start my adventure all over again.
Just so I don't feel like I'm
giving charity money to Blizzard.
Just
really hoping something fresh comes
from Guild Wars 2. Not being
a hater or a troll, but it
would be exciting to see a new MMO
come out and be the prolific wow killer.
Your thoughts? And this is from
Travis. I'm gonna
use this opportunity to give a cheap plug
to the best little Horde house in Azeroth.
www.hordehouse.com. It's the
other show that I'm on on
VOG Network that debuts Wednesdays
here at VOG.
I will say this about World
of Warcraft. And I've said
this many times on Horde House. The
game that will kill World of
Warcraft is
World of Warcraft. That's right.
That's gonna be the thing that kills World
of Warcraft is itself. Because
this is the type of thing that inevitably happens.
What's killing Diablo 3?
Question mark.
Itself. So
I think the only thing that's gonna
really kill World of Warcraft is itself.
Not that that's never gonna happen.
I mean the steam's gonna run out someday.
And I guess maybe I
should say instead of itself I should say Blizzard.
Because whatever Blizzard's next
MMO ends up being will probably be
I mean as long as they
don't make some of the mistakes they made with Diablo 3
which I think is inevitably gonna
push back Titan or whatever this
new MMO ends up being.
I think it could have
a large impact on WoW's user
base. But I think World of Warcraft's gonna be around
for a long time to come.
Because so many people have invested so much into it.
It's just the way it is.
Anyhow. That was it.
Oh that's it. Well then you should send more
emails for next week. Mailbag
at OrangeloungeRadio.com
I wanna hear from some of you PlayStation home folks.
Give us some PlayStation
related questions and so forth.
Or I
here's a serious question
for the home people. Do you think the PlayStation
home gets a bad rap? Because there's a lot
of people that don't
take home very seriously or
don't get home. And I'm gonna open in
Liam Mill. We've been kind of those types of skeptics
on the show in the past. Because
you know home was kind of
plugged as this big
centerpiece gateway
that you know instead of like the cross
bar on your PlayStation it would be home.
You would walk into home and you would have that
you know trophy case filled
with all your trophies and so forth. And
you know maybe the way we envision home
in our mind hasn't actually been
what's executed. Do you think
your place has gotten
a bad rap? I will say
this. The community of course is wonderful
and events and things like this. And I think home
is a lot better
now than it was three years ago. And there is
a lot to unlock in there.
And fun stuff. But you know
kind of wanna throw that out
there. I wanna hear from some of you at our mailbag.
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Alright.
And Black Wolf is reporting
from live within PlayStation Home that
the PlayStation Home folks agree
that Avengers was better than Dark Knight.
Thank you.
I love you all. I love you all my children.
Cause I mean
fucking Hawkeye. Sorry Hawkeye.
Or as
I've heard
one smaller child say not
Becky's son but like a seven year old
Hawkeye.
Alright.
Moving on. It's time
for us to get angsty in a segment
we call the FUs of the Week.
Why do we have a segment called
the FUs of the Week? Cause we can.
FU.
While driving to San Francisco
yesterday I was
on this little bit where the
carpool lane splits off
to sort of bypass the
rest of traffic to get to the
just past Emeryville
to get to where you pay the tolls.
And some
sixty year old Asian man
and now I normally
do not support stereotypes
but sometimes they exist for a reason.
There
has to be something that
enabled the stereotype to
exist. Why it's you know usually accepted.
Well definitely driving while Asian.
In his little Mazda
MPV
decides that he's going to change
lanes right where I am.
And as
Marissa is my witness cause she was sitting
there in the back. I beat
Luckily
she had some airbags to protect
her. I
beeped my horn. I flicked
my lights.
And definitely screamed
what the fuck are you doing?
Several times in the car.
And Becky was in the front seat. She was
a mess after
cause he ran right into where she was.
Luckily he wasn't going very quickly. We were
going at speed. I was at going
sixty five because
of the way traffic was moving. And some other guy was on my ass
so I couldn't slow down.
There was no right to merge.
And on top of that he was trying
to cross and right where the line was starting to go solid.
Moving that fast
having a collision that fast
I mean no matter what
it's lucky. I would have been
like Becky. I would have been hysterics like
I would have been me. She was just tensed up.
Oh no I would have been full on tears.
Well here's what happened.
Me when I panic I either
cry or scream.
And I opted for screaming.
You're very good at it.
So here's what happened. He basically
thankfully
I guess he
got defensive enough or something
and I honestly think that he started to pull over when I was
in his blind spot. He knocked
my passenger side
rear view mirror off.
Which I'm very pissed off about because you know I love my car.
I love the Pontiota
the rally vibe whatever we call it.
And scraped up the side of my car
I mean it's not bad damage. The car
drove perfectly fine after that.
But um
so we stopped in the little divider like right where the
lane split. So it was
we had room to move around there.
And
he comes out of his car yelling at me.
So I'm like what the
fuck dude you broke my car you
still have a mirror.
And just I was like
and he was like yelling
stuff I couldn't understand. Like please speak with
some intelligence I can't understand you.
And
his wife was definitely a lot
more reasonable than he was. And we got it worked
out and it's funny
we're both through AAA for our insurance.
So I just had to say oh he's with AAA here's his
number. Because I'm with AAA.
Oh he's got his record right now.
I've got photos because I
am like that and take photos.
Well on my
phone.
And now here's
what the stupid thing was in his little
Mazda MPV
he had mattresses
stacked right behind
their heads to block his rear view mirror.
Including blocking
his blind spot.
Which is not illegal
but definitely not safe.
And not good for his insurance.
And I have photos of it.
Because I'm kind
of an anal bitch that way.
So um
the other parts of
my F.U. now go to the California
Highway Patrol. Now the guy didn't take a
report because nobody was injured.
The cars were relatively
fine.
Well
they can
but at this point
I was just like fuck it dude I'm hungry
and I'm
and I'm you know I was
you know how I get when I get on that
verge of anxiety
where I'm just kind of shaky
and don't want to deal with shit. That was me.
So um
I stopped and
did some deep breathing and but this is
funny because we kept seeing people pulled over
the whole fucking way from Sacramento
to San Francisco and back.
The highway patrol is everywhere
we wait like 20 minutes
for them to show up.
Giving out chicken shit tickets
is serious business. Very important.
Well it's like
and I
I have to say that my defensive
driving is pretty good.
Except the thing is that I couldn't
swerve to the side because there was a wall
next to me and it would have been
worse to run into the wall
than have the dude run into me and I
I tried to speed up to get around him
which is I honestly think that
me speeding up was why the
collision wasn't worse because
and it's like his mirror was just like
tipped up just a little bit just tipped
up a little bit. Mine was gone.
Mine is somewhere in Emeryville right now.
So fuck him.
Um now
this is the other part of the fuck you.
Fuck everybody on the road who was beeping
at us and going nice job.
Didn't help when I
got out of the car either.
Keep it classy California.
Well one of the guys managed to
stop like slow down
just enough for me to go
you get out here and fix it then.
And he rolled
up his window.
Bastard.
I love it when your anger isn't directed at me.
Alright. Well it's
just
I don't you know I don't get
and you know the lady at Allstate
she was like oh it's always the people who
were at fault that do the yelling. You mean AAA?
AAA. Yeah I called Allstate first because
I was so well when I got home I was
every time I looked over to look
in my rearview mirror and didn't see it
not there I just get pissed again.
So when I get home I'm so pissed off and shaky
and you can ask Marissa. I was pissed
off and shaky. I
went to Allstate instead of AAA.
Oops. Nice. So
I'm on the phone with freaking
Allstate and they're trying to find information for me
like wait I'm with AAA. Hang up.
Well Misty in our chat room
at live.vognetwork.com says if I find it
when I pass through Emeryville next time I'll get it back
for you.
I've got I will
share a picture from my Facebook with everyone.
Alright Loki I don't know how you're gonna follow that
but good luck. FU?
FU to
people that change up tournament rules
15 minutes before the tournament starts.
Come on. That's a little ridiculous.
Thankfully I'm patient. If my wife had it
her way I'd be
trying to get my money back.
I'd be trying to get money for the gas. I'd be
trying to deface their
website and smear them
all over all the other sites. I just
I don't I don't want to put
that much effort. Thank God Nelly wasn't in
Jamie's car. You should break off his rearview mirror.
To kind of go a little bit
with what Jamie said. FU
to people that change lanes without signaling.
And there's a lot of them.
This guy didn't signal either.
It's like dude you're like
and they were elderly people
but it's not just elderly people.
All shapes and sizes.
In my case it's elderly Asians.
But seriously I mean and the people that
are older
not necessarily elderly but like at least
in their 50s. Dude how long have you been
fucking driving? Really is the
turn signal like a new thing to you just now?
You haven't figured out how to fucking use it?
That's just sheer laziness is what
it is. And the fact that you don't signal
means probably not looking either so
you know fuck those people because
they're the ones that are dangerous out there like
not paying attention to anything
or drifting into other lanes.
I hate that too. Or when you make a
fucking left turn and the guy just like
I'm gonna take a really wide turn
so I have to go into like the median just to get
away from the guy. So fuck people
that just don't pay attention
on the road.
Well I'll go next.
I don't know I don't really have any traffic I've used
this week. Sorry to break form here but
I will say this. F you to the
fact that I kind of hurt my knee pretty bad
last week because in my role
that I was playing in Repo the genetic opera
I got to die three times
as three different cops. So
one of the times I died
I hit the ground pretty hard and I
kind of fucked up my knee doing that.
Maybe I should actually wear the knee pads next time
but I didn't have time when I changed my
costume to get them on because they can
kind of be a pain in the ass. So F you to the fact
that I fucked up my knee. Oops
not that music. This music. Oh yeah one other thing
F you to the hills in San Francisco
and having to walk uphill both ways.
Just saying. Through the snow. Walking from
Japan town to the Castro
L and back. Marissa
if you have any F yous.
Um this is gonna
this is gonna absolutely
shock anyone that
loves me and then you know knows me well but
I don't have that much to bitch about right now.
I know it's
those of you out there in radio land that
know me are gonna be like.
Well I mean yeah F you to that guy on the road
I mean I'm
from L.A. where you know
you know. You can't fucking
complain about anything traffic you
people are crazy in L.A. You're just
constantly in the upright position on the
road out there.
Nice. Oh yeah well I
would say F you to the gentleman I mentioned
earlier.
But I don't want to
never mind because that involves F you.
So um
but yeah so yeah F you to
bad drivers like them.
Well played.
Reminds me of a time when like one of the
first times we went out there for
I think it was
yeah it was for one of the our first E3
out there I'll never forget we were driving
I think to the Final Fantasy
concert or something like that.
Something that was on the freeway and I remember
we saw someone passing on
the right of us we were in the right lane by the way
passing on the right they were actually
off roading to pass us
on the right in the right most lane
of the freeway.
That's that's that's
that's ballsy.
All right two more stories for you guys then we're gonna
get to the Skype line at one eight seven
seven game O.L.R. but not just yet
because we have a few more stories
starting with Loki. Yes so one of
the games that's being kick started right now is
actually another Shadowrun game Shadowrun Online
and they talked a little bit more
details about their game and showed a little
bit of game play which looks pretty awesome it kind of
it's like a high res
HD version of like the top down
Shadowrun game on you know Super
Nintendo except you know the way you shine
your graphics and stuff. The game
though is gonna be kind of set up like
Guild Wars where you pay once and
basically you're
playing the game. There's no month to month fees
however of course there's gonna be like micro
transactions later on down the line if you want to
buy special things and
stuff. And also they're showing
some of the different things in there
they have a portion of the game where
okay you go these hub worlds and you get
your mission and there's a part of
the mission that requires
you to do the investigation work and
leg work and so if your leg work
isn't very good you may not know that hey
there's an easier way to get into this
you know location
in order to get this information or hey
this is gonna be heavily guarded by something
so you'll kind of you know
know a little bit about it
but
that's kind of cool. And then of course they're saying
that the game at launch is gonna
retail for $39.99 of course
if you back the Kickstarter you'll
get the game at $25
at that donation level
and
I guess a new campaign
they're gonna be launching every three to
four months for $15
so it could be kind of add on
expansions.
Sound like something you might be putting money down for?
Maybe, I mean
I've already backed one
Kickstarter Shadowrun game
so I'd be kind of curious
but once again I don't have time for MMOs
but the game sounds like
it's more
single player with other
people at the same
time kind of I don't know
you can play it single player
you can play it you know co-op
or you can do PVP
so it'll be neat
I mean I'll have to see when it comes out
I'm probably not gonna back it though. Alright
just because I've backed too much stuff recently
so. Alright one more story
for you guys before we get to the
Skype line and this has to do with
Jet Set Radio you know it's gonna be making
a renaissance pretty soon with the
Playstation Network and Xbox Live
ports that are coming very soon well maybe
you want some clothing inspired by the
games there's a company in the UK
called Insert Coin Clothing
and they have a line of
clothes called Sega Reloaded
and it features authentic
recreations of the t-shirts
worn by Beat and Gum in Jet Set
Radio which actually have the character
names on them there's shirts and
hoodies based on the leather
jacket from Shenmue
and there's some other Sega designs available
referencing Streets of Rage, Golden Axe
Sonic, Shinobi, pretty awesome
there. So yeah if you want
some Sega clothes sounds like something
up at Dark Soccer's Alley although it
costs an arm and a leg to import
maybe you can get a friend in the UK to help you shop
at Insert Coin Clothing. Dear Mr. Kidman
Alright
InsertCoinClothing.com
if you want more information on that some of the
official Sega clothing. You know what I fucking want?
Excuse me Sega, I don't know if it's official
but Sega inspired clothing. I just want
the N7 hoodie. That's all I want is the
N7 hoodie. Somebody get it for me.
Alright
Okay I'm getting a message
via Black Wolf from
PlayStation Home. Blender wants
to do another contest. Pick an animal
and the first person to type that animal
into the home space
wins another prize in home. So
an animal. What animal
are we going to pick? Should we go obvious?
Dark
Sakura why don't you pick for us?
What animal do you think they should type
in the home chat?
I can't tell them that though. They have to
guess right?
Pick an animal. Wait
wait are we
You're going to have to clarify.
Do we say it?
Do we say it or are they supposed to
guess? Okay yeah
Black Wolf says yes. Say it.
Lemur. A lemur.
Alright there you go.
I didn't say ferret so all you people who
were trying to get the jump know.
Alright a lemur.
Alright good luck.
Alright
Love it.
Lemurs are fucking cute okay.
Let us know who wins Bobby.
You know what else is cute?
Baby sloths.
Come on baby sloths are adorable.
So whatever.
And no Garris is not an animal.
Garris is
turian.
Alright and remember
He just said that.
I'm risking an animal
in the sack.
This is all I hear
from people that play Mass Effect so
Remember. No it's
Kayden for me.
If you talk to the gays they'll all say
Kayden.
Kayden's an ass
who actually his
model is like the guy he's modeled
after and who did all the face cap and stuff
is like a gay partender from the abbey.
And he's hot.
Oh my god.
I gotta admit he was easy on the eyes.
Alright Skull King
won of course he did.
Of course he won.
But you know what he deserves it for
for helping support the
vog
participation with Summerfest.
Lemurs lemurs cutie furry lemurs.
Alright let's move on
to the Skyplane.
I gotta open that up 1877 Game OLR
The Skyplane is open right now
for you guys to give us
a call and if you wanna call us
from Playstation Home awesome.
If you're one of our regular listeners who wants to call us
that's awesome too. We will talk to you
at 1877 Game OLR.
Meanwhile let me get
to some Twitter topics. We have a few things
that were sent to us via Twitter
and I wanna look at this from Tigerclaw
cause this tweet here from Tigerclaw just
jumps out at me it's like wah wah what?
Irrational Games
Job lists 85
plus Metacritic score as
a requirement.
This is the developer of Bioshock
and Bioshock Infinite. It's Irrational
Games. They posted a job listing
for a design manager
and apparently one of their
resume or whatever has to have a past
work that has a high score
on Metacritic. That's
kinda surprising. It's posted on the Gamasutra
job boards. Credit on at
least one game with an 85 plus
average Metacritic review score.
How do you feel
about Metacritic score having
such weight especially when you consider the games
like Child of Eden got an 84
Mirror's Edge got an 81
hmm
Remember that whole controversy over
Fallout New Vegas and the bonus they didn't get
because it was an 84?
hmm
So what's
the job requirement is that they've had to publish
or worked on the game that received
Metacritic over 85?
You have to have some credit. Alright well
let's go to the phones. What if like their co-worker
Bob just really bombed
when it came to like you know
it's like yeah we did all this really good work but man
he just like he's made fart noises
into a microphone for all the dialogue in
the game and it just
really hurt us.
Alright let's go to the phones. Hi
you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hey it's Oscar. Hey Oscar
Thanks for sitting there waiting while
we got through that last conversation.
What's on your mind buddy?
Oh that's fine.
I just wanted to say that this past Thursday
I made the 6 hour drive
back and forth for 12
hours total to Virginia
like right outside of the DC area to see
the Zelda Symphony.
Oh my gosh you drove 12
hours to see the Zelda Symphony.
Well I went to... It was well
worth it. I went to LA to see
the Dear Friends concert so
yeah it's about the same. It was worth it?
Yeah definitely. Tell us a little bit
about the experience.
Like um I don't know did any of you guys buy
Skyward Sword and like see how they had the orchestra
CD packaged in with the game? Sadly
no I never got around to that one
sadly. Alright well like
it has like 7 or 8 or so tracks
on that CD and
it's
they played pretty much most of those but there were so
much more like they had complete like symphonic
movements in each of the game. Like there was
Ocarina of Time movement, a Twilight Princess
movement, a movement from
Link to the Past and oh my god
the friggin Link to the Past one like I
teared up at one part where they did the credits
music cause I just forgot about that.
That game is so good.
Yeah
like don't get me wrong Ocarina of Time is my
favorite but that game has some moments
so that just I don't know.
So you didn't just
go by yourself I imagine you went with friends.
Yeah I had a couple friends with me
that went like um
actually it was one of my friends who posted on Facebook
I'm buying tickets today who wants to go
and like I was one of the first people to respond
and so he bought my ticket
which was only $65
for that theater it was like the Wolf Trap
Theater near DC.
They were really good
seats actually like they were pretty
close. So you drove from
where? You live in Ohio?
Michigan? Yeah well I live
in Northeast Ohio but my friend
who bought the tickets lives down in
Athens Ohio which is like the Southeastern portion
of it so
like I had to go down
there anyway to like move stuff out of my apartment
for the next year
so it was no big deal
driving down there myself but then
he drove to DC for the most part.
Wow that's a long
drive but that's awesome
I mean sounds like it was quite the experience.
What was the crowd like?
Um
it was a mixed bag
like I thought it was going to be a lot of kids but actually
it was only a few
and like a lot of teenagers to adults
and like
the kids that were there like I saw their
dads that were with them all had their 3DS's
out like it was just a street pass fest
like just non-stop I
probably got 100 during the course of the day.
Oh my yeah you probably could have beat
find me in
one sitting there that's awesome.
Oh definitely it was
I don't know you need to go
like you really should like um
I do if they come back through here.
The last concert was in San Jose on December
14th did you try to link that one?
Is it? I might just do
that actually what day of the week is December
14th let's see the 6th is umlaut
and that says Thursday so
that sounds like it would be a Wednesday no it's a Friday
hmm maybe
that would be great.
Go to zelda-symphony.com
and there should be a link to the schedule up there
and you can check it all out. Anyone want to go?
Anyone? Anyone? Anyone?
Alright we'll see I'll find
maybe Alan will want to go we'll make it a
trip I have friends in San Jose too
Mel and Mel live there and you know them from this show
and it would be cool to go see something
like that so yeah well thanks
for the tip and I'm glad to hear you had a good
time. Yeah
I just hope that they release like
another orchestrated CD like maybe after
the tour is done because some of those songs I
just really want to hear again. I'm sure
they'll be another Zelda pre-order disc in the future.
Yeah there has
to be. Alright well
Osfer I'm going to let you go to get more calls but thanks for the call
okay? Alright no problem.
Alrighty 1877
Game OLR our username on Skype is
OrangeLoungeRadio if you want to
give us a call. Meanwhile
some other tweets
one more from Tigerclaw I let people have
two tweets just a kind of a quick
headline here Microsoft halts
further development on what was to be the
free-to-play game Flight
it was supposed to be a free-to-play entry
in Microsoft's Flight Simulator
franchise I wonder if that has to
do with the Vancouver layoffs we heard about earlier
well
I don't know it's
it's I like the Flight Simulator
games back in the day but I mean they're
so intricate now like I don't actually
know how to fly a plane people
but it looked fun and pretty
I remember those used to be like the graph that the
high-end graphic games with the Flight Simulator
games yes Marissa? Well I mean if you
really wanted to make them properly accurate you need to have
bitchy flight attendants
that's a real flight simulator
I want to join the Mile High Club
you know bathroom
alright we got another phone call hi you're on OrangeLoungeRadio
who's this? It's Shane
with a very bad voice right now because I'm
Flemmy
Hi Flemmy
so what's on your mind tonight?
The PlayStation All-Stars
thingy majigger
that's right so you're about to violate every NDA
in the world it's not my NDA
it's my friend's NDA
I'm violating his NDA sounds very dirty
technically by letting you play he's already violated
the NDA there you go
alright well given I'm not giving out
his PSN I'm not giving out my PSN
name so go tie it back
to me Sony go well I
I wouldn't throw down a challenge like that actually
but so let's that was a joke
so please don't you have
allegedly played the beta
yes allegedly
so why don't you give us allegedly your thoughts
um
so right now the beta
that I allegedly played
very much feels like
a lifeless Smash Brothers
clone which you know
not terrible I guess but it's not
really fun yet which
I think games are supposed to be fun
last I heard why wasn't it fun?
um
because there's no charm to it yet
even having Parappa
in the beta the beta is only like six characters
um and
I've only seen two different stages so far
but there's
just I don't know it's
a boring game
and Smash Brothers to me is pretty boring to begin
with so maybe I'm biased but
I expected more you were telling
me that the beta is only multiplayer
correct? yeah I have to connect
to somebody else I can't play against computer players
now I have not tried to see if I could
play like two people on the same console
but part of the problem in the beta
right now is you know when you play Smash
Brothers and you get like every
person in like a tight area
the camera zooms in it doesn't
do that well in this game so
it doesn't matter how close you are to the action
your character is still really far away
and it can make it very hard to figure out what's going
on at any given time do you think
that might have hurt your impressions a little bit though
the fact you couldn't fuck around in single player
at all? um
no because
ideally that style of game is
just really
multiplayer based I feel like
Smash Brothers isn't fun by yourself
at all let's be real though
being able to play online multiplayer is a
feature that Smash Brothers I guess the
one on the Wii had it but it didn't do it very
well it was terrible it didn't really do it very well
but to Smash Brothers credit
and I'm not like you I like the
Smash Brothers games a lot but I
think they're bad games I just I think they're overrated
let's say that here's the thing
that what I always loved about Smash Brothers is that
they're very robust packages
like there is
so much in especially those
most recent Smash Brothers games
so many unlocks so many other modes
so many like mini games and other
things to experience you know and a lot
of that was brought into Kid Icarus too
so I think you know the projects
that that team does tend to be very
robust experiences
and I think if Sony doesn't
offer fans that same
really rich experience
which you're not going to see
in such a limited beta I think
you are going to feel short changed a little bit
well and then
one of the things I feel like they really get right
are the stages I really
like the fact that they change
and kind of mix up
different games in one stage like I was playing
a god of no I was playing
the Ratchet and Clank stage and all of a sudden
it turned into God of War which is
really cool and then
one turned into like Padapon
I don't remember which stage it also was but
I really enjoyed that feature
I just after now
I didn't know about that leaked list of characters
that people you know
datamined from the beta I'm kind of sad
that there aren't those real
robust options
that Smash Brothers offers but
I will probably get it because
I love that Dante and I will
play as him even if he's a terrible character
so despite everything you just said
about not feeling super great about it
you're going to buy it anyway
because they're adding that Dante that's really really hot
it was good enough to make you want to buy it
in the end
yes well I think it has potential and I think
you know I'm not judging
really purchasing it based on the beta
because you can tell that the
beta whatever build they're using is really
early on there's a lot of like
barren features
in it so
I don't know I just
I'm not going to hate the game yet
but it still needs to do more to wow me
I think they can pull it off though
well we'll see what happens in the coming months
hopefully there's a lot of good stuff to be
unlocked and things we haven't seen yet
and some of these characters in the leak sound
potential which by the way I think
Shane coming on here and giving his
alleged thoughts on the beta he may have allegedly
played is a whole lot less of an infraction
than whoever hacked the damn files
to pull out those unlockable characters
yeah and they had pictures of the stages too
I kind of thought those stages were neat
as the illegal secretary I approve
of your legalese ass covering
thank you
I appreciate that
I think we need to hire Marissa as a consultant for other
shows in the future
oh and Prab is awesome in it like
he's really cool
do you get to actually rap?
no but okay remember
that stupid boombox
in the game that
okay you get to throw him around
and I like that because I hate that boombox
is there a stage that's you waiting to use
the toilet?
not in the beta at least
because that was like the funniest stage from the first
Parappa game remember? I love Parappa
why won't they do another Parappa game?
I need to go just as bad as you
it seems like the perfect Playstation Network game
the perfect goldmine for Sony is a
Parappa online game
with little minisodes and stuff like that
why is Sony not doing this?
because Parappa 2 was not that
good, they should do another Umjammer
Lammy because that game was amazing
alright I'll take that, Umjammer Lammy is pretty
fucking good
I'm sad that she's not a leaked character, that would be really cool
you know there's always
DLC
I will buy Umjammer Lammy DLC
if I could get the one stage that everybody
except for me hates as
a stage you can play in the game I would be
so excited
shame before I let you go
we have a question for you from
playstation home summerfest
blackwolf in
playstation home says where is your
rhythm thief review?
in written form
no no no no no no don't spoil it here
I want it in written form
no I'm not going to spoil my review
here's the thing
my 3DS is busted
so yeah
for some reason when I hit the B button
it turns off which is usually the
function of the off button
but um
don't say Alan, I can hear Alan
laughing at what you just said all the way from the kitchen
hello
why?
because the B button is, nevermind, forget it
it sounds like you've got a short
is what it sounds like yeah it does
sometimes when I hold it funny it turns off
I'm like whatever I just don't even want to play you
um something inside there
yeah and I couldn't find a screwdriver to open up
because I would open it up
wait yes you did spill something on your 3DS?
no no no I didn't spill anything no no
did the dog try to eat it?
I've got all these tri-wing screwdrivers just sitting in my house
aw too bad he lives in Kansas
um what I was going to say is
I will probably be getting an XL
in two weeks thanks to my job
so I'll start playing it again
which we can't talk about
any further on the show but I will
talk to the other host about it off air
it's like the 3DS but
bigger
alright moving on uh
I guess that's it so when you get your
3DS situation figured out we want the review
now that it's not timely
not
my fault I can't even play
Pokemon do you know what a like a
pain that is to me we really need more
written content at VoG and granted I'm
responsible for this too but I mean
I've just had so much going on this week
um but uh yeah if you have some time
and you're interested in writing for VoG
it doesn't have to be about video games it could be anything
geeky movies books I would love
somebody who reads a lot of books
and even comic books and manga
I bought a book Rob
I bought um one of the Vampire
Hunter D novels that I hadn't read yet
it doesn't have to be geeky books because my wife reads a lot of books
but I mean like right now she does read
a lot of geeky books she reads a lot of
you know what your wife
is hilarious so yes I don't
care what it is she should do book reviews
I should say this funny enough
I'm seeking a book review
I actually am doing one for
a friend site of VoG
I'm just not done with the book yet but
it shouldn't be too difficult to figure out who
but I'm hoping to have that done with him next week
This is Fifty Shades of Grey
It is not Fifty Shades of Grey
Then you need to redo your review
We're like Fifty Shades of Shit
Fifty Shades of I'm Hanging Up On You Bye
Bye
Alright
Oh lordy how about one more call
I don't think he mentioned Mass Effect at all
He didn't
That's awesome
Gotcha Shane
Hi you're on Orange Launch Radio
Who's this?
This is Azoramay
Say that one more time?
Azoramay? Azoramay? What's on your mind tonight?
I just wanted to
I just noticed that
there's going to be like a Final Fantasy 11
like revival
of music
concert going on in your area
and I was just wondering if you were aware of that
I am very aware of that and I
kind of sort of want to go actually
it's just about you know if I can convince
somebody else to go with me so I don't have to go
by myself but yeah it's in Berkeley
they're doing like a Final Fantasy 11
You know what's funny? When I signed back up for the game
about a month ago like I got those emails right away
and then that's the log on message
I don't know if everybody sees that or I just see it
because I'm in the area
but when I log into the game it says don't forget
you have tickets on sale now for the Final Fantasy 11
event in Berkeley!
That is so funny because
I'm a fan of it
but I haven't really logged on it for a while
I mean I got a letter
via email about it
I was really thinking about going
but I'm on the East Coast in New York
and I actually went to go see
the
Distant Worlds at the Brooklyn Academy of Music
and it was really great
but like I said I have the same problem
as you do trying to convince
friends to actually go ahead and see it
it's like a once in a lifetime
opportunity
Would you think they're
going to bring it out here at all?
It really depends on this first one and if it does
well that's kind of the deal if it makes money
it'll tour
Here's something else to consider
we're going back years and years
so you can't really judge what's going on
at Square now to these standards
but when that first Dear Friends concert
happened which was what? That was the first year
I went to E3 so that was what? 04 I think?
04 or 05? It was 04
was Dear Friends
and that Dear Friends concert
was so good and so well received
and so amazing and that
in turn had been inspired by that
what was it? It was the 222
2002 concert they had in Japan
that had the CD
it did so well that they took that around
the country and it was a
good show and they took it to a lot of
big cities however the next year
they did a new show called More Friends
that was at the Gibson Amphitheater
I think at Universal Studios
and I went to that as well because I
loved the first one so much and More Friends
wasn't good I mean
it's not really the fault
I don't want to fault the musicians
I don't want to fault the guest stars
I don't want to fault the talent behind it
but just the production of it was
really not good and a lot
of that was acoustic problems
and a lot of the sound problems
and there was a lot of live issues and I heard
you know I don't know how much truth
there is to this stuff but I heard some dude
got fired on the spot by Nobui
Matsu for how freaking terrible
More Friends was and
Oh really? Wow I didn't know that
They didn't take that on tour
So it was like a once in a
lifetime event
Yes I can say it was a once
in a lifetime event that I got to go to and
I do consider myself lucky even though it was a bad
show they actually had like the
and I forget her name maybe you know it
the lady from Final Fantasy 10 who sang
that
I can't remember the name of the song
I'm sorry I can't say it again
Thank you
Yeah she was there singing it
and so to hear that live was really
amazing but that's
you know and so I'm thankful
for moments like that but
I realize you know
overall unfortunately the show was not a success
Oh okay well I mean that's kind of like
all I really had to
really ask Hey no it's a great question
I'm tempted I will say
I'm very very tempted we'll see I'll let you know
what I end up deciding
Alright thank you Alright take care
Take care Bye guy
Alright thank you so much for the calls tonight
I'm sorry to those that didn't get through but send us an email
mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com
if you have a comment you want us to read on a future show
when he phrases it that way
he says it's a once in a lifetime opportunity
and I do have to realize this is
it might not be like totally my backyard
but Xtaphir lives in
Oakland Berkeley now I could totally like go stay with him
for a night and go to the concert
so maybe I should
you know might not get the chance again
and for somebody that wasn't a Final Fantasy 11 for so many years
you give me a lot to think about
a phone call to
Orangelaungeradio might just have sent me back about 50 bucks
for a ticket we'll see
we'll see
alright that's it for phone calls tonight
again if you didn't get through please please tweet us
twitter.com slash o-l-r or email us
mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com
it does mean we are getting very close
to the end of the show
we're getting close to the end of the party
at Summerfest and Playstation Home
last call last call everybody
before we close
out tonight I'm gonna ask
Loki if he has any last minute stories
nope wow
I didn't even look
shame on you
I couldn't think of anything that we didn't cover
that was really really big
I do have one of the tweet I will read that
and that was from actdeft and it also reminds me to talk about this
actdeft tweeted the show and said
played beat hazard during the
o-l-r break and start of part b
quite fun and then he linked
it on the steam community or he linked his
picture on the steam community
this was something I posted on the vog network
forums if you're a fan of the game
beat hazard and you have it on pc
it is very easy to
mod the game and it's not like
you're not doing a bad thing you are editing
text files to the developers like put instructions
on how to edit it in there
you can actually add your own internet
radio feeds cause beat hazard you can play the
internet radio and it's very easy to add
vog network as a radio feed
so yes you could play beat hazard
to my voice
but it's you know when there
is no live or taped program on
the voice of geeks network there is a music
feed so it's really meant for that
but some people are playing along to our voices which I think
is kind of funny too so uh you can do
that marathon mode
so if you like yell something really fast
or something that gets harder is that yes yes
anti-disestablishmentarianism
I actually do know what it means
swear in Jewish frantically there might
be a there might be a boss
God that's hot
you know it's funny that people think like oh you're Jewish
you must have like grown up learning this no I know
because I grew up in Los Angeles
you know
nice
alright um
if you need more information on how to mod that
I posted something on our forums if you're not registered
at vognetwork.com why not
go get your loot at vognetwork.com
register and participate
further with the show in the forums
and so forth misty in chat says
Sky's voice the game goes beat hazard
let's hope not
alright
well with all those tweets and all those
chat comments it's time to
get to the end of the show but we are gonna go
around one last time to get everybody's final
thought starting with Marissa tonight
Marissa thank you so much for being on the show
tonight and I think it is a-ok
that you don't play a whole lot of games you're a
nerdy enough girl and I mean that in the best
possible way to fit right in with the family
here at Orange Lawns Radio thank you for making
me literally literally
laugh my ass off tonight
you're the best Marissa do you have any
final thoughts for our listeners? I do take it as a high fob one actually I do
I feel like I might need to explain
myself a little bit to the audience especially all those
new listeners please do
I know some of you must be thinking who is this
large breasted yappy singer-songwriter
slutbag
in reality
I actually have a major confession to make
I am a recovering
comedian
so that
explains the majority of the material tonight
very nice
but otherwise thank you so much for having me
it's been a pleasure and again any of
you people out there that enjoy
metal music please check out Prilosis
P R Y L O
S I S they're fantastic it's a good
CD oh I'm glad you enjoyed it
they're fantastic and they're funny so they have a
great YouTube channel and again it was such
a pleasure hanging out here
and sharing such stories
well go check that out especially fans of metal
Prilosis we would like our guests to be able
to plug stuff anything else you want to plug
anything else I don't know if you
if you want to see me not being
a yappy slutbag
if you want to see me singing if you look at Marissa
Concusto which is my nickname and they are
S S A C O N G U S T O
on YouTube there are some links
of small clips of me
doing little covers at Kool X Wood Shed
so thanks
and looks like Loki
just giving away little big planet carding
codes right there in the chat room
cause the beta ends on Wednesdays
gotta get em go get em sorry
I didn't think of a way to give em away earlier
that's alright if you don't get one through there
go to Joystiq they had an article a couple pages
back that you can generate free codes
where do you think I got mine
nice very nice
thanks again Marissa
more final thoughts Loki your final
thought since you have the mic
speaking of Wednesday
Adams Wednesday happens to be
August 1st
happens to be when the 3rd gate opens
oh shit the race is on
do you have time off from work to do it?
I took the day off well for multiple reasons I took the day off
to take Josh
cause it's his second
birthday but also
because I'm going to be staying up all night long finishing
whatever game they have
same reason I took
September 25th off work
understandable
I hope
the game is not hard enough
for me where I can't finish it in one night
cause I'm going to be disappointed if
I have to stop
playing to sleep or
do other things
but um
I don't know
who knows what it is no one knows I just hope it's not a crappy
Facebook game please not be a crappy Facebook
game cause that was already a
crappy Facebook game for Gate 2 and I
can't take another one I will just say
I will throw over a table and just say fuck it
I'm going to sleep
alright um let's see
uh Dark Soccer your final thought tonight
fucking
fucking fuck wherever you mirror
uh my final
thought tonight is first I want to
thank everybody that participated
in PlayStation Home Summerfest with us here
on this lovely evening thank you Blender
thank you Skull King for putting
that together I really appreciate it
uh thank you to those that stayed up late
in the uh
Aurora 1.5 space apparently
longest event
ever in PlayStation
Home so thank you guys for
uh making it a success there's still at least
10 people in there doing the running man good times
thank you guys so much um
great community really appreciate it
and a big welcome again to all the new listeners
dude that's awesome the rumors
that they're going to be bringing them Battle Royale TV show
I don't know how I feel about that
I read about that this week I'm like what
the heck otherwise my final
thought my real final thought of the night
would be Bilbo
Bilbo Baggins
alright forget it
uh that's
Leonard Nimoy he's my hero dude
alright that does it for another week
at Orange Lounge Radio hey if you like the show
all we ask you know what we don't have advertising
rampant throughout the show we are
not sponsored by any
gigantic you know multi-million
dollar magazine we're sponsored by
Keurig and Pinkberry we're
sponsored by our fans so if you
like what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio
please tell a friend or
two about the show help spread
the word leave us a nice review
on iTunes or some other
place to get podcasts we really appreciate
all that homegrown support that being said though
we probably will have some giveaways soon for
a few things
alright
it's just like you just gave away three beta codes right there
well better than that that was just crap
but I'm talking about like actual
things like I have things in my bag
I have things that I brought that I will bring more
of and I have things that I have yet to bring
alright
have a great night everybody this stuff's already been brought
yes this stuff has already
been brought we'll be back in a week to do
it all over again we'll see you next Sunday here
at the Voice of Geeks Network have a great night
you've been listening to Orange
Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is a production
of OLR Studios
to join us for a live
show tune into
VoGnetwork.com
Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific
9pm Eastern
the views and opinions expressed
in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff
of Orange Lounge Radio or
VoGnetwork but you know
they were all still true
see you next week!
you