Message for you, son!
Attention!
Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
The Monty Talk and then some.
Orange Lounge may contain adult cunt.
Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex in this episode.
Hey, are there any balls down there?
That's the biggest player you've ever seen, Jingle Berry.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls. Absolutely frightening. What's yours?
There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself. That's my job.
It's less a time on sprockets than we does.
I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too.
I know cunt food.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gay?
Oh, what I expect for funny sex with a cunt is handsome.
Hey!
Dark Saffron.
Shut up! Where's my gun? This is my boom stick.
Skye.
Come on, girls, it's time to drop the bomb.
I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind and what human being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live, but not really.
And this is episode number 42 for April the 27th of 2003.
You're tuned into the Bomani Scene's most premeditated radio station of all things Beeeemani.
My name is Rob Roberts. You might know me as Skye.
Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
You know her better as Dark Sakura.
Or tonight, as her name tag says, Miss Pac-Man.
I like your shirt. That's a cool shirt.
It's retro.
Loki is out today because he's doing stuff.
He broke his track record again.
No, it's amazing. I don't know what he's doing tonight. He's just doing stuff.
Yeah, he's fapping.
He's pecking and fapping.
Actually, we have a secret.
We're not really live tonight.
No, we're really dead.
Unless it's Thursday for you right now.
If it is Thursday the 24th, then yes, we're live.
We're premature this week.
We came a little early this week to your sound waves.
It's going to be an interesting show tonight because there's really not a lot tonight.
It's just Jamie and me.
We might have one special guest who's around here somewhere.
We're just going to talk about stuff.
Jamie and I are both kind of in moods where we just don't give a fuck.
My socks are stripy.
I like your socks. They're pretty.
I can't say that I don't like your socks at all.
I'll get you my pretty.
Does he know?
Yeah, so let's take a quick break.
We're going to start off with some old school five key songs.
This is our chat room. CaliPomani.com. Click on Orange Lounge, click on chat.
Mr.. Random person on the street who by the way is not an actor
What do you think of the orange don't play money music and more show the music is like being transported to?
just this
dancing spaceship place it's
Unearthly it's like being in a club except. You don't have to you know I should ask someone to dance
Hey, you're listening to orange lounge radio episode number
42 and tonight, we're being a little bit sneaky. We're actually pre-taped tonight, so
But that doesn't mean there isn't a party going on or not around mommy and daddy aren't home in the chat room
So I'm sure there's plenty of people causing a commotion so go on in there and party with them. They're over at
www.calibomani.com and you click on orange lounge, and then you click on chat and
join all our
Yeah, don't click on that button that says don't click me
Click here for goat say
Yeah, that was that was another April Fool's joke. I was like how can you do goat say radio?
Maybe maybe next year for April Fool's we can play just play gay porn over here
Oh my god, I finally did monkey sex an orange lounge
Oh finally whoo, I think whoo whoo, what was it?
Well Conan O'Brien has the masturbating bear
I think a video took these people at the zoo and the monkey was Lincoln. They show that on cable or something?
That's one of those skinnamax looks
Oh my god, I watched the blue girl live-action
Le blue girl live-action. God, it was horrible describe Le blue girl for the uninitiated. It was an anime it was really crappy but oh my god I never need to see that again it was like volume 3 or something oh so there's more than one. Yeah, it's like a story
Is acting in as bad as it was in the anime?
Actually there was some decent acting but other than that it was like oh, it's a garden hose. Oh, it's going in my mouth. It looked like they were like spitting up vegetable oil I neglected to introduce our special guest tonight. Hi to Brad, by the way.
Oh shit, I had something I was going to say. Did you try to make him eat that microphone? Yes. Suck it, suck it good. Oh I hit his teeth. Oh my bad. I'm going to wipe it off now, excuse me. That's a really good radio.
Today we're painting on Orange Lounge Radio. We're going to make a happy cloud. Fluffy white clouds of cocaine. I was so sad when Bob Ross died.
That's sad. What other people have died recently that made me go? Mr. Rogers. Oh, Nell Carter. She was cool. Shut up. I like Nell Carter.
I used to watch Give Me a Break. So yeah, interesting week for us. I think we've all just been very busy and doing like random sorts of things. It's been like a crazy week for me.
Your car passed smog? Yeah, doing 50. It's been really random. I've been working on pictures. I have a desk lamp. It clips onto my shelf. It makes things bright so I don't go blind when I draw.
It clips onto your shelf so it's a shelf lamp. Sort of. It's just a clip onto a desk but I don't have a desk that it'll fit on. It's multi-purpose. You can clip it anywhere. You can clip it on your nipple if you wanted to. No. I have these shelves that are over my computer desk where we keep our old school stuff.
Not a nipple clamp lamp. It's a tongue twister. Nipple clamp lamp. That's the new Erotic song, isn't it? Yes, the new Erotic single, nipple clamp lamp. Yeah, it's the bee side to temple of butt.
You know what's interesting is that Dark Tetsuya, who is an obsessive listener of this show, pointed out in the chat room a while back that actually in an earlier episode, and he cites episode 12, I apparently actually said something about Mr. Rogers is not dead.
By the way, and I appreciate our listeners, but when you remember episode numbers, that's the time that you need to go on vacation.
Well, if I remember right though, episode 12 was the second episode we broadcast this week. Okay, but I haven't been keeping up with episode 12. I haven't either. Dear people, if you refer to a specific event, don't refer to it by episode number because we sure as fuck don't remember.
Do you remember episode three? No. Oh my God, I wasn't here. Yeah, you weren't here. I remember that because I remember when Orange Laundry started, you were here the first week. We had everybody here the first week, and then the second and third week, it was like, I'm going to Anime Expo. Bye.
That was it too. I was like, I'm in LA. Bye. I'm in San Diego. Bye. And then we were just kind of here without Jamie for a couple weeks. And then I went to Alabama. Bye. Oh, I'm stuck in traffic in San Francisco.
I thought Alabama happened before. We've been doing the show since June 23rd. Okay, then never mind. I was stuck in traffic in San Francisco one time. I remember that too.
And then Julie and I were like, fuck this, we're going back in. We went back and got all yucked on.
Not always. Huh? Who else would have a higher? Matt. Jamie or Matt. But, oh well. Not me. I couldn't show delinquent. It's all good. Verbal warning. Because I do stuff.
You know, I have taken the microphone out a bunch of the time when I've not been here. And sometimes, even when we're not having a show, I take the microphone off. I do fuck off all the time. So maybe I have the highest attendance after all because I attended my own home.
I work from home. You work from home? I see. Seriously. So, God, what else is new this week? It's such an interesting show tonight because there's just nothing to talk about.
You call that interesting? I know. Aren't you excited about tonight's show? Any listeners. I know how to get you excited. Go download some porn. It's funny. Let's just get drunk. That'll be funny. I'm just kidding. I know I have work. Actually, I have work tomorrow. I can get drunk. Sure.
Let's just pretend we're getting drunk. And then if the show's really bad because we're lagging, we can just say we were drunk. Sorry.
Jamie will get drunk and I'll get high and then you'll be sober. You can get drunk, you can get high and I'll have sex.
I'll be in the other room. It sounds like the real world. No, because we need to have, we need a black person. We need either an Asian or a Pacific Islander.
We need to have, yeah, we need a person with bad hygiene. We need everybody to hate somebody else. We need the racist. And the racist has to be a roommate. We have Loki.
We have Loki. I don't know where Loki is tonight. He just said he wouldn't be available tonight. I think he's either fapping or he's probably getting ready for the moving on Saturday, which is one reason we're taped tonight.
He's having special time with that significant other. That's possible too. Who has time for relationships? I sure don't. Yeah, see there's like a special on the Matrix tonight.
Well, there is a little bit of news. Actually, there's a lot of news. We're just being lazy. We're procrastinating for next week. Who said we'd bring you news timely? Come on. You know what I realized? We kind of lied last week. We said that last week was the last episode of Orange Lounge Radio from this studio, but we're actually in the studio tonight.
Tonight's the last episode in the studio, even though we're pre-taped. I'm confused. I just went cross-eyed. Yeah. I want ice cream. Let's go get ice cream. Fuck this show. Bye.
I had salad today. Did you? From where? The grocery store. Did you toss your salad? Yes, I did actually. It landed on the cat. You know what's funny? I had a salad today too, and I shook my salad.
Yeah.
All right. One interesting thing that's in Bamani News this week. DanceMania EX3 just came out, and I don't have a copy, and I want one. So somebody get me one. What the fuck's on this one this time? Get this. Ace of Base, first track. How cool is that?
Jamie's blinking. Okay, then again I did buy an Ace of Base CD, didn't I? This is great. Creamy has a song on DanceMania EX3 called Help I'm a Fish. Cool. I have to listen to that. Oh my God.
Track six is called Help I'm a Fish. New Smile Decay, new Captain Jack, new Bus Stop, new 2 Unlimited, new DJ Alligator, new Lasko, which is like no surprise if you've been following the EX series, a trance remix of Erotic Gimme Gimme Gimme, the 2003 mix, and then another Creamy song, a remix of I Do I Do I Do.
I'm looking forward to Help I'm a Fish. As soon as we get a copy of that, we'll play that for y'all. That would be fun.
And Bus Stop, it looks like this time around, is covering I Was Made for Lovin' You. You know, the only way I remember that song is through Moulin Rouge.
I've never seen Moulin Rouge. I know, you've never seen Moulin Rouge. We've got to make you watch that sometime. But there's this part where they, you know, they're going back and forth between all these love songs, and then there's that part where I was made for lovin' you, baby, you were made for lovin' you. I should never sing on this show.
Yes. Indeed. Quite.
I Was Made for Party on You. I Was Made for Stiff and Glue.
This has nothing to do with Bomani, but a lot of you that follow Bomani also follow Konami, and Konami has another game series that's somewhat popular. It's known a little bit. It's Castlevania. And get this, the new Castlevania is coming out, and look at that, it's 3D.
Come on, Castlevania dungeon. Okay, wait a second, but the last time they tried to do a 3D Castlevania game, it sucked shit.
This is new. Yeah, it was up yesterday. Okay, you know what? But this is what it says at the bottom. It says the article says this game will be entirely in 3D, but is not intended to be like Castlevania 64, which the producer openly admitted to hating.
The game takes place in the 11th century, apparently, but other story details are pretty vague.
God damn it, they need to do another one with Richter. Everybody pray to whatever god you believe in that this game does not suck, please.
They need another game with Richter. Or as Maria said in the English version, Richter.
What's that? Freaking Gradius 5. What's that about? It's new. I think it's soon. Gradius 5 on PS2. On the piece of shit too. Sorry.
Just because they took parts out of old space shuttles and stuff to make this thing doesn't mean it's like a system.
I just think people can't program for it for shit or else we would definitely have games that looked better.
Metal Gear Solid 2 was nice, but it was better on Xbox, I have to say. Because there was more room for anti-aliasing.
That's why I like the new substance on PC. It's just as good as your system is. If you've got the best card in the world, it'll look better than anything you've got.
Rob, what do you have to say? Rob is off, you know, scratching his head. I don't know. I have nothing really to say on Castlevania.
You know what's interesting? I don't own a Playstation 2 American, and I'm not really going to be importing any games outside of Bumani games, and games that are really really easy for me to understand, because A, it's too fucking expensive, and B, I don't have time to learn Japanese.
I have really no interest in getting a US PS2, so I really have no interest in US PS2 games.
I'm going to be getting Final Fantasy XM2, hopefully next month. I've already seen the ending.
No spoilers. You can just get a mod chip.
No.
Because any other game that's going to come out after that is not going to work.
So how about if you mod your system now and then Seventh Style comes out and it won't work with your system?
Then I'll go buy Seventh Style. I mean, Seventh Style will work as a purchased version. I don't need to take pictures of it to play it. And Seventh Style won't come out. What? What, Rob? What?
Well, I've heard that before about, you know, that you get the mod chip, and then Sony could release a game that would basically fuck up your mod chip, or, you know, they override the computation, kind of like they did with the early chips.
Right to the end of the PlayStation's life. Right. And what's interesting about that is what they could do with it is they could do it through online purposes.
It's possible, you know, if your PS2 is online, you go online with Final Fantasy XI, and then sneak-sneak, it's updating your BIOS.
That's why I just will play on the computer, because it's coming out for computer in America.
By the way, if anyone is interested in that, if you go to squareenixusa.com, you can submit an application to beta test Final Fantasy XI for PC or for PS2.
I really hope they choose me.
Please, please, Square, I've played your game since the beginning.
I'm more than positive I'm going to get selected because I've done game beta testing before.
I played Ragnarok online, ew.
Yeah, that sucks they didn't continue that over here, because I really want to play Ragnarok.
There's still one beta testing right now.
The paid release is going to be out, I think, for the next couple months.
And they are going to America with it? Because it sounded like they were neglecting America.
They have an American beta test open right now.
Well, I mean, it's a closed beta, but they have it going on right now.
I know it's been talked about on here, but for those who don't know, RagnarokOnline.com, I don't know how it's spelled, R-A-G-N-O-R.
R-A-G-N-A-R, okay.
Okay. It's a really cool game. It's like Secret of Mana and online or something. Is that what you'd say?
Yeah. It's 3D environment, 2D characters.
That's actually what I was thinking, is that every time I see Ragnarok Online, I go, God, I really want to play a Secret of Mana online. Seriously.
It's about the closest you can get.
It's like Secret of Mana with Final Fantasy Tactics-
And you can beat up ants and grasshoppers that play the fiddle.
Fucking fiddle playing grasshoppers.
I don't know if you've seen it, but PopCap.com, they're the folks that make Bejeweled and all those really addicting little web games that people play online.
Oh, it's pretty addicting. Atomica, you probably haven't played any of those games, huh?
Well, PopCap's the company that makes all those games. They have a new game on their site that's kind of like, you know, it's a multiplayer-ish type game, which is online world type thing.
Which, at first look, it kind of, you know, first instinct was, oh, it's like a 3D Ragnarok kind of thing.
But it still needs a lot of tweaking, but it's interesting. It's worth checking out at PopCap.com because it's free.
I think if you pay money, you get special things, but...
Hey, I'm still doing Neopets, okay?
I have not checked on my Neopets in two weeks. The damn thing's probably dead.
Give me all your money.
I don't want to give you my money.
If you love your pet, give me your money.
Why?
So that I can get up to 500,000 Neopets.
I think I have like 25,000.
That's actually about what I need.
Really? Mwahaha.
But seriously, I've been trying to get up to...
Is that like the last level of saving?
No. That's about free on it.
I'm trying to upgrade to my next bank account.
Okay, why don't we take ourselves a quickie little break. We're going to come back. We're going to talk about Max 2.
Max 2, Japan came out this week, and there's been some interesting early reaction.
We're sitting here on Thursday night, pre-taping Sunday show, and there's already been some early reactions.
Some folks in the States have picked it up and have some interesting things to say about it.
So we will take a quick break.
About the overwhelming lack of monkeys.
Yes, about the lack of monkey sex.
We're going to play some Anothers for the hell of it.
We're feeling saucy.
So let's start this off with Spica, Another.
We'll be back on Orange Lawns Radio.
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
Thank you for listening, and we'll see you next week.
Thanks for listening, and we'll see you next week.
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
Thanks for listening.