No! Message for you sir! Attention!
lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, orange lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
this episode.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gay?
No! What I expect for Spanish acquisition is gay.
Hey, hey!
Dark Sakura.
Shut up! Where's my gun? This is my boomstick.
Sky.
Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb.
Loki.
I can't for the life of me get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind of war human being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live, and this is episode number 40 for April the 13th of 2003.
You're tuned into the B-Money scene's most interesting radio station of all things B-Money!
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts in this corner of the Happiest Bunny on the
Farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
You know her better as Dark Sakura.
reppin cool
and uh... in the back playing with our brand new mixing boards t say hello to
our tech mass on loki
and then make sure it isn't going to be a little too much
and uh... also with us tonight will be turning down rob's channel a lot
hey now
are you saying that i have a voice that carries
this is great because you can see
with this new mixing board you can still hear me
The show is over the hill now.
I know! We're turning 40 tonight! We're over the hill!
You're like magical and stuff.
Does this mean we're going to have a mid-show crisis?
We just went after last week's breakdown mid-show.
Oh my god! I feel old! I need to go to the first gate!
Remember how we almost like had a big crisis mid-show last week? Like a giant fight?
Starting with zero? It was so neat.
No, that was just going off on a stupid song. But see, I am
the mid-show crisis. Have a good day.
Ooh, we'll have to hear more about that when we come back from the first break.
Sounds like we have a lot to be thankful for this week.
I'm going to have to get rid of the FUs and do a happy segment.
Fuck that!
Okay, fuck that.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Lots of people saying hello to Zero in the chat room,
including Angel and the other folks here.
However, if you want to get in our chat room and say hello, it's easy.
It's easy, just go to www.calibomani.com, our friends over there, and click on Orange Lounge and click on Chat.
It's just not supposed to be.
Alright, we're gonna start off this break with what, Jamie?
Crap!
This isn't crap, I like this song.
We're gonna start off with old shit.
Old shit, okay, so we're gonna hear some old Bomani music, and we'll be back to talk about a lot of stuff.
There's a lot, a lot, a lot of stuff to talk about this week, and by the way, tonight, you guys, get your friends on the station,
tonight we have Kyle Snyder's new single live from March Madness. I'm moist with anticipation.
It's a miracle I actually convinced him to sing it a second time, because he kept getting
getting interrupted, he's like, I'm not gonna do it anymore.
Smoke it out, when nobody wants to beat anyone, and nobody's backing me
I wanna be with the creatures of frames, I'll stand by the lights, watch the rain fall and say
Grab what you can, we'll head for the wild past three
La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La La
Now
Oh
When the time has still come, I'm gonna call your name
I don't want to die, you won't get it
Stay with me, Saturday, ladies
Stay close to me, cause I wanna see
Wanna see the color of the blue eyes, baby
This is the night, when you see the light
Of the fire burning in my heart for your big love
You get it, get it, daddy
Come on, come on
Yeah, Mr. Raps from the M.I.C.
This song get it, get it, all the young busy messin' up, you know
But you are getting so young, that goes in busy
Scared heart attack, a lot of woman talk, a easy die
Took guy to E-Wake, a girl, straight like law
You are a loss of law
Dance with my mom and my money
Not good standing, money
My money, not a man, no man, make money, money
I can't wait to see you again
I'm gonna do this to you
It's like you want, can't do it
You are the one who did everything
You're gonna be alright
I want to make you who you wanna be
Can't fake it now
I can't wait to go out
Just play with you with me all night
Yeah, everyday, everywhere
Come on, come on, make it so I can stay.
This is what, this is what.
I've been forced to pay, but who won?
You can't stay.
Now, I just can't, make it so I can stay.
This is what, this is what.
Hi ho, Kermit the Frog here,
informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio
is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
Okay, Japan Man wants to know where in the hell he can get his hands on that new slagwork remix you did that we debuted last week.
Um, nowhere right now. I'll put it up later.
Well, where's it going to be?
It's going to be on my site.
Where is your site, for those that don't know?
It's going to be www.willddrforfood.net slash leech from Loki.
Beautiful. So that's where you can download this new slagwork single. Whenever Loki gets off his butt and puts it up.
it up. Yeah. Or you can get it from Dark Sakura because she's got it too. You can beg
one of us in chat and we'll give it to you. Just not during the show because we're trying
to do the show. You have to offer me favors. You have to buy me that hot rod toy. Oh, I
can do this later. Keep going for it, I don't care. You know what, we totally neglected
the sim update last week, so let's just start tonight with the sim update, shall we?
Well, I got ahold of this guy who goes, what the hell is that? Oh, he got food. Not for
me though. Anyways, this guy is shoey. He's just done a bunch of stuff. He's, right now,
what he's been doing is like the DDR Game Boy stuff. He has all the sim files for all
the DDR Game Boy tracks. So, we've got those. But, we're going to swap our collections.
And this guy's got 4,000. And I have 2,000.
well but uh... he has like one of everything he he he
collects like
everything up the site so
you know whereas i might have like one good one for uh... you know
slide work whatever you'll have everything one ever made first light
work with
obviously i don't want to do but
it's cool you know so we're gonna be trading those and that's awesome and i
can't wait to do that
and then uh...
i finally got up all my uh...
uh... job uh...
downloading scripts so that's all up so you can actually get files now pretty
easy just going through the site
and then uh... i'm hopefully trying to do some more updates but it's been kinda hard
because i've been getting ready to pack and stuff and
you're not really been concentrating on doing a site right now so
i don't know uh... right now i'm averaging about one update a month so that's about
you know what we're gonna have been
aside from all that uh...
let's see
definitely check out bamani symptoms because you can always get you know new
files there even though some of them are like rehash old shit but you know a lot
of new stuff especially uh utter dude and he he does some really awesome sim
files he's like my number one now only because healing vision doesn't do him
fast enough but he'd be he'd be net my number one if you know oh speaking of
healing vision I'm gonna have he's my first sim file creator interview II and
so I've got that coming up along with all of his files so that'll be later on
And then, I don't know, just not too much going on. There's, you know, what was it, Havok got a hold of the EuroMix 2 disc, so he's ripping the banners and stuff from that. So hopefully we'll have some clean banners for that.
And then, oh, just a bunch of minor stuff. Not really anything new with stepping in, no new releases or anything. Yeah, Zero's files are back up on BimaniSims and, oh, that's pretty much it, you know, not too much.
All right.
So happy 40th birthday everybody.
We are 40 weeks old.
Actually we're older than that because we did two pre-taped shows and a pre-empted week
so we're actually somewhere around 43 or 44 years old.
But it's the 40th actual show you guys.
Favorite memory from the past 40 episodes.
What do you think?
Favorite memory from the past 40 episodes?
Out of every single show we've done, what was the funniest or best memory that we did?
My debut.
Which was, do you remember what number that was?
32.
I don't remember shit.
You remember, Loki?
I'm thinking.
This should be a list list some week.
We'll do that for 50.
I'm thinking because I want to say there was one that I had you guys laughing really hard.
I can't remember what it was.
It was one of the FUs of the week.
I just can't remember.
Anytime I have food, because I'm hungry and I'm broke at
the moment, I haven't taken any money out from the bank.
So I need food, but.
I would say episode, probably, either episode number eight,
which was the one, it was a really early episode.
We had DDR Mike and Jazz here.
I remember that, because that's when we had got into the
whole discussion about pantsless rage and
three-titted Emmy.
That's a classic.
and uh... episode i think it was twenty seven that was the one when angel and
stress that there were those are first visit town
that was the night
when i realized that orange long to take it over this house
because we're so damn many people here that night you remember that
it's crazy
and i quit myself
i don't know shit
some folks in the chat room say their favorite memory is all the poor talk
uh... i like when i had balls
What was that?
I don't know. It was the first time Jonas showed up.
Yeah, where's our balls? Jonas is supposed to bring some for us. We're still missing them.
You having trouble fighting your balls?
Yeah, because I paid him two dollars to go get them.
I hope he remembers to get food for me. Sending brainwaves, brainwaves, brainwaves, brainwaves.
Where's what? Video recorder?
Is that it on the ground? Okay. Actually, no. Jonas left stuff here.
My favorite thing was March Madness when I just went off.
I think it was so funny because I pissed people off. I don't know why.
Well, then I guess we could say my favorite thing was slowly becoming insane during Shaft.
Oh, yeah. That was classic.
I'm sick and I don't care. I want you to die. I'm hungry. Ooh, food.
Yes. I like that.
To avoid our coverage of Shaft and March Madness, we have B3 coming up, which B3 is the weekend of the 17th, I want to say.
God, I hope I'm not wrong. I'm not looking at a calendar, so forgive me if I messed up.
17th?
Isn't that right? Of May?
I hope not.
Why? What's that?
Because of E3?
Yeah, it's like right after E3. It's right after E3.
Is E3 the week before?
No, E3 is like Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, and B3 is Saturday, Sunday.
Shit, I hope... God damn it, I'm gonna miss Matrix!
No! Can't have this!
We're trying to see who we have to blow to get B3 tickets, by the way.
E3. I'm sorry. Oh, I'm sorry, yeah. We don't have to worry about B3 tickets.
But if somebody there needs blown, whatever.
I'm sure people would mind getting blown for free.
We're trying to get tickets to E3 really, really badly.
Don't put that up in my mouth!
I was trying to make you practice.
Rob's trying to shove the microphone up my nose.
I don't have to really say anything because this thing picks up everything.
I'm holding the microphone across the room, and it's blinking.
Missy?
Rob's taking volunteers of people he can practice blowing.
No!
For E3.
Not me.
Not me. That's why we have an intern.
Fuck you all.
I suppose we can talk about actual Bemani news tonight.
Alright, this is the one that's on everybody's mind and you know we have to bring this up, you guys.
The big, big news that comes out this week.
Electronics Boutique on their website is now taking pre-orders for Dance Dance Revolution
Xbox Mix.
This is Xbox, because you can't have an Xbox Mix, because that just sounds stupid.
What do you think of this DDR Xbox Mix?
Well, considering that it looks like it has characters again, obviously, so I'm wondering
if they're going to try to port the DDR PC version over to the Xbox, which I would like.
I'll read this story. This is the official story coming from GamingHorizon.com.
It was only a matter of time until we saw the popular Dance Dance Revolution franchise
scatter onto other consoles besides the PlayStation.
DDR first started in the arcades.
Electronic Boutique's website informs visitors of an upcoming DDR game from Konami entitled
Dance Dance Revolution Xbox.
The game is supposedly going to contain all new songs, exclusive tracks for North America,
Xbox Live integrations so gamers can download more songs, characters, and dance steps.
New game modes are also going to be implemented in that have never been seen before in other
DDR titles. Unfortunately, Economy of America hasn't sent out an official press release
yet concerning this recent news, but we can almost guarantee to see something during E3
in May.
Will we get stuck with another diet mode?
i think that this is it has as much a validity to it as uh... to yes you say
i don't know it's got picture
i can't i mean pictures are true great
they know is ever
take the picture of
i'm gonna dissent i think it's true
i i i really think this is true
because i just don't i don't see electronics boutique having that big a
balls
did you call me
you want to know what i think is absolutely stupid
DDRX or something, and so they call it Xbox.
As if it couldn't...
As if, where's the imagination there?
It could be a working title. Because it's only for the Xbox!
It's only for the Xbox!
And if you look at the box art, and I just posted a link in our chatroom
to this story,
it says, only for Xbox. But this is probably that fake art, you know how
sometimes the big gaming stores,
GameStop, EB, and all those. They do like the fake box art when they're doing it taking pre-orders?
I'm gonna go and draw
just DDR, Xbox, and put it up on the site and say this is the official art.
First of all,
it's DDR on a non-PlayStation system.
And I loved my Dreamcast ones, you know, they're great.
We can't make edits and take them with you.
And you can't use paint mode, I mean,
you know, paint
it was like the best thing about third mix
i think it's
a big pile of stinky dog poo
i guess we won't find out for sure till E3 but i don't know um...
i think
i think there's validity to it i just
it makes sense
microsoft's really straggling right now to get something that's going to be
successful for their system you get a really
popular kind of growing thing like DDR and there's going to be those
obsessive freaks that will buy an Xbox just for this mix.
I won't. I won't either, but there will be obsessive freaks that will.
Oh, I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't wait. Oh, wait. Oh, it sucks.
The Xbox is all about having Steel Battalion. So as the one person in this room who actually
owns an Xbox, Jamie, what games are worth playing on the Xbox?
The game of throwing the Xbox at children. Just Already a Future.
D.O.A. Beach Volleyball
There's nothing funnier than watching men
trying to accessorize a swimsuit
Fuck that, we're just trying to figure out how to take it off
D.O.A. 3 was good because I am a
fighting game heart
Fable, I'm looking forward to
club knockoff? Fable is an RPG where you start off with him as a child and you run through
this character's life and whatever decision that you make, like say you lose an eye, well
after a while the people might start calling you Winky or if you lose an arm you'll be
like Lefty or whatever. What if you are without arms and legs, what would they call you then?
target
but like um... they also have like if you you know kill um... like this whole
family and leave like a child alive
the child can make it their life's quest to kill you
or they'll be afraid of you or you know things like that it's like whatever
decision you make. So when your character goes and sexually molests other children and other families and then
they'll have issues later on in life
yes it would work that way
okay just checking
I don't know, I think it would be kind of neat, although I don't really like...
It's sort of like the typical American-looking art for RPGs and the like.
I don't really like how it looks.
But then again, I didn't like how Wind Waker looks in this neat game,
because, you know,
Link looks deformed and semi-retarded.
Because Link's in... Then again, it's not really Link, so it doesn't matter.
What game is this again?
win-waker
table
babu
japan
uh...
hill is pretty but it makes me throw up a lot of sucks act
hills hill so i think so
hill is not that bad it's good if you like a mindless
adventure shoot him up tight
where did you get them forever
Hello to the Ice Queen, by the way.
Oh yeah, hi.
No, I'm sorry, but Halo was alright, but I thought it got real repetitive after a while,
and Halo 2 is just gonna be just as bad, probably, except you can play it online supposedly, yes or no.
Who knows what they do anymore.
I want them to take the first Doom, and make it look really cool.
Yes.
Doom 3?
No, I don't want Doom 3. I want the first Doom done really cool.
I'm just waiting.
I want them to take Hexen, and not Hexen 2, I want Hexen.
I want them to do a sprite-based, first-person shooter collection, and I want it to work
with the Steel Battalion controller.
And I want them to have level editors so I can play Gachamon Quake.
They did a Gachamon skin for Quake.
I'm trying to figure out how to make a forest level for Counter Strike so I can have the
whole battle royale theme.
I have four characters made out of forty.
There's white cream on my shirt.
No comment!
No I would like to see...
All I'm waiting for is Return to Castle Wolfenstein on the PS2.
Why play it on PS2?
cuz i don't play on the computer soviet you can get all jagaty edges
and motion blur
most of my life jagaty edges in motion blur i'll have you know
you know everybody hates motion blur because of the bouncer it was nothing
but one big blur
or if there was a risk for people that there was to be
i wanted or tend to be a good day actually ended in have yet to play it
i wanted
Well, Dan got it for me because I'm a big Orphan fan. I love the anime.
I wasn't wondering about that, because I've played Orphan, the video game, and it was alright.
I mean, it was...
Well, I wouldn't say it completely sucked, just because I'm like...
I don't know. It was okay.
I slacked off on collecting the DVDs.
But is the DVD worth watching?
Oh God, the anime is awesome.
Really? Okay.
I've got like five laserdiscs of the second series, Orphan Revenge.
How many series are there?
Two.
And I think there's OAVs, I think.
Do they make the box sets?
That's...
Yes.
Yay!
Okay, now I have something to look forward to.
But, dude, well, Orphan's already...
I think the whole series should be out now, back on DVD, but I've only got the first three.
I totally slacked off on it, and I love Orphan.
Cool.
I've played stuff from, music from the series on one of my fuck-off shows before.
Buddha Me 2 is coming out, too.
Which one?
Buddha Me 2.
Oh.
This is...
Welcome to Anime Chat!
Hi.
EOSFBB says, remember Commander Keen?
That game was the shit.
That was the best game except there were like a million sequels and it got redundant.
Jazz the Jackrabbit.
No, I'm sorry.
Best Sonic ripoff ever.
Commander Keen 4 was like better than like Super Nintendo.
Leisure Suit Larry.
Anyway, back to DDR on Xbox.
Wait, it's all about the Crystal Caves.
Who in here remembers Phantasmagoria?
Okay.
A game I never got to play.
I know, I got to see the end of it.
of it but miss annoyed the hell out of me I have missed on Saturn I think I
still have the discs for phantasmagoria around here somewhere I'm gonna have to
find them for you everyone who has a Saturday we own you whatever you have
access I have two patterns also one's modded we add two styles of Saturn's the
The only reason why Jamie always says, everybody who has this raise your hand, because she
has everything.
She will always win.
I don't have a Jaguar.
You don't have a game slave too.
You don't have a crappy Jaguar, good, save yourself.
I want a Jaguar for the version of Tempest 2000 on it.
Did you ever see Sean Baby's list of the 10 worst video games ever?
Like five of them are Jaguar games.
And then the others are the Zelda games on 3DO.
of them was it was a 3d or cdi i think the worst game was what gilligan's island or something
i don't know i'll pull up the list no the worst one the worst things ever is the version
of et that's on the atari 26 yes that's it that was it that was it it was the et on
their whole little rumor is that they had there's like 2300 cartridges buried out in
like mexico or something that is not a rumor it is it really and i would have buried it
forum for free. That was bad and I can't believe they're making another ET game like a million
years after ET came out and is done and gone. They're gonna make... No, they're gonna redo
them to take out the guns and put in cell phones. Return to the green planet or blue
planet or whatever. How about return to my butt? Okay. Let's... This is an... This is
an interesting topic. This is an interesting topic so we'll just... Let's do this anyway.
This is Sean Baby's list of the 20 worst video games of all time. I wanna see if I own any
Hold on, I have to, um, hold on, we'll go through these one at a time, okay?
Okay, uh, I'm posting a link to seanbaby.com slash NES slash egm.htm.
We're gonna run through these right now.
Okay, 20.
Extreme sports with the Bearstein Bears for Game Boy Color?
No.
Oh my gosh, I remember that.
My little cousin had that, and I like, threw the Game Boy halfway across the room.
That was the worst thing ever.
Number 19?
Number 19 is Bible Adventures for the NES.
the zelda game on the gameboy
the old gameboy one
the where he like has a penis for a sword goes around you know
like dildo man or something
now do
do remember that this article is probably about four years old that we're
looking at something includes anything for game cube playstation two anything
like that that's one
next one is now this is great i think jamie owns this i do indeed own
crisscross make my video
and you weren't there when i wanted to know what she bought
i thought a brand new copy i was a liquidator really what i thought there
was a market mark when i watch about it i don't know about my problem but i do
want to cross one okay
we need to play that on the show yeah you gotta bring that i think i see
anything giving the crisscross one to dance for an eric
that get it back because we often
we need to instate like it or john's extreme challenge and have like you know
part of it to make the coolest video for it
these are things we need to bring the b_-three
we need to go and buy all these games and see who can stand to play them
I'll bring my CDX and the Marky Mark 1
number seventeen Bubsy 3D for the PlayStation
as if Bubsy 1 wasn't crap enough. Anyone ever play Bubsy?
I play Bubsy
and Bubsy 2
Holy shit! Bad Street Brawler?
that was a fun game
number sixteen is bad street brawler for the n-e-s
i came
would have this game the only game i can think of that was like worse than bad
street brawler and it's not on this list i can say it
was that fuckin by you billy
i did not like it you know i am by a billy
number fifteen is total recall for the n-e-s i used to have a kid
i feel it downstairs to death
have a picture of the three to the check your own some baby site
I'll tell you the worst one, hold on, is it on there?
I gotta make sure it's not there.
Well, no, we're gonna go through one through...
Oh, okay.
No, I know what you're trying to say.
All right.
Okay, no, the worst Arnold Schwarzenegger-based game was Predator.
On the NES.
I don't remember Predator.
Oh, it was bad.
You couldn't even jump when you needed to.
You'd like jump on his own.
Do everything on his own.
Oh, my God.
Number 14, Rap Jam, volume one.
Oh, God.
My friend had this game.
You could play Queen Latifah versus Coolio, all in a big game of basketball.
Dude, I'd play as Queen Latifah.
And they say, it says here on Sean Baby's site, Queen Latifah looks like a 130-pound
Mexican boy.
Alright, next.
Number 13 was Air Cars for the Jaguar.
Um, no.
It looks like a piece of poo.
Number 12, I think Jamie owns this, Night Trap.
Yes.
I want the 32X one.
night trap started driving through state of play dole
start and i think it was me night trap was good it was like the first real
controversial game out there that night
chapel required intelligence to play it because you had to know
what you monitor your things and that we've actually been done and i think it
was a little like i really didn't know all this other stuff
i want a new version of maniac mansion yes
it says i always made the house exploded they have a medium as a cartoon
That was a live-action TV show.
I have the data tentacle, and that was funny.
Monster in My Pocket.
Yes.
Monster in My Pocket, before there was Pokemon.
Okay, we're going down Sean Baby's list of the 20 worst games of all time, except it's
a couple years old.
No!
It's Dragonlance!
Number 11 is Dragonlance, Heroes of the Lance.
I want that game.
I don't even remember this game.
Because I love the books.
I don't care if the game sucks.
It sucks. It makes a complete mockery of the books.
I had one of the Dragonlance PC games that came on the big ass floppy disks.
I've never seen the PC version. I've only seen that version and that... no.
Yeah, because I read all the Dragonlance...
Okay, this one I absolutely agree with, because the home versions, even down to the Saturn version,
suck so much ass, Revolution X.
Aerosmith, Stars in Revolution X.
That was only good in the arcade. I could get, I could pick which toilet stall he was in, and I could, because you have to watch, when you first start the game, the cat, the direction that the cat goes in is which way you have to pick the toilet. And then you get one of them.
And I would do the one in the warehouse too.
I just played it yesterday actually at Scandia. It was the best, but the Super Nintendo version was, I gotta say though, the Super NES version was better than the PC version. The PC version was worse.
Okay, number nine. Jamie, do you have this one? Custer's Revenge.
I have a ROM of this. Dan has a ROM of this.
Yeah, I think a lot of people have the ROM, but nobody has the actual cartridge that we know.
If you want to think of it, I may actually have, we have a ROM chip player for 2600, and I think we actually may have the ROM chip for this.
Now for those that don't know what Custer's Revenge is, the way it works is you play a Custer, and your job is to fuck this woman with a feather in her hat over and over again.
That's a dildo on her head.
Or it's a dildo on her head, I don't know.
I like that caption.
And you have to dodge the falling arrows.
I like the caption it says erotic imagery. I've masturbated to sexier Legos
Okay, dude x-man is not on this
What's x-man x-man was this one where you you play as this little he looks like scissors except
It's a guy with a big dick the size of his body
And you walk through a maze and then when you get to the center of the maze and avoid the traps
You like have to there's this woman on all fours and you have to bone her
number eight white men can't jump for the Jaguar
whoops there it is
I hate that game I haven't played it because I got flacked for my last name
because of that stupid movie
number seven superman 64
played it never got it I knew it had potential to be cool
6. Zelda, the Wand of Gamelon
This picture is about to give somebody head.
Dude, it's like, it's the designs from the costume series.
Oh, yeah, it's so good.
Well, excuse me, princess.
Why is Link being played by Prince?
That's all I want to know.
All right, number five.
He's not Link anymore, he's like, an ocarina is like what his symbol is.
A game for the 3DO called Virtuoso.
Virtuoso, oh my god, no.
Being played by, um...
A hairband guy.
It's Vince Neil.
It's a succeeded film.
4.
Captain Novolin.
No, what was it on?
It's a game about diabetes.
It was put together not to educate children about diabetes, but to blatantly taunt their
disease.
Okay, I've played better flash games than what this looks like.
There's this flash game about sexually transmitted diseases, and you have to catch the jizz in
a condom.
This helpful nurse will come out and say, you need to check your blood sugar four times
a day, but you can check it more often if you like.
That's a helpful...
I don't want to stick a needle in my finger.
Here, let me do it 20 times a day.
No. Diabetes is nothing to joke about, but that's why this game is so bad.
I know it's not, but still, it's rather wrong.
That's why this game is bad.
Fight for life.
Number 3 is a game called Fight for Life from the Jaguar.
I think this game sucks.
Wow. It looks awful. Why is the sky green in there?
Wait a minute, that's one of my old nicknames.
Number 2 is...
Yes, Rob's old nickname is Why is the Sky Green Back There?
Number two is a game called Club Drive for the Jaguar.
It looks like, um, you remember Hard Drivin'?
Yes.
It looks like hard driving, like, but shittier.
Dude, I actually have a cool story about hard drivin'.
You know the deluxe one that had the chair that swung in and out and fell into the really
dark covered machine?
Mm-hmm.
Well, one time I was working at my arcade, and no one, I hadn't, didn't have any sleep
the night before, so I took a nap in one of those for four hours, and no one came in the
whole time
number one
as we mentioned earlier
the number one worst game of all time
e t the extra game and it's
all
pretty off me that
and and and and and the whole game
although i would actually and and and and and and and and and and and and and
with the e t sprite
and a big
anti
Don't be doggin' E.T.
Dude, I want a shirt with the dragon on it.
We should open up an Orange Lounge store that sells these things.
One of those crappy Cafe E-Press stores.
I've got one, too.
Well, let's just take a look.
All right.
I think what we're going to do at this point...
Did everybody get off their chest what they wanted to say about DDR on the Xbox and all?
I think that picked up on the mic.
quick question for you guys we're getting asked by the chat room about
this and I said yes because I know at least I'll be here next Sunday is Easter
are we still doing a show yeah anybody anybody have to celebrate Easter only if
I get to burn something I get Easter is really about the eggs who gives a crap
about this Jesus shit not going to be celebrating Easter we're gonna celebrate
Let's celebrate my birthday!
Oh, where did 420 come from? 420 is the police code. You know how there's all these police codes for different crimes? 420 is smoking marijuana.
I've got a 1337. I wonder what a 1337 is in police code.
I call a homestar runner break.
A homestar runner break? You want to do a homestar runner break? Did you bring some on your CD here?
And now more sounds of E.T.
In two weeks, however, we'll be taped.
Why are you sending me to Home Star Runner?
I have no idea what Jamie's doing.
She just took over my computer and she's loading up stuff on her Star Runner.
On my computer, I have it loaded to where it'll start up.
Hello stupid and welcome to your crappy computer.
I want that.
I can send you the MP3 if you really want it.
Cool.
It's from, it's Strong Bad saying it so it's pretty cool.
Oh dear.
Loading, loading, loading.
Eh eh eh eh eh eh eh.
I'm glad underscore v-mail dot v-x-e.
Answer.
Dear Strongback, why don't you and the Chief pull a caper of some sort?
It seems like there's been little cooperation between the two of you as of late.
James, Detroit mate.
Well, you're right.
It's no secret that the Chief and I haven't been getting along very well since he screwed up our last caper.
I don't care about the crosswords, man. Just the jumbles. The jumbles.
I don't know.
I don't know. Go look over there.
Look out!
Oh great man!
He's tall and sad.
Batman.
Who are you going to steal from my house?
We've been ID'd.
Every man for himself!
Thanks for stopping by you guys.
Thanks for breaking my cowlamp.
The cheat man.
Where did we go wrong?
Seems like just yesterday we were setting fire to Strong Sam's Underwears.
I was yesterday.
This one's for you.
I got mad at the cheat
For screwing up the jumbled paper
I hope I don't see his name in the paper
In the obituaries
His dad would mean he's dead
I'm so glad to cheaters not dead, the cheaters not dead
I'm so glad to cheaters not, Just a clap, just a clap
I didn't know you had any rhythm.
Oh sure, I got tons of rhythm.
You got the clap.
Keep it rolling for me guys, keep it rolling.
The cheetah.
I just wanted to say that.
Uh huh.
Oh, I can't stay mad at you.
Oh, how about a little kick for old time's sake.
And I'll have these kids, man.
But I don't...
Who's that?
Whoa! Watch me now! I had you there!
Okay.
Dude, what the hell was that?
You guys are so cute!
I should probably get dressed or something.
What is it, like three in the afternoon?
Looking good, Homestar!
Yeah, what's the deal?
Here, I didn't know you had to shave.
Oh, I don't. It's Cinnamon.
for a long long time two weeks ago during March Madness we had the world
debut of Kyle Snyder's song I could never be Japanese and you guys tonight
here it is an opportunity to go poop so this is it this is it the world premiere
well the second second premiere I guess because we already did this once we're
This is a clip from March Madness of Kyle Snyder singing his new song, I Can Never Be Japanese. Enjoy, you guys.
I remember when I was young It would come every Saturday evening
I would watch some Japanese TV It never did get boring
It was all I cared about There was nothing else for me to do
Then I suddenly hit reality And a message came through
I could never be Japanese No matter what it would never be
Even though I never gave up hope I had to face reality
I thought it would all end there, but somehow I kept going on I'm so interested in Japanese culture and that is why I wrote this song
If it weren't for my brother, I wouldn't know much about your culture
I would be so ignorant, it would be pure torture
I'm sure there are others who are into Japanese culture too
I'm glad I'm not the only one
Otherwise I'd probably be a fool
I could never be Japanese
No matter what it would never be
Even though I never gave up hope
I had to face reality
I thought it would all end there
Yet somehow I kept going on
I'm so interested in Japanese culture
That is why I wrote this song
There was much I didn't know
That I learned as the time flew by
I was shocked about what I learned
I didn't know why
Then it started to come to me
Though I wasn't born in Japan, life would be too hard for me
It must be part of the Lord's plan
I could never be Japanese
No matter what it would never be
Even though I never gave up hope, I had to face reality
I thought it would all end there, but somehow I kept going on, I'm so interested in Japanese
culture, and that is why I wrote this song.
I could never be Japanese, no matter what it would never be, even though I never gave
I had to face reality
I thought it would all end there
Yet somehow I kept going on
I'm so interested in Japanese culture
And that is why I wrote this song
This is fucked up
Here is justice. Here is punishment. Here is...
This is fucked up.
And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's
favorite perverse baumanni band, Erotic.
Do it all night.
Do it with me.
No, no, that was awful, bloody terrible.
Why don't you take vocal lessons? Kill your teacher!
In the heat of the night.
Oh god, I think my ears are bleeding.
I liked it.
Shut the bloody hell up, Paula. Next!
Oh, that was cool.
Do you even know why you're here? That was just bloody pathetic. Next!
Come on, baby. Come on, do it with me.
Yes, yes, that's it! We have a winner!
A star is born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
while I was singing, and I'm trying not to laugh. My face is actually bright red.
He walks away, I drop the microphone, and burst it into laughter.
It was so bad. That's why he got interrupted the first time.
Alright, the studio's
just erupted into chaos because we just had arriving. We have Dark Child's in the house, yay!
D Child in the heezy pacheezy.
And also back there, DDR Hollie, say hello.
Hi everybody!
Look kids, we have a new mixing board, isn't it pretty?
Yes, knows how you do not hear, but...
Where's the mixing board?
Ow!
That's worse, I feel bad for the people at home.
Also in that break, if you enjoyed that fucked up mix of Schlagwerk...
Ooh, yummy, cookie.
If you enjoyed that fucked up mix of Schlagwerk, you can thank Loki for that.
That's the dark, uh, that's the Schlagwerk, Dark Sakura will fuck you up mix.
Everybody should fuck someone up for that last one.
Also Gamelan de Couple, which we're finally starting to get...
We're starting to get some feedback in the chatroom that you know what you guys? Maybe that's overplayed a little bit. Do you think so? Do you think that song is overplayed or what?
It's back all over again everybody!
I have never ever had one of these before. Do I push the marble in?
No. Did you take the plastic off?
I took the plastic thing off.
Well there should be a green thing in there.
Oh.
now it's not
oh yeah i'm getting a lesson you take your thingy off
yeah it's good
cool
yeah it's
they do
no i don't want to see that
What? I haven't thought of it for a season.
What is this?
Everybody use your imagination at home.
I stuck it in my mouth.
Or better not, don't use your imagination at home.
Rob just didn't want to get it on the floor.
You know I just had to lick that all up.
Better to let it shoot off in your mouth, right?
Oh my God, my friend Garrett, earlier this week he took me to, what's that Japanese store?
Oh, Toto's I think it's called?
I think that's what the place was called.
It's over on, and I apologize for those out of Sacramento who aren't going to get this,
it's on Fruit Ridge and, Fruit Ridge and what's the other after, Freeport and Fruit Ridge.
That's where it is.
That's like a mile away from my house.
Okay.
They have...
If you're not in a car, don't go throughout the area, you will die.
I'm done.
We went and we got that and there was a reason I was
telling this story.
Oh yes, he bought the explosive Hello Kitty drink.
And it's this drink and it has Hello Kitty on it.
And it tastes like, do you remember those fruit candies
Mamba from high school?
Mamba candies.
It tastes like a liquid version of Mamba candies.
But when you open it, it opens worse than a bottle of
champagne.
He has to point it away.
We open it in his backyard.
And when you open it, the plastic top flew 40 yards, and he didn't even shake it.
So that's why we call it the explosive Hello Kitty drink.
You should shake it.
Yo, watch this, pointy-handed bird.
Shake it and take it to RVGL.
Oh!
Oh my god!
That's a great idea. Who wants to take an exploding Hello Kitty drink to RVGL?
We can, like, shake it up, like... First of all, who wants to go to RVGL? Cricket noise.
you can hurt you know i think it's an rv g l
i dislike pick the crap out of some stupid little river kids
ideally funding for me to do it i'd be jealous to have people thrown out
which i do and that's one of these every time we go to another uh... he was
looking at me for a like him and he had else
now i do that can if i don't like people there
i haven't run out
and the people happen out of the people who are being disruptive and causing a
big thing anyway right
So, I have people throw it out all the time.
I'm eating.
You know, we kind of got it on a tangent.
We were talking about bimani news.
We had tons of it to cover.
And then I got my pillow back.
Kickass!
Everybody!
What do you want to talk about now then?
Sleepy time!
There's still plenty of bimani to talk about.
about something new? Sure. Let's talk about DDR Ultra Mix. I was about to say that. That
is the stupidest idea in the world. Why? It's DDR PC 2. No, it's Ultra Mix. Get it right.
It's Ultra Crack. I mean, ooh, what, are we going to have more lovely characters that
we're all going to drool all over? No. Trojan Man is the first unlocked, just so you know.
This is being leaked, by the way. Somebody had discovered this on the ratings board website.
There was this website that you go to to get the ratings.
How sad is it that people browse that site to look for new games that are coming out?
Huh?
Yeah, it worked.
This is something I brought up in the chat room a few nights ago when I mentioned this for no apparent reason.
It's like, probably about 85-90% of the Bimani community, probably worldwide, knows about
StepMania or knows about DWI. So it's like, why waste however much they're going to try
to charge you for this stupid-ass game and just go spend a few hours a day downloading
a bunch of songs and you'll be just fine? Or do you really want the most retarded characters
in the world?
Because it's all about the kick-ass characters and the possibility that there might be new
new stuff even though there will never be new stuff. Now, Jazz in the chat room makes
a good point. You can't judge it till you play it. Oh, okay. Sure. I'm going by track
record here. Well, I don't know. If I'm correct, I've heard that from plenty of people before
DDRPC came out. You know, oh, you can't judge it before you play it and then you play it
and they get mad at you for judging it
it sucked and they all suck
wait what am i sorry did you say i was a guy?
alright i heard that about anal sex one time but uh...
i'm not going to try it i'll judge it before i try it
you know we were doing really good with this show not going any type of porno way
and now all of a sudden ANAL SEX POP
the
house and i saw a seriously
the else has something they want to say about uh...
the role to mix
what new characters can we look forward to wonderful ideas will come out of
America come out with
ultra active
there's a list
will we get another paranoia
nope
did i'm so tired of her and i
may have one more time and i want to find someone
you know i don't think there are a lot of survival and i had
that was the only way
good one that in evolution
well marionette survivor max is so original to with it and if you think i
was led up
all rightly as far as i'm concerned
paranoid is done
now he needs to die
and
well though he died and there would be no songs for dvd art is every hour to
say but that may be good cool do all the music that we need to get me to cool
intact to do all the music
and talk at the
but no key
now he needs to go back and do more great music
it here you know that
and yet we need more young ok
uh...
but seriously though they were
what they need to do
didn't seem like everything with the action which is being lazy
but they're leading in the whole of my system they're lazy on the songs that
they put in there they're lazy on the soundtrack to be released
into the whole things like you know
i could have made this a good game but you know i just kinda want to sit down
and sleep
Here's something more fascinating than DDR, whatever that crap is, Ultimate Battle 22.
We went to extreme.
Meat eating Pucky is more amusing.
Here's the reason why I figured they didn't really care about how well they made extreme.
Because they know that they have the fan base, and they know that every-
That's wrong, I don't want to see that, thank you.
Anyways, they know that people are going to play a game no matter what.
For the record, Rob did something phallic.
Anyways, yeah, so Ultramix sucks ass, and I won't buy it, but I'll download it off of some site, I'm sure.
I have video game news.
Oh.
I got you something.
Hold on a minute. Jamie, everybody has an announcement.
I have two announcements, and neither of them are related to Bivani, shock shock shock shock!
The first one is in a few weeks from now, in IRC, or possibly AIM if I'm feeling like
being, you know, nice to people who don't use IRC, I'm going to be running a battle
royale game stat-based like a tabletop game except on IRC and then I saw
something cool one of my friends online made me download something cool it was
the the teaser for Kingdom Hearts 2
it's it's really cool except there's all this like neat hardcore fighting and
It's like one of the people doing hardcore fighting, landing in cool poses while wearing lots of black is Mickey Mouse
So with all this hardcore fighting, is there any hardcore sex?
I don't want to know about that associated with Kingdom Hearts 2. Thank you very much
Yes, I do. You just do it with the Final Fantasy characters. You don't do with the Disney characters
this is the best fan art ever for anyone who remembers the race at the beginning of Kingdom
Kingdom Hearts. This is the best fanart ever.
What's the score now, Eric? Don't you agree?
Final Fuck X, yay! Kingdom Heart On.
I don't know, maybe that's the name of the doujinshi somewhere.
Kingdom hurts!
Oh my god.
This could like take up the whole show right here.
I'm fine with that.
RPG related
Like Secret of Mana, Secret of Flesh or something.
Welcome to the Temple of But.
Poking at Mana.
Ness151 in our chat room has an interesting motto for life.
When life gives you a lemon, toss it back and scream HENTAI!
Toss it back and scream, HENTAI!
You know, my friend was telling me about this porn, about this lemon, but never mind.
When life gives me lemons, I poison the lemonade.
That's beautiful.
When life gives me lemons, I decide to talk about something else.
Okay, anyways, DDR Max 2 obviously is coming out in like two weeks, more information being
released by Konami.
Of course, we know we were, you know, assuming that there's going to be more stuff about
the being able to create Oni's and that is in there, that you can create your own Oni
courses.
So that's kind of cool.
Plus, as before, we were talking about previous songs from DDR Extreme which are going to
be in there.
Two confirmed songs from Konami right now are Level of Shine and Crash.
Stop it with the ninja cookie thingies, crackers.
I am disappointed by this box of pokey.
It does not have a special unit CD, but the words special unit are really funny.
I have a special unit.
You and your special unit can go stand in the hall, sir.
Will there be any good porno in the hall?
Yeah, why don't you go see?
Then I guess me and my special unit won't be working together today.
Oh, there's a barcode.
code I win a special unit CD I've been asked to play a movie that we got here
in the chat room I don't know this might cause drops though so if this causes too
many drops we're gonna have to cut we're gonna have to cut this segment but we'll
try it because I have done movies on the show way back on episode number like
three or something you remember that whole controversy I wasn't here I
remember I remember ever the you know it's like a giant spaceship place oh
Oh yeah, we did play that. You were here for that.
We need to do that promo back in.
We'll play that after the next break.
Okay, but anyway, let's see if this will work.
I don't know, we might have some dropouts, but we'll see if it works.
Okay.
Loading, loadingly.
Here we go!
Zelda, Duke Onkka is under attack by the evil forces of Ganon.
I'm going to Gamelon to aid him.
But father, what if something happens to you?
I'll take the Triforce of Courage to protect me.
If you don't hear from me in a month, send Link.
Ampa!
Don't worry, Zelda.
The Triforce of Wisdom promises the king will safely return.
Enough! My ship sails in the morning.
I wonder what's for dinner?
Oh boy! I'm so hungry, I could eat it off the rock!
I'm so hungry, I could eat Zelda!
he's Zelda. Shut up, you hippie!
Dude, she's touching him erotically.
Dude, Link is totally gay.
Great, great.
Wake up, Impa. We're going to Gamelon.
Alright, dear. I'll get the Triforce of Wisdom.
Beautiful. You wanna see another movie from that game?
What's that Gamelon?
Alright.
One more.
Since there's such a huge demand for it, let's see another movie.
Rob, can you give me back those minutes of life you just wasted?
No. In fact, I'm gonna take more.
Gee, it sure is boring around here.
My boy!
Cuz I'm playing this game!
I'm a true warrior strive for!
I just wonder what Ganon's up to.
He's wearing lipstick.
No teeth.
Your majesty, Ganon's up to the island of Koridai.
Oh my god!
A son of bin lion came to visit them!
Hmm, how can we help?
It is written, only Link can defeat Ganon.
Great!
I'll grab my stuff!
There is no time.
By Ganon we mean George Bush.
enough how about a kiss for luck you've got to be kidding squatter that we are
off Wow what are all those heads these are the faces of evil there's a big
conquer each I guess I better get going here is the map where do you wish to go
the
are you violated one more quick one quick one
oh i have to click play i forgot to click play
the game is not recognized as part of the Zelda universe.
I don't know, did you play Majora's Mask?
Yeah, Majora's Ass.
Um...
Yeah. So...
Also in Bamani news this week, we can talk about this. This is big news.
This has all the kids excited.
2DX Night Style!
Is location testing!
I love the look on his face.
Some of the songs that are going to be in 2DX9 style, I have to find the link to that
page.
They have it?
I'm going, I'm trying that, but there was another, there was another site that also
had, there's a site, the Japanese site that had all the 8th style location tests that
has it too, and I don't remember where that's at.
I am two seconds behind Rob on Legend of Max.
Since I could finally get back to the stage now.
I don't remember where that one site was, the Japanese site.
It's not coming up.
Snore.
Thank you, somebody gave me a good link.
Thank you, Arcadian42, you gave me a good link here.
That's the one I was looking for.
They're going through the whole solar system.
That'll be beautiful.
Sampling Masters Aya, Sampling Masters Mega, both of them.
Emotion 2003.
Emotion 2003, which is EOS remixed by Taka.
But I thought Taka did the Emotion remix that's in Core.
BeatMania Core.
Well, that was also called Romantic.
So it might be the same damn song, for all we know.
No, it's Emotion 2003. Get it right.
Good Cool, featuring Andrea L. Hopkins, called Your Body.
You got a grooved, extended joy style.
A new Naoki Underground song called Prelude.
Akira Yamaka with a song that's in Japanese.
I think it's called Body, or that's the genre's body.
Lion something.
No new Orange Lounge song in 2DX9 style, which is kinda spooky.
This is the Heavens remix by Ryu, the guy that won the remix contest back then who did Starmine.
I believe he has a new song in this also.
Ryu has a new song? I didn't see that listed.
I thought. I looked the list really quickly.
chat rooms, kind of making some observations, like there's a lot of collaborations. Oh,
Arcadians got it. It's Lion Suki. That's it. No new Orange Lounge song listed as of yet,
but if I remember right with eight styles test, the Orange Lounge song didn't show up
until after, it didn't show up till later. I want Pocky.
There was also two different ones. There's sampling masters Aya and I guess Aya, whatever,
Okay, here we go. There's some screenshots of night style right there. Again, it's very
blue and orange. It's got like the space station theme here. It's kind of interesting. But
look at this. What do these look like?
Looks like e-cards.
They look like e-cards.
Because they say E on the bottom. That's the whole... Okay, how much you want to bet? Okay,
I'm going to...
here first there will be e-cards for Extreme 2. Oh for the new DDR whatever it is? Oh I'll bet you
I bet you there will be in fact it will get rid of the whole memory card thing. It seems to be the
way where Konami is going between Guitar Freaks and Pop Music. I have this feeling that they're
going to bring out some type of reader to use with your PlayStation 2 or whatever that reads
those cards you know another system they tried to do that with the Neo Geo where
the old MBS units you could take a card and put it on your Neo Geo system at home
I've got I've actually got the Neo Geo with the slots open on it I just haven't
found a machine with working MBS slots all of our slots are wide open you said
it not mean well isn't that special I think now is a good time for us to take
a quick break and we're gonna come back and do the F use of the week we have to
play that one promo one promo oh yes right we'll play that when we come back
so if you want to send it in over private message right now the F use of
the week you can send them over p.m. to me in the chat room hi I'm sky and to
To get to our chat room, just go to callebomani.com, click on Orange Lounge, then click on Chat.
It's just that simple.
We'll take a quick break.
We're going to start it off with something from 8 style.
We're going to play some tack.
I only have the long mix of abstracts, is that cool?
You want to hear A?
Okay, we're going to play some A songs.
We're gonna play abstract, the radical mix, and then we'll play A, and then we'll be right back with the FUs of the week, so send those over private message right now to me.
...
Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of
the Orange Dance Baymara Music and More show?
The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
It's unearthly.
It's like being in a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
That sounds like a guy who must have been part of Heaven's Gate or something, talking about going to spaceships and shit.
We're having fun opening Ramune.
I don't have a...
Ra-moo-nay.
Ramune.
Even if there's a Ramune named Ramune.
Rob's a hick.
Honky.
Okay.
Alright kids, shall we do the FUs of the Week now?
No, because Jamie has to go watch her guys.
Dark Child 1 didn't know where that promo was from.
That was that little clip where the guys talk about Dancing on Spaces.
That's from a movie. Do you remember the name of the movie?
Somebody entered it into some San Francisco film festival.
It was in San Francisco. It was somewhere back east, like Rhode Island or some crap like that.
Delaware, I don't know.
Anyways, it was on the KOA site. Um, I don't know where it's at right now, but yeah.
Okay, um...
Alright.
Okay. Are we ready for the interviews of the week now?
No, I heard... Okay, really quickly, this needs to be really quick.
Sure. Sure.
Um, oh, and, and watch, watch, watch the board.
Hey! It's a board!
I heard something about there was a rumor going around about karaoke karaoke revolution
yeah that's also listed on EB's site if I'm not mistaken it was either on EB's site or
the yeah so now there was that there was that E3 press release that came out a couple weeks
ago that started all these rumors because it said Konami will have you dancing and playing
outdoors and singing in 2003. And that kind of made people go, what does that mean? And
as far as I thought, I figured that meant that they were probably just going to bring
karaoke mode back into DDR. You remember in third mix, you'd have the lyrics on the screen?
So you two could sit at home and go, oh, Nick, please, not so quick. You know I want it big.
That would be cool to come back, though. And then I believe there was a DDR machine
that also had karaoke in it, if I'm not mistaking.
Akuma GM says something like that. Very rare. Yeah, they're very rare.
But I think there was, there was a separate machine.
But then there was also, wasn't there a standalone? Okay, you were thinking about that.
I was thinking you were talking about the standalone karaoke game. Like the one they have at CyberZone?
Should I go to CyberZone? No, I've never been to CyberZone.
But you may have heard about it.
Okay, like I like karaoke. You're pretending that I care about karaoke?
I think you just don't admit it.
I just think it'd be awesome for a segment, okay? That's all I'm saying.
Blink.
Karaoke is Japanese for tone deaf.
Can we do the fuckies of the week now?
Yeah.
go.
Okay.
Here is justice.
Here is punishment.
Here is...
Okay.
My five year week goes toward onedollarhosting.com for having morons for techs who don't know
I know that when I say moving to new server, that does mean moving to new host as well.
If I say I'm moving to a server, you know what that means, right?
Okay, everybody knows what moving to a new server means.
Apparently the techs at One Dollar Hosting do not.
So they're big morons built stupid heads.
They're monkeys that fling poo at each other.
Okay?
And that's a lie.
Okay, I'm sorry.
That's a lie too.
It's not really one dollar because you have to pay a membership fee.
paying one dollar a month.
I'm done. My angst is somewhat worn off.
on may 15th and not last friday and the fact that um um you suck
yeah warner brothers they suck ass there's one more reason why i hated them but i can't remember
what it is offhand yeah because they smell and um let's see there's also a big f-view for um
Stupid people of Scandinavia, because that's so generic, and stupid spammers, and...
Damn it, I...
Bammers, you jackass!
Spaniards, what fucking problem is...
Ugh.
Oh, let's see.
Oh, oh, oh, and also to the core, because that movie sucked ass and should have never been made, and it was a waste of time for anyone that went there.
In fact, that movie probably slurred your soul, so, um...
Then why did you go?
I didn't go.
Oh.
Hahahaha!
Haha!
Yes, I didn't go, but I can still base it on that.
Um...
Um, also a big eff you to New Line for releasing, uh, Kangaroo.
Or, that stupid kangaroo.
Kangaroo Jack.
Captain Jack.
See, now, that would be more entertaining if it was Captain Jack running around in the,
you know, the Outback, and, you know, two or three people shooting at him.
Well, if it was Captain Jack, there would have been a wet t-shirt contest in there.
I want to go see the movie! Now!
It will be there when you get back.
E3 is not going to be there.
It will be all over the internet.
I don't want to see the movie opening day!
You can see it down in L.A.
I want to see it opening day! I already bought tickets!
You can see it?
Why would you want to go there opening day with all those stupid geeky guys dressed up like Neo?
Because he is one of those geeky guys who dresses like Neo!
I set that one up for you perfectly, Dara.
You're welcome.
The glasses and the trench coat still sue me.
Did you see his dynamite rave routine at Scat?
Did you see it?
You have all two seconds of it.
Yeah.
I don't really have that much this week.
I was pissed off during the week and then I just slowly cooled off.
I hate that.
See, fuck off shows will be awesome when we move because
I'll be able to spout off my dislike for society on a daily basis.
kostjamrh My f-view of the week goes out to Pokemon Ruby, because ever since I bought that game, I can't stop playing it, and I feel really immature. But you know what, it's fun.
How many Pokemon are in that one?
Like, about 200. It's a lot.
Really quickly, this will only take a second.
FU to the press, because they don't realize that all these Iraqi children that are killed in the street are probably from all the gunshots that people are firing in celebration of the fact that the regime is over.
They don't realize that bullets go up and then they come down.
Why are all my children dead? I do not know!
so
right
I'm they fire off a gun and there's birds falling everywhere
squirrels little Iraqis suicide bombing squirrels
you know I came up with a good idea for your Pokemon thing is if like they had
like a fighting game
where the Pokemon actually had to fight each other. Pokemon stadium!
no like to the death and like there would be three to
There'd be like different, yes, there'd be like different classes. There'd be adults, and then little ones, and then some of them have their stages.
Yeah, yeah, like, you know how you have like Pikachu becomes Rayachu, and that's all they have, but then there's ones where it's like Squirtle, and then I forget what he changes up to that, and then he becomes Blastoise?
Yeah, Wartortle.
Anyways, there's one more thing really quickly. They're releasing a live version of Battle Angel.
Battle Angel. Remember the cybernetic chick that fights people and shit? A live action version.
Are they basing it off of a comic? Yes. Because the comic strolled.
Alright, I didn't really have any FUs of the Week outside of that, so I guess I'm done. Let's go around the room and hear from everyone else.
Zero.
Okay, I actually have a couple, not a whole lot, and this is the worst music to choose.
What a feeling!
Anyways, no, um, okay.
One of them I realized at Arden Fair Mall.
To the stupid bastards who can't wash their hands after they go to the bathroom.
I don't want to touch the fucking door handle after you touched it.
I don't want your lemon juice all over my hands.
Um...
After the stup-
I don't give a shit what it is, it's fucking gross.
And then, like...
No, and then the next thing is, for the people who made those stupid hand dryers, make them
warmer or something because make them actually fucking work.
You're not reading the directions, it says rub your hands together.
It works.
Trust me.
No, you know what those hand dryers are for?
No, I know.
You have those in the men's restroom.
In the men's restroom.
You want to know why?
So they don't have to restock paper towels for us.
Women have paper towels.
They also have nice mirrors, nice toilets, everything's clean.
is
it's not like you're in in this one of the dumbest people in the universe
and i water everywhere
and like another f you don't go through the whole thing
used to die quickly
is it's gone way too long
followed by uh... you have a stupid lately because that's not to and you do
Yeah, bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Magic cards were cool, like, I don't know, ten years ago, or whenever they came out.
And, um, exactly!
It's not pretty, Hashi, the old cartoons!
They weren't good, they-
Oh, ooh!
Oh, I mentioned this later. Never mind, that's alright, that's fine.
Oh, one more thing, uh, F.U. the Konami for not releasing the VR stream,
because I'm starting to get bored with the VR stream.
I have another F.U.
I'm getting bored.
My other F.U. of the week goes toward not having money, because there's certain things that I need.
I need a tablet, a graphics tablet for my computer.
I need a light table to use for my art.
I cannot find...
Where do I get non-photo blue pencils?
I need non-photo blue pencils.
I know where you can get money for that stuff.
Put it on a wish list.
What?
You should do what those people do on the internet, like the ones who say,
my bills and people send them like five bucks just tell people help me help me
make my comic help me help an aspiring you know comic art the thing is is that
my comics gonna be all fucked up anyway hello I guess fucked up comic sell well
that's the whole point I don't know would anyone in here buy it if I'd like
published it I'd buy it because I like your I like your writings as it is you
should make a comic of it well my other big fuck you goes toward not having a
a proper drafting table and illumination because once I scan in all the stuff that I've drawn,
I see all this crap that I missed because I don't have the proper light to do any of
it. So yeah, fuck not having a drafting table with a built-in light.
F you to not having money, okay? I have to get a fucking costume ready for the damn convention
and I have no money. We're going thrift store shopping.
I know, I found out the perfect idea for the number two is to-
I figured it out. Actually, he helped me figure it out later. Anyways, I'm done with my F.U. because, just, fuck that.
No! Some of us other people have fuck-yous too.
Okay, fuck you then.
No, don't fuck both of us. Anyway.
Okay, come on, continue. Is Anita up next? I'm sorry.
Okay, alright, I'll go next. Um, mine's not very long.
Okay, first of all, fuck you to Roosevelt Golf Land for getting rid of the Para-Para-Para machine.
I'm highly disappointed, now I have to- Huh?
Yeah, fuck them in general, but fuck them especially, most especially because they got rid of Para-Para-Para.
Now I have to go very, very far away to play Para-Para-Para.
You should get the PS2 version.
I don't have room, but I could try.
It's not the same.
Hey, it's fine. You can be even stupider in your own house instead of out in the shade with a bunch of people.
Okay. Well, this leads into my next Fuck You of the Week, which is
Fuck You to Milpitas Golf Land, because they have
Okay, just Disney Disney mix that stupid Disney DDR. I hate that game because
Because you can't see the damn arrows and when you start messing up
They start to flicker and you can't tell what the hell you're doing. Plus Milpitas has like big-ass fan in front of you
So you feel like you're in a tornado while you're trying to play DDR. It really sucks. I can't breathe
I can't see so I fail every time and also
Oh, I had one more from Milpitas. I forgot what it was. Oh, what's that place we went
to with all the video games and the alcohol? Dave and Busters. Fucking at Dave and Busters
we're not having any bimani. Dave and Busters doesn't have any bimani? None. What? But they
have alcohol. They have alcohol. They had Pump It Up. They have Horse Crack at Dave
but
this derby orders but yes
but no money around really sex
so anyway those are my book usually thank you very much
hook me up, I'm next, I have a quick one
don't say no to me
i owe you
uh... hit and slap on uh... file mix
okay whatever
okay my fuck you goes to another fucking old one or whatever but
people on the internet who don't want to label files correctly
when they're sharing on pcps and stuff
i downloaded a seven hundred and twelve megabyte file
yesterday and and and i'm gonna sell and it should go fast but it's on kazaw so it was
going at like at the fastest 20 anyway it took it took uh like a day to do i try to
install it it's return to castle wolfenstein it's supposed to be grand theft out of white
city i i was like yeah yeah exactly wait wait i was like exactly return to castle wolfenstein
fine i'll play that it gets all the way through the installation to 99 this file is corrupt
Please download it again.
I'll give you that game.
Oh, cool.
Make a picture of it.
That will teach you the pirate software, little boy.
You haven't come out for the PC yet.
Yeah, you tell that.
But there are, like, release betas out there.
Ah, that's what you get for trying to get that.
See, I had the same thing where I tried to get Lord of the Rings 2, and I got Sorority
Boys.
I got Sorority Boys all the goddamn time.
Sorority Boys was, like, everywhere for a while.
Like, any movie you downloaded was Sorority Boys.
we're going to have an evil time once battle layout 2 is out
what was the other one, oh there was another one I tried to download that said it was GTA advice city
and it was like uh
some, it wasn't porn but it was like some kiddie game
it was like Mavis Beacon 2003 or something
as if, Mavis Beacon's the shit, I'm sorry
as if it's a little
that's how I learned to type
I already know how to type, I learned how to type from playing on IRC
on Mavis Beacon.
Yeah!
You're gay, dude.
If you didn't get that, Zero says Mavis Beacon is the city where the 50-pound black woman.
Is she really?
Mavis Beacon is the Oprah of computers.
Oprah's not 250 pounds.
She was.
Maybe her breasts are.
You know what's really, really, really scary?
She's gonna be posing nude.
No.
Yes, serious.
the one who can you know shave off 300 pounds off of her but oh really this
week for a lady of her age she looks pretty good she's like 50 something or
about 50 I don't know but but the point is we don't need to see her naked I
don't want dr. Phil jacking off to her magazine Oprah needs to gain 200 pounds
it
people
that people lose personality when they lose weight they lose IQ too
they turn into hoes and lose IQ
let's get through the last two people FUs in here please
okay my FU time
Fuck you, Anthony for kickin' my ass in Street Fighter II.
That's the only fuck you I can think of because things have turned around.
I can't really say fuck you to anything.
I'm not pissed off anymore.
Fuck you for me not being pissed off no more.
Fuck all of you.
Okay, uh, I have two fuck yous. One is to Zelda, the Wind Waker, okay?
It's an awesome thing.
Or you don't need to fuck you for having Zelda. I don't even have it. I can't get it because they're out of stock everywhere, I guess.
Fuck you for telling him to fuck off because he has Zelda.
Yeah. Anyway, fuck you to Zelda, because the story was so incredibly cool. I won't spoil the ending for any of you, but if you play it, you'll know what I mean, I think.
Link wins.
link does not win
like i said i'm not spoiling it for anybody
so fuck you to zelda because you'll see what i mean when you play it
yeah and the fact that link looks like a monster
and especially fuck you to that little kid with the booger hanging out his nose on your home island
my second fuck you is fuck you to the world for not giving me anything to
complain about this week except zelda i mean my god
i'm actually happy this week and that's not okay
fuck you to this week
Because it seems like everyone who normally has lots of fuck yous has lame fuck yous because they're too goddamn fucking happy.
Yeah, Jamie's were cool, though.
Alright, let's see what the chat room has to say.
Let's get into the chat room.
No, we're going to do the chat room fuck yous now. Here we go.
USFBB would like to say, um, fuck you to whoever decided that POWs are heroes. What the fuck? If you're a prisoner of war, that means you fucked up.
That was more politically incorrect than anything Loki's ever said.
Who said that fuck you?
What's the screen name? Who said that fuck you?
P.O.S. F.B.B.
U.S. F.B.B.?
Alright, well what the fuck is that?
Fuck you. P.O.W.s are fucking the shit.
shit you know what kind of hell they have to go through they fucking get
tortured and all this shit they are fucking heroes because they made it back
alive that's because I'm an ex-military guy so I swear to God it's only irony
that I have this background song I didn't plan that Wow okay nest 151 says
F used to me being poor and not being able to play DDR anymore no tokens equal
no life
get a hook up at golf land and scandia then you won't have to pay for tokens
remember that we're an international show so they don't have golf lands and scandias
everywhere
alright uh... muhimer says fuck xenon for having such sucky easy steps
fuck people for sucking and people all PMSE
fuck coalition
is that coalition i have no idea, cotlession dates
You barely know who are friend of friends who don't leave you the fuck alone all night like they own you
It was so bad in fact that I had to ponder using the I'm gay approach to get her the fuck away from me
You know I just have to say this over air. What do you mean Jamie? You have a little bit of drool right side?
It's gone
It's original
Soutome Ranma would like to say, alright, F used to no new Murmur Twins lady song, that's
you tokiwa.djw song, and also to Shitty E-Cards taking over everything from drum media to
Animal Crossing, as well as Battle Royale for Haunting My Dreams.
Wait, somebody needs free web space, try flatface.net.
No, we don't need free web space, we actually need to be on our good space.
Who needs free web space try my server in my friend's closet
Dark Tetsuya would like to say fuck being single and not having enough nerve to talk to the ladies
Just do it screw thing here's two balls here have
He won't talk to ladies. Is that what it was? I exed out of it already. I think it was
This is going to be Jamie being a bitch, and please forgive me for being a bitch.
Get over it!
Just go out there and do it, and stop being sorry for yourself.
Yeah, you know what?
That brings me to a fuck you I can remember.
I'm going to say it now.
I'm going to just jump in on these chat room ones.
Fuck you, Vaj.
Vaj, come on, man!
You had D.D.
Archaholic go up and pimp a chick for you.
Get some fucking balls, man!
It's just a girl!
Hey, hey, hey!
best advice ever. If you want to talk to women, go to a fucking strip club because they're
forced to come talk to you. They will carry on a conversation for long hours and you don't
have to pay them shit. They'll just come talk to you and then after you get done with the
conversation, they'll be like, do you want a lap desk? No. See, it's perfect. You only
spend an initial $20 to get in, but talking to strippers is awesome and you'll just totally
get over the whole fact that you're intimidated by women because they're really hot. Or you
Maybe we can go to a hospital to ER where people are stuck there laying in their hospital beds and can't get away.
Oh my god.
It's because when you're talking to hot, retarded women, it's not very intimidating.
When you're talking to hot, intelligent women, that's why I'm intimidated.
You must be going the city limits, man, because fucking me, dude.
up
all right so this is what i'd like to say fuck you did cap penis sucking tree
hugging weed smoking hippies
the thought it would be a very cool idea to take a perfectly good
fd rx seven twin turbo
without the motor and slam in some weak ass electric piece of shit motor how
fucking dumb can you be
you take a rare special and very fast sports car and you turn it into some fucking
tree hugger beacon
that radiates pure shit fuck you
Also, fuck you to this thing, and he gives a couple flash things that I'm not gonna look at right now.
Uh, fuck you to the people who made those for not giving out any warnings to people who have heart problems.
I don't personally, but those could either A, kill fat people, or B, scare the holy living shit out of kids.
Maybe some people, not even kids. I mean, those are just kind of fucked up.
There's some fucked up flashes that I'm not looking at right now.
Angel, I would like to say F you to whatever sickness everyone is getting,
because I caught a bit of it too earlier in the week.
F you to Magus being away, and yeah, I'm better now.
By the way, I haven't gotten sick yet, just letting everyone know.
The point is, it's not SARS because I know a lot of people who have gotten sick and they all got better within about three or four days.
Fuck you for being way too serious. God damn, it was a fucking joke.
Well, it's because my better half is very sick right now and it would suck if that was SARS, okay? It wouldn't be a funny laughing matter.
Yeah, I should've done that. I haven't been to Hong Kong in a while, but I got better.
Fuck, flat-faced on it, I have no idea.
Okay, SkylineDC505 says, F you to hormones, nuff said.
Mm-hmm.
Indeed.
Shadow would like to say, right now the only F you I have right now, uh, the...
I hate not being able to find a nice, quiet place with my girlfriend.
Fuck people for being around to nose around and spoil the mood.
That's how you go to your house.
vidpower would like to say FU to my computer for not booting up Windows XP correctly, FU
to my monitor being all screwy whenever I turn on my computer, and FU to turning in
homework during Spring Break.
All right, FUs are over, yay.
Now would be an excellent time.
I think now we're going to talk about the Orange Lounge cage match, yay.
Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, quite a controversy breaks out over
the song that won, which was a band called Freeze Pop, with a song called Science Genius
Girl, and that was the song they did in frequency.
And Zero and T.A.W.
and S.H.I.V.E.M. got into it, and I made them hug when it was all over.
Did you like that, Rob?
turned me on little bit of man-on-man action I wrote in no I did not join in
okay as for that whole little argument we got in we were actually talking in
IRC and I admitted that yeah I do like some free spot song but I actually
can't stand that and we made up and we're friends again ah you made out your
friends again yeah you made out your friends again all right here's a clip of
our easy rocks here's a clip of last week's owner remember you can vote for
For three songs, you can vote for the song that won last week or one of the two new songs.
And this winning song goes into rotation on Orange Lounge Radio, Spelvani Museum, or forum.
Alright, here we go, last week's winner, here's a clip, Freeze Pop, Science Genius Girl, here
on Orange Lounge Radio.
The theorems stick to me, Microscope is in my hand
Fun, fun, fun, sweet, fun, in the street
When I call the human being, It will walk to all my hands
When I call the human being, It will be a member of my band
It will be a member of my band
When I go to do my wishing
Remember what my name is
I'm sorry we were out just then we had dead air just there I had the stuff muted because
people were talking over that last one you're gonna have to introduce the song again real
Sorry about that.
Okay.
Let me run the title through one more time, because I need to give actually the name of
the mix.
It's M&M mixed by DJ Tripp.
It's Without Me, Darktide, The Force mix.
And where did you find this?
Well, he brought the CD with it over to my house and I ripped it.
DJ Tripp is one of my fiance's good friends, and he's a DJ in Santa Cruz.
And apparently, it's just been played on a quad locally before, on the DJ David X show.
And usually, we don't care for Eminem, but this is a remix.
Alright, here we go. This is Eminem mixed by DJ Tripp with Without Me.
Two thread-apart girls go round the outside, round the outside, round the outside
Guess who's back?
Back again
Shave his back
She'll look free
Guess who's back?
I created a monster, cause nobody wants to see Marcel no more, they want Jadie, I'm
stop living.
Well if you want Jadie, this is what I'll get ya.
A little bit of weed, mixin' some hearts, they got some thoughts, da-da-da-dum, start
my heart, quicker than the shots, when I get shocked at the hospital, while the doctor
when they're not cooperating, when I'm rockin' at table, while he's operating.
You waited too long to stop debating
Cause I'm back, I'm on the brag, and I'm ovulating
I know that you got a job, Miss Janie
But your husband's heart problem's complicating
So the FCC won't let me be
Or let me be me, so let me see
They try to shut me down on MTV
But it feels so instant without me, so
Come on, shit, I'm on your list
Fuck that, come on your list
Put someone to taste and get ready
Cause this shit's about to get heavy
I just settled on my lawsuit
Fuck you, damn, yeah
This looks like a job to me
So everybody just follow me
Just follow me, cause we need a little, cause of mercy
Cause it feels so empty, without me
I say, this looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me
Cause we need a little, cause of mercy
Cause it feels so empty, without me
Little hellions, kids feeling rebellious
Embarrassed, the parents still listen to Elvis
They start feeling like prisoners, helpless
Till someone comes along on a mission and yells BITCH!
A visionary, vision is scary
Can start a revolution, balloon the airwaves
A rebel, but just let me revel in that
And the fact that I got everyone
And the fact that I got every one kiss I'm a dastard, it's a disaster
Such a catastrophe, but you receive so damn much of my ass
You ask for me, well I'm back, nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
Bitch, you better send it to me, nah nah nah nah nah nah
I'm gonna enter in and out front of your skin like a splinter
The center of attention, back for the winner, I'm in a resting
The best thing since wrestling, investing
In your kid's ears and nesting, testing and templates
Still attention, soon as someone mentions me
Here's my ten cents, my two cents is free
And who sent, who sent, you sent for me?
You don't know me, it's too old, let's go, it's over
Nobody listen to techno, no, let's go
Just give me the signal, I'll be there with a hole
It's still a new impulse, I've been don't
Suspenseful with a pistol, ever since Prince sent himself into assembly
But sometimes, as it just seems, everybody only wants to discuss me
So this must mean I'm disgusting
But it's just me, I'm just a scene
So I'm not the first king of controversy
I am the worst thing from hell, expressly
To do black music, I'm self-evident
Use it to get myself wealthy Hey!
It's a concept that works 20 million of the white rappers emerged
No matter how many fits in the sea It'd be so easy without me
Now this looks like a job for me So everybody, just follow me
Cause we need a little controversy Cause it feels so easy without me
I said This looks like a job for me
So everybody, just follow me Cause we need a little controversy
Cause it's been so easy without me
Alright, that was M&M Remix.
by DJ Tripp, a song called Without Me. Now we go around the room and see what everyone
Some thoughts, Jamie?
I personally, I mean, I more or less really like it, just because he's a cool guy, you
know, fan friend.
Um, that, I look at the overall presentation, because if you think about it, a lot of what,
you know, rap that you hear nowadays is just, you know, more of the same specific surface.
I think it's kind of neat to hear it done a little differently, and I like how it flows
together.
You know, I give it a 9 per play.
Alright, 0.
Actually, I am really not an M&M fan at all.
Everybody who knows me knows I absolutely hate them.
But I've actually seen DJ Trip one time in Underground and I thought it was really good and everything only gets better from this song.
On this song, based alone, I give it an 8 because it was done pretty well.
Moving on, Loki.
Even some of the most simplest stuff works, but I'm going to have to give it like a 7.
Did you get a Holocaust?
Hey, yeah. I'm going to give it like a pretty decent score. It sounded really cool.
Put together well, as far as I can tell, but I really don't know that much about putting those things together.
But if Lucky says it wasn't that difficult at all, I believe that too.
What I really like about it is that it put visions in my head of Darth Vader doing hip-hop
dancing with the Stormtroopers behind him, and titled like DJ Vader, and then the big
titty girls in the back with the Princess Leia hair going, oh yeah baby, DJ Vader, Hoochie
Mama Girls, and the Stormtroopers featuring DJ Jazzy, Emperor, Jeff, and all that kind
and you know all that kind of stuff. And then the octopus headed race doing it. I haven't
seen the part two yet. But um. Blue nose guy. The guy with the blue nose plan descended
doing scratching in the background. Oh the band from Jabba the Hutt or yeah. Yeah the
blue nose guy. He looked like an elephant thing. Yeah so you know it could have maybe
I've maybe done a little bit more with it, added some stuff to it, but it was pretty neat, I liked it.
Call it an 8. Give it an 8.
overall
that you want to make a right
yes it's wrong to make a right yes
three let's do
all right
three left that's what we have to say on eminem mixed by d j trip without me now
loki what we hear last
today here's song by
group called haven't heard
i was introduced to the song by uh...
our friend eric tonight
And it's called Duck Toy, and you'll see why.
I'm very scared, but here it is.
This is Hampenberg with Duck Toy.
Enjoy!
Oh you bastard I want it, I want it
I need it, I need it Oh yeah, yeah
I want it, I want it I need it, I need it
Oh yeah, yeah
I want it
It gave me a headache, I mean it was cool, it was really neat, but it gave me a headache.
And then it was like, when that woman started talking and making moaning noises, my response
This was Meanwhile in another song, so yeah, it gets a 7, but it still gave me a headache.
Hi.
Zero.
Okay, as we all stare at the bondage for it, I don't know, okay, the beginning of that song sounded like a bad bowel movement, and then it moved into making me laugh my ass off once the rubber ducky started going.
And then all of a sudden it just switched songs and started going into a chick, starting off with something that sounded like, you bastard.
Um, altogether, that song really confused me and it might as well have had the smell of the sound it started with. I would give it like, a pour.
It was hilarious. The first time I listened to it, it was hilarious. I don't know where that shit came from, but I think that was an edit for the same song, and I think it's longer, and I think it starts out with the chick, and then it goes into the duck, and so that would make more sense.
But if it is funny, and I was just thinking when I heard it, I was like, what an ingenious idea.
I wonder who was out there thinking, I wonder if I can make a song with this duck.
I'll make a techno song with this rubber ducky. I mean, it's just, it was funny.
DDRholic?
I thought it was really funny too. That's a killer, killer duck.
What kind of people was really a duck? It sounds like a dog toy to me, but it could be a dog toy, duck, whatever.
The thing, I don't understand the girl thing either, but it's genius what they did with the duck.
It's genius the way it mixed, it raps, it did, you know, it's scratching, and it sounded like it had an orgasm too, but that's okay.
So I don't know, it's pretty good, I'll give it an eight.
That song brought to mind erotic imagery of Bert and Ernie, and for that it gets a 6.9.
6.9? What does that mean?
Alright.
That means it's gettin' some.
You can send in your votes now, and here are the three songs you can vote for in tonight's cage match.
Last week's winner, Freeze Pop, was Science Genius Girl.
I want to roll my hands, when I call my name.
This is Eminem mixed by DJ Tripp with Without Me.
And Hamburg with Duct Toy.
alright uh... you can vote for either one of those three songs right now
right freaking now
send those votes to me uh... private message sky in the chat room
and uh... some folks in the chat room saying all three songs suck this week
and they're not voting
you'd be damn glad i was gonna play the Kyle Snyder song again okay
that's right you know what i said last week
if i didn't if i i wasn't planning on winning that last week i don't think i
was going to win with that
and i said i was going to play the house and i don't know i a m
to vote
or i will be angry with you
uh...
and you don't want me to be angry with you
uh... right
uh...
we're going to take well i don't i don't really want to take a break so we need
to talk about something else uh... what's that was a
Can I break something?
Okay.
I don't have anything to break. I can't break the bottle lid again.
Zero, do you want to talk about video games? Do you have a review you want to give us?
Oh, okay. I can try to throw something together here. I wasn't fully prepared, but
Kingdom Hearts 2 does actually sound decent. I can't wait to at least see like a
good demo of it.
Oh, finished Kingdom Hearts?
Okay, I'm almost done. I just beat Agrabah, but I've been playing the getaway lately,
Which is on my review list, even though it's not really a new game.
I don't know, the gameplay of that game is cool, it's kind of sketchy sometimes.
All the model of the character models is really good, until they start moving.
When they start moving, it looks like a bad epileptic seizure or something.
Sometimes it's really smooth, and the other times they start doing the whole classic PS1 movies where it's all really blocky and jittery.
The gameplay is good, the story is good, involving, nor have I ever heard a game use the word fuck so many times in ten minutes.
And so it's fucking this, fucking this, fucking that, and it's all in an English accent, so either way you'll get to laugh pretty well.
Yeah, they get away.
Some of the mission objectives are kind of hard to understand, but you can't understand what the fuck they're telling you to do.
It's because you're not speaking English English.
I talked to my friend in the UK and they said, and I was talking to him and he's all, I can't understand you so I want you to speak English, I said I am, you're not.
Anyways, another game is, oh yeah, a big one right now, Auto Modelista. I have a couple, did you just say Auto Molesta?
That's basically what, basically that's what Auto Modelista does to your wallet.
Basically, you pay $50 for a game that looks really good, but the game is basically nothing but drifting. You get a 3000GT, which is supposed to have one of the best handling capabilities ever, and it's a constant drift. You touch the joystick and your car goes into a spin. It's kind of pointless.
That means to be good at it, you don't play it.
It's kind of a hit-or-miss thing after the Xbox. I really don't have anything up my sleeve right now
I haven't had a chance to play anything
But Oh save up $200 get steel battalion
$200 mine just played at your house
Steel battalion will make anyone feel manly
When you sit in front of this gigantic controller, it makes you feel like you have the world's biggest penis
As Brad comes in and demonstrates!
Let's see. Metroid Prime, still play it, even if you haven't. That's about it for right now until I start playing more. Now that I have a job, I'll be able to actually play more games, but I've got to go over to your house and play games at your house because you have a bunch.
And then more of you need to play Phantasy Star Online with me and Rob.
Yes, and I need to get my broadband adapter thing back.
And I'll be able to play it as Rob's character when we move in.
Yeah, you can put up to four characters on one card.
My character for Phantasy Star Online looks like she's twelve and has these big pink pigtails.
Well, bless you.
I thought you were going to say big pink boobs, sorry.
Next week I have a few games that I'm going to get a hold of and play and see what they do, so next week we do it again. I'm going to have a lot better of a review.
still play clock tower 3
Every movie where they have dolls, they're always the biggest killers.
So, yeah, I can't wait. I'm going to have a doll.
It's going to be the Loki doll. It's going to be a monkey.
They're like, monkey, kill him.
Once again, I'd like to remind our listeners that probably in about a month or so, we're going to be running a battle royale tabletop style game over IRC.
We'll have stats, we'll have the details published somewhere soon, possibly on DarkSakura.com.
You still have to teach me how to play so I can join in?
Everyone will have to learn how to play, we're making up the rules.
Okay, good, then you'll have to teach me.
I win!
No, you don't win.
I will go ahead and reveal a couple of little tiny things that aren't major secrets.
Can I be the guy?
You know the guy that does the thing?
We will be allowed to have a proficiency, but some proficiencies will be assigned, and one of the proficiencies is lucky bitch power.
Yeah, and Darkchild and I will actually be playing a lot of games this week. He's kind of like the other guy behind my reviews and such.
So, this week we'll try to at least get eight games and try to run them and see what happens.
And that's all I got right now, but next week will be better.
I have a review for Dracula X for the PC Engine Duo. Best game ever. Go save up the $300 and buy it.
I have a review for E.T. for the $2600. Best game ever.
I have a five word review for that. Actually, no, an eight word review. Ass ass ass ass ass ass ass ass.
Oh, Jimmy likes the ass.
I have two words for you. Attack.
Wait, for the new ET coming out, the best part is, it's not out.
But it will be.
The best part will be when you don't turn on your console to play it.
Okay, I think now's a good time to take a break.
Yeah.
Alright, this break, since the last break we did all these songs that start with A,
I thought it would be only appropriate to do songs that start with X, Y, and Z.
all sex. So here we go, we'll be right back.
Yeah
Alright, we're setting up now for Orange Lounge match game we're going to play tonight, but
we have to jot down some questions really fast and get all the celebrities prepped,
and we have to get some contestants, so the contestants that will be playing match game
tonight will be the first two folks in the chat room who can answer me this question.
Alright, Jamie's going to get good because I don't.
What is Jamie's favorite shooting game?
Will people be able to get that though?
Yeah, that's because I've said it a bajillion times.
What's your question?
Who's the artist that did Dead End, and the actual artist, not Naoki?
So you have to answer both those questions.
A, who is the artist that did Deadline?
No, not Deadline.
I'm sorry.
Dead End.
Dead End, OK.
A, who is the artist that did Dead End, not Deadline?
That's question A. And B, what is Jamie's favorite shooter?
She said it a million times on the show.
We don't have anyone that gets A and B right.
I think A's a little easier, so we'll use A as the answer
than B as a tiebreaker.
so
uh... jamie's favorite shooter and the artist of the dead end
and uh... in the meantime we're gonna play a nice little song to uh... prep us
all for match game
uh... and that's all will be
doctor bomb a because this show needs help and i think this is also an inside
joke with jamie american right now at least i pick up on that
it has nothing to do it but i mean that the name of the song if you say it is a
word does
little bit of dual meaning
I'm an indie anime
I used to walk around with the space in my hand
Dr. Pompei is my name and my father has the same
But everything it changed here in Tigerland
It's always that Tiger took my father
It's always that Tiger took my brother
It's always that Tiger took my mother
It's always that Tiger took my family
I lived with my family and friends in one house But now they all are gone, and life is not so fun But what can you expect here in Tangerland?
It's so wet, that I just took my father
One day in the warm jungle, a tiger took my stake
It wasn't really fun, it was a big mistake
I took my brother's screenshot and chucked the tiger down
This is how we do it here in Tigerland
It's so wet, the tiger took my family
Orange Lounge Radio. If we put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
Alright, we are back and let's get to the winner of the match, or not the match game, we don't know that yet, but the winner of the cage match tonight,
SAD BUT TRUE, YOU VOTED DUCK TOY AS THE WINNER OF TONIGHT'S CAGE MATCH.
Oh boy. Want us to say that again?
That sounds like some strange Vietnamese soup. DUCK TOY! I WANT DUCK TOY!
That's okay, because I can bring the other Freeze Pop song next week.
Alright.
Okay, so now let's talk about contestants for Match Game.
Nobody got both questions right.
Right, but we have people that got one right, and we have people that got the other one right.
But nobody got them both right. So, first off, the person who got
Jamie's favorite shooter question correct, Jamie. What's the favorite suitor?
First of all, for you people who try to name Doom and Hexen, those are first-person shooters.
Those are not shooting games.
Those are first-person shooters.
There's a difference.
A shooter is like Gradius or Parodius or Radiant Silver Gun.
And R-Type.
R-Type's awesome.
But Radiant Silver Gun is my favorite shooting game, followed closely by Osha Berry Parodius.
So Dark Tetsuya was the only one to name Radiant Silver Gun as Jamie's favorite shooter, so
he's in by default.
So we have Dark Tetsuya versus...
Nah, we decided to eliminate all the people that put Hexen in Doom, because that was a
pretty good amount of people.
And we were left with somebody who said Gradius, which is kind of like Proteus, but, oh well,
you win by default, so Justin's Circuit is contestant number two.
A lot of people got NNS.
I was talking to all the people who, a lot of people got NNS.
What's funny is Dark Tetsuya, that's the one question he didn't get.
But he got the Radiant Silvergon one.
So we got one person that got in one, and one person that got in the other.
So we have Dark Tetsuya versus Justin Circuit.
Yay!
No, the blue wire!
The blue wire!
Anyway, I'm still trying to come up with questions as we're going here, so actually you guys,
I am not going to participate in Match Game tonight.
I'm going to write the questions.
But we do have our other lovely celebrities, and they are.
Let's go around and say hello to our fabulous celebrities.
Celebrity number one, tell us who you are.
And what are you here to plug this week?
Contestant number two, say hello.
Your mom.
And what are you here to plug this week?
Likes cheese.
All right, contestant number three, what is your name?
Hello.
And what are you here to plug this week?
Iraqi Suicide Baby.
Fun.
Contestant number four, say hello.
Hi Rob, how are you?
What's your name?
Kyle Schneider.
And what are you here to plug this week?
Um, cute cell phone danglies.
Alright, contestant number five, say hello.
I...
Actually, you're not a contestant, you're a celebrity. Celebrity number five, say hello.
I have a penis.
And what are you here to plug this week?
Would you like to have sex with B?
I have to actually think about that, it's been that long.
Alright, celebrity number six.
Oh, you're not participating. Okay, so we only have five celebrities.
The actual match game had 5 celebrities, and we do too now tonight.
Question, Norman the newbie was so nude at DDR, but all the regulars were really getting
fed up with his antics and wished he would really stop doing the blank every time he
played. Norman the newbie was so new to DDR but all the regulars were really
getting fed up with his antics and wish he would really stop doing the blank
every time he played
I don't remember what this song is, but there's a video done to Golden Boy where they have
I've heard the jiggling done in time with the music.
Okay, are all the celebrities in?
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
Everybody in? Everybody in?
Alright, contestants first or celebrities first?
Contestants first.
Okay, here we go.
dark Tetsuya says Norman the newbie was so new to DDR but all the
regulars were getting really fed up with his antics and really wish he would stop
doing the caution drop every time he played. Justin says Norman the newbie he
was really sick that Norman newbie would and wish Norman the newbie would stop
doing the pelvic thrust every time he played.
Alright. Jamie, what did you say?
The truffle shuffle.
The truffle shuffle!
Zero.
I said that he would quit head banging to Daiken Kai.
I'm tired of all seeing those damn bastards sit there while they're playing Daiken Kai
on Easygon.
They look like fucking morons.
morons
okay radio by the way
yes i'm sorry i was stamping in place and
putting the little metal symbol up in the air and
bang it had been
it's the stupidest thing in the world and knock it off
bogey
uh... i said that he would stop seeing with the music basically actually not
really see making noise music like uh...
known for the whistle song and clapping at odd times because you know newbies, they don't
have rhythm in the first place so they can't keep up with the song. They're all like whoo
whoo, oh. Yeah, it's like that. All right, Anita. Norman the newbie needs to stop doing.
Oh, I don't want to say mine.
Norman the Newbie needs to stop doing the watermelon crawl.
I know. I know it's sad.
That's fabulous.
Darkchild, I really wish Norman the Newbie would stop doing the coin slot.
It won't fit.
Oh, God.
I know.
You know, you might be small enough.
You might not have a problem with that.
In-house speakers are down.
All right.
OK.
So.
You're rapping cool.
Here we go, next question.
It's all tied up at 0-0, everybody.
Let's get to the next question.
You were close to my ass, you said.
not close enough. Alright, next question, here we go. Zero, intern Zero, was so happy
when he got his first extra stage on DDR Extreme that he blanked all over the machine. Zero
was so happy when he got his first extra stage on DDR Extreme that he blanked all over the
machine.
He was so happy when he got his extra stage the first time that he pranked all over the
kostjamrh Are all of the celebrities in?
kostjamrh Come on, you live with them, Anita
p0k3smot42o
0 was so happy when he got extra stage on ddr extreme for the first time that he spit
propel all over the machine. Justin Circuit said 0 was so happy when he got his extra
I was so happy when he got his extra stage on DDR Extreme for the first time that he blew up all over the machine.
Alright, I know that could have a lot of reference. I think he's trying to go for a gimme.
Jamie, he was so happy he had a violent bowel movement all over the DDR machine. Amazing.
Hey Zero! Zero was so happy, what did he do to the machine?
I was so happy that I basically shit all over the machine.
He shit all over the machine!
Figuratively shit.
Alright, and Loki. He was so happy that he...
There's nothing that has to do with suicide babies in this one!
Jeez! I know my timing!
Okay, alright, um, that he came all over the machine. There we go.
He came all over the machine. Alright.
Anita, what did he do? He was so happy when he got extra stage that he...
Urinated!
Urinated all over the DDR machine. Okay.
And last celebrity, Dark Child. He was so happy he...
busted a fat milky nut all over his man-juice coating the machine like a
Krispy Kreme glazed donut.
Hold on. Wait. Good answer! Good answer!
I have to respond to that. Do not defame the Krispy Kremes.
Can't you say like Bel-Air donuts or something?
I'm hungry now and I want Krispy Kremes.
I don't want those Krispy Kremes.
New flavor of the month!
Krispy Kreme Lemon
And you know how many they'll sell? Here's a hint, it's in his name.
Alright.
Moving on, next question.
Jamie was so excited to walk into game land to find that they had a radiant silver gun machine.
The first thing she exclaimed was blank
I'm waiting on one more contestant.
Oh, I just changed keys.
Yep.
Jamie was so excited to walk into game land to find that they had a radiant silver gun
machine.
The first thing she exclaimed was blank.
Do we have all the contestants in?
Everyone in?
Zero?
I should go last.
Here we go.
Okay, if you want to go last, we'll go last.
All right.
p0k3smot42o
the first thing she exclaimed, Justin Circut says, the first thing she exclaimed was, this
game is mine! Dark Tetsuya said, the first thing she exclaimed was, squee! Alright, here
we go, around the room. Jamie wants to go last, so we'll start with zero. What was the
first thing? Oh, we're gonna go this way. Okay, we'll just go in backwards. Dark Child,
first thing she said was
okay Anita
first thing she exclaimed was
beautiful
oh my god
I just made my own Krispy Kreme glazed donut
You're welcome.
First thing she exclaimed was?
This is a hard one.
Squee, of course.
Alright, Squee, so we have a point for Dartsuya, hooray!
Next up, Zero. First thing she exclaimed was?
Why the fuck isn't anybody playing this game?
I actually did think that.
It was sitting there, beautiful, all alone, and for one credit, and I have to hold the
microphone away so everyone holds your ears, I went, Squeak, like that.
I actually made a mistake.
Justin Circuit's answer was actually, because I only saw the part that was in caps, he actually
said, Squeak, this game is mine. That was the full answer. So he actually got a point
too. And they both get two points. Yes. So. But I did a very high pitched Squeak. Okay,
so we are all tied up at 2-2. Oh my god, that game is beautiful. Okay. And Ikaruga is going
to be out on the GameCube soon. Alright, uh, one more, okay, two more questions. Here we
We're playing Orange Lounge Max game, Bomani Match game.
Thank you for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio.
If you want to visit our website, just go to calibomani.com and click on Orange Lounge.
Then click on Chat to join our chat room.
We have both of our contestants locked in.
Are all our celebrities locked in?
No.
Still going.
p0k3smot42o
But the arcade owner refused to get it because if I get that game there will be too much
Justice circuit says pole dancing too much pole dancing
Dark Tetsuya says there will be too much humping the coin slots. All right, Jamie
What did you say nudist colony couldn't get it because there will be too much groin stank from sweaty balls groin stank from sweaty
Oh my god, I
I now have to save that to put into one of my future stories because I like that reference.
I've just mentally thrown up.
What?
Okay, but the nudist colony couldn't get it because there will be too much...
Old people body parts flopping around.
Old people body parts flopping around. Loki, I fear this answer.
Does the nudist colony refuse to get parapar because there's going to be too much?
Well, actually, you're going to have to rephrase it, because there's going to be too much of a nice fish market smell in the air.
So kind of the reverse of the Stank Balls answer.
Pubic Stank!
Oh, God! That's a phrase I never wanted to hear on this show. It took 40 episodes to hear Pubic Stank on this show, thank you.
Oh god, are we in kindergarten? We're making milestones every minute.
Absolutely.
Well, you know what my original answer was? My original answer was flying snake grenade.
The pub stings.
Anita, the nudist colony refused to get far apart because there would be too much...
I don't understand why this is so funny. There would just be too much testicular dryness.
this is a very serious subject we're talking about here I mean you don't do
you understand the incidence of testicular dryness in this country you
just don't even know how serious a problem it is Anita I think Anita just
wants to volunteer to go over there and lick everyone's balls I have testicular
If you want him to come faster, you need to lick his balls.
Wow. Wow. All I can say is wow. Let's see if we get a match on this last one with Dark
Child. Can I get the sound from Jamie, though?
Yeah, we can. Okay. There will be too much bootleg porn on
the internet. Bootleg porn on the internet. Good answer,
but not a match.
Robin was surprised that no one at the local gay bar knew what the DDR was
he thought the best way to explain it to them was to blank
however surprised that no one at the local gay bar knew what DDR was he
thought the best way to explain it to them was to play
Rob was surprised that no one at the local gay bar knew what DDR was, because DDR is such a gay game. He thought that the best way to explain it to them was to blank.
One contestant is locked in, I think. Let me just verify this answer.
Ah, brilliant answer. I'm waiting on one more contestant.
justincircuit says, we're going to have a tie, and there's not enough time for a tiebreaker.
Alright, everybody's in.
Okay, here we go.
Justin Circuit says,
Rob was surprised that no one at the local gay bar knew what DDR was.
He thought the best way to explain it to them was to
undress slowly while on the DDR machine.
Blink.
Except there's no DDR machine at the gay bar,
or else I, I just, wouldn't I just point and say that's DDR?
You, you, you point it, just not with your fingers.
Whatever.
Alright, DarkTetsuya says the best way to explain it to them was to grab the nearest chair and start stomping his feet wildly like he's playing Legend of Max.
There we go. Good answer.
Alright, let's see if it's either one of those two matches.
Jamie, Rob's best way to explain this at the gay bar was to...
Propel.
Oh my god.
That was a total, like, EOSFVB answer. Anyway...
It was zero. The best way to explain it to them was to...
Tell him DDR stood for Dick Dick Revolution.
And with some of the players, that's very true. In fact, if you go to this one arcade, it's called... never mind.
That's a match game question for next week.
Loki, Rob thought the best way to explain it to them was to...
Was to point out anybody that's doing White Boy Freestyle.
point out anybody that's doing white boy freestyle beautiful
Anita, the best way to explain what DDR was was to
I thought the best way was to strip butt naked
in country line dance in front of the karaoke machine while playing
It's Raining Men. I did that two weeks ago
at least that involved nudity which is exciting
The best way to explain DDR was to shimmy, sashay, pirouette, left cheek, right cheek, blow a kiss, pose. It's fabulous.
Oh my god!
Everybody wants to know how a dark child knows this.
Well, what was that from, dark child?
I don't know, it was from a bunch of two other things.
Oh, even worse!
It kind of reminds me, I think it's a scene in Dropkick Gorgeous, but anyway, doesn't matter.
doesn't matter
i was just thinking more of a priscilla queen of the desert ah there we go yes
uh... so it ended in the tide tonight two points for dark tetsuya and two
points for justin so that means we have
no winner
you can do we like it when there's no winner
no
uh...
get better next time
i think i like you to all the players who lost
i'd i'd like it when no one wins because then we don't have to think of prizes to
Well, what are some consolation prizes we should give these two for tying?
A box of Rice-A-Roni, the San Francisco treat.
Ding-ding.
How about their own personal home version of Deep Pick Revolution?
You two will personally get me explaining DDR to you in Anita Fashions.
How about you make them get the next PC version of DDR?
Mr. Spanky will come over and explain.
They get a hand in a bottle of Crisco.
That makes me a sad panda.
Did you see what I thought you said?
They get a hand in a can of Crisco.
Ha!
And it's time for the jingle.
Ready?
Rice-a-roni, the San Francisco treat.
no
by the way i have to give a public thank you over the air to uh... sharks girl
for my filler bunny
and then they
is the big pink one that they can do it in the test tube
nobody got me a filler bunny for my birthday
hahahaha
alright uh... it's time to end the show guys so let's go around and get
everybody's final thought you'll start in your last or what
final thought
ask me
zero i'm just happy i got a fucking job
credulous
low-key needs food badly
anita final thought
I've just detected a fault in the AE-35 unit.
Ice Queen, final thought?
I need sex.
Dark Child, final thought?
Dark Child is about to die.
And my final thought is also, my final thought is also, I need sex, but not with Ice Queen.
The final word of the night.
Jamie got it last week.
Anita, what is tonight's final word of the night?
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loki.
If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio.yahoo.com.
And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
Dungeons and dragons, Satan's game.
Your children, like it or not, are attracted in their weaker years to the occult.
and a game like D&D fuels their imagination and makes them feel special
while drawing them deeper and deeper into the bowels of El Diablo.
This afternoon, the Dead Ale Wives Watchtower invites you to sit in on an actual gaming session.
Observe the previously unobservable,
as a hidden camera takes you to the inner sanctum of Dungeons & Dragons.
Galstaff, you have entered the door to the north.
You are now by yourself, standing in a dark room.
The pungent stench of mildew emanates from the wet dungeon walls.
Where are the cheetos?
They're right next to you.
I cast a spell!
Where's the mountain dew?
In the fridge, duh!
I wanna cast a spell!
Can I have a mountain dew?
Yes!
You can have a mountain dew, just go get it!
I can cast any of these, right?
On the list?
Yes.
level one what room I want to cast magic missile he hasn't cast anything yet I
am though if you'd listen I'm casting magic missile why are you casting magic
missile there's nothing to attack here I'm attacking the darkness fine thanks
You attack the darkness. There's an elf in front of you.
Whoa! That's me, right?
He's wearing a brown tunic, and he has gray hair and blue eyes.
No, I don't. I have gray eyes.
Let me see that sheet.
Well, it says I have blue, but I decided I wanted gray eyes.
Whatever. Okay, you guys can talk to each other now if you want.
Hello.
I am Galstaff, Sorcerer of Light.
Then how come you had to cast magic missiles?
You guys are being attacked.
Do I see that happening?
No, you're outside by the tavern.
Cool, I get drunk.
There are seven ogres surrounding you.
How could they surround us? I had Mordenkainen's magical watchdog cast.
No you didn't.
I'm getting drunk. Are there any girls there?
I totally did. You asked me if I wanted any equipment before this adventure and I said no.
But I need material components for all my spells.
So I cast Mordenkainen's faithful watchdog, but you never actually cast it
Yeah, you are
Yeah, I did though I completely fed when you asked me no you didn't you didn't actually say that you were casting the spell
So now there's ogres. Okay
Man, I got an ogre slaying knife! It's got a plus nine against ogres!
You're not there! You're getting drunk!
Okay, but if there's any girls there, I wanna do them!
There you have it. A frightening look into America's most frightening pastime.
Remember that it's not your children's fault that they're being drawn into a satanic world of nightmare.
It's their gym teacher's fault for making them feel outcast when they couldn't do one single pull-up.
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.