[SPEAKER_20]: the following live program is a special presentation of orange lounge radio
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody, you're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio and it is that time, 6.30 for Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: On tonight's program, is DDR Extreme 2 still a good game even though Sana got censored and doesn't say fuck me anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll talk about that tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also tonight, one of the biggest wishes the Bomani scene has ever had got granted this week
[SPEAKER_02]: and I don't think half of you noticed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to talk about all that tonight right after this introduction.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_19]: We are live and this is episode number 158.
[SPEAKER_02]: For this, October the 2nd of 2005, you're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want, and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_02]: or plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got legs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got legs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you like bread?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you say you got legs?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have legs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was listening to some of my Eddie Izzard stuff before I left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if you're trying to play DDR, legs are a good thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: There are people without legs who play DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or at least who were watching them.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you play DDR without legs?
[SPEAKER_17]: There was a guy who played with the crutches and did a free show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, that infamous video on the intranet.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, also not here tonight, just yet, is Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's actually running a little bit tardy tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what that means, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: FIRED!
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll be here soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, we're kind of bummed because we don't have any special guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's us, and we're special enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's just the three of us, and of course your calls on the skyplane.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, we have somebody who's returned to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, goody, who?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to tell you what I found this week after incessant listener demand.
[SPEAKER_02]: We dug him up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Loki will be here soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually what's kind of sad is that Miklatov, one of our regular guests, was just here not even an hour ago and was going to stay for the show but unfortunately due to some commuting issues had to get back before the show started.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he says hi and I guess
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I'm going to tell you, you may not want to listen tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But honestly, there's some real good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just stick with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm assuming that a lot of people out there who were trying to really stay careful of the spoilers probably...
[SPEAKER_02]: Have either already unlocked this stuff for themselves by now or just, you know, don't care at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just want to warn you guys, we are going to talk about and probably play some music that is unlockable in DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you guys, it might be a spoiler, but who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's been out for several days now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can spoil.
[SPEAKER_17]: If they don't want the spoiler, they can all go see Serenity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, we'll talk about... So that it can make the 80 million and we get a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll talk about Serenity, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll talk about other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about that big, big secret.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not really a secret.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's out there, and people have been wanting this in a Bomani game for so, so long, and it's out there, and nobody... I know somebody found it, because people were talking about it, but nobody I know knew about this, really, except Miklatov, who pointed it out to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we will talk about all that after this break, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Extreme 2 Music
[SPEAKER_09]: We drift deeper and life goes on We drift deeper into the sound Traveling somewhere, could be anywhere There's a coldness in the air, but I don't care
[SPEAKER_09]: Back with another one of those block rockin' beats!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are in the midst of our October 2nd episode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we are live here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is episode number, what, 158?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm starting to lose count.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting so high.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, God.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have to keep innovating.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're what, like three and a half years old now?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're pretty well potty trained at this point, and we're going to start preschool soon.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: We don't have to use the big kids' pants anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, we have like pull-ups.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mommy, wow, I'm a big kid now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Occasionally we still do have an accident or two.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, in that break you did hear some music from Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: You heard As the Rush Comes, Block Rockin' Beats, Genie in a Bottle, and I Will Survive.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you didn't really get a chance to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I know you're eating cake over there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let them eat cake.
[SPEAKER_17]: No one's supposed to know I'm cheating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody listens to this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tons and tons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hundreds upon hundreds of people want to listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a couple do.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're in our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that's for the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on Chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be one of those nights tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on chat and you can join our chat room and there's a whole bunch of fun people in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are they talking about right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think some comments there on some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Except for the Akira Moka one.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're assuming it's Akira.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't really know because the saying Akira... The beat was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how it couldn't be Akira Yamaoka, honestly.
[SPEAKER_17]: The beat was cool, although it's like I'm very picky about that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would have been I Will Survive.
[SPEAKER_17]: But the Genie in the Bottle one made me feel highly nauseous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Genie in the Bottle's been a very split down the middle one in the community.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I've been reading a lot of feedback, not just on our forums over at Orange Lodge Radio, but the more...
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, now you didn't really get a chance to check out Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2, did you Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: You haven't really... When I have no life.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did, I ran out and got it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to wait for Loki to get here because I think he's been playing it too, so I'll wait and share my thoughts with him.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in the meantime, let's go ahead and start off tonight's show as we do every week, playing a little bit of How Was Your Cake?
[SPEAKER_02]: How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll start it off with the one and only DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_17]: The sugar is burning a path down my throat like vodka.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played Nintendogs, lots and lots of puppies.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't even touch World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although we did have a very nerdly discussion Friday night after Serenity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we were starting to talk about games for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about...
[SPEAKER_02]: God, what were we talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just different DDRs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And our various MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Various MMOs that we've played, like Ragnarok and Final Fantasy XI and World of Warcraft and City of Heroes and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about all those games, and one of my poor friends who isn't much of a gamer was just kind of sitting there going, blink, blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this was also like his birthday dinner, so...
[SPEAKER_17]: I only got onto the Angel discussion and Buffy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, then you guys started talking about Buffy and Angel all night, and then that was the part where I started going blink, blink, blink, because I'm not much of a Joss Whedon whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, I did go out and see Serenity, because I was essentially dragged by all my friends who are Joss Whedon whores.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Serenity.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not like OMFG Serenity, like I'm going to make all my LJ icons Serenity-based.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a Serenity icon, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just teasing the general.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I just noticed this huge influx this past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just Serenity whoredom amongst the nerds on my LJ list, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, God knows I have my nerdy things as well, so I'm not one to judge, but I just noticed that the past two weeks, you know, have been like, Serenity thing's been on overdrive.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not like OMFG over the movie, but it was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked the action scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was action-packed.
[SPEAKER_17]: I liked that part at the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I liked the black chick with a gun.
[SPEAKER_17]: She was cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Zoe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because black chick with guns are cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's my opinion on Serenity.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Rob's movie review.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we actually have Extra for here, and he's going to give his movie review a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's actually sitting in Loki's chair.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're our new co-host now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we fire Loki, you're going to have to step in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate Macs and in the groove.
[SPEAKER_17]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: He fits right in.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a Mac now.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that a Mac?
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a Mac now.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have an iMac that I named Easy Mac.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's the graphite one, so it fits in with my dark personality.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extra, for what games do you play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you play the DDR games at all?
[SPEAKER_16]: I...
[SPEAKER_16]: Enjoy watching people play them.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I do, because as a person who's not very good at DDR, it felt more natural.
[SPEAKER_16]: Pump It Up felt more natural for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's interesting, because I think in a lot of ways Pump It Up is actually a harder game, even to pick up and learn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think DDR is a little more beginner-friendly than Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to knock Pump It Up, I just don't see it as beginner-friendly.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just don't have that...
[SPEAKER_16]: Why is Fiona Apple on Myspace?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for completely derailing our previous topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, come check out our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they like paste a huge ass image of a flyer.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my sister's MySpace for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because my sister is like the biggest MySpace whore I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, my sister has over 1,000 friends on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has over 1,000 friends.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I have 227.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to go there.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I've posted about 10 entries since I've had my... I don't post any entries.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have my profile.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have my live journal to post entries.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my sexy MySpace emo pics, which reminds me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last night, me, Extifer, John, and Precious Amanda were all here last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, you kind of have the emo pic thing going on, on your MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good emo pic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every MySpace profile, we're talking about MySpace.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's me holding the camera over my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that's the way to take an emo pic, is take a picture of yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we were actually taking emo pics last night, because I think John was borrowing his parents' digital camera, which is kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we were taking pictures of ourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were doing that thing where you take a picture of yourself in the bathroom mirror.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you're like half flexing and you look really like sad, like you're going to cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like you just listened to an entire Linkin Park album or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Evanescence, you know, and then you're sad inside.
[SPEAKER_16]: But Evanescence makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sarcasm.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, you know, Amanda and I, we were trying to do an emo pic where we were both in the bathroom and she was holding up the camera and taking a picture of us, which is funny because, you know, that way...
[SPEAKER_16]: Why would a person do that?
[SPEAKER_16]: Which makes it funny.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like that one better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm waiting to see how my emo pics turn out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will put them on my MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, kids, Orange Lounge Radio has hopped on the MySpace bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Toot toot!
[SPEAKER_02]: And we've got a club thingy on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't really done anything with it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And join it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when a lot of people are in the club, then they'll go, Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are all my friends in this Orange Lounge Radio Club?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they'll be likely to check out our station and our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we get popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we can sell commercials on this program.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we can all quit our day jobs and do Orange Lounge Radio forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_17]: That means that I can't move.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I'm not going to.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, MySpace.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know how to access our club on MySpace.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's like MySpace.com slash...
[SPEAKER_02]: Clubs slash Orange Lounge Radio or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just do a search in the clubs for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't imagine that there's like some other club named Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty sure we're the only club named Orange Lounge Radio because I can't think of anybody else that would call themselves Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: So look for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: So how was your gaming week, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll talk about my gaming week on the podcast, but I'll talk about my regular week now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: My week was
[SPEAKER_02]: And I barely slept last night at all, and I took a big ol' nap today, so I didn't really do anything on my Sunday, which kinda sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop laughing.
[SPEAKER_16]: But you didn't do anything with your Sunday?
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to Lions and ate.
[SPEAKER_16]: But you didn't do anything else?
[SPEAKER_16]: This program.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but this is nothing noteworthy.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was starting to think that Rob was starting to do stuff like ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ice cream?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have ice cream?
[SPEAKER_02]: Your sundae.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, we should totally get ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I totally want ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for when Loki gets here, you're our ice cream bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should go get us all Cold Stone.
[SPEAKER_16]: Should I really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome!
[SPEAKER_17]: Except I have no money.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I don't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just get us a big tub of Ben & Jerry's.
[SPEAKER_16]: A big tub of Ben & Jerry's?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, is my picture, does it look emo?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody commented today that I look like I've lost weight, and I credit that to the three days of DDR I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just for that, but I've been playing quite a bit of DDR and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_16]: It doesn't show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're still fat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Extifer, why don't you go?
[SPEAKER_16]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_16]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_16]: My week was good.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just worked at blah, blah, boring, etc.,
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: Do you feel abandoned?
[SPEAKER_16]: Are you having abandonment issues?
[SPEAKER_16]: I do.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was planning on, you know... That precious Amanda Miklatov had to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was planning on hanging out with Miklatov as he was doing the show with you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, usually when Miklatov is here on the show, he'll drop in and say hi, and then he retires out to the living room because he just doesn't really want to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: And we got a new gay channel here, logo, that I was just watching in the other room.
[SPEAKER_16]: Super!
[SPEAKER_16]: I know.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's super fabulous.
[SPEAKER_16]: And we... They were having a...
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that funny?
[SPEAKER_16]: What are you laughing at over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it the chat room?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just the way he's super fabulous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a big queer.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I'm not, dude.
[SPEAKER_16]: We went, so I was watching that channel and they have, you know, a lot of super gay programming on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, imagine that.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, on the gay channel, what are you going to have?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to have... Well, you know, they have Wonderfalls, which isn't totally gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Madonna documentaries and, I don't know, what else do you show on the gay channel?
[SPEAKER_16]: They don't have Madonna.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was actually, it was a reality show based around this gay...
[SPEAKER_16]: I like sitting here right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't know that?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura as a straight woman, do you ever look at a guy and go, I bet that guy has some nice balls!
[SPEAKER_17]: Occasionally?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm more like, I hope he shames those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes Harry is better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just lost half our listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we're down to one listener.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_16]: You lost half your listeners like last week.
[SPEAKER_16]: We went from two to one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good job.
Great.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, so that's how my week was and my day.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_17]: Your week was balls.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was Hairy Balls.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, and Serenity.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hairy Balls and Serenity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I'm so glad that this show just instantly went down the toilet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Legend of Zaku gets it!
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: What did Legend of Zaku say?
[SPEAKER_17]: The in-your-mouth line after... Didn't you see Jay and Silent Bob straight back?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did, like, years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it first came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Dance Revolution Xtreme
[SPEAKER_02]: In this break we're going to hear some more music from DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to hear Injection of Love, but this is the version of Injection of Love that has the vocals not in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So see if you like this version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little bit different there because they actually stripped out Sana's vocals because...
[SPEAKER_02]: Controversially, Sana says, fuck me, in one part of the song, where she says, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, some people are saying, no, she doesn't say, fuck me, she's actually saying, suck me, or something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: She totally says, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: She totally says, fuck me, and even if she's not trying to say, fuck me, she says, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know if the lyrics, in fact, let me see, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no problem with those words.
[SPEAKER_02]: God damn it, y'all got me on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me pull this up real fast here, because I have to prove something to you people.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for those of you guys that have never heard Injection of Love, even though we've actually played this quite a bit on our show before this was ever in DDR Extreme USA, here's a little piece of Injection of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you tell me if this doesn't sound like fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit after this part, let me fast forward a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_02]: She totally said fuck me right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: She totally said fuck me.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's called injection of love.
[SPEAKER_16]: Of course she said fuck me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Isn't that giving your injection of love?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm gonna inject you with my meat rod.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, my love.
[SPEAKER_16]: My love rod.
[SPEAKER_16]: In other words, my cock.
[SPEAKER_16]: And in some weird porn way, my balls too.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I understand if you guys, I don't know, you probably went on some website and looked up the official lyrics or something, and maybe it's not fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let's face it, if it's not supposed to be fuck, she did a pretty bad job.
[SPEAKER_02]: She did a Freudian slip.
[SPEAKER_02]: She was thinking about fucking when she sang it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so she said, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: There, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does fuck mean?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because, get it?
[SPEAKER_24]: She doesn't say fuck right?
[SPEAKER_24]: She says fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, to me it sounds more like fook me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Fook Me and Fook You from... forget it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_16]: It just wasn't funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: So needless to say, they had to strip out the vocals because, you know, they weren't going to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm assuming, anyway, that that's why they stripped out the vocals is that, you know, because it sounds like fuck in the song, although in Dance Dance Revolution Extreme, they let a little fuck slip by and the song highs off you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's so hard to catch.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's even more controversial as to whether they're really saying...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuckin' You Up is the lyric.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, I don't know if you know this.
[SPEAKER_17]: I used to think that in... What was that one that was in Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_17]: God, now I can't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_17]: I always thought that they used to say Often Kissed by a Boy Band Fucker.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Often kissed by a boy band fucker.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, that song.
[SPEAKER_17]: I forgot what the song was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was in one of the earlier USDDRs as well as like, what, third mix?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like way back when?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear we're going to get to the song, but I just wanted to get that out there about, you know, word censorship and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting off this break, the instrumental version, or as they're calling it, the Hina mix of Injection of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: And after this, we're going to hear some Inside Your Heart, Make a Difference, and My My My.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back after this.
Um, so, thanks
[SPEAKER_09]: For your dreams, for your heart For your dreams, for your heart For your dreams, for your heart When a world feels so lost in itself And you feel the life is not so easy for you and me Don't forget that you're not by yourself For together we can make this world better place Give it a chance
DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hope you enjoyed that break of more EX2 music, including Injection of Love, Inside Your Heart, Make a Difference, and My My My.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a reminder, tonight's show is filled with Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2 spoilers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you are afraid of hearing something that might spoil Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2 for you, let me remind you, Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2 is not a movie or a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is nothing to spoil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh no, we told you a song is in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You still have to work to unlock it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of those things I kind of don't get, quote unquote, on DDR Freak right now, get, putting quotes, is that everybody in the Extreme 2 thread is, even I had to do this myself because I feared the angry mob if I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were, you know, putting all the spoilers in hidden, like you have to highlight with your mouse type text because, you know, they don't want, you know, people are not wanting the game to be spoiled.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm thinking anybody with common sense would think if I don't want to spoil this game,
[SPEAKER_02]: I probably shouldn't go on a discussion forum where people are talking about how much they've been playing it and how great the game is and all the songs they've been getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm not sure I get the point of why we're being so insensitive about spoilers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe somebody will call up and yell at me for spoiling Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I warned you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We all did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Loki's here.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's back here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm not fired.
[SPEAKER_25]: I had top secret work to be working on.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's going to be... And I have to get a sandwich also.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're allowed to be late once in a while, but don't let it happen again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_25]: My week was okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Today was kind of weird because Nelly decided, you know, instead of watching the Food Network today, she wanted to watch TLC, which they were playing...
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like a whole lineup of medical procedures that could go wrong.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, for example, they had plastic surgery gone wrong.
[SPEAKER_25]: Then they had another one that was when medical instruments get left behind.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, a whole series of people... Oh, look, we left a sponge in you.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, look, there's scissors in you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, but we've replaced your heart with a baked potato.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have five seconds to live.
[SPEAKER_25]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_25]: It was just like, you know, I didn't need to be watching that stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_25]: But other than that, no, really not too much going on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Except, I don't know, I'm just getting some more games to sell back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, I'm clearing out, you know, my excess crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else was I going to ask you about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, actually, I wanted to tell the listeners about this before the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: You missed a little bit of show, obviously, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luckily, you missed the conversation on balls, because extra for...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I don't take note of everybody's gender sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: This person actually sent me a picture of the 2DX Red booklet that actually shows the lyrics here to Injection of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sure enough, something something in Japanese, touch me, something something lick me, something something stroke me.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's supposed to be saying stroke me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so keeping that in mind, here we go again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to play you the vocal version of Injection of Love, that little piece here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You tell me
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck or stroke?
[SPEAKER_02]: You be the judge.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's clearly an F. That is clearly an F. That is not stroke me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Fuck me does not sound like stroke me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Unless she has some weird fucking accent, that's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_25]: If she pronounces her S's like F's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, we're going to go club some baby feels?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or we're going to... I don't... Yeah, it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care what the lyric book says.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The restaurant is down the feet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do appreciate you sharing the lyric book, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least I know... Maybe she was drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Sana.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sana.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I remember when I was drunk at Dave & Buster's and I called my food a chili feet steak.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was a Philly cheesesteak.
[SPEAKER_02]: MPQ in chatroom says, Akira Yamaoka said stroke, but Sana said fuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Discussion over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can agree with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sana butchered the lyrics to Injection of Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes for a good Bimani drama story.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, naturally, that's followed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave this to our chatroom with Sakurina saying, Akira Yamaoka must have big balls.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys are so immature.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Balls!
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you're talking about the drink, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about, um, I want to talk about Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about one more thing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about Pump It Up first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, what do you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, this is the first time I got, well, yesterday I got a sandwich at Rayleigh's.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Today I got a sandwich in there.
[SPEAKER_25]: What kind of turkey would you want?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm like, I thought there was only one kind of turkey, you know?
[SPEAKER_25]: The bird turkey.
[SPEAKER_25]: But, um.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I am all, I just want that one, because it looked like the turkey I normally get.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, this is salsa turkey.
[SPEAKER_25]: Now, I don't know what the difference is, but it sort of tastes like it was dipped in salsa.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's a Mexican turkey?
[SPEAKER_25]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_25]: I didn't know there were Mexican turkeys.
[SPEAKER_25]: Is there a Lombada turkey and a... More importantly, is it tasty?
[SPEAKER_17]: Foxtrot?
[SPEAKER_25]: It tastes like salsa, partially.
[SPEAKER_17]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_17]: That doesn't sound yummy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pump It Up Step Chart Editor
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something that you download on Xbox Live, and when I say download, it's actually very similar to the way the characters in Ultramix 2 were unlocked, where you're basically downloading a code or something that unlocks it inside the game, because it's only a five block file, and I have a hard time believing that a step editor would fit in five blocks of data.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you download this thing, and then you suddenly have a step editor available to you in Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_02]: No big deal, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just puts it up there on the level with DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can create your own steps to songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in fact, the editor in Pump It Up is a hell of a lot like the DDR editor, but, you know, with pump arrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the really interesting thing that I think might have slipped through the cracks and some people didn't notice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only can you edit the steps to songs in Pump It Up, but you can create brand new step files to songs loaded on your Xbox hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: custom soundtrack feature to create your own arrows to songs that you rip to your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: So finally, we have this game out there that allows you to create steps to your own music, which is something people have been wanting in DDR for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, licensing issues, of course, make that a nightmare.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, obviously, you can't really take these files and send them over the internet to other people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I imagine there must be a way to do it using an Xbox memory card, maybe?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know enough about Xbox...
[SPEAKER_02]: Memory to know if you can transfer, maybe one of our listeners knows, to know if you can transfer a soundtrack, quote unquote, something you rip on the CD, to take something that you rip on the soundtrack to a memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, you could take the step file and put it on your memory card, but I don't know if you could take soundtracks and put it on the memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hypothetically, if you could do that, put the soundtrack on the memory card and your step file on the memory card, you could essentially...
[SPEAKER_02]: Give these to your friends via the memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the other cool thing about Pump It Up, putting your own songs, your own step files.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has this preloaded background movie, so your song even has its own background movie, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just a generic thing with one of those rotating cubes and lights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it with the boobies?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the booby law, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the booby law.
[SPEAKER_22]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: Somehow a lot of people didn't notice this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was actually announced on the official Pump It Up website that this actually came out on the 29th and Miklatov and I were just randomly surfing the internet this morning and he was like, wait a minute, did you realize that they put this out there?
[SPEAKER_02]: So we hooked up Xbox Live and sure enough, we just went on and downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you own Pump It Up Exceed for Xbox, I don't think this exists in the PS2 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: This only exists in the Xbox version as far as I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, obviously it wouldn't matter because PS2 doesn't allow you to have custom soundtracks
[SPEAKER_02]: Rip your own music to the Xbox hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very easy to do within the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, what I did, I burned a CD from iTunes and just ripped it on my Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have like a mix of music.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I understand that not all Xboxes will read burned CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because from what Mikulatov was telling me, his Xbox won't read burned CDs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ours won't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine will.
[SPEAKER_17]: It also depends on the quality of the CD that you use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's theorizing this because I have the Halo Xbox that maybe somehow the drive in mine is different and it allows it to read the burned disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So before you try that, realize that your Xbox may not read the burned thing and rip it to the custom soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm hoping you still have some legitimate CDs in your collection out there, boys and girls, so you can certainly rip those.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think a lot of people didn't really realize that because I don't think a lot of people are following what's going on in the Pump It Up scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's what we're here at Orange Lounge Radio to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: So have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go dig up your copy of Pump It Up and have fun making your own steps there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, somebody in the chat room is actually telling me, Ron Chan is actually saying that there are three different types of Xbox Drives.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, possibly, I have one of the ones that will let you read the burned CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, the old Xboxes don't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, a lot of our chatroom is using this opportunity to say, Andamiro wins, Andamiro effed Konami in the A, Andamiro loves us long time, Andamiro, yay, yay, yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, I realize this is a feature people have been wanting for forever, but did Andamiro serve Konami?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this going to revolutionize things?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: But the problem is you have to set the delay as well, and that was a real bitch for us to figure out the delay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there was no easy way for us to, like, there was no press the X button when the song starts type thing, so we had to actually calculate in time the delay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was kind of a bitch to do, but once we got it, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know how many people were going to take the time to do that, just to play their own song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, maybe I'm underestimating what people want to do out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a whole SimFile community that has to do it the same way, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but the thing about the sim file community is that you can zip those up, send them on the internet very easily.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stepmania practically endorses that, I mean, they don't endorse it, I guess, but they thrive on that type of distribution, basically, is that, you know, you even have, what, the SM zip file, you know, an archive file that's specifically made for Stepmania, which is the way, what, like, FoodMix and stuff was distributed, right?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, it's just a zip file with some other program that runs it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, it is the same as making a sim file, but at the same time, a sim file is very easy to get out there and share.
[SPEAKER_02]: And let's face it, I think that's what motivates people, is because people want to share what they've done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think one way that this could be improved upon is for Andomero to set up a database very similar to what Ultramix 2 had, where users can submit their own step files,
[SPEAKER_02]: and then share it with each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the problem is, of course, you wouldn't be able to share the music because that's all type of copyright laws.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, if you had maybe like, you know, you say, this is track one on the latest garbage album or something, you know, and then assumably if everybody ripped the same track, it would all be the same, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you kind of understand what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe not so feasible, but it's a way to do it legally where you could distribute the sim files.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, go figure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I'll be really using this feature for anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried it once.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute, but I don't really want to make my own step files to dance to because I'll be able to beat it too easy if I made it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't have Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's surprisingly good.
[SPEAKER_17]: I got a free game, though, while Dan was in Texas.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_17]: I have Taiko Drum Master.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, Taiko Drum Master.
[SPEAKER_24]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I haven't opened mine yet, but I've played other people's, and I kind of want the Japanese one, just because of the other songs in it.
[SPEAKER_17]: But he picked up the Red Octane drum thing, so I'm going to do a comparison of them so that I can talk about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, very good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I've been hearing from a lot of people that the red octane one is highly inferior to, of course, the official stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, that happens with most of the... Right, well, I mean, when they're trying to sell it cheaper, they're going to use cheaper parts.
[SPEAKER_17]: I look at it, it's a cheap knockoff.
[SPEAKER_17]: All their products are cheap knockoffs.
[SPEAKER_25]: At least it wasn't as bad as the Rave Discman.
[SPEAKER_17]: The what?
[SPEAKER_25]: The two triangles that were the 2DX controls.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're going to... I think we're going to open up the Skype line pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to go to another break just yet, so I guess we'll go into the next topic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about what's been going on, of course, with DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Loki, have you gotten to play Extreme 2 at all?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't really talked about our thoughts on the game yet, so I'm kind of curious, because I want the listeners to be able to give their feedback when we come back from the next break on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we should share what we think of Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: How is Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_25]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just got to play it for like one night, though.
[SPEAKER_25]: I haven't really gotten to play too much of it, but
[SPEAKER_25]: Unlocked, like, quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, in the Dance Master mode?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: I like the way they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_25]: The hidden steps that are in there, that's kind of a throwback to the old Guitar Freaks, you know, first mix.
[SPEAKER_25]: I wish they'd do that with the rest of the songs, like, instead of just one step, have a bunch of them in there.
[SPEAKER_25]: That'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_25]: And then, just some of the, well, the characters I couldn't give a crap about.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think the fact that you have to buy their other outfits for like $100,000 is retarded.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, I'm like, hmm, should I buy one outfit or 20 songs?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's a tough one there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the outfits are something I think you save up for and get later on with the points.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I do like the whole shop thing and the way you unlock songs that way.
[SPEAKER_25]: So that way it's like,
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I don't want to unlock that song, so I'm going to save my points and unlock another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was pretty much passing up a lot of the stuff that I've had played to death before in other DDR versions, like Air.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't bother to buy Air.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already have that in Extreme Japan, so I saved up the money and bought Inside Your Heart instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of interesting that I could choose to unlock things.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, about Inside Your Heart and some of those other ones.
[SPEAKER_25]: Politary can't sing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not Politary in that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: I know that, but Politary Can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is true.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm talking about the new songs that she did.
[SPEAKER_25]: Passion and Love?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, Passion and Love.
[SPEAKER_25]: That was crap.
[SPEAKER_25]: I was like, oh wow, everything that happened with Orbit Tribe just went down the tubes, just went back to sucking it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just was amazed at how much she really sucked on the Longan Midnight Action.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think she's alright on there.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think she's actually pretty good on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: A woman can't hold a key!
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Xtreme 2 Xtreme 2
[SPEAKER_02]: FYI guys, Sakura and Daikinkai were in the E3 demo of Ultramix 3 and from what I recall, I would have noticed if they changed those banners.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't change those banners in Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So unless something changed between E3 and when this game comes out, whatever that poster said is going to be absolutely right where Extreme 2 had their backgrounds changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Extreme 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extreme 2 had their backgrounds changed and Ultimate 3 did not.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, but the artwork for the backgrounds is going to be the last thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're of course going to use whatever they have at the moment for the backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_25]: So who gives a crap?
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, we're talking like a few pixels here.
[SPEAKER_25]: I mean, who cares?
[SPEAKER_25]: So what?
[SPEAKER_25]: It's translated.
[SPEAKER_25]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's an American game now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she has Sakura tattooed on her face, which makes no sense now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, it's probably not a tattoo.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's probably just the fucking name of the song.
[SPEAKER_17]: If they were going to translate it, they just would have put Cherry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could have done worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could have just given us the English names of the songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could have been worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what is interesting about, speaking of Sakura, I actually haven't gotten to the song yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've only been reading fan feedback on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you notice that the background videos are all totally different and extreme, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no... It looks like they don't use the looping thing anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know how it would go, like, video A for a little bit, and then video B. Go to the spinning Beethovens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now go to the little plasma-looking thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're all their own videos now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're all, like, all full videos now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Some of them are featuring the looping video stuff, but a lot of them feature the backgrounds as well.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, I noticed in Happy Wedding and in Irresistible Monk, they were different.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what was the other one that really used a lot of their background?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, like La Copa De Vida has a lot of soccer themes running through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the one against all odds is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just has like a very 70s looking art piece with a woman and hair blowing around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like how they did that with all the different steps.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a step in the right direction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very interesting that only one song in the whole game has, well, at least that I've gotten to so far, but I haven't heard of any others.
[SPEAKER_02]: One song in the whole game has an actual music video, and that's Get Busy, which is probably one of the most, well, one of my least favorite songs to play in DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a big Get Busy fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what song that is, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: The reggae one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a big fan of Get Busy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting point, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reading in our chat room over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sakurina says, why did they do that, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Kakumei was left as is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why did they change this, but not that?
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_25]: Interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_25]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_25]: Why are you guys putting this much thought into it?
[SPEAKER_25]: My thoughts on the extreme... It's not tattooed on her fucking face!
[SPEAKER_25]: It's just the logo that happens to be on her face.
[SPEAKER_25]: Doesn't mean it's tattooed on her face, because who the hell would tattoo a word on their face?
[SPEAKER_25]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_17]: I honestly think that they should have left it as Kanji.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because with any sort of sense of logic would assume that if you're playing a song with a Japanese title and you see Kanji, that typically it's probably going to be the same thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, duh!
[SPEAKER_17]: There has to be somebody pretty stupid in their localization department at Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snare has a comment there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Palavstian... I can never pronounce this damn name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Palavstian Dances and Chorus has its own full music video too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say that's kind of borderline because that's a Konami original and all the video is clips from the game that that song is featured in, which is Oz.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Oz...
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: My thoughts on Xtreme 2, geez, it's very interesting that this is the first mix that they've released that isn't an arcade port, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, even when you look at Xtreme, the last one they released here in the US, Xtreme, even though they radically changed the interface and everything, I think for a lot of people it was still our version of the port of the Xtreme arcade mix, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is really the first game where there's been no arcade mix to base it off of.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you really, I think, see that evolution from a game that is a translation of an arcade game for the home mixes to a game that is specifically made to be played on a home mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think that's why it centers so strongly around Dance Master Mode because that's a very single player, adventure, conquest type here's a goal, a long term goal to get from point A to point B that you can't really do in an arcade game so I think it's really interesting to kind of see that transition now I think this is really the first true transition that we see from DDR as an arcade series to now DDR as a home series
[SPEAKER_02]: with Dance Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, is that a good thing or bad thing for the series?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they kept an arcade-like thing in there still by having the free mode, which, you know, basically has the look and feel of a DDR arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just very interesting that now the focus is on Dance Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you don't play through Dance Master Mode, you're not going to really unlock a lot of songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I thought it was very interesting that the only songs that are available at the outset is the licensed songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a different direction for the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I like it, though, as somebody who's a DDR fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I was somebody who was buying DDR mixes just to have house parties, though, I'd be kind of ticked off at this mix because there's not a lot to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you just buy it to play it once in a while, you know, let's get drunk and play DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'd probably be a little irritated with it because there's not a lot of songs to choose from.
[SPEAKER_25]: But even though I'd say the casual person doesn't like playing
[SPEAKER_25]: All the stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sure that they're not that great at DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: You can play through the mission mode type stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: It starts off beginner stuff and goes all the way to really hard.
[SPEAKER_25]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_25]: You can get better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Dance Master Mode is kind of a way for you to get better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually reminded me a lot of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell did they call that in 2DX?
[SPEAKER_02]: Drill Mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Trial Mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Drill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drill Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drill Mode in 2DX 6th Style.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had that Drill Mode, and I think it was in 5th Style as well, where it was like play these little sections of songs and meet these certain qualifications.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like they took Drill Mode and really changed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Drill Mode really helped me get better at 2DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wish I could contribute more to that.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_24]: You could maybe borrow my copy later this week or something if you want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know when I would play it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Spider Stomp is an excellent game.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just there's no music, so it sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have Puyo Puyo to keep me happy on the MAME.
[SPEAKER_17]: But we're discussing, though, buying a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_25]: Speaking of which, I'm not sure if you saw that I posted...
[SPEAKER_25]: I went and opted to get the correct poppin' music buttons for my poppin' music controller, so they're gonna be arcade-style.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: Can't wait for that to be done.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wanna try to build one for myself, like, so that I can actually play on something other than the dinky pad.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, it'd be easy.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just, the buttons are, like, 70 bucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: Cheaper than 400?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: You show me how to, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_25]: There's a fact.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll email it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the favorite of Orange Lounge Radio, Paula Terry with Naoki with Passion of Love starting off this set.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also in this break we're going to hear a Palafstian dance and chorus, Seduction, which you guys have been begging me to play since the beginning of the show, so you'll get that, as well as Silence in this break.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio dedicated to video games and what gamers really want to know.
[SPEAKER_19]: For live, up-to-the-minute gaming news and for more information on our interactive live programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: Live 365
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll find you free, free Here I found the sense of love that I wanted to
[SPEAKER_09]: Cheap and Normal
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're back here on Orange Launch Radio, and people remind me in the future not to reset the router while we're trying to broadcast so that Loki can get on our wireless network with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: So since that was kind of my bad, and I dropped a lot of you guys during the song that everybody in chat was like, OMG, waiting for, here it is again, one more time, Seduction.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello kids, we're back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, stop complaining, you got to hear seduction.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, we all make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of us more than others, granted, but we all make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I'm looking at this really cool new thing that Loki was a big part of putting together along with one of our other behind the scenes people, VXJasonXV, and it's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think we're going to announce it tonight on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have to check with Jason and make sure everything's good to go.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And where's Waldo?
[SPEAKER_25]: and the added bonus, which I picked up last minute.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_25]: That was the brand new t-shirt, which says, In the Courtroom.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, did you get that?
[SPEAKER_25]: I got one for myself and one for the winner.
[SPEAKER_25]: Wow, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So somebody is going to win an In the Courtroom shirt, which is, what is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the In the Groove logo, but it says In the Courtroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So somebody's going to win the In the Groove thing and the In the Courtroom t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, Miklatov wanted to throw some prizes in as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: SILENTHILL3 STICKERS
[SPEAKER_02]: Mikulatov gave us like 10 stickers, so we're going to just give them all away with other prizes that we give out later on throughout this month.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I'm thinking there will be another contest to go with the announcement that we'll make on the podcast later as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super!
[SPEAKER_02]: We got tons of giveaway crap going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's cleaning house.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to give away stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's give away the ferret.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_25]: We already gave away a ferret, and there was like three other ones.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, did we throw them all away?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're hidden.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're in my butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Skype line's open, and people are already hammering us on the Skype line, so if you want to call, head on over to OrangeLaunchRadio.com and click on Interact With Us, and we'll go to our first call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello, Sephiroth1215 here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Sephiroth1215, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically just extreme, too, but my first thought was, like, why was I playing in the groove over the summer?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, why?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I don't know, it just kind of revived the DDR back for me, at least.
[SPEAKER_00]: Except for the arcades, of course, but still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I'm the one out of the three of us that doesn't hate on In the Groove as much.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, In the Groove for me was exactly like you're kind of referring to here.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the Groove was holding me over between real DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of how I felt about In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like, well, this is, you know, it's like, it's, I can't believe it's not DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: That they didn't license any good music.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to look at DDR Extreme 2's song list, which is pretty phenomenal, and really sucks the fans' collective cock in every way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, honestly, every fan bitching that was going on on DDR Freak was really granted with this mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe not everything, but let's face it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people that were whining and bitching that they never got erotic, they got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people that were whining and bitching that they were never going to get cartoon heroes, they got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people that were bitching they were never going to get Sakura and Daikin Kai, they got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Albeit a little bit butchered, but they got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this mix really delivered to the fans in every way, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, it's your call, not my monologue.
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep cutting you off.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are your other thoughts on Xtreme?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, well, first of all, yeah, I was really pissed about the Injection of Love thing, because it came up randomly, and I was happy, I was excited, I'm like, oh, what's Hina mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, all the lyrics are just gone, which just kind of ruined the song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like how I think somebody on Freak put it this way is that somebody said imagine you've never heard the 2DX Red version and I realize it's hard to do because you have heard the 2DX Red version but imagine for a minute you haven't heard the 2DX Red version as a standalone song it's not that bad there's been worse songs in DDR although I agree it's a little disappointing for the lyrics to be cut out of the song but you know there's all I can tell you is that there's a reason for everything so there's probably a really good reason why it turned out the way it did
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if it's a reason for censoring, I think it's poor, because some of the other songs in there, like Get Busy, or even the Erotic song, I mean, I thought they weren't going to censor anything after that, since it got an E10 rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think of it this way, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it wasn't done for censoring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's assuming it was done for censoring, but what if it wasn't?
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't really know, so... Just food for thought.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just hoping maybe they'll put in Ultramix 3 or something, since they're probably better on that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which kind of reminds me, the quest mode in Ultramix 3 is probably going to be similar in some sort to this mission mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of thought about that too, that I'm wondering if the quest mode in Ultramix 3 is going to be the very central part of the game, such as Dance Master Mode was in this Dance Dance Extreme 2, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it will be, because honestly, from what I played at E3, and granted, a lot can change from E3 to the home release, because Ultramix 2 at last year's E3 sucked humongous, hairy, extrovert-loving balls, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: The version that they ended up releasing is probably one of the best DDR mixes that they've ever put out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in my opinion, I think the song list in Ultramix 2 is better than Extreme 2's.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I realize, you know, not everybody shares the same opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Ultramix 2 is phenomenal when they released it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Ultramix 3 at E3 this year, I can tell you, really didn't feel that much different from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just Ultramix 2 with new songs thrown in and hey, this new little quest mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, I think it was explained before as Quest World's probably going to be like that mode in Virtua Fighter 4 Evolution where you just go around different arcades and fight people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Virtual Fighter 4 Evolution I didn't really play the Virtual Fighter Oh, Jamie's making the gag face I hate Virtual Fighter Sorry, we don't catch the reference because I don't really play a lot of fighting games I thought it was pretty, but I don't like Virtual Fighter What was the last fighting game I really liked?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Capcom vs. SNK 2 Tekken 5 Tekken was okay Anyway, I need to get to some other calls Do you have any other thoughts on DDR Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really, I think
[SPEAKER_02]: Most people should buy it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean... If you're a fan of DDR, you need to have this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Period.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a fan of music games, you need to have this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a casual, hey, I like to play DDR when I'm drunk, you're probably not listening to this show, for one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if that does happen to be you, you may not be so into this mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would recommend if you're going to start somewhere, like if you're a brand new, I'm brand new to DDR, I want to start somewhere in the series, I actually think Max 2 is the place to start for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a toss-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other thing I want to ask you, Sephiroth1215, what do you think about the Pump It Up custom soundtrack feature?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um... Alright, I guess it's okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's not something I would probably use, but, I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how we can't... If DDR is selling as well as everybody says it is, I say Ultramix or some version of Xbox DDR on the 360 is inevitable.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe Konami now has something to dare to achieve in their Xbox series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, we're going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to get to another call, but have a good night, and thanks for calling, alright?
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it loud enough in studio for you, DarkSakura, or do I need to turn it up a little bit?
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't hear it badly at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was probably a little low.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let me turn it up a little bit for you, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to take... I don't think we've heard from this one in a while.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello, yes, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, this is Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, Dark Knight, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_23]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, what...
[SPEAKER_15]: About the online mode on DDR EX 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we didn't talk a lot about online mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played a whole lot of it, but what's up?
[SPEAKER_15]: I tried it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It has a major flaw, and that is you cannot pick your opponent, nor can you pick the song to play against.
[SPEAKER_15]: To play against with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess, yeah, it's kind of one of those things, well, it's DDR's first adventures into the PlayStation Online realm, which...
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I understand, from a player perspective, the Sony online network is just not as good as Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just not as set up as well as Xbox Live is.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm kind of not surprised that the online features aren't as good, but yeah, that is kind of weird that you can't even pick your song, of all things.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but I mean, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: As far as gameplay went, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was pretty synced up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it was pretty synced up when I played my match.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna have to get on there and kick some ass on DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you tell if people are using a controller or not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, no, you really can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_15]: You really can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a button button master.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna get on there and kick some butt.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll play against somebody, and he's playing on heavy, and I killed him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel kind of bad for admitting to that, but at the same time, you know they're all playing on controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe there's one or two guys out there playing on a dance pad on Heavy, and props to you guys for having the guts to do it, but come on, they're all playing on controller.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I will still play light and standard songs on a dance pad against someone on a controller because on Xbox you can see what they're using.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if they're using a controller... Whoa, we just had a major net split on IRC, and I think I split from the rest of the chatroom, but hopefully they'll reconnect soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, just wanted to give that update.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I mean, like I said, other than that, the normal mode, yeah, deathmatch mode, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_15]: That way you can open the songs a little more quicker.
[SPEAKER_15]: But at the same time though, it depends on the player's skill on a home pad because right now I'm just working on the B course right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I ain't even hit the hard levels yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually been pretty good about sticking to playing Dance Master mode strictly on a dance pad because I want to get back into actively playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I say actively, meaning like I'm actually...
[SPEAKER_02]: Step on 150 Arrows
[SPEAKER_02]: but not any of the arrows that are actually in the step chart.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you step on one of the arrows that are actually in the step chart, you lose.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it's on FAQ, if you step on the down arrows, you will fail.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another mission like that too where you can't step on any down arrows and it's really hard to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried doing that mission on a dance pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could not get 150 notes to register with my feet.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think of one song where you have to intentionally play bad to pass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a whole bunch of weird stuff there in Dance Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, do I have to literally get a D to pass a song?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I'll just step off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other thing I want to ask you, Dark Knight, before we go to another call, what do you think about the Pump It Up thing, the custom soundtrack thing on Pump It Up?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's just like a major, maybe it might be a major code goof, i.e.
[SPEAKER_15]: hot coffee, but hey, to each his own.
[SPEAKER_02]: So are you saying that kids everywhere now can make, you know, Step Files to Porn soundtracks, or...?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't like where you're going that far.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only thing I can think of though, Xbox Live, you can't upload.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: How?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can upload if the game allows it, but Pump It Up doesn't allow it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultramix 2 does though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Ultramix 2 does.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe somebody might get funny outside and maybe find a code for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know what might happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Microsoft really does plan on setting up this big music store for their 360 that's going to compete with iTunes or whatever, which is a big rumor, they're going to set up their own music store to compete with iTunes via the 360, wouldn't that be interesting that not only could you download the song, but then you could also have, hey, you could have this fan step chart in DDR that you download with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, that would be kind of cheesy, but I could see it happening, I don't know, might be a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway, we're going to let you go, see if we can get to another call, but thank you so much for calling in tonight, and have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more, guys, before break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's up, it's Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Ron Chan, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, not too much, just, you know, been playing the hell out of Extreme 2, how about you?
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been playing the older mixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: As soon as I get a job, I'll pick up Xtreme 2 and have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so you're still on the older mixes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm following what's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everybody's bitching this song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look, if you want this song that badly, buy the import or shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't see...
[SPEAKER_02]: People are always going to find something to complain about.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just inevitable.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this mix is pretty solid, honestly.
[SPEAKER_21]: Overall, you can't make people happy.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_21]: But let's take a little step from DDL.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's do a little para para.
[SPEAKER_21]: In case you haven't heard, I went to the Yoko Ishida concert in New York City today.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, how was that?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm posting pictures from the concert.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was a free concert at the Manhattan Mall.
[SPEAKER_21]: It took about 100 pictures, and if you go through the pictures, you'll see a lot of people up there power-powering as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that is so gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's great.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't power-power because I was too busy taking pictures and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I had fun, but one thing that always pisses me off is the fact that when they don't have any type of
[SPEAKER_21]: Anime or Video Game Gathering, whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have that one fanboy that pisses you off.
[SPEAKER_21]: You just want to strangle him and your friends are like, no, don't.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at some of these pictures very randomly on the site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, don't they look cute?
[SPEAKER_02]: You were up near the front, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you look at this one picture I'm about to post, this is when I got my Powerpuff Mix CDs signed and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, go you.
[SPEAKER_21]: and the one before that, my friend Aaron, we pushed him onto the stage so he could do Power Power as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: How many people were at this thing?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, there was about 40 people downstairs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, everybody around the first and second floors is about 100 or so.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it was just so awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: Words really can't describe per se, but I did find somebody that videotaped it, so I'm trying to get a copy of the footage of the concert.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I remember that guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I met that guy when I was in Jersey.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, Aaron.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fanboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: He looks very happy to be with those three sexy ladies there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: What we did was after we took the pictures, we went back and wished Yoko Ishida a happy birthday because her birthday is this Friday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I also found out that supposedly she's going to be on live with Regis and Kathy Lee, no, Regis and Kelly doing Power Power this Friday.
[SPEAKER_21]: No way.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who needs to take that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I've heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big props to Ranchan, by the way, because that's the first time in about five years where I said, no way, and then I got the response, way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so gonna TiVo that I'm so gonna TiVo that too
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like that, there's a comment in the chatroom, somebody needs to TiVo that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will TiVo it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Comcast Ghetto Knockoff TiVo, whatever they call it.
[SPEAKER_21]: You do realize, somebody's going to TiVo it, and it's going to end up on a torrent site somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good, because we haven't done movie time on Orange Lounge Radio in months, so we need a good thing to skewer, so I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_21]: Speaking of movies, one of my friends saw Serenity.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is what he said.
[SPEAKER_21]: I liked Serenity when it was called Outlaw Star.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard people complaining that it's way too similar to certain animes out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here comes Extaper the Weed and Whore.
[SPEAKER_16]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just grabbed the mic.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just heard Serenity, so I automatically darted for the mic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is it a rip-off of popular animes?
[SPEAKER_16]: I have no clue because I don't watch anime.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: But if it is, it's really good, and I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go out to your nearest theater.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess it happens.
[SPEAKER_21]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, maybe he was indirectly inspired.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's a fancy coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, there was the whole show that preceded it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of tough to decide that your movie is going to rip it off after the fact.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, from what I understand, the series ripped off Outlaw Star and Cowboy Bebop.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, hey, everybody steals from somebody.
[SPEAKER_24]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_24]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Imitation is the finest form of flattery, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go ahead and let you go, Ranchan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much for calling in, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Peace.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, fellas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peace, y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: She actually had to run out to take a call real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: She said bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go to one more call here since I don't want to get in a cage match with that DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: So our old buddy Zaku is hammering the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, as always.
[SPEAKER_02]: As always.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you've got an opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: If anybody's got an opinion on Xtreme 2, I know you've got one.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what is it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, first of all, since I'm too broke to buy me a PS2, thus I don't have the game, but I have been hearing around that it's pretty good that people, especially within the city, there's a lot of city players I heard who are actually playing the game and actually going through the hell of Dance Master mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about Dan's master mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it appropriate for DDR on a home mix or should they have just stuck to the make it look like the arcade?
[SPEAKER_14]: In other words, it only appeases to one type of player, like a hardcore person, like a seasoned DDR player.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dan's Master Mode
[SPEAKER_14]: It depends, I mean, from what I'm hearing, like, certain challenges where you can't step on the original arrows, or you can't step on this particular arrow, which is basically an in-the-group rip-off, if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Those, well, now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, mines, come on, come on, you gotta admit, Konami's trying to play the mine card in this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, poison arrows existed in Ultramix before that, and other mission modes, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like when, you know, I could say that In The Groove ripped off the multiple arrow idea from either Pump It Up or DDR Solo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Both of all had multiple arrows, so it's... Yeah, but not more than two.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about more than two at the same time?
[SPEAKER_25]: Actually, DDR Dancing Stage or DDR First Mix, one of the songs that was supposed to be on there, had three arrows at one time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But... Solo... Okay, the step charts for Dropout Maniac on DDR Solo has four.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to hit four at once.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm, alright, anyways, MTV2 had their video mods thing on Friday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, how did that go?
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't catch the beginning though, so I can't vouch for what they had for DDR Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you know, they're going to air it again in about two and a half hours from now, East Coast time.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'll probably see that beginning part when they had it.
[SPEAKER_14]: What the hell was the DDR reference on this thing?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know because I didn't see that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I couldn't catch the beginning of the video.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, what good are you?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_14]: As I said, you know, they're going to air it again in like 1.30 tonight, so obviously I'm going to be able to stay up to see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I can't vouch for it now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll set the TiVo.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish I had a TiVo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Besides, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zaku, I want to know your thoughts on the Pump It Up thing, the custom soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, let me... Obviously, this is no surprise.
[SPEAKER_14]: Xbox is pretty much so... You could pretty much sell an Xbox on the whole idea of basically playing games with your own tracks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Except none of them use it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, well, I've seen a lot of, there's some folks I know that actually use it in certain games.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyways, the whole thing, it's too basic, in other words.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's not a robust step editor, in my honest opinion.
[SPEAKER_14]: You need something, obviously, to find the BPM, but also something to calculate the gap.
[SPEAKER_14]: And something to assist you, you know, to take every measure.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that way, you know, your song, so that way you can make your song sync up.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so, you know, it doesn't feel robust.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you've got to check out the pump editor, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very similar to a DDR editor, but just with some extra stuff there to support the custom soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zaku, I'm hanging up on you now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a cage match to get to.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to get into the Orange Lounge Cage Match here momentarily there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting calls tonight, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to think if there's any other things, little pieces of news I wanted to get to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not, so why don't we get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, which I'm so not set up for, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I need somebody to stretch some time, because I'm so not set up for tonight.
[SPEAKER_25]: The question is, has anyone actually played the Karaoke Revolution party demo yet?
[SPEAKER_25]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I haven't because I can't find my microphone.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie doesn't sing in public.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can play in the privacy of your own home if you so choose.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't sing outside of my car.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would play it if it had gorillas.
[SPEAKER_25]: Karaoke Revolution Automobile Edition.
[SPEAKER_25]: Singing in your car.
[SPEAKER_02]: karaoke revolution for your cell phone maybe in fact that's what they should have as one of the stages you know you're singing in your car or you're singing in your shower oh yeah cause like how you sing in different locations like you know you're at the country bar and then you're at the super bowl or whatever it's called they should have the first stage that you're singing on the toilet or something they need to have like the toys level where you're in the bathroom at the toys factory from toys singing in the corner
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm ready for the cage match.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you guys?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into tonight's Orange Lounge Radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_02]: The way the cage match works, boys and girls, we're going to put three songs in, and they're going to do battle head-to-head against each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you guys will vote for your favorite, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Ramani Music and Video Game Music program, which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, on this station where we're not here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's your guys' vote that makes or breaks the cage match.
[SPEAKER_02]: The rule for how a song gets put in cage match is
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to want to put it in GageMatch.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's really no other rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't have to be a Bomani song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't have to be a 2005 song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just has to be something cool that we want to play on the air for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to start off with last week's winner, of which you're only going to hear a clip of because it was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to be song number one you're going to hear tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a remix of V from the Diverse Systems collections.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's Diverse Systems?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was this 8?
9?
[SPEAKER_02]: 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: From Diverse Systems 9, this is last week's winner, Dorisia with V. Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number one in tonight's cage match, V, a little remix there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're going to get into the rest of the cage match tonight, and we're going to go into song number two, which is Jamie's pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, I had a hard time figuring out what your pick was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you care to explain it here?
[SPEAKER_17]: I couldn't think of anything because I was busy doing my last bit of illustrator homework.
[SPEAKER_17]: So this is from Team America World Police, the montage song, because I couldn't think of anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is the montage song from Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also featured in South Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a very random pick, I must say.
[SPEAKER_17]: I couldn't think of anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to go into song number two tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the montage from Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_06]: And show us the passage of time, we're gonna need a montage Show like things happening at once, remind everyone of what's going on And with every shot, show a little of who
Just a beginner to a pro, you need a montage Even Rocky had a montage
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number two in tonight's cage match, Montage from Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely a random pick, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what did you think of that on a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ten, fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_25]: X to fur on a scale of one to ten?
[SPEAKER_16]: I would give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've never seen Team America because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's not as funny as South Park.
[SPEAKER_16]: I never got into South Park until this year, so if it's that kind of humor, I may like it.
[SPEAKER_16]: But that song was great.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki, your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_25]: It started off as a 5, but it became a 9 because it gradually got better over time.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a montage, yeah, I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My thoughts is that, damn, between your song and my song, we're practically handing Loki another victory tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are we going to need a montage for this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait until you fucking see what I picked, alright?
[SPEAKER_17]: But anyway... Do I need to go hide?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I was bad tonight, but this was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, funny enough, I picked a montage.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was...
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny, but I don't think people are going to vote for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it gets a 7 because it is a pretty funny parody.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think the funnier song in Team America World Police was the Everyone Has AIDS song.
[SPEAKER_17]: I almost picked... Actually, it was a toss-up between the montage, Everyone Has AIDS, and Pearl Harbor Sucks and I Miss You.
[SPEAKER_16]: Even... There's a song called Everyone Has AIDS?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're parodying Rent in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Abba!
[SPEAKER_02]: This is definitely one of those guilty pleasure things, and there really is no excuse for me liking this song at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I apologize in advance, but I'll be damned if this isn't just a damn fun song.
[SPEAKER_02]: So my pick for tonight's Cage Mass is a brand new song by everyone's favorite lesbians on the planet, Tattoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is their new single, All About Us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number three in tonight's cage match, Tattoo with All About Us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see what you guys thought about that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_16]: um actually I can't I couldn't hear because I could hear myself too loudly um it was repetitive and it sounded like everything else I've ever heard them do so it gets a 5 extifer it's um not a very good song it is very stupid I don't like them I don't like tattoo I want to get a tattoo but I don't like tattoo and uh but the the guy getting shot is pretty cool
[SPEAKER_16]: But he should have raped her.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: He should have raped her because... Scale of 1 to 10 before the angry emo come in.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, um, 2.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know, it would have gotten a higher score with me, but I just didn't really know what the song was about.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, um, it's getting... It's not about them.
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought it... Okay, well.
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, it gets a 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, Loki actually gave it a higher score than everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: I give that song a 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Tattoo is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're so awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the guy gets shot in the video and blood goes everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's badass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: She should have been raped.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just what Russians do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, song number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number one, Doresia with Vee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number two you can vote for tonight, Montage.
[SPEAKER_02]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Tattoo with All About Us.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I had to choose the best lyric from the song there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You two weren't singing all about us in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Place vote now, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song number one, song number two, or, if you so choose, song number three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, this is the part of the show where we go over to Loki and ask what's going on in the sim scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki, what's going on in the sim scene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a damn thing, huh?
[SPEAKER_25]: Nothing important.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, actually, I guess one small thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: Someone put up a conceptual artwork for what will be Step Mania 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it will be Step Mania 4?
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, someday.
[SPEAKER_25]: And it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't really know how to describe it.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's just going to be the same damn thing with another skin on it.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, so much for what's going on in The Simpsons, I guess.
[SPEAKER_25]: I did see, though, there was a new music game coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_25]: as much of a music game as Rez was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't we talk about that on a podcast like four weeks ago or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen much more about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not E3, but a Tokyo game show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's called E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_25]: The game's called E3.
[SPEAKER_25]: I remember now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has screenshots come out of this yet or something?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I watched the Tokyo game special on G4 and they showed... That was one of their focuses.
[SPEAKER_25]: They were showing that game.
[SPEAKER_25]: Looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like a first... It's like a shooter game, but it's not...
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought G4 was Spike TV for kids now
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, they have their moments, but this, they actually had, you know, the two people from X-Play, Kevin Morgan, or Adam Morgan, and then they had that Kevin guy from Attack of the Show.
[SPEAKER_25]: The smartest people on the network to cover Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank God they, like, said whoever else that they have there that's really retarded.
[SPEAKER_25]: But they got the smart people, and they covered it pretty well, and...
[SPEAKER_25]: They kind of went more in depth with the Nintendo Revolution stuff and just everything.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it looked cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, if I could just show Jamie something real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to make sure Jamie got a chance to see this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is something we were talking about just a second ago, if you don't mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need a gun to keep myself from harm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I realize this is a radio show, but those of you that have seen this music video will know exactly what I'm talking about right here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here we go, and bam!
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_02]: Blood!
[SPEAKER_16]: It looks kind of like jelly.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, it's making me hungry.
[SPEAKER_16]: I need to get something to eat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, does that change your score any?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just curious if that would alter your score.
[SPEAKER_17]: Four.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute, didn't you give it a higher score before that?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, but now that I've had time to think about the song...
[SPEAKER_17]: It needs a montage.
[SPEAKER_23]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: So... Loki?
[SPEAKER_25]: We have to save it, don't we?
[SPEAKER_25]: We have to save that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give him a hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give him a little hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can drop a little hint.
[SPEAKER_02]: We... made a new webpage.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's a good hint.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's new!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's new, exactly.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it's a webpage.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what I haven't done yet?
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: What I need to do?
[SPEAKER_25]: I didn't have time during the week, but I need to pop in the DDR Extreme 2 DVD to find the track list.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think some folks already did that over on DR3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they found it already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not... There's nothing really in there, from what I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the other thing I didn't want to point out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we talk about Downgrader?
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP firmware?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seem like we talked about that on the podcast, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, it didn't happen until this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the actual downgrade didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked about on the podcast the fact that 2.0 had been exploited, but we hadn't talked about the downgrader yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what does this mean for hackers on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_25]: It means if you bought one that happened to be firmware 1.51 or 1.52 or 2.0, you can actually downgrade it back to 1.5.
[SPEAKER_25]: And the way you do that is you run this bit of homebrew code using an exploit in their image, their photo gallery thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: It basically is a buffer overflow which allows you to run your own code.
[SPEAKER_25]: And what that does is the program makes your PSP think it's a version 1.0.
[SPEAKER_25]: So then what you do is then you throw in the version 1.5 update.
[SPEAKER_25]: that came out a while ago for the Japanese, and you run the update.
[SPEAKER_25]: And what'll happen is it'll crash out at the very end because it realizes, hey, wait a second, this isn't, you know, version 1 PSP, but then you just kind of reset it a few times and you're back at version 1.5.
[SPEAKER_25]: Problem is, is because it's only a 99% install, we don't know what kind of repercussions that will have later on.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've heard things from people couldn't get their web browser working again to other stuff.
[SPEAKER_25]: But then again, I don't know if that's just people spreading rumors or what, but people have downgraded, upgraded, downgraded, upgraded, so you can do it, and so you have the best of both worlds.
[SPEAKER_25]: On the other hand, I thought about selling my other PSP to downgrade it, or downgrade one and sell it, just to get some more money.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm actually going to keep both because I don't know how...
[SPEAKER_25]: obviously they're working on version 2.5 which is going to come out soon so gotta keep one for that stuff and one for the homebrew stuff keeping one at 1.5
[SPEAKER_02]: Dokkan no Naka no Mozart
[SPEAKER_02]: and Hoppin' Choppin' we're going to play and Mario No Carnival.
[SPEAKER_25]: They really need to put the Para Para Dancers with that commercial that they had for Mario in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_25]: commercials.
[SPEAKER_25]: I think that would be great.
[SPEAKER_25]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to come back after this a break of music from DDR with Mario so you guys can check this out and we'll be back with more Orange Launch Radio.
Orange Launch Radio
Thanks for watching!
Mario's The Superstar
Mario the Superstar
[SPEAKER_18]: and Superstar!
[SPEAKER_01]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sup kids, we're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was some music from DDR with Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go, the Mozart one, Hoppin' Choppin', Carnival, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you think of DDR with Mario?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the first time some of you guys are hearing that music.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's incredibly happy and makes me so happy I could puke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that made me so happy that I think I pooped my pants because it lost controls in my bowel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need medication anymore.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Use Effexor?
[SPEAKER_16]: No!
[SPEAKER_16]: Just listen to Mario DDR.
[SPEAKER_25]: I heard Ice Clamor sound effects in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_02]: The typical Nintendo traits.
[SPEAKER_25]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I know why we don't play that anymore.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, it was cute.
[SPEAKER_25]: I thought some of it was cute.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like, Hoppin' Choppin' was a cute song, I thought.
[SPEAKER_25]: You know what that game needs?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: A lot of seizure-inducing strobing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should have.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny is that you'd think I would have heard that music at E3 when I actually got to play DDR with Mario, but I really didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the funny thing is, to put in perspective how difficult DDR with Mario is, I AAA'd the song I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the first time I ever played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not this, I don't profess to be some type of DDR king, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I'm not that great.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_02]: My cousin, Dr. D, does, but I do not profess to be some type of DDR god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, do you kids want to hear who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet you do.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's hear the results in a montage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, you could probably spell out the results in a V formation.
[SPEAKER_17]: That song gives me such a headache.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's tonight's winner.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other two songs not performing quite as badly as I anticipated, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was actually kind of close.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extover, you've got a mic?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I was just thinking.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is everybody in the chat room straight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because V is like for vagina.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, does everybody just like this song that much?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think just like the real world...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's probably some straight people and some gay people and some I don't know what the hell they are people in our chat room I don't really take the time to ask, you know, I don't go around everybody Let's take a poll I don't want to take a poll No, take a poll, you don't want to take a poll, you're gay I don't care You like taking polls Yeah, I don't want this to turn into ASL chat, okay
[SPEAKER_02]: or ASLS, you know, sexuality or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm here to talk about games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care who's gay.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_17]: We will know how many of our listeners are gay next week when I put ABBA in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, also, any of you that voted for Tattoo are obviously gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's not true because I know who voted for Tattoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just, you know, let me know if you're a porn loving motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just...
[SPEAKER_16]: Tell me.
[SPEAKER_17]: You made Roz cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: She just wanted me to say that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Why?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because you made her cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why?
[SPEAKER_17]: Why did she cry?
[SPEAKER_17]: The chatroom made her cry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who's Roz and why did she cry?
[SPEAKER_17]: She's one of my friends from the Gorillas board.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hello, friends.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the chatroom just made her cry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Why?
[SPEAKER_24]: For voting for that one?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_25]: The tribe has spoken.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think she should come in the chat room and bitch everybody out for me.
[SPEAKER_25]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, this is completely on a tangent, but since, you know, we're not going anywhere right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: You said friends, and that made me think of the Friends game.
[SPEAKER_25]: I got to watch a video of the Friends game, and let me just say, I wouldn't wish the Friends game on my worst enemies.
[SPEAKER_25]: I watched a good eight-minute video of this thing, and I wanted to fall asleep.
[SPEAKER_25]: I didn't even want to play the game after watching the game.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's just that awful.
[SPEAKER_25]: Is this another game that we need to get a copy of and autograph?
[SPEAKER_25]: It is bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: It is really bad.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's Friends, the one with all the trivia.
[SPEAKER_25]: It is narrated by the woman that does Janice on the show, the Fran Drescher wannabe.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_25]: And it's completely bland, and it just shows a bunch of clips from the show, and the trivia is just lame.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just want to fall asleep.
[SPEAKER_25]: I can't watch this anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a Friends game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you got the memo.
[SPEAKER_16]: Does it have... Wait, this is the TV show Friends, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, like the TV show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's a video game Friends.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I think that that is stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay, we'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's do...
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get into a segment that we're trying to make a regular segment on this show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or irregular, depending on what you have for dinner.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm trying to find the background music here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to... Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's the wrong track.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big Boobies No. 1
[SPEAKER_02]: Big Boobies No.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2, Big Boobies with Cocks in Them, Blood Spattered Boobies, Boobies and Sunflowers, Boobies for Milking, Boobies in Pee, Mastectomy Leftover Boobies, Hot Hairy Saggy Man Boobies, and then my last, my favorite here, Women in Roller Skates Peeing in Glass Bowls.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why did you do that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not gonna, you know, if you're gonna download that shit, I mean, don't blame it on me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, this is from the person that left us with the bleached asshole joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: By the way, um... Did they use something other than bleach?
[SPEAKER_16]: Did I talk about the asshole strips yet?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, well, you know how you have, like...
[SPEAKER_16]: What about the kind that are supposed to dissolve when you go?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm disgusted.
[SPEAKER_16]: I am so disgusted.
[SPEAKER_16]: Remember, mint scattles.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, we're going to just get into this here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get into a new segment here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's actually a returning segment, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're trying to make this a regular segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Extraverse Movie Review, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that's gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, just like you.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, Extraverse, what movie are you going to review today?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: The Long Kiss Goodnight.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is an old ass movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Serenity.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Serenity.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've already talked about Serenity, but of course everybody probably knows that I'm a Serenity fan.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm a Firefly fan.
[SPEAKER_16]: What did you think of Serenity on the second viewing this week?
[SPEAKER_16]: The second viewing was great.
[SPEAKER_16]: I got to see it with a lot of people and they all liked it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was sitting in the straight guy row, so I was an honorary straight guy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I counted all the girls' boobies and it seems like they all have two.
[SPEAKER_16]: I also...
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_17]: Does that mean that I was an honorary gay man that night?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jamie was sitting in the gay man row, which you were sitting in.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, thank you for reminding our listeners.
[SPEAKER_16]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I also... Oh, that's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyways, I just wanted to talk about Serenity more.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyways, so Serenity is great, and then the third time I watched it, which was yesterday...
[SPEAKER_16]: I was enjoying it a lot too.
[SPEAKER_16]: And my sister like hit me in my arm when something really shocking happened in the movie because she really likes Firefly as well.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, but it hurt.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Serenity on the third viewing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thumbs up, thumbs down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thumbs fucking up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, how about Long Kiss Goodnight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, this movie's like 20 years old.
[SPEAKER_16]: How old is this?
[SPEAKER_16]: I loved that movie when I saw it the first time because Geena Davis kicks ass and it's just a cheesy, like, action movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: But, I mean, I saw it for the first time in years with Garrett, who was on the show last week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right, the Poppin' Music Whore is what we call him on the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, Poppin' Music Whore.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Poppin' Music Whore and I...
[SPEAKER_16]: Make fun of it quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, there are so many cheesy lines.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's like this line where this guy goes, where Gina Davis says something like, I'm saving myself to get raped.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, it's just so random.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm like, okay, you know, that was, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was, you know, it's a fun movie or whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's a little long, but I give it thumbs sideways.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: For you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, lastly, you told me that you were going to be reviewing a TV show tonight because you didn't get to really see a new movie in the theater.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to review a TV show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which TV show?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, The Will and Grace.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad you prepped for tonight's movie review segment.
[SPEAKER_16]: Will and Grace.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'd never gotten to Will and Grace until this year when I moved to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, like, I think it's pretty damn hilarious.
[SPEAKER_16]: But they had their live show, which, you know, I was hoping for them to mess up more, but they didn't.
[SPEAKER_16]: But it was funny anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: I had a good time with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so thumbs up or thumbs down for Will and Drake?
[SPEAKER_16]: Thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Up.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is so boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Extrofer, for that movie review.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now get off our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get off our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get into another segment we love to do here on Orange Lounge Radio every single damn week because you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: We are full of angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am full of rage.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's why we have to do the FUs of the week every single week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkSakura, what's your excuse?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do we have to do the FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_15]: Balls.
[SPEAKER_17]: A big F you goes toward my sinus infection that I'm finally over and the fact that I haven't worked out.
[SPEAKER_17]: An F you goes toward the Adobe company for making Illustrator.
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate vectors.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know you've been doing Illustrator homework for too long when you start seeing real life in terms of vectors?
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate them, hate them, hate them.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I am posting my homework in my chatroom.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think you're like that one best, which is in a red monotone.
[SPEAKER_17]: It really is looking like shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I also am mad at people in SUVs.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's that kind of like one, the Escalade?
[SPEAKER_17]: It looks like it's a fake SUV with a truck ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like the SUVs that look like a box.
[SPEAKER_17]: Someone at Sam's Club last night was double parked in one of them.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I totally made fun of them loudly in the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_16]: Was it a lesbian?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it was some stupid...
[SPEAKER_17]: I was screaming, hi, I have money, and I have shit for brains and I can't park, and he heard me, and then I drove off.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, I called a lady a cunt one time, because Rob told me to.
[SPEAKER_16]: Really?
[SPEAKER_16]: He told me to roll down the window, because some lady cut him off in the parking lot, and he goes, that lady's a cunt.
[SPEAKER_16]: Christopher, roll down that window and call her a cunt.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just jokingly, you know, and I'm like,
[SPEAKER_16]: I looked at him and I looked at everybody else in the car and I said, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: I rolled down the window and I said, you're a cunt.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Rob can back me up.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's not making this shit up.
[SPEAKER_16]: He really isn't.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, and Legend of Zaku, you get an F you because I've had my Wacom for a very long fucking time, and I still hate that stupid goddamn program because he made us fucking use the pen tool.
[SPEAKER_17]: I could have done the whole thing with the drawing tool, but no, we had to do it with the pen tool.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, don't fucking ever correct me again, you don't have the right.
[SPEAKER_17]: A second FU goes toward Loki's song because it gives me a headache every time I hear it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And an FU to gold detailing on cars that really don't need gold detailing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also another FU to Legend of Zaku because I was not a math major because it was a waste of my time.
[SPEAKER_17]: And really...
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, if he says anything more about what I need, I'm fucking kicking you, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: In fact, I'm going to do it anyway just because I fucking feel like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You piss me off every time I come here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Stop pissing me off!
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, and, uh, FU goes toward, uh, everything else.
[SPEAKER_16]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_17]: That was.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_16]: Next up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, um, I've really got, like, one major one that I need to get off my chest, and that is, fuck you the fact that I'm potentially have to go to jury duty on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell them you're in school.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'll get out of it until December.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just don't want to get, I just want to get out of it, period.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, uh, fuck you that.
[SPEAKER_25]: Tell them you're incredibly racist and homophobic.
[SPEAKER_25]: No, I'll just, I'll wait, because I might not even have to go, and if I do,
[SPEAKER_25]: Um, I'll take care of it.
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever I need to do, I'll do.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's your duty, duty.
[SPEAKER_25]: I just basically made it look like I don't want to be there.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, you know, if I don't want to be there, I don't want to be there.
[SPEAKER_25]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: And, um, yeah, pretty much that.
[SPEAKER_25]: And for some reason, um, I'm having problems with certain things.
[SPEAKER_25]: A webpage related that pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_25]: But, um, ah.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's all I really have.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, my turn then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to give an F you to me for not getting enough sleep at night throughout the week and on the weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to give an F you to the fact... Shut the fuck up, Christopher.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to give an F you to the fact that I haven't been eating very well all week, but at least I've kind of... Despite my irregular eating patterns, I've actually managed to lose some weight, so I guess I can't complain too much, except, you know, I don't want to, like, kill my liver or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so an F you to lack of motivation for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: An F you to other drama that I'm going through professionally right now, but I'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just...
[SPEAKER_02]: and FU to the fact that I still have work left to do and it's Sunday night and I've got to have it done by tomorrow morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to Fandango because it costs like $1.25 to use Fandango.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did you do the Fandango with your credit card?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fandango.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hobocamp.
[SPEAKER_02]: And come to find out that Serenity wasn't even that crowded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I could have just walked right in and got tickets.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought...
[SPEAKER_02]: Because of all the hype on LJ, I thought that theater was going to be packed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I'm sure that the earlier ones were, but I still think it's funny that I woke up late and then made it down the freeway in 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, that was crazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Things I do for fandom.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, let's get to Extover's FUs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, FU to people with unnecessary drama.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, um...
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm so indifferent to you.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't bring it and put it in my face.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know?
[SPEAKER_16]: But otherwise, a big old fuck you in a good way to everybody I like.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because it feels good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_16]: A big old anal thrust to everyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, you're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on to the chatroom, shall we?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkKnight says, F you to gas prices, work, and studying for tests.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDArcoholic says, information for me that wasn't an F you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomokun says, fuck not getting my para para para machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck my cold and fuck my bad ram.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounded dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sakarina says fuck Life 365 for making me miss the first quarter of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that guy who's been stealing that 12 year old I find cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck Illustrator because it makes DarkSakura angry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And fuck Tomokun in a friendly way for interrupting my bisexual erotica reading session.
[SPEAKER_02]: And F you to all USDDR mixes for not having little bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I need to get Pump It Up and put it in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: MPQ says, F you to guys that pretend to be girls on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like a fucking internet cliche.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to my router for being a piece of shit and randomly deciding to not let people connect.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to Injection of Love Hina Mix for reminding me of Love Hina, which I hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goggle says, F you to Garden Burger for tasting like meatloaf instead of a burger.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the awful lag I'm getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is all about the bokeh burger, honey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snare, F you to V for still being there.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to BevMo.
[SPEAKER_02]: for having such great drinks that suck my wallet dry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another F you to BevMo for having paper bags that have no handles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jazz says F you to my computer's hard drive completely dying.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, yay for backup drives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also F you to me getting seasonal winter long cold.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate my immune system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Illusion says F you to Family Guy for sucking so much recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: All it has become is a bunch of lame illusions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh ho ho.
[SPEAKER_16]: I would agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: To older episodes that string along the already thin plot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree 500%.
[SPEAKER_02]: Family Guy sucks this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rini says my...
[SPEAKER_02]: Upmost Ultimate Fuck You goes to Dance Master Mode's mission with Boom Boom Dollar KOG G3 on break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck break like all get out because it's the worst modifier ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: This fuck ass mission has literally made Dance Master impossible to complete for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everybody, I want you to use fuck ass in a sentence later today.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the word of the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And fuck anybody who said the Dynamite Rave heavy on reverse on hard because it wasn't and it still wasn't
[SPEAKER_02]: when you had to not do well on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, one for Sky because of his hidden bad omen from last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys may or may not remember, I put a hex on Rini last week because I was mad at him about something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember what now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brightsta says F you to gas prices, F you to people who smoke, I'd like to sue you for second hand smoking F you to this asshole who's in our dorm and keeps playing his music really loud F you to the campus store for having such high prices for food F you to my router which XP keeps showing as disconnecting my ethernet cable physically And just an FYI as someone who used to smoke, your anger is not going to make them stop any faster
[SPEAKER_17]: By the way, as far as the people in dorm rooms that play their music really loudly, what I used to do is I used to, when the people across the hall would play their rap really loudly, because I hate that type of rap, I would turn on my stereo really loud, which was on top of my chest of drawers, and we had cinder block walls, and would crank Vanessa May to the ultimate loudness on Takata and Fugue in D minor.
[SPEAKER_17]: But you should do that with the organ version, because I guarantee you,
[SPEAKER_17]: It will chase people off, and you will have the entire building to yourself.
[SPEAKER_17]: It works!
[SPEAKER_16]: To the person quitting smoking, um, maybe you should think about, uh, you know, having to fuck ass.
[SPEAKER_16]: Every single time you want to smoke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Acer800 says, A big F you to my trig teacher who is a lazy master student who teaches shit during class.
[SPEAKER_02]: And F you to the lady who was behind me while I was driving and freaking honked at me when there was a cop in front of me and I didn't want to be arrested.
[SPEAKER_02]: LegendOfZaku says, F you to not having a modded slim PS2 and some Bomani games when I should have had them by now.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to my ever so weak and shitty DDR stamina.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to me being a bitch about whether or not to compete in freestyle in a major tourney that you probably already know about next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkTetsuya says, F you to Mission C30 and the mission with Dynamite Ravoni.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, you have a lot of angst tonight, chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the fanboy, says Ron Chan, at the Yoko Ishida concert.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one cares you came from Boston.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were loud and rude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go jump in traffic.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to use that at some point this week during a call.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, tell one of your callers to go jump in traffic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Enjoy your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not going to pay your claim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go jump in traffic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Color of Sakura says, F you to all the stuff I bought on eBay in the last month, and it's still not being here.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the brake modifier in New York.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly, GS191 says, F you to my college for putting all my core classes, especially math, online.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to websites that are taken down without warning and call it redesigning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I'm looking at you, DDRmaniaX and BomaniStyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to myself for not having any better F yous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_02]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, you guys had a lot of angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are just mean people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mean people.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember kids, down the road, not across the street
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to get to the rest of the Extreme 2 music I wanted to play tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to play Spin Spin Sugar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow
[SPEAKER_02]: Ask Orange Lounge when we come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you guys had a lot of questions last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't even get to all of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we missed your question last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's your chance to get it answered after we come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: So send a private message to Sky with your question for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to be with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to take it easy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Capture and pray.
I've got so much to show you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Mm-hmm, mm-hmm It's a wonderful night, you gotta take it from me It's a wonderful night, come on and break it on down It's a wonderful night, go ahead and release It's a wonderful night, come on and break it on down You know the music's searching, you need a tune-up Soon as they out the gate, they all the wanna hear the corner, uh-huh Boy, that was cool, but now, but then I heard a rumor, uh-huh Your crew was riding for a while
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a wonderful night, you gotta take it from me It's a wonderful night, come on and break it on down It's a wonderful night, you gotta shake it from me It's a wonderful night, come on and break it on down Girl, I want it, you got it, your body's like a narcotic The thought is auto-erotic, come on and break it on down Can I get it on credit against your brick house?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll bet it, take it as far as you let it, come on and break it on down
[SPEAKER_10]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crap-free Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're about ready to get into Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, first off, I wanted to point out that we actually have somebody who... There was an FU back there that was about Bomani style and how they're down all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we have somebody who happens to be one of their moderators over at Bomani Style that would like us to clarify...
[SPEAKER_02]: They aren't down for redesigning.
[SPEAKER_02]: The motherboard on their server went kaboom.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been word, however, that MimaniStyle 7.0 is progressing nicely, however.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a friendly clarification.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need to also make the announcement, the one that I mentioned to you during the break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: There will not be a Pump Up the Volume this week because of other reasons.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I will be returning the week after with the much-promised, because actually people did ask for it, Blur Marathon event.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ask Gorn's Lounge
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_02]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_02]: My question is this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who will be the first person to use the word fuck ass in their question?
[SPEAKER_02]: MPQ says, what would your ultimate video game be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Golf Land Birthday Party Sniper would be my ultimate video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, do you have an ultimate video game?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I'm not sure if the question is like... Completely redone for one of the new systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be very sexy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Guardian Legend, the MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extifer, what would your ultimate video game be?
[SPEAKER_02]: In the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what would your ultimate video game be?
[SPEAKER_25]: Um...
[SPEAKER_25]: I think they should have a fighting game with every character from all the systems.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just one giant brawl.
[SPEAKER_25]: Call it, like, Console Wars or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Allusion says, What's it all about, Alfie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want... Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't watch crappy Jude Law movies, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I didn't watch the crappy original either, I'm sorry to say, so I don't really know what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_16]: Apparently they weren't crappy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, they got some critical mass, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the first one I'm sure was critically loved.
[SPEAKER_17]: You say Alfie, I start thinking of, like, in Barbarella, her ship.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alfie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I think of the little creature from Melmac that liked to eat cats.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Alf!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you could call him Alfie as a nickname.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_17]: I kill me!
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn you people.
[SPEAKER_16]: He, he, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brightsta says, can you pass me the first of the Mario Mix songs we heard?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to add Captain Lou Albano to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, kids, piracy is wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Email me off air.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it did sound an awful lot like, you know, the... Actually, let me get into this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do the Mario!
[SPEAKER_02]: Swing your arms from side to side.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, it's time to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do the Mario!
[SPEAKER_16]: Total silence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Socorina says, will my request for that Diverse System remix of Quasar be played before the end of the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not likely tonight, my friend, but probably next week when we don't have so much Extreme 2 music to worry about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Socorina says, what does each member of the Orange Lounge Radio crew prefer, hairy or hairless balls?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's a toss-up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because, you know, there's some days where I'm like, you know, wake up in the morning, you know, and, you know, want to get my daily, you know, porn for breakfast.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it's like, maybe I want to see hairy balls.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sometimes, you know, I wake up in the morning and I want to see hairless balls.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sometimes I have that, you know, aching desire to shave my own balls.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, here you go.
[SPEAKER_25]: How about balls that aren't as hot as the surface of the sun and fucking sweaty all the time?
[SPEAKER_25]: Those are the balls that we prefer.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about bowling balls?
[SPEAKER_25]: I like cheese balls.
[SPEAKER_25]: Cheese balls are good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jazz says... Jazz, the answer to your question is I can't say that on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like meatballs.
[SPEAKER_02]: For my Kia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me and cheese balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jazz, don't repeat it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't repeat it, Jazz.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zachu says, what will I win if I guess the DDR song used in last Friday's episode of MTV2's Video Mods featuring DDR Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Does anybody in this room watch MTV?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they giving it away?
[SPEAKER_17]: Reject boss icons!
[SPEAKER_16]: Because we're not.
[SPEAKER_16]: After they did that next marathon for like five days straight, I was like...
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't watch this channel anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jaded wants to know, where did you get the Ask Orange Lounge intro music?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Ask Orange Lounge intro music is actually Journey to the Wonderland from Keyboard Mania 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Keyboard Mania 2, it's Journey to the Wonderland by NPB.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the lyrics, of course, are sung by yours truly, One and Only Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Knight says, Hey Sky, you should play Get Busy just to throw the chat room off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, you know, there's a reason I didn't play Get Busy tonight, and that's because I had to play it, um, 20 times this week in Mission Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rini wants to know, Could you help a poor soul with my break problem, pretty please?
[SPEAKER_02]: I already use Step Mania, and I can't do that fuck-ass syncing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, hee hee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um,
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Break, I remember, was in one of the Oni courses in Extreme, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you had to play Sexy Planet Oni on Break or something, and it was a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The best way to do it was to play that song over and over in regular mode, and so you kind of, like, you start to hear your feet as a separate rhythm in your head.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very similar to the way you get really good at 2DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: You start to hear what the key patterns sound like in your head.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what you're going to have to do with this DDR thing, is play the song over and over in regular mode and hear the pattern of the steps in your head, and then...
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, then again, if it's a song he hasn't unlocked yet, I guess you're just fucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Break, by the way, is when the arrows slow down as they reach the top.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the reverse of boost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bugged wants to know, what fuck-ass games have you had the joy of playing as of late?
[SPEAKER_02]: None.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Pack'n Roll earlier today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll talk about that more on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can't even remember the last video game I played.
[SPEAKER_24]: Didn't I make you play something?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sweaty Balls of the Game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_16]: As in Sweaty Balls of the Game.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sweaty Balls of the Game.
[SPEAKER_25]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: As in The White Mage is the Bitch of the Game.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, I had to feed Taco again this morning.
[SPEAKER_25]: He hasn't run away yet, even though I haven't fed him for three days.
[SPEAKER_25]: And I played Lost in Blue a bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to really get a dog named Taco.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a cool name for a child.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm telling you, after the joke last night about why Helen Keller's dog ran away, my next dog's name is... The other day I was telling Helen Keller jokes to Loki and his fiance and they just loved it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was even funnier because I was partially drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the funniest I've seen you in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, I know, because I can't be funny unless I'm ripping off other people's jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, we need your mama joke of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give me a second.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you need to work on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkTreadStudio wants to know, Will Sky's voice, the video game, ever return, or is it doomed to obscurity?
[SPEAKER_02]: My friend, it is doomed to obscurity.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an inside joke from like two and a half years ago on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to get on the, we used to do, before we were a real structured station, not that we ever have been a structured station, but DarkSakura and I used to do what was called fuck-off shows where we would just randomly get on the stream.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't have scheduled programs.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would just randomly, like it could be midnight on a Tuesday night, we would just randomly get on the stream and kick everyone off and go live and do our own show, just play music we wanted to play and do whatever the fuck we wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we called it a fuck-off show because if you didn't like what we were doing, you could fuck off.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I used to get on there and I would sing my own versions of Bobani songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I had my own version of Cowgirl and other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think they're wondering if I'm going to do that again and the answer is no.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: Your mama's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to hype this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I have never heard that Helen Keller joke before in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did Helen Keller do when she fell off a cliff?
[SPEAKER_02]: She screamed her hands off.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to get some angry emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what we do here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't ready to do it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go to your Big Boobs 1 icon.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, you probably hit all my music in the Big Boobs folder.
[SPEAKER_16]: Peeing in glass bowls or whatever the shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to make up for it by saying a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright kids, it's DarkSakura's Yo Mama Joke of the Week.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a couple.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yo Mama's so stupid, I told her drinks were on the house so she went and got a lighter.
And my other one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yo mama so stupid she took the Pepsi challenge and chose Coke.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_17]: I said that joke wrong because I meant to be Mountain Dew.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yo mama so stupid she reckoned a quarterback was a refund.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're laughing at yourself.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yo mama so stupid she sold her car for gas money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your mama says stupid, when you were born she looked at your umbilical cord and said, well, it comes with a cable.
[SPEAKER_02]: ColorofSakura wants to know, if you could remake any video game from the 16-bit era or earlier, what would it be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter II.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Repeat the question.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you could remake any video game from the 16-bit era or earlier, what would it be?
[SPEAKER_17]: Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll say something different, then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just said Street Fighter II, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: X-Man.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think that they've already remade all the games that I like.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oregon Trail!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the last question we have tonight, Nince wants to know, will Loki singing ever come back to the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have to wait for Karaoke Revolution Party to come out.
[SPEAKER_25]: I hope not, and we don't really have the setup for that, luckily.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we can always make it happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think that you should play I'm Stayin' In.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I have it anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta dig for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to have it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: We gotta do a retrospective episode at the end of the year or something, and we'll do it on that.
[SPEAKER_25]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: I know where I should put that song, even though I don't want to put that song there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_25]: On the thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, the thing, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what we should do is get Loki to go to one of those recording studios that they have at the theme park and cut his own CD because I did that once and the old radio program I was on years ago before this show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I went to Great America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Six Flags.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, it's not Six Flags.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was Paramount.
[SPEAKER_17]: We went to see Margaret Cho.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_16]: I saved the best for last by what's her name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Penthouse model, American Beauty Queen Vanessa Williams So I recorded this song and then somehow the CD fell into the hands of Travis who was the host over on Understation Live and every week he would play that song and make fun of it I don't know Alright
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it's about time to wrap up the show, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_24]: The show's over.
[SPEAKER_24]: I know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sadness, huh?
[SPEAKER_24]: First off, it's already over.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can I get quiet now?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, if you want.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can go cry.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've never stayed through a whole show before.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were our special guest tonight, extra.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a special guest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extra special.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our chat room seems to like you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of them think we should add you on permanently, and to that I say... You gave us the Bleach Household joke.
[SPEAKER_17]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_17]: You gave us the Bleach Tassel joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: I did give you that Bleach Tassel joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: I am taking immense pride over that.
[SPEAKER_16]: That is really funny.
[SPEAKER_16]: Keep doing that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, let's go around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am going to choke that ferret.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_17]: We sent Zero on fire and sent him back to his flea infested... I'm sorry, did I say that on the air?
[SPEAKER_17]: We sent him back to live in a hole.
[SPEAKER_25]: Extifer, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: Akira Yamamoka should be a drink called Akira Yamamoka.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wait, did I pronounce his name right?
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extifer, hand him the goddamn microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: My microphone?
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, turn on the goddamn microphone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all his fault.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is why your novel would be on the show.
[SPEAKER_25]: Never.
[SPEAKER_25]: Never, ever.
[SPEAKER_25]: I've been evicted from the room.
[SPEAKER_25]: No one can hear you because you don't have the microphone.
[SPEAKER_25]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_25]: My final thought is... I have to finish the thing.
[SPEAKER_25]: But it's done, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay, super.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my final thought, just for you, chat room, you bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is Polovistian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Polovistian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pavlostian.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_17]: Reject false icons and sweaty balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: One word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_02]: To shut the show up.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.orangenautoradio.com Don't forget to check out our podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rate us a 5 in your player window so that we have a really high rating on Life 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't forget that we do broadcast 24 hours a day, 7 days a week with lovely music always going and playlists that's getting updated recently, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Surprise, surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: And check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check out our MySpace community.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check out our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_02]: And tell a friend about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell an enemy about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Either way, that's more attention for us because we crave attention.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just big old attention whores.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final word of the show, one word to sum it all up, everything in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what is tonight's final word?
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to do olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_20]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Link, they've come to town, come to save the Princess Zelda.
[SPEAKER_05]: God has took her away, now the children don't play, but they will when Link saves the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hallelujah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now Link!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.