[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of October 17th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody!
[SPEAKER_06]: Once again, welcome aboard for the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that video game podcast on the internet dedicated to all the gaming news you really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there's a whole lot of gaming podcasts out there now, so thank you guys especially for choosing us and sticking with us because I think if you go to the iTunes list of video game podcasts that are available, you get like a hundred.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's tons of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So thank you guys for choosing us.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: My name is Zul.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you the Keymaster?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also with us, Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't believe you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not the gatekeeper or whatever?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: No gatekeeper.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good, because then you guys would have to have sex or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be nasty.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm married.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: GAMING WEEK
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all about me, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: The diva of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I was so busy all week, I haven't had much of a chance to play things, although I have put in effort.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got a Dalmatian on that dog game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendogs?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: How quickly we forget.
[SPEAKER_01]: After forgetting to feed my dogs for like two days.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a new dog that lives with my Corgiine and my Shiba Inu Minchi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dan also got me that Lawyer game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Phoenix Wright, Ace Attorney.
[SPEAKER_01]: Phoenix Wright, Ace Attorney.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's ironic that there's like a lawyer game and a doctor game out like right around the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doctor game's getting a sequel too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard Trauma Center is really difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't gotten a chance to play it, but I hear Trauma Center is really, really difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, unfortunately that brings me back to the game of Life and Death.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that game back on the PC way long time ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think about Operation, but sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wouldn't Operation just be... Operation the MMO.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, too many doctors ruin the operation.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, I was going to play it and then Dan started to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's still playing through Castlevania, that butt, so he needs to let me play the attorney game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need to solve cases.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm good at that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also tried to play some Katamari, but I was too busy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I screamed obscenities at Illustrator this morning.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you could check out an Illustrator podcast to help you out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's got to be one out there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: We hate Adobe Hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you to everybody that helped out with that, sending your donations in online.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: And then turn over the proceeds with our donations.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I actually donated my own copies of Polarium and Field of Magic, which I'm done with both of those games very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because I remember how much you love Polarium.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's worse DS games out there, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check out my review of Sprung last week if you want to hear a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still need Electroplankton.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to check that out, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, how was your game of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't play too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did get to play a new game for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: That's still fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't get boring at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game I haven't been playing is Nintendogs because I'm tired of that game now and I'm not feeding my dog.
[SPEAKER_05]: My dog floated to the top of the bowl.
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to bring Taco over so I can play with Taco before he runs away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Burnout.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to check out some different games this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got SSX on tour.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm anticipating Warriors, which is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll definitely be reviewing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing Castlevania DS still.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I talked about it last week, but I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've been playing a lot more of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, not a whole lot of new stuff until today.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Day We Were Recording This Show
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think I finally narrowed it down to a couple.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know DarkSakura and I will both be playing on one of those servers together.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be on Scarlet Crusade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're both playing Alliance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please don't cyber-stalk us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'm not saying who our characters are or what.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they won't be named after ourselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you want to cyber-stalk us, send us an email.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody sent me an email that says, hey, I want to add you to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I said, okay, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they kicked my ass in Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wondering if they're doing new gamer tags for Xbox Live for the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm curious about that too, because I want to try and get Sky, just Sky, but... Same.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I'll be able to do it, but I will be willing to, you know, get on Xbox Live right when I get the game, so... Because I don't have just plain old Sky on regular Xbox right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise I got backup.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: but I'm playing a warlock but I'm only like level 3 right now but I thought it was pretty badass because I actually got a spell where you can set something on fire and that was cool like actually setting it on fire I have not left Final Fantasy XI I'm just going to try and balance the two games I'm going to balance the two games for a little while there's things about Final Fantasy XI that were really starting to get to me so I want to play World of Warcraft no there's things I like about Final Fantasy XI there's things I dislike about Final Fantasy XI I really need to sit down and
[SPEAKER_05]: Dedicate time to play the game I haven't played in months And I really, I don't want to give it up I still want to play the game But I need to dedicate a day or something In which the fiancé will not interfere with the game And I get to play I need to give WoW a fair shot Because honestly, I owe it to our listeners To give an unbiased perspective of what's going on in WoW Let's give away some crap You can send me a letter We'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's give away some crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last week we promised we would give away some crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to give away a copy of Death Junior and pull a number out of the hat there, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see who's going to be our lucky winner of Death Junior for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number two wins Death Junior on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to somebody who didn't say anything in their email, so I don't know if they have a screen name, but it's Noam, and I hope I said that right, Noam P. Noam P. I'm not going to say the whole last name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Noam P.
[SPEAKER_06]: won the copy of Death Jr.
[SPEAKER_06]: on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now we're going to give away Coated Arms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pull another number out of the hat there, if you will.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twelve.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number twelve.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Jason, and there's no last name, but I think it's cute because the username, it's coming from a Gmail address, and this is not the same as the username, but it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: and Otakuland is how their name comes up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otakuland is one of our also regular writers to our 2GoBox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otakuland won a copy of Coded Arms for the PSP, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just remember, folks, if you do have PSPs that are version 1.5 and you're going to be playing these games, I think Coded Arms does have a 2.0 update on it, so you want to go get that version changer, which is available on PSP Updates.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also would like to mention that Otakuland has actually been very helpful to me by suggesting there's a site called GameTZ just G-A-M-E-T-Z dot com that has people who deal in import games trading import games and someone on there has Panorama Cotton they want 500 freaking dollars for it and I said no but they do trade in the rare that would be a great Christmas present
[SPEAKER_01]: If some dear listener wants to spend $500 on little old me, I ain't stopping you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a sucker, for one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I ain't stopping you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, congratulations to our two winners there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad some people that are involved in the show could win those.
[SPEAKER_06]: So good job, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will do another giveaway very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tune in next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we'll have something next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, do we have anything in the prize vault for next week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got an assortment of anime soundtracks, like a ton of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well, we'll just have to give a whole lot of those away, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: and also comparing it to what the current laws are.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, there's one in particular that is actually the first one used.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, the person who wrote this article did a comparison by showing the law about the sale of alcohol to minors compared with the law regarding the game sale.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the game sale one reads as this, except as otherwise provided in subdivision C, every person who sells, furnishes, gives, or causes to be sold, furnished, or given away.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, actually, that's the alcoholic beverage one.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyway, are given away any alcoholic beverage to any person under the age of 21 years is guilty of a misdemeanor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any person under the age of 21 who purchases any alcoholic beverage or any person under the age of 21 who consumes any alcoholic beverage in any on-sale premises is guilty of a misdemeanor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, compared to the violent game law, I'll just read a little bit of part of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Violent video game means a video game in which the range of options available to a player includes killing, maiming, dismembering, or sexually assaulting the image of a human being if those acts are depicted in the game in a manner that does either the fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: It goes into...
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole outline of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of what it's going into as far as trying to define is that it's going on the assumption that it's depicting a violent act on a person.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thing is, is that they're not people.
[SPEAKER_01]: and their video game images.
[SPEAKER_06]: Without rehashing this whole same argument over and over again though because it seems like we've had something about violent video games like every week on this program for the last three months.
[SPEAKER_01]: The point is it's not a clear law.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who makes that definition?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is violent?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who makes that definition and who's checking on them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we've got a system of checks and balances in this country.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's checking on the people that are making these calls?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the whole point it makes here is how clear the sale of alcohol law is.
[SPEAKER_01]: In comparison to this
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: When the same something does not exist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't necessarily disagree with trying to control the sale of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like you would say that an under 17 person shouldn't buy an R-rated DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: But my whole thing is that the bill is so vague that it seems like it's just prepared to be there to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Target things when they come out like Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's built so that when somebody kills somebody and blames Grand Theft Auto, that's when people are going to panic and say, who sold them the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Find them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Invoke the law.
[SPEAKER_06]: But my question is, no, no, before that all happens, who is making the determination what is a value?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my biggest problem with the law.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I suppose they have to do what they have to do, and I'm okay with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was all for ratings.
[SPEAKER_01]: because ratings puts the power in the hands of those who should possess it, the parents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not have the bill just adopt the ratings that are in place right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what this is?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically legalizing censorship as far as... In a way, in a way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's limiting free expression.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not stopping the games from being made, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's putting the scarlet letter on them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a great comparison right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But let's face it, in some of our demographic, I know for me, the games that have the scarlet letter on them, or should I say the scarlet number, I'm going to be more attracted to and go, ooh, do I get to see some titties in this one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want more titties in my games if
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they're going to be preventing kids from buying them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means, Rockstar, the gloves are off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do whatever the fuck you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just release the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think...
[SPEAKER_01]: I look at this as the government basically trying to take the power from the people, trying to take the responsibility out of the people's hands.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do admit, the game companies do have a duty of responsibility to the consumer to make sure that the product that they put on the market is exactly what they say they're selling.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: To rate the game appropriately and market the game towards the appropriate audience.
[SPEAKER_01]: To compare, when I was studying business law, they brought up a case about a woman who was suing over having pieces of clamshell in her clam chowder.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she broke a tooth.
[SPEAKER_01]: So she sued.
[SPEAKER_01]: The thing is, is that there is an expectation that there may be clamshell in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: She lost, not in the game, but in the soup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warning, this game may contain clam parts.
[SPEAKER_01]: But she lost the case because under the rights and responsibility for, say, food handling, having bits and pieces in that, chicken soup, you know, or buy fish fillet.
[SPEAKER_01]: You may have a fish bone in your fish fillet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, to compare, when you buy a game that is rated M, you should expect that there's going to be mature themes in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You may see some boobies.
[SPEAKER_01]: You may hear the F word.
[SPEAKER_01]: Regardless, you have been warned.
[SPEAKER_01]: By that little N being on the bottom of the game, you have been warned.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I do think that Rockstar was lax.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, and even so, I can't really fault this either.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, removing the code, bracketing it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's done all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aren't we feeling a little blue in the face here?
[SPEAKER_01]: I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, honestly, there is and is not fault in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Technically, they did remove access to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just happened to be somebody out there who's curious enough to find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no easy answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we welcome your feedback, as always, to go at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm tired of talking about this subject.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, then let's get to a new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about, ooh, Digital Life happened this weekend, which was that big expo in New York, which I really wanted to go to, but I couldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I heard it was very crowded.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had some folks call in on our live show Sunday nights that were at Digital Life, saying that just crowded amongst crowded, just really, really crowded stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: A few folks got to check out some new games, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing that did happen was that the Xbox Live Arcade lineup was announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Loki, I know you talked about this a little bit last week because you had some photos of some of the games in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they did kind of officially say what's going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I think is interesting, a whole lot of PopCap games showing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Astro Pop, Bejeweled 2, Zuma going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other games in there as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gauntlet, Joust.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then of course the Marble Blaster talking about Robotron and Smash TV which is kind of interesting to me that they would put these in the arcade when you can just buy the Midway Arcade Treasures Collection which would be a much better deal I think for some of those games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember, don't shoot the food.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not the complete list but those are the only games that sound very familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out if you're curious on your Xbox 360 when you get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also on the Xbox 360...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing this in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be doing a beta test of Final Fantasy XI on the brand new Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: The console launches in Japan on December 10th, and if you purchase the limited edition Xbox 360 package, you're going to get a free Final Fantasy XI beta test disc while supplies last.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you have a story about the 360 as well and some kind of bad news about the dev kits.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: We did cover about the theft of the 360 dev kit
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so, but if we didn't, I'm sure people read about it or heard about it on another cast or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, some dev kits were stolen.
[SPEAKER_01]: At any rate, a Dutch newspaper reported that Microsoft is preparing a $100 million lawsuit against those responsible for the theft.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they're wanting to protect the security so that you can't hack the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which you know is a big problem with the Xbox here is that they pretty much broke it right away.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we started having a meme on the Xbox and extra huge hard drives.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, why are you laughing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm laughing because the way they set up the whole hard drive situation anyways is just asking to be hacked.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also an interesting statement on here, though, from the hacking group who's, I guess, responsible.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's from, I hope I'm saying this wrong, it's smartxx.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: You hope you're saying that wrong?
[SPEAKER_06]: He said, I hope I'm saying that wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, I hope I'm not saying that wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: I threw a ferret at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: but they're saying the website the pictures of the stolen dev kits emerged claiming Microsoft was actually complicit in the group's acquisition of the kits they went on to say I'm going to just quote this here according to the poster people within Microsoft unaware of the operation went on to inform the police that they should investigate SmartXX leading to the current situation and that Microsoft was going to deny it as usual
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought that was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of people getting busted...
[SPEAKER_06]: A Game Pirate in Richmond, Texas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we should say in a legend.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I guess not a legend anymore because this guy was sentenced to three years and ten months in a federal prison and a fine of $1.15 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Dashiel Ponce de Leon receiving this sentence there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That $1.15 million representing the retail value of all the software this guy sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, this guy wasn't doing the thing on BitTorrent or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy was actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: Downloading stuff online then reselling it through the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the worst kind of piracy right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the kind that a lot of people say even they want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: That hurts the pockets of the developers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just downloading off BitTorrent doesn't?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, stop making crappy games.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's one person as opposed to one person multiplying the efforts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I buy games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at my collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have tons of games that I pay money for.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think that anyone who lives in my house cannot say that I don't buy a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't want to buy an import system, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I am so sick of this loser.
[SPEAKER_05]: He needs to team up with that guy from the 700 Club.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, this is the guy who was saying, video games are evil.
[SPEAKER_01]: And people refute him with backing up everything with solid evidence, and then he goes, well, you're just a pissant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I thought this was interesting, is that earlier this week you might have heard the National Institute on Media and the Family, NIMF,
[SPEAKER_06]: The President David Walsh kind of wrote a letter that kind of distanced himself from Jack Thompson and said, I really wish you'd stop using our name in your arguments and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: A quote from the letter here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your commentary has included extreme hyperbole and your... Hyperbole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hyperbole.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was correcting myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: And your tactics have included personally attacking individuals for whom I have a great deal of respect.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dr. Thompson fought back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doctor?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he, is he a doctor?
[SPEAKER_06]: He's a doctor of... No, he's not a doctor.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's a doctor of things he can't say on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of fused two words together there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, no, what he did there is that he actually kind of denied, saying, the fact is, I have never suggested that Dr. Walsh approves of what I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have countless times told people that I believe he is an expert around the dangers of video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: The mistake I made, apparently, naively, is thinking that a person of his expertise would use it actually to help some bereaved families rather than choose to protect his relationship with portions of the video game industry and its reckless retail network.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then he goes on to say, I'm a Christian and I think Dr. Walsh is as well and there's a passage in the New Testament.
[SPEAKER_06]: What does that have to do with anything?
[SPEAKER_01]: Thou shall not play violent video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really wondering why people keep bringing up Christianity as an illustration of morality.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a whole other topic for a whole other cast.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to go into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just I find it highly hilarious how he's defending himself saying, oh, but I'm a Christian.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yet he's going around saying,
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically slandering innocent people.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, like I said before, when people are presenting him with evidence that proves him wrong, he's going back and calling them names.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't want to get into religious debate, but from what I understand about Christianity, there's only one judge.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, he's going to have to answer to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's only one judge.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not Wapner.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Judge Wapner, guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, he's doing the pet court or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Jack Thompson compared this guy to Hitler.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's one of the people that this group associates with.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things I was going to mention is remember last week we were talking about how he was proposing that game companies create his game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: So then Penny Arcade, of course, said he would pay $10,000 if his game was created.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're like, well, that's kind of weak because we donated half a million dollars for this charity.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what did he do?
[SPEAKER_05]: He found their phone number and their signature that was in their email and yelled at them, literally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Called them up and yelled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yelled.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty lame.
[SPEAKER_01]: This guy is obviously mentally unstable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, obviously, this guy is becoming kind of like the laughingstock of the video game community, so now you're seeing him in all sorts of mods, and what did you find?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's the Jack Thompson murder simulator called Defamation of Character.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's basically a mod for Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, and you can find this at hellfish...
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a guy you compared to Hitler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and basically they kind of go through what you can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is Jack Thompson, who also is his alter ego, Bandman, who they actually have dressed up in some weird box and just some funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways, you go through a bunch of different missions, including murdering, I believe it was two live crew.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they're going to like that very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're murdering two left crew who they have a picture on the website hanging, looks like upside down, dead from his ceiling.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was actually also the one responsible for the whole cop killer thing with Ice-T.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of you guys have a lot of free time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of you gamers have a lot of free time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I thought here's what was funny, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the special abilities he had, he can do, of course, bullet time like every other game.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has legal immunity, basically when the police are coming or whatever, you can instantly get them to go away.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has the Holy Escort, which is this Harrier jet that makes him invincible or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Press Relations, which you can basically just pull a publicity stunt and get everyone to forget about stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beautiful, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I need some real morality here on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need some real morality.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I turned to DarkSakura to bring that morality to this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she provides that for us every week with her weekly advice column.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, there is more to life than just gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you played video games all day long, you would have no time to watch the people's court.
[SPEAKER_06]: You wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Judge Wapner was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even that new lady that's on it is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just don't watch TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so DarkSakura, what are you going to be telling the kids about tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Today's bit of advice is excuses you can make for falling asleep at your desk at work and then how to fake being asleep at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to know this.
[SPEAKER_01]: To be asleep at your desk, first of all, blame work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say, I'm so exhausted I was here until midnight last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do not attempt this if your boss works late and you do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I had a fellow co-worker actually say that to me the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if that was something they were doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number two, blame medication.
[SPEAKER_01]: Claim that your new allergy medicine has been making you drowsy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say, those antihistamines just knock me out.
[SPEAKER_01]: It usually works for me because I take Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number three, blame lunch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say, wow, I guess I should not have eaten that turkey sandwich.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tryptophan always makes me sleepy, which is true.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is a sedative.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be aware when taking a nap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Always rest your elbow on your desk and keep your arm perpendicular to the desktop.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your forehead should rest on your four fingers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your thumb, spread apart from the fingers, should support your jaw.
[SPEAKER_01]: This position will keep your head up and aimed at your desk.
[SPEAKER_01]: Face in a direction so that it is not immediately visible to someone approaching your desk that your eyes are closed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep an important group of documents in your perceived line of sight so as to appear to be reading intently.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, this also worked in high school.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final piece of advice, do not stay up all night playing Final Fantasy XI, you freaking addicts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or World of Warcraft, or Ragnarok, or whatever the kids are playing these days.
[SPEAKER_01]: I never let that get in the way of my sleep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except when I was unemployed and had no excuse to go to bed.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got some music game news for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, Orange Lounge, we were all about the music games when we started.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still are to some extent, but we talk about other video games too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this is some big music game news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that brand new game coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those of you guys that were wishing and hoping that they would make, like, Amplitude or Frequency, like a new one, from what I understand, they kind of have.
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of did make a new one, except it just involves a guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's called Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Red Octane's the company that's putting this out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Red Octane, of course, famous for making a lot of
[SPEAKER_06]: Music Game Peripherals, and Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Harmonix being the folks that did bring us Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix developed the game, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: And made Karaoke Revolution as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix just wrapped up work on Guitar Hero, and Red Octane is going to put it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's scheduled to be out November 8th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of licensed songs in this game, including More Than a Feelin' by Boston, ZZ Top, Sharp Dressed Man, and Franz Ferdinand's Take Me Out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now,
[SPEAKER_06]: I had other commitments.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, back away from my nerddom.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has an excellent song list.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played I Wanna Be Sedated, and then I played More Than a Feelin', which I love Boston, and I love the Ramones.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also Stevie Ray Vaughan in it, Franz Ferdinand, Megadeth.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not the actual bands, but the folks that they had playing the music was just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Smoke on the Water
[SPEAKER_05]: and Iron Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want to say take me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really fun game to get into since I'm a big fan of Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is definitely a step in the right direction because I like how they have the extra buttons on there so it is a little bit more difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for those people that did actually master Guitar Freaks, this is a whole new challenge for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm just... I didn't get to play it, unfortunately, but I'm just excited that we're getting, like, Amplitude, but, like, different with a new peripheral.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just... because I love Frequency.
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of excited.
[SPEAKER_01]: Being that I heavily imported all the Guitar Freaks games that I could get my hands on except for the FNs, there's no comparison.
[SPEAKER_01]: This game, Guitar Hero, really blows it out of the water.
[SPEAKER_01]: The music quality, being that you're going from basically MIDI to real, you know, instruments...
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Freaks has also just kind of gotten stale over like 13 mixes or something like that, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like Simon.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like playing Simon.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, press the button in the right order.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this, because you've got the five keys and on top of that, the way that you move your hand, they're calling them fret buttons, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got a whammy bar on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jeez, how much cooler can you get?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I know I'm gushing about it, but I've got my game on reserve already.
[SPEAKER_01]: The controller itself is...
[SPEAKER_01]: Suitably more substantial than the Guitar Freaks controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're the horns.
[SPEAKER_06]: 24 Hour Fitness is going to put DDR machines in their kids club portions of the gyms.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they have kids club at all, the gyms, but the ones that do, some of them are going to have DDR machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: So an interesting fusion there between Dance Dance Revolution and a legitimate gymnasium.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that it's a fascinating marketing tool, and it's sort of one that we've seen it coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: With all the schools that are putting DDR machines in their fitness programs...
[SPEAKER_01]: It was inevitable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Konami was also working on DDR Studio, I think it was, where it was going to be like an eight-person DDR thing, and it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was meant for gyms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although we didn't really see if this ever got actually implemented, it's interesting to see this partnership take place.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still think Pada Pada would have been a better choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but that, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get your upper body moving, but then you'd have to listen to the music.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's nothing wrong with the Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: I watch Initial D.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhythm Gymnastics, the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rhythm Masters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you guys have some news on Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to hear this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what did you have on Dead or Alive 4?
[SPEAKER_01]: DOA 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, their lobby system has been revealed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Famitsu was talking about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The description that I have seen is that it is wacky.
[SPEAKER_01]: The lobby features 10 various areas.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's like a Halloween theme, a swamp room that you swim through.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which, you know, honestly, it totally just fits, you know, what I would have expected.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if they gave us a volleyball, they'd have to do something goofy.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also have various avatars.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe that there is around 30.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also can have, like, a ninja, ghost, cat, penguin.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get a penguin, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And each lobby can hold a maximum of 20 people, and you can chat with people and watch fights that are taking place on a widescreen display.
[SPEAKER_01]: No screenshots yet, but of course there's shots of the game out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was in the recent issue of Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before I get to Loki's side, I just want to say something real quick about Famitsu Magazine, because it kind of relates to Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually just did a study on how the Japanese are kind of looking at the next generation of systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: 24% say that they do want to get an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: 40% are still undecided.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 3, way ahead still.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's just interesting because the Xbox is making a little bit of progress, because the Xbox One, or whatever you want to call it, the regular Xbox, kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: D.O.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: Female character, I believe from Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it, I mean, to be honest, looks exactly like Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks exactly like Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you get to play this game with this character.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that possibly some alternate costumes that might reveal more of her, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are forgetting what DOA is all about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course they put in a female Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm a betting man, I'm going to say the code is probably Justin Bailey.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I don't think that was it Tecmo had anything to do with Metroid?
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, moving on, I got a quick news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: It relates to Final Fantasy Advent Children.
[SPEAKER_06]: 700,000 copies sold since September 14th when it came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And 7 million copies pirated on BitTorrent in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And don't forget, there's a big pre-order push for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then today on the Advent Children Release date, you know, it's basically now the end of January.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think January 29th is what I heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my, again?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: End of January.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they foolish?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this thing's all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless they're going back to add extra content to make us want to get the DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they're going to be pushing, I'm hoping that it's going to be a theater release.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're actually, I have heard from other, though I cannot say who, reputable sources that are saying that it's going to be a limited theater run.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that would be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe IMAX?
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember mentioning that a while back that I had heard that IMAX was what they were gunning for.
[SPEAKER_01]: That might just be a fanboy's wet dream.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's my wet dream.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, thanks for sharing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on, DarkSakura, you have some news about what's going on in the UK in release dates.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have our release dates.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is going to be, all of these games are to be released on the 21st.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Buzz the Music Quiz on PS2, Cold War for PC and Xbox, Crash Tag Team Racing, Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tenkaichi,
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I know how to pronounce Japanese.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dual Master, Shadow of the Code, Fear, which I know a lot of people are looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fable, The Lost Chapters, Genji, which is already out over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: L.A.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rush for PS2, Xbox, Marvel Nemesis, Rise of the Imperfects, Namco Museum, Battle Collection, Pokemon Emerald, Rengoku, UFO, Aftershock, WRC Rally Edition, and X3 Reunion.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another couple of notables.
[SPEAKER_01]: The 28th, we have Dancing Stage Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Makai Kingdom, Chronicles of the Sacred Tome for PS2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pack and roll on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mentioned Fable in there, or Fable Lost Chapters, which is out here already.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I just have one quick minor bitch about Fable.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't work with my TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like garbage on my TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like my HD wigs out on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like there's something weird about the mode it uses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope the 360 doesn't do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's the only game that I have problems with out of my collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have quite a few games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get the Lost Chapters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want the Lost Chapters.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to play the one I bought.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you want the Lost Chapters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: See something also November, just that might be a little fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: SingStar 80s for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: SingStar.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Donkey Kong Country 3 for the GBA.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like... Cool, it's Donkey Kong Country.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also had something about Alien Hamed, which was a game that's out here, but... They are releasing downloadable level packs for owners of Alien Hamed for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the level packs are saying there's the chicken pack and the Ultra Hyper Load, both containing 25 levels.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so far, it sounds like there are going to be free downloads.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I said Ultra Hyper Load, I was just picturing a long-ass loading screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alien Hamednid, or whatever it's called, not a game that I was very interested in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watched Loki play it for a length of time, and I thought, how boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love the comments on here, just a quote from Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mothers, buying your kids 2D shooters will make them better geeks in years to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have some news regarding Castlevania, because I've been playing, of course, the DS one a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there are brand new Castlevania games coming out for the Xbox and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Curse of Darkness is the game coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should be very cool there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's set three years after Castlevania III, Dracula's Curse, and Curse of Darkness follows, I guess, a new character, Hector, a former minion of Dracula.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: November 1st is the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just around the corner.
$49.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: M for Mature, because you know it's got lots of blood and the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should be a good game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope it's a little better than Lament of Innocence.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that Lament of Innocence was bad, but it wasn't Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm more looking forward to Matrix The Path of Neo coming out that same week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did just find something very interesting that I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: A Bone game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You remember Bone?
[SPEAKER_01]: The comic?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just glanced over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Telltale Games Apparently they're releasing a Bone game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I will try to go into more of this next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just saw this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I mean, for anyone who's fans of the series, it actually looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found the link on the front page of Eurogamer this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I would suggest everyone check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you'll get some emails on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of emails, togo at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: We get emails and we like to read some of them on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have time to read all of them, but we do read them all.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we love you guys for writing us and letting us know you care.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we want to respond to some on-air right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, DarkSakura, what is in the old Orange Launch Radio mailbag?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the one about comparing just how bad the video game law is.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was actually sent to us by Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our friend Rob with two Bs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, he's king of our forums lately, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's a nice guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: A great addition to our forums, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, we have one from...
[SPEAKER_01]: Paul in Belfast, Northern Ireland.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really glad to hear we've got listeners so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: International.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love hearing from the international folks.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has a question for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will just read this.
[SPEAKER_01]: My question is, have you ever given it some thought of doing a video of your podcast for us to download on PSP like they do with Dignation?
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be totally cool, just a thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the problem with Videocast, is that it's more money to get a video set up and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a matter, the execution is, how in the hell are we going to do something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, when you're talking about Dig and stuff like that, I mean, that's backed by people who have been in the television industry already, so they kind of have, you know, their ties on how to do it, do that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't really have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got a little crappy 15-year-old recorder, but I don't know what kind of a TV show we could do with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plus, it's a lot, lot more time because I have worked in television in college and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a lot more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Preparing stuff for the Internet is not fun either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm willing to do it, but again, it's just a matter of the fact that we have a budget of $0 and no place to shoot it.
[SPEAKER_01]: that once I get my camcorder, I think that it might eventually be feasible to do a special.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's in the back of our minds.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that place we were at, that warehouse we were at the other night, I thought would be a fabulous place to do an Orange Lounge type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I told you about that already.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something that's constantly been sitting in the back of my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someday, someday, especially with this new iTunes 6.0 and the way that they're really pushing video now with the new video iPods.
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course we like PSPs as well and we've been trying to support that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a natural evolution of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see it happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just not going to happen cheaply.
[SPEAKER_01]: That means I have to go buy a veil.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other mails?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, one last one tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of our listeners, Joseph, wrote in.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's one of the ones who wrote.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, he won.
[SPEAKER_06]: The rare CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, those prizes are on their way.
[SPEAKER_01]: He would like for us to plug that they're having their Poly Bimani Games Day at Cal Poly in San Luis Obispo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope I pronounced that right because I'm not from here.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's at the Chumash Auditorium inside the University Union at Cal Poly State.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've asked us to go, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you're going to be busy with the Podcast Awards that weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually am going to be at the Podcast Awards on the 11th and staying in San Diego to go buy wine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I might be putting in an appearance.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to check my calendar, see if I can do it feasibly, but I would like to do it, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get back to these folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still seeing, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's a little harder to get to do the PR things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee, I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not coming by myself, though, so I'm bringing a random... I might have to bring Extifer from Orange Lounge Radio's live show.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take the Digicam with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I go, I definitely will.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get in touch with this guy on email.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah, I'm already going to the podcast awards, or I would be more than thrilled to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also would like to go to the podcast awards, but I can't, but that's a very bitter subject, so we won't go there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, real life sucks sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have some more fun, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: You remember our friend Steven Spielberg?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't we have lunch with him last week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I told him to kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want more money for the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I ran into, well, not ran into him, but I was eating dinner at Skywalker Ranch.
[SPEAKER_01]: George Lucas walked past us, and I almost flipped.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tell that Lucas story every chance you get.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, he's a meatless flicking distance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, tell us about Spielberg.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, just a little quickie.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has basically signed a deal with Electronic Arts to publish three original game properties.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will they be overrated like his movies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Likely, but only time will tell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it wouldn't be an original property.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's going to be original.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Indiana Jones.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want War of the Worlds.
[SPEAKER_01]: He has been quoted as saying the new technology represents the future of cinema, and in the future you will physically be inside the experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Inside the experience.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another thing they were asking how it's going to work, he said, I invented it, but because the patent is pending, I can't discuss it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully being inside the experience includes Pam Landerson.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get to a story that Loki's got about PSP on the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something that you've been following for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, everybody wants the PSP to be on the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's only, you've got the UMD movies, which are selling like crazy, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first thing, of course, they have the PSP2 TV, which is actually kind of a,
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that working.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it doesn't require modification, and I think that's kind of the selling point of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You also had a story about a mod for the Nintendo, with the GBA Micro being so popular right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, the guy behind all those portable systems, like the portable Atari, Ben Heck, he actually created a brand new NES Micro, as he calls it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got screenshots on his site here on BenHeck.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: The NES Micro is like...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, they're saying that other than the game stores currently in existence, the GameStop ones, they're not going to have that big of a presence.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not going to really shift things.
[SPEAKER_01]: And from what I've heard, a lot of the EBs are still going to stay and keep operating under the EB name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that explains what's going to happen when you have a mall and you have EB, which is right up... We have here in Sacramento, we have a mall...
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a mall where there's a GameStop and then right around the corner there's an EB next to the Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think either of those stores are going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: People probably wondered, with a merger, is EB going to be GameStop and you just have two GameStops in the mall?
[SPEAKER_06]: Which would be a little crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe it's still operating under... From what I understood, they were supposed to dissolve the EB name.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, the EB stores are still there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I don't know how they're going to manage that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's say I have GameStop A and GameStop B. GameStop A and GameStop B. And for the record.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be like Express Men and Express Women.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could have GameStop Nintendo and GameStop Xbox and GameStop Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do need to correct myself, though, as far as Barnes & Noble's involvement in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: GameStop is now a fully functioning business.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're still associated with Barnes & Noble, but they are their own business.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: No longer a fully owned subsidy, I should say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got one last story for you guys, and then we'll let Loki finish this out tonight, because I think his thing's a little bit cooler.
[SPEAKER_06]: My last thing is Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe I saved this for last.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is big news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul Calibur 3, though, for me, it feels like it's been flying under the radar a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's just because I'm not following the same news I used to, but I remember Soul Calibur 2 was like this huge freaking deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul Calibur 3, certainly if you're a fighting game fan, is still a huge deal, but this one's kind of been seeming to fly under the radar for me, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still going to look like a cool game nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's because, A, it doesn't have Link in it, and B... Link was cool!
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, but he wasn't the whole game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the arcade version of Soul Calibur II was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ivy is the whole game, really, is what it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Xbox version of Soul Calibur II was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, Soul Calibur III is for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out October 25th, which I was kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, whoa, that was quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also rated T14, $49.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, the big thing about this is that you're going to be able to do, you know, some...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: via Flash on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the old-ass Prince of Persia.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not talking the Sands of Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you mean by the Prince of Persia that was on the NES, the Commodore 64, the Apple, the Game Boy?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on every system ever at that time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can find us at www.gamespot.com slash promo slash princeofpersia dash game slash flash
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Slash partridge in a pear tree dot org.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Check that out, you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dot EU.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple really quick things.
[SPEAKER_05]: PSP firmware 2.5 came out that allows the movies on the go type thing where you can stream over the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad that the peripheral that you need to use that is $350.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sucks for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to play more games this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSX on tour looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is World of Warcraft, setting things on fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Full report next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one more thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: More fun stuff coming to the PSP site.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had your last thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, check out the PSP site, olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: We haven't plugged that yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: We have barely heard from somebody this entire show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, our little pet ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are those things called?
[SPEAKER_06]: Scoozies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Scoozies.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's our mascot, the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: You see him in the little album art for our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You see him, like really, really tiny.
[SPEAKER_01]: The ferret.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have just been sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now I've been reunited with my ferret friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for downloading us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check us out next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back, as always.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have we ever missed a week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want a vacation.
[SPEAKER_06]: When do I get a vacation?
[SPEAKER_01]: You missed one show.
[SPEAKER_06]: One show.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you guys next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next update.