[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of October 3rd, 2005.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody, once again...
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your home for all that news that gamers really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks so much for subscribing to us.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really do appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are an independent production.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's just three buddies here doing a show out of a spare bedroom in one of our apartments, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we appreciate you guys supporting just, you know, the independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do this because we love video games, and we never shut up about them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that right, Dark Sakura, one of my lovely co-hosts over there?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't shut up about anything ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Video games is one of them though, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'd have to say video games are probably up at the top of the list.
[SPEAKER_00]: That and Serenity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki's here as well, the Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he never shuts up about video games either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and in fact, even the people I work with who we sell video games and they still don't like listening to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you love bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have my I Love Bacon shirt on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, that's something.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did go into Bark mode about three times this week, though, with other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Were you able to get any cool unlocks that way?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, my friend has an extra fireman's hat and is going to lend it to me, because if you ever have the fireman's hat in your inventory at any time, you will automatically have the Dalmatian, even if you give the hat away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm going to get a Dalmatian next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been that into Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of my interest in fading.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did your puppies run away?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not yet, but they all have fleas.
[SPEAKER_03]: because I haven't been bathing them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what's your game of the week been like?
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried Lost in Blue a bit for the DS, and that was kind of fun, and then had to play the stupid dogs because otherwise they'll run away.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm actually taking two of my copies back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want them.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's not that interesting, and after...
[SPEAKER_03]: You did kind of make a mistake by buying all three versions, not realizing that all 18... I didn't realize it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You need to bring your other versions so that I can get your dogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have to do that before I return them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so other than that, I've been playing DDR Extreme 2, and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good dance game, except my dance pads don't work it right now, so I have to play it on the controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, when I was staring at my copy of Graffiti Kingdom this week,
[SPEAKER_02]: If it makes you feel any better my copy of We Love Katamari is still unwrapped
[SPEAKER_03]: But you did finally get it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I got it the night after the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not such a touchy subject for you anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, not as touchy.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a very wrapped subject.
[SPEAKER_00]: I keep it under wraps.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_03]: I did it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, things that I have been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually checked out Pack and Roll for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of those, like, kind of quickie games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it's a game that I don't think I could really see myself, like, oh, I'm going to sit down for three hours and just have a marathon Pack and Roll session.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of one of those things where, like, yeah, I could, like, fire this up, play a level while I'm waiting for something else, then just save it and do it again later.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of a nice, like, simple, relaxing action game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I spent at least 30 minutes on it at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I didn't find it to be quite so addicting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a really cool concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it kind of whores the stylus features of the DS out, but, you know, it's in a good way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess that's what the stylus is for.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the idea that you kind of use Pac-Man as like a trackball, although part of me kind of wonders what that game would be like if you actually had a trackball.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game would surprisingly be a hell of a lot like Crystal Castles, that old, old Atari game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It made me think of Marvel Madness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marble Madness kind of, I thought, because with the dots and everything, it really reminded me of Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_03]: But instead you were using the stylus to kind of draw your kind of roll with the pen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you do like all these different moves.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still kind of only like a borderline recommendation for me, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think if you're a fan of this type of genre, I think you'll get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's also a type of thing that I couldn't see myself playing it for a heck of a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't see myself playing this game until I beat it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'd kind of get sick of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the graphics weren't...
[SPEAKER_03]: The graphics, it looked like a PlayStation game on my DS, which I guess is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I really like the graphical style of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't care for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Pac-Man looked really cute in the little bottom window where he's the controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better than Pac-Pix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pac-Pix sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got rid of that game quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I got this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was just like, eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_03]: so borderline recommendation for pack and roll for me the other game I didn't play this enough I'm not going to make a final judgment on this game I did play a little bit of Lost in Blue it seemed a little I don't know if it's just not my type of game if I'm just not into those point and click games although I don't know for some reason I was like thinking like King's Quest but with the little added like you can actually use the stylus to dig in the sand and kind of explore seemed a little gimmicky to me but I don't
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I played enough of the game to really get a feel for this yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to give the game another shot, so I'm not going to make a final judgment on it yet, but I did check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I'm going to like this one, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just doesn't seem like my kind of game, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it for the first day that you're on the island, and it's like you have to do things really...
[SPEAKER_02]: in order, otherwise your only player is going to die, because you start off with very little life.
[SPEAKER_03]: It seemed like it would be really easy to lose in the beginning, a little frustrating, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to wait and play them a little more.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty frustrating.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hear trying to hunt the animals and stuff later on is even more frustrating.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games are very frustrating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and the text boxes were horrible, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You only see one line of text at a time, and you have to wait, even though I put my display speed on fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like that method of showing text.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if I'm going to like this one, guys, but I'm not making a final judgment yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: There might be something that happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of games I first play and I don't like them, and then I warm up to them later.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of games coming out next month I want for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to check out Trauma Center as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's something I'm waiting on for the GBA.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: A whole lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gunstar Superheroes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game looks like it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: One other game I checked out this week was Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, Orange Launch Radio was started on the music video games and kind of grew beyond that, but I still have a place in my heart for the music video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2, if you are a fan of the dancing games in any capacity, you must, I highly recommend Dance Dance Revolution Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I talked about this a lot more on Sunday night's live three-hour show, but I think it really kind of transitioned...
[SPEAKER_03]: Beatmania 2DX's Drill Mode
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're more of a casual fan or if you're curious about DDR, I would recommend you start on Max 2, which was from two years ago, but it had a very solid song list, and I think it was a lot more accessible for people who hadn't really played DDR before.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's just my recommendation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, graphics in the game are great.
[SPEAKER_03]: They gave every song a unique music video this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: The sound, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kick-butt song list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Couple of licenses I didn't like, but that's bound to happen when you have such a diverse song list.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the gameplay, it's DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Highly recommend if you're a fan of music games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of borderline if you're not so much, if you just are interested in dance games and want to get into the series.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to disagree with most of the music selection though because I wasn't too impressed.
[SPEAKER_03]: With what you heard?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was a bunch of repetitive, same old trance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think when you see what they picked from the old games to put next to it, though, I think it makes it a lot more solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: They really took a lot of the things the fans have been asking for for years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sakura, Daikinkai, Cartoon Heroes, Sync, it's all in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of nice that Konami really listened to their DDR fans on this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually did have something that I had forgotten to mention earlier.
[SPEAKER_00]: Back to the Gunstar Heroes release, there's actually going to be a Sega Ages treasure chest.
[SPEAKER_00]: I found this on Treasure's homepage.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's featuring Gunstar Heroes Dynamite Headdy Alien Soldier.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, in the Sega Ages 2500 collection, it'll be sold for 2,500 yen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hope that comes out here.
[SPEAKER_00]: and also Treasure is doing the Bleach game.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that's off of the anime.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's Treasure, it's gotta be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I actually liked the Sega collection they put out.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people really panned it and said it was awful, and I guess that's probably because of the Golden Axe remake, but I thought it was a good deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was better than that Namco collection that just came out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I thought the Sega one was way better, but... I didn't buy it because we've already, so far, have some of the Sega Ages games we went to since we imported them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have any of you guys picked up the Midway Arcade Treasures 3 yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm definitely interested because it has... I didn't even realize this game was in it, but it has Iron Man's off-road in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was, like, my favorite racing game, which is kind of not even really, like, it's borderline racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've heard good things about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll tell you what broke my heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our landlord, who's actually good friends of ours, cleaned out some stuff out of their attic in the garage and brought down an Atari 2600 wood grain that had cobwebs all over it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It made my heart break to have a box full of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, no!
[SPEAKER_00]: Except it was like that slow motion, no!
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki got me thinking about racing games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you hear about What's Coming to America?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Kart GP 64DD Collection
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: and the first thing is we're going to give away a copy of the DDR Extreme 2 V-Rare as well as a copy of the Max 2 V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: We gave one away on the live show last week and we told you guys on the podcast you had a chance to enter this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Many of you did, so DarkSakura, pull a number out of the hat and let's see who's going to win the copy of the V-Rares.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember guys, these aren't...
[SPEAKER_03]: Games, they're the VRares, the soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some folks in their email subject said, I want to win the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, guys, it's just the soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have that big a budget yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, who are we giving it to?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the number?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 28.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 15.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will be number 30.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is 28 right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our winner is Joseph E. Joseph E is the winner of the other soundtracks we're going to give away there.
[SPEAKER_03]: his email address says red star in it so I'm guessing that's his handle there so congratulations to you you've won the other soundtracks good job
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, what we're going to give away, we're going to give away... Now, this is a game that we're giving away.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're giving away a copy of In the Groove, and this is another dance game that's out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a lot of dance games to give away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we going to give away some non-dance games in the coming weeks, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, we love dance games, but we've got to give away some other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, this is a copy of In the Groove that has been autographed, quote-unquote, by all the hosts here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what you had to do was write a haiku about In the Groove, and it had to be five syllables, seven syllables...
[SPEAKER_03]: 3 syllables, not 575, because that's a horrible inside joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki is going to sweeten the deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're throwing in something else, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm throwing in a t-shirt that says, In the Courtroom, but it's in the style of the logo for In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, they got sued by Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to throw in something that says, In the Courtroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we're also going to give away to all of our winners, not just the folks who won the In the Groove,
[SPEAKER_03]: we have some Silent Hill 3 stickers that were given to us by somebody at Konami so we're going to give
[SPEAKER_03]: SILENT HILL 3
[SPEAKER_03]: Minds, Mods, and much more.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the Groove will help you score, just not dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's our runner-up.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually had a rhyme in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's our runner-up, AsianBuddyPaul.
[SPEAKER_03]: AsianBuddyPaul is our runner-up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: And here is our winner.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want a haiku?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe about In the Groove?
[SPEAKER_03]: They got sued.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Justin M is our winner of the In the Groove contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did get lots of good ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys crack us up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So good job.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to do more creativity competitions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Xbox Chief Officer, Robbie Bach
[SPEAKER_03]: Expects half of all Xbox 360 owners to be on Xbox Live In the article it goes on to say that only about 10% of current Xbox users Which would be about 2 million people Use the current version of Xbox Live But because they're going to have this free silver version of Xbox Live That's going to be on the 360 The chief officer there believes that 50%
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Because what, Silver, we did this a few weeks back.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were talking about the differences between Silver and Gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Silver just basically got you on there and you could communicate with people, but you couldn't really play them, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to go to Gold for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if they end up saying that 70% of the people are on Xbox Live, well, does that mean 70% of the people are playing games on there?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how much weight this story holds.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just huge numbers, that's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was kind of surprised this story got as much attention as it did because I'm like, so if it's free, yeah, people are going to use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that wins the award of the evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, you actually had a story about the Xbox 360's launch as well, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I got an email from one of our listeners, one of our regular writers as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, right on.
[SPEAKER_00]: From Rob with two B's.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just going to go ahead and read this email real quick just because I think it's very well written and brings up a good point.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been hitting the internet gaming news about Microsoft rejecting the Blu-ray DVD format.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not really interested in the reasons, but rather why it's an issue at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: So maybe the crew can help me with that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually thought it would be a good thing to bring up for discussion.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unless you have three hours of video, why would one DVD be insufficient for a game?
[SPEAKER_00]: The reason I ask myself this is, how can there be so much code and support files to engulf an entire DVD?
[SPEAKER_00]: The compiled code itself should be a fraction of the entire content, but I've noticed that games of practically the same complexity as Tetris are three megabytes and higher.
[SPEAKER_00]: This can only mean developer kits, uncompressed files, and non-optimized code.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: All of that accepted, it still has to be unnecessarily large support files that really push them over the edge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Overly large and or detailed bitmaps compressed along with the code instead of as bitmaps.
[SPEAKER_00]: The same with video and sound.
[SPEAKER_00]: It may not use more of the file-specific compression algorithms.
[SPEAKER_00]: It brings me to the conclusion that if the file fills more than a DVD, you may want to reconsider your content.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make sure that you're not adding fluff to distract the player from the core game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is absolutely
[SPEAKER_00]: from the core game is absolutely piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Almost every movie license game fits this description.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, my initial thought as to why you would need so much space, though, is that isn't the Xbox 3, if I'm not mistaken, isn't Microsoft forcing all the Xbox 360 games to be high-def compatible?
[SPEAKER_00]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo, are you listening?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that would take up more space by default, I would think.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think it would take up a full DVD.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I think it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is, when you're pushing these higher-res games, you're going to have higher-res textures.
[SPEAKER_02]: More of them, if you've seen Project Gotham Racing, the whole buildings are textured.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, it takes up more space.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not coding that's going to take up space at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coding is tiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically all these textures and audio and stuff that you've got.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know how many channels of audio you've got on the 360 and stuff, 5.1 and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the difference between why a DVD video file is 4GB
[SPEAKER_02]: and a DivX file is only 600 megs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, in quality, you're going to see a big difference there, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Blu-ray, well, the only reason they're not going Blu-ray is because Sony's the one that's making Blu-ray, so, duh, they're not going to support their competitor.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree, though, with what's being said about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really comes down to the quality of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's going to be those crap games that don't make good use of the space, but I really think there will be games out there that are just going to have some stunning...
[SPEAKER_03]: Cutscenes and things that could take up feasibly more room than a normal DVD could handle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if there'll be any launch titles, but I think down the line, if there's that room for expansion, naturally the games have to grow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: They will have to use the hard drive, but as we know, developers can't assume the hard drive will always be there for the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: So his question is, do you see this as a growing trend where we're going to see more eye candy and less gameplay?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think unfortunately that's kind of... It's happening already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's been a trend that's been happening already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's games... But you know, sometimes there's games out there that have a lot of good eye candy, but they have good gameplay too, like Xenosaga comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, God, that game was like half just sit and watch the cutscenes, but it was still a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think, you know, and I think the other person who emailed, was that Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think what he said there about the movie franchise games are some of the biggest culprits of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not always, but usually the biggest culprits of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he made an excellent point with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, yeah, those games have always been about the eye candy a lot of times and making you remember the movie and things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's kind of a trend that's going on already.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it'll just continue to go.
[SPEAKER_00]: I honestly think that that was the big thing that spawned the whole PlayStation is better than Saturn bullshit of a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: The thing is, though, is that most of the people that were saying that never imported a single Saturn game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And were not 2D gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this goes all the way back to Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember those games that would whore Mode 7?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was really nothing else to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just, oh, look at the pretty Mode 7.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then again, the Super Nintendo, they were one of the first systems to do polygons.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although actually there was a system out before that that did it, but not in America.
[SPEAKER_00]: The PC Engine Duo had a game called Sapphire that was one of their arcade card games.
[SPEAKER_00]: That system was so intelligent to have those upgradable cards to support the different games.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I've played this game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's got really pretty graphics in it for its time.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in-game polygons.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there were some great Mode 7 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pilotwings I loved and some of the other older ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: We had Star Fox.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, even effects in...
[SPEAKER_03]: and, um, like Dracula X. But see, you had the Star Fox game, but then there was some buggy racing game or something that was stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Step Race FX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Step Race FX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was, I didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um, but, uh, the, uh, some of the other, F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: F-Zero was mid-seven.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to move on, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to email us, send us an email at togo at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get to some more emails a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you had a story about, now, the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was some type of teaser site going on, and the countdown finished this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: OriginXbox360.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have been great if you live in the UK, because guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a UK launch site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically, you can enter to win a trip to the launch party that's in, I guess, Vegas, if I remember correctly, or New York, in the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you have to be in the UK in order to enter this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the website was teasing it with some cut-out pictures of rabbits and this giant tree that was growing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And at the very end, you have these rabbits, and the whole thing reminds me of Monty Python, the way it's done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, the rabbits, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them eats the fruit that makes them hallucinate, and then you go to the maiden site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a complete letdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were thinking it was going to be something cool, but unless you were in the UK, it was not.
[SPEAKER_00]: But we do have listeners in the UK, so hey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, good for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has rabbits that talk, and they're little bunny things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love bunnies, and then ten bunnies would be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem is they multiply too fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a really cool site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, it's only for the UK.
[SPEAKER_03]: The punchline sucked, in other words.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really dumb, because the whole thing... If you have a launch site like this, and you're basically making it seem like, oh, the world's connected... Except for you people in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not connected to the world, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura wants to let you guys know what's going on for the release calendar in Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have a number of games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Black and White 2 for the PC, Armored Core Nexus, Geist, King of Fighters 2003 for Xbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: Here, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Nintendogs is coming out in the UK on the 7th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shattered Union, Stargate 1, SG-1, which I actually really want to play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tim Burton's The Nightmare Before Christmas, The Pumpkin King.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also on the 14th coming out, we've got Driver for the GBA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Driver 3 for the GBA.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Driver 3, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Marvel Nemesis Rise of the Imperfects, Namco Museum Battle Collection, Rengoku Tower of Purgatory, Serious Sam 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those are some of the ones coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also, I don't know why it took so long, but they're also on the 21st getting Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tengaiichi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Budokai Tenkaichi hasn't come out yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not coming out until November.
[SPEAKER_00]: According to Eurogamer, their release is October 21st for the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lucky them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because November it's not coming out until, I think, second or third week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, no, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was October.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting it a week later, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a good thing I could care less about Dragon Ball Z. Genji is also coming out, which is actually a game that I have at home.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we did bring a pack and roll earlier.
[SPEAKER_00]: They get it on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Zenoseca Episode 2, also on the 28th.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you know a place that rents DS games, seriously, rent before you buy on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's one of those ones you'll love it or you'll not.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to, I've got to ask Loki, you know, kind of our hack and crack guy, you know, I don't follow the hack scene so much, but obviously I heard the big news about the 2.0 downgrade.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so the people that, you know, found that bug to begin with in the 2.0 downgrade
[SPEAKER_02]: Firmware basically be able to launch their own code by doing a buffer overflow.
[SPEAKER_02]: They basically created this program to make the PSP think that's version 1.0.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so when you do that, then you can run the version 1.5 update and basically downgrade your entire PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this method has been posted all over the place.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it started off at PSPHacks.com is where they originally posted it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you know where to get them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're the one that's in the homebrew site, they do have links to the firmware.
[SPEAKER_02]: They do keep copies on their servers for the Japanese and stuff, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not surprised Sony's ticked off about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, you'd think they'd embrace the homebrew thing a little more.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you'd think they'd take advantage of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'd take advantage of it, at least, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was telling my guy that represents H-Tech, I'm like, why aren't they coming out with RPG Maker for the PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, it'd be freaking sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could put your own textures and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can distribute your games online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's homebrew, but it's legal.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, what more would you want?
[SPEAKER_03]: I always found it interesting that in the 2.0 upgrade, there were things like
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember there was the hack a few months ago before 2.0 came out that would allow you to change the background on your PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they implemented that in 2.0.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other reason is people are only really upgrading to use the web browser, but when you think about it, the web browser is kind of useless anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless, I mean, you just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a lot of sites that support it right now, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: and it doesn't support Flash and it's really limited on, it doesn't support Java so it's like, they're teething oh well maybe future firmware updates will implement that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well thank you for releasing something crippled for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: A good way for them to cover their tracks when this kind of stuff comes up though.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the whole thing is they're working with Homebrew on even the 2.0 and if they get smart enough they're going to figure out how to just rip stuff out of the different updates and put
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And speaking of updates, I have to warn a few people here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was something going around, actually, that was basically saying it's a patcher that will fix your PSP to, I think, add the browser in there as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's basically this patcher that's been going around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know who was releasing it, PSP Team.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it will actually crash your PSP and destroy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's got to be somebody that wants to mess it up for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't download that, but do find the big links for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, speaking of the PSP, we here at Orange Lounge Radio have a pretty hefty announcement, and I think it's time to mention what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what is going on, Orange Lounge Radio PSP-wise?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, everybody's having the PSP, and those people that do have the 2.0 browser or a web browser out there that they're using on the PSP are looking for more portals and links and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we here at Orange Launch Radio decided it's time to get with things, and we like to be innovative and jumped on the whole podcasting thing right when it was kind of getting started here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now we actually will be announcing the launch of OLRPSP.com
[SPEAKER_02]: which will be our PSP formatted site.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to find links to download our podcast straight to your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to have downloads just like we have a wallpaper on there now that you can download for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: and plus you'll be able to keep up with the news that we have and a lot of other things, just more features.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you can visit this on a PC, on your regular Internet Explorer or Firefly, but it's going to look kind of crappy because this site is formatted for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is specifically for those folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it looks kind of okay on a... It's okay, but if you're wondering why it looks all funky, it's because it's specifically for a PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: That looks pretty good if you have a high-definition screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looks really nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki and VXJasonXV, our tech guy behind the scenes, you guys did an incredible job on this, and I think people are going to love it because I love the way you guys designed the site.
[SPEAKER_03]: You used a lot of image maps in your design, and I think that's a great way to browse on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check it out, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've got my 2.0 PSP that I was actually testing it with right as I'm making it, so make sure that everything worked, that it looked nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it just works awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the first wallpaper we have, I have it on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't detract from the icon so you can see everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And ironically enough, it worked out that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so check that out, olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: No www, remember, folks, because otherwise that won't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, just olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to another story here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a story about Disgaea 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of folks are really into the Disgaea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cute story.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had a very cute story to it and a very interesting game there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Disgaea 2 has been announced in the latest issue of Dengeki PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be out for 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is going to be what is coming out and the Etna, Devil Girl Etna
[SPEAKER_03]: and the Prinies, the little penguin guys, they will be coming back in the next Disgaea as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some cameos as well of characters from Makai Kingdom, which was another game in that same series, I believe, or at least from the same developer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's the same series.
[SPEAKER_00]: What game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not La Pucelle.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a different game.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Makai Tenshou?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Makai Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check that out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a very similar game with the combo system and everything is coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's Disgaea 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go on to, I think what we should do now.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've talked an awful lot about a lot of games so far, haven't we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think what we need to do, we need to talk about some real life things.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we can't play video games all day long because if we played video games all day long, we'd have no time to design websites.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, DarkSakura is here to remind you guys there's a whole world out there, and she would like to give you some advice to help you survive in the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, DarkSakura, what are you going to talk to the kids about tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Today's bit of advice is how to survive a bird attack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like in the Hitchcock movie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's even, I even have a picture that looks like it's from the birds.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number one, watch for hovering and clacking.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you observe this behavior, be ready for an attack.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't wander on to the set of Hitchcock remakes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also they're birds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should be able to fight off birds.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're small.
[SPEAKER_03]: When they say don't feed the pigeons, they effing mean it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bird.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like a giant duck or goose or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you have like a flock of geese or something that are... A flock of seagulls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or a flock of... Well, seagulls are just pathetic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they'll drop dead when you give them, you know, Alka-Seltzer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, I mean, they're birds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you should be able to fight off birds.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was attacked by a flock of seagulls once, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I ran.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ran so far away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did it give you bad hair?
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you've got a story about the Nintendo Wi-Fi DS system that's coming up, and I'm really excited about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am so excited about the DS Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope this isn't just one of those things that's a good theory on paper, but I really hope Nintendo doesn't let me down on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is going to be bigger than I thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought this was just going to be Animal Crossing and Mario Kart, but not the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they have a lot of things announced for it, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Nintendo Wi-Fi site actually launched
[SPEAKER_02]: By launch, they mean there's a teaser page there now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, if you go to NintendoWiFi.com and you check it out, their wonderful logo for it, the games that they're saying that are going to be utilizing the Wi-Fi, they have a huge list here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is only partial, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, of course, Animal Crossing, Bomberman, which I was surprised, and I'm assuming that's the Bomberman that came out already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe there's another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There might be another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't heard of one, but
[SPEAKER_02]: Castlevania at DS, which that's coming out in a couple of days here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Contact, which I hope is not a game based on the really crappy movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I somehow doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Digimon World, of course, they'll probably make a DS version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dynasty Warriors DS, which I heard was actually pushed back to who knows when.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some really good ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles DS, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope that's playable.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Kart DS, of course, no surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metroid Prime Hunters, which isn't even coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Monkey Ball DS, which whoop-a-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tony Hawk's American Skateland, which is the DS version of American Wasteland, but they did their own specific version for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Top Spin 2, Tenchu DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they have some generic card games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have Ultimate Card Games and Ultimate Brain Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then World Soccer Winnie-11 DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: For the record, Contact is by Goichi Suda, who is the director of Capcom's Killer7.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it shouldn't suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: No Jodie Foster.
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't launching until November, but hey, that's when Mario Kart's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the website for that, the teaser site?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo.com?
[SPEAKER_03]: NintendoWiFi.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grandma's Boy
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, Grandma's Boy was the one I had.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even realize the trailer was out already.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a brand new Adam Sandler movie that's coming out now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would we care here on a video game show about an Adam Sandler movie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because in the film, Grandma's Boy, he plays a 36-year-old game tester and aspiring developer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's about, oh, it's about Adam Sandler stuff, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got the mom from...
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody Loves Raymond in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a little more serious of a game adaptation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Siren is going to be made into a live action film in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see, the film is going to be directed by Sada Yoshihiko, who made Trick and Kizoku.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope I pronounced that right.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's writing a treatment right now that's supposed to come out about February 11th when Siren 2 comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is being plotted right now to come out, a Siren video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another franchise is getting their own movie pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: God of War is being worked on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not a surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Adaptation, but you know they're going to cast Vin Diesel or The Rock for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I saw finally on the big screen for the first time was that trailer for Doom, which I hadn't seen yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, that first person thing, look hokey.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to use that way too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I can understand, let's do that sequence for like maybe 30 seconds of the movies to kind of throw back to the, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you know what that reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_03]: It reminds me of, what was the, not House of the Dead, I think it was, where they had the gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that what it is?
[SPEAKER_02]: House of the Dead, yeah, where they threw in actual shots from the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Worst zombie movie ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you hear about the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going on with the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_00]: They won an Emmy.
[SPEAKER_03]: An Emmy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it one of those things that Ellen gave out on the awards?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't remember hearing about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Ten years to the day after the original PlayStation went on sale in North America, the console has been awarded an Emmy for...
[SPEAKER_00]: Outstanding Achievement in Technology and Advanced New Media.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that must have been at one of those tech awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how they always do the tech awards that aren't good enough for TV?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the Oscars and the Emmys do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, the 57th Annual Technology and Engineering Emmy Awards.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not all that they've won.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else did they win?
[SPEAKER_02]: They've won... Banishment from the Vatican.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I'd consider that winning.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony Italy has recently put up a full-page advertisement depicting some guy wearing a crown of thorns, much like Jesus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except this guy has no beard and no mustache, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Except this guy looks like he's a, I don't know, some... A nerd?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some, yeah, nerd reject or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, and he has a crown of thorns made up of the PlayStation symbols, you know, the X, circle, square, triangle stuff, and
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the subtitle to the whole article, which I love this, Ten Years of Passion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: How did that get by?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think it did.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Vatican took exception.
[SPEAKER_03]: How did that get by at Sony, though?
[SPEAKER_00]: So is the entirety of Sega Corporate X communicated now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they've actually had it pulled out of the Vatican.
[SPEAKER_02]: You think?
[SPEAKER_02]: They executed their Vatican powers.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We promised earlier in the show we'd get to some more of your e-mails.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you have an e-mail for us, you can always send us one at togo, T-O-G-O, at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And DarkSakura is going to rip open the mailbag violently and salvage some letters to read on air.
[SPEAKER_00]: Smash, smash, rip, tear.
[SPEAKER_00]: 16Bit sent us an e-mail, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome name.
[SPEAKER_00]: A correction about Panorama Cotton stating that it's just fairly uncommon.
[SPEAKER_00]: and there were several thousand.
[SPEAKER_00]: I tend to exaggerate with that game because I've had no luck finding a copy for less than $500.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm impressed somebody out there actually knew what the game was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I sure as hell never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Panorama Cotton is fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although it actually does give me sort of motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Rainbow Cotton didn't, which is really weird because usually it has to be the 3D game that makes me motion sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: While we're on the subject of corrections, I actually have to correct something too, because I got an email about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S wants to know that the Miyamoto meet, which we talked about last week, the article that I was referencing talked about that it was going to be the first ten people.
[SPEAKER_03]: would get to do Bark Mode with Miyamoto's dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: But unfortunately, if you think about the way Bark Mode works, there's no way you can restrict that to just being the first ten people in line that are going to be able to do it, because Bark Mode is going to pick up on any DS that's within 100 feet, so really it ended up being anybody that could get to Miyamoto's dog got to do Bark Mode with Miyamoto's dog.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so a lot of people outside actually ended up getting Miyamoto on their friends list, which I think is just awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, DJ Ranma S, for sending in that correction.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, one of our Canadian friends, Aceman, sent a question.
[SPEAKER_00]: Said, I'm thinking about getting the 360 when it comes out on launch, but the thing is I don't know about the game selection.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, I know which ones I'm going to get for myself, Gears of War and Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_00]: My question is, are there any four-player co-op games offline that you guys know of that I should pick up other than Ghost Recon?
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, I'd like to mention you might think of some better games to pick because Dead Rising and Gears of War are not coming out of launch, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Gears of War is to be announced right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead Rising has never even been on launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, you've got a good selection of sports games.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a sports fan, you have the entire 2K series and the EA series, you know, their games.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I may, I actually have the full list of launch titles in alphabetical order.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, go for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Amped 3, Call of Duty, Condemned, which is Sega.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dead or Alive 4, Elder Scrolls 4, Final Fantasy XI, Full Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Final Fantasy XI is a launch title?
[SPEAKER_03]: They are not launch titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That list is wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm still going to read the list because these are either launch or near launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: Full Auto, Ghost Recon, Advanced Warfighter, Gun, Cameo, Elements of Power, Madden NFL is...
[SPEAKER_00]: NBA 2K6, NHL 2K6, blah blah The Outfit, Perfect Dark, Project Gotham Racing 3, Quake 4, Ridge Racer 6 Saints Row, Tony Hawk's American Wasteland, Top Spin 2
[SPEAKER_00]: Second wave of launch titles announced by EB as of November 16th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Burnout Revenge, FIFA Soccer 06, Peter Jackson's King Kong.
[SPEAKER_00]: By the way, speaking of that, they showed a scene of King Kong to the GameStop managers and it apparently is supposed to be very awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: NBA Live 06, Need for Speed Most Wanted, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 06.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect Dark, isn't that a four-player?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me correct that list real quick here.
[SPEAKER_02]: King Kong is coming day and date with the PlayStation 2, Xbox versions, and GameCube versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's launching on every single platform the same day.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else we have here?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was... I know Frame City Killer got pushed back to February, which was one I was looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know Saints Row isn't coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full Auto's not coming out next year, and I'm really disappointed about that, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: The ones I was definitely going to pick up, Quake 4 looks good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Project Gotham Racing 3 is going to be friggin' awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Need for Speed, most wanted, is coming out the week before launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have a November 19th release date for Frame City Killer by Namco.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got pushed back last week to February.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's also an initial price list from EB that all the games will be $59.99, except for Cameo, which is listed at $49.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some other ones that are $49.99, but yeah, Cameo is one of the cheaper ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking forward to Quake 4 and DOA 4, which is weird because I'm usually not into DOA, but for some reason, I'm looking really forward to this new one.
[SPEAKER_00]: EB listed Halo 3 as being July 1, 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: They haven't even announced anything yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're stating that they're presuming it to be the same day as the PS3 release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_03]: So any other emails, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to close the mailbag until next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So send us some emails to go at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Castlevania will be going next-gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's already in development.
[SPEAKER_03]: Koji Igarashi has confirmed that the next-gen entry, it will happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, it shouldn't be a surprise to anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of Konami's most successful series.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, one thing that you might have been curious about is that the handheld releases, it will continue to depict a different timeline.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the handheld releases will still be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_03]: Curse of Darkness, I think I...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto and a Grand Theft Auto-like game
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, everybody's been waiting for the Grand Theft Auto Liberty City stories, which is going to be coming out for the PSP at the end of October.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of the things that I, especially I, have been wondering is, you know, are they going to have some support for Wi-Fi?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we haven't really heard anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the answer is yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll actually feature a few different modes, multiplayer for up to six different players.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will basically have...
[SPEAKER_02]: 2 that have been released so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said about 7 modes.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first one being Liberty City Survivor, which is your basic deathmatch style gameplay, and Protection Racket, which splits players into teams, which they must protect or destroy a number of different limousines at bases somewhere in the city.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're basically saying that multiplayer mode will be identical to single player, but you'll have more vehicles available up front and 60 different player skins.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, of course, power-ups and standard hoo-ha there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, Microsoft can't be out of any sort of franchise, so their supposed answer to the Grand Theft Auto series is a game which, I don't know, it looks okay, but it's basically a Grand Theft Auto-ish type game with kind of a superhero character.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you're basically a superhuman guy who can who's basically cleaning up the city and by cleaning up the city you can steal cars throw cars at people just really interesting stuff I don't know it doesn't look that great to me the screenshots I saw I was like who gives a crap you know I'll pick it up because it'll be fun to play I like throwing cars at people but it doesn't look that impressive I mean especially looking at the other games coming out it just
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a third-party release.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just not really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, hey, beta shots, who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a couple more stories, then.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got just a couple more here.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing I want to talk about is the Mana series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you know, Secret of Mana, Legend of Mana, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Children of Mana.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually an RPG that's in development right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming out for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was confirmed in Famitsu Weekly Magazine this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know how it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Take advantage of having the two screens and the touch thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All we know is that it's happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Children of Mana.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just hope it's better than Legend of Mana because I could not... Legend of Mana ruined the series for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't stand it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That PlayStation one was awful.
[SPEAKER_00]: My problem with Legend of Mana was the fact that I imported it in a fit of... Ooh, Mana game!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to make this bold statement.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll probably get hate mail for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was uber text heavy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I liked Secret of Evermore more than I liked...
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Mana
[SPEAKER_03]: Neither one of these games, I should point out, is World of Mana, which was that thing they teased at E3 this year, like a big movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows what the heck that is?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a hunch it's an MMO, but I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's an MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think when you call something world, I have a hunch it's an MMO, but we don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last story tonight, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Katamari Craze is spreading the nation, of course, and if you want to check out Namco's website, katamari.namco.com,
[SPEAKER_03]: If you sign up for the website, you can actually download your own little version of the prince who will roll a katamari across your screen at various intervals and will play little looping music.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, you can actually click and drag him and throw him places and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to have a goat that did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess this would be fun for about five minutes and then get as annoying as those little purple bonsai buddies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thirty seconds, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thirty seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you try this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, it replays the whole thing, just over and over, and he just rolls the thing all over the screen, basically back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does he pick up your windows?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought he would, and I thought that would have been awesome, because I have a lot of icons he could roll up, but he did not, and it was a great disappointment.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll just have to send a message to the King of Cosmos for somebody to...
[SPEAKER_03]: Shoot some frickin' laser beams out of their eyes at Namco.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: That just makes me really miss the little goat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the little goat would occasionally run off to go see Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got a few last-minute stories here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, there's going to be a new Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one's coming out for the DS, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resident Evil Deadly Science.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deadly Science.
[SPEAKER_03]: You people and naming your franchises...
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything that will work with the DS acronym.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically, Resident Evil 4 DS, nothing more to see here, move along.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, the other thing is, in November, they're going to be bundling the Red DS with Mario Kart for the price of $149, much like you have seen with the Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yippee, skippee.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Red DS is already available for import.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some info about Zelda...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you know how Twilight Princess was supposed to be coming out this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're adding new features.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what those features are?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically going to be enhanced for the Nintendo Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be adding, if you plug in your GameCube game to the Revolution, you'll be able to use the wonderful Revolution controller for God knows what.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's basically why it's been pushed back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hoping they would put it on the Nintendo system, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, they should have just done it for the revolution.
[SPEAKER_00]: The best description of that controller is on VG Cats.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, the reaction is, I feel dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the last story... You promise?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last story is, Kojima clarifies that the No Place to Hide in the trailer that we saw from Metal Gear Solid 4 is about Snake's age.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, this doesn't take no place to hide from death.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, because he is a clone of Big Boss, this is only a few years later after number two, or three, I guess, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, number two, because three took place before two.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've gone cross-eyed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so they haven't really said too much else other than there's going to be two different sides that you can either ally with
[SPEAKER_00]: It's still like the little snatcher bot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks sexy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still need to get into Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_00]: Honestly, though, there's another fun parody of that on VGCats, also their most recent comic.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really a solid snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they paying you money under the table or something?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I just love that.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's like my favorite webcomic.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Spamusement all the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, video game related webcomics.
[SPEAKER_00]: Spamusement, I have to say, is the only one that makes me crack up like crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're definitely done.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we're talking about webcomics, we know we're done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nail, coffin, bang.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thoughts, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLRPSB.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Visit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Download a wallpaper.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reject false icons and balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my final thought is Blue Mage on Final Fantasy XI.
Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't make a time out of me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me know when they get GM answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, are you going to come back?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I just want to laugh.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Time made.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys for subscribing to our podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: And tell somebody else you know about our podcast because we are independent, so that's really the best way we can get the word out is word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you guys very much for listening, and we'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next update!