[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of October 10th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody, once again, welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for subscribing and downloading the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're here to talk about video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all the gaming news that you really want to know about here on Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we really appreciate your guys' support in downloading and checking us out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means a lot to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, not just me here on this program, Rob Roberts, but also I'm joined by the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, still here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the one and only Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're still working on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP community for responding so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: and those of you guys that are downloading the show onto your PSP, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great use for your PSP, all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still working on more stuff for it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Loki's still working on that website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're looking at maybe a shell box and looking at chat, possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check out olrpsp.com and celebrate olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about a giveaway?
[SPEAKER_03]: DeathJunior.com
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We won't spam you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We won't put you on any list or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just send us an email and you might win.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you put a funny message in there that uses bad grammar, I will laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start off tonight's show talking about how our gaming week was going.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how's your gaming week been?
[SPEAKER_05]: Busy, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had the week off of school, so I basically sat around and did, you know, crap all day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, of course I had work, but I played some Nintendogs, although I do not know where my DS is now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I locked my DS in the drawer at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did the dog eat it?
[SPEAKER_05]: What dog?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: She'd probably run in fear.
[SPEAKER_05]: She does look alarmed whenever the puppies bark.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a little jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think she hid it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She hid it in her litter box and took a big shit on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're remembering to feed your cat, right, as well as the dogs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: The cat doesn't let me forget because she hops on the bed and goes, Mom!
[SPEAKER_05]: Feed me!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've also finally opened my copy of We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cracked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Dedicating a virtual car we can never afford.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, technically, we can't afford one right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, in the real world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like an Xbox 360 and a PlayStation 3 and a Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox 360 does not come first on that list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Release date-wise, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Opinion-wise, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you've been gaming with this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: God, yeah, playing lots of Taiko No Tatsu, Taiko Drum Master, I have the US one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your roommate, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have our Firefly Monday, Firefly Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And afterwards, we went out, we kidnapped my husband and all went out to Lions and came back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Late Night Lions on Firefly Friday and played lots of Taiko no Tatsujin and my hands were all bruised and we were watching the cracked out opening, sleep deprived, thinking, oh, that's so cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: How does the Japanese version compare to the English version?
[SPEAKER_05]: When was the last time Jamie played the Japanese version?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you haven't played it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you had.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played both.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't had time.
[SPEAKER_04]: The English one is a little bit scaled down compared to the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot scaled down.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's still cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cute, but I'm going to go on and import the others.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't honestly have much interest in it beforehand.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now that, I mean, I played it before, but I just was like, eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: The arcade one is a heck of a lot of fun because the Taiko drum is like, Taiko, it's actual size.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a heck of a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like playing the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, I only know of like one arcade, and that's in LA, which is not exactly around the corner from us, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to bring out the PSP version here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the same when you've got a game like that on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the same when you've got a game like that on the PSP because there's no taiko drum.
[SPEAKER_03]: It still works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Dan's been playing Castlevania Dawn of Sorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm definitely going to touch on that later because I picked that up too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's looking pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get a chance to play yourself yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: I turned it on in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: He left the DS in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I trip over the thing because we have this hanging basket in our bathroom and he had it sticking out and I ran into it and knocked it across the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, oh shit, did I break down the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: I keep the cat box in the bathroom too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was afraid I knocked it into the cat litter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Narrowly safe there, the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing World of Warcraft too.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that going?
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: So strange to me, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's pretty cool, because the thing is that it was passing to any character in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, people can teleport in real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the thing is that it was passing on to any standing character in the game that anyone talks to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was passing to the NPCs.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's how it was spreading, is that people would contract whatever that is, heal themselves, they would contract it, teleport in, talk to the NPC, heal themselves, the NPC gets it, passes it on, because it cuts something like 200 and something life each time it drops.
[SPEAKER_05]: For someone who's level 50, that doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: For someone who's just starting off, that's instant death.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it keeps happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they counteracted it by having them infected with something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fixed, but I never had to worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you play anything besides Burnout?
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Burnout Legends.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're becoming a broken record.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I play this during the week, and I don't have time to play stuff at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really wish I did, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I play Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Taco's still alive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of done with Nintendogs now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really care about Taco anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the virtual pet thing wasn't for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just I lost the attention to it because you can't really do that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still a great game, but it's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun to throw bones and stuff at their head, but it's just, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Bark Ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all about the Bark Ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe if there's expansions later on that your dog can learn to do more things.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you quit playing, give me all your stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just waiting for Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so looking forward to the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be cool, except, I mean, how's that going to work with people coming to your town?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we could have people destroying towns.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure they have tested this thing into the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll have a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Folks can interact with us in our town.
[SPEAKER_04]: You probably can only allow certain... You probably get to allow who comes into your town and which trains can run into your town.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like Bark Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's going to be like Bark Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to be in like Town Mode or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Wi-Fi somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously you can't run when your DS is off, so you'd be able to monitor who's coming in and out of your town.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: No retro game stuff pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I got to play against Mario Voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: At E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: At E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you said I was lovely.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole reason I bought...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Animal Crossing was such a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I would still be playing it if there was just a little more to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they bring out a really expansive version of it later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: For any of those companies out there, I'm willing to advertise in my town for your products.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And the thing is, I don't know if anyone's ever listened to when they speak in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: when they're actually saying every letter in the words that they're speaking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in the Japanese one, now they do say it very fast, it's hard to catch it, but they're saying every syllable.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're actually speaking Japanese when they talk to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's very fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just very fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cartoon-y style.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if you listen carefully enough, you can actually hear them talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slow it down, record it, slow it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you've been playing this week, Logie?
[SPEAKER_04]: My week, a few games I want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to follow up on Lost in Blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something that I kind of touched on last week, but I didn't really get to give a more in-depth impression of it because I feel like I didn't get to play enough of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I played a little more Lost in Blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to say it didn't really hold my interest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have to say borderline not recommend Lost in Blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there is an audience for this game out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really reminds me of an old-school computer point-and-click game, like an old-school King's Quest, Loom-style game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's definitely some creative things to be done with the stylus, like digging in the sand and starting the fire and some of the things you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was just really bored with the story, and it seemed like I got so close to dying.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you get the milk a goat?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get that far to the milk and the goat part, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard it was almost impossible to milk the goat.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game, honestly, I didn't really want to play it that much longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just really didn't hold my interest.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can't really recommend Lost in Blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do think there are people out there that would like this type of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not going to completely say avoid it, but I'm going to say borderline non-recommend because I think there are people out there that might enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like those old-style computer point-and-click games, you actually might get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might like this more than I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I did like some King's Quest games and some of that stuff I just wasn't like really into it so that's why I can't King's Quest bored the tears out of me but I love Loom see I love King's Quest 4 like that is an awesome game and some of the other King's Quest in fact I have a King's Quest related story for later but we'll talk about that in a minute the other game I played based on a recommendation in the forums I didn't even know this game was out but a Tecmo Arcade Collection I think it's the official name Tecmo Collection something along those lines
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's kind of how I felt playing a lot of these games in the Tecmo Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, boy, I remember this game being a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And granted, you go into a game like Rygar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Rygar on the NES was completely different than it was in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: The arcade was like a side-scroller action-based game, where the Nintendo one was...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really like gems hidden in this collection that are very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I like Solomon's Key, the arcade version is very cool and some of the other stuff in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my biggest problem with the Tecmo collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $29.99 not $19.99 and I honestly think $29.99 is a little high when you consider that most of the retro at least where I paid for it, it was $29.99 and there were other retro collections sitting right next to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Midway one, the Namco one for $19.99 and I just
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the price additional is really justified with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what if it has Tecmo Bowl?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think $19.99 is a more fair price to be charging for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to borderline recommend it just because I think there are some good titles in here that a lot of folks might remember from the NES, but they never got to play the arcade versions of some of these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are a lot of really good gems in this series.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's nothing to drop everything and go right out and buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so bored with this game, I forced myself to play the game a little bit longer, but I was just like, this is stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is this a game on the DS?
[SPEAKER_04]: This should be a game that's a flash thing on somebody's website.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe somebody will waste their money on Sprung.
[SPEAKER_04]: I definitely do not recommend, avoid like the plague, Sprung.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a scenario-based borefest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep in mind that those games are very, very popular in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but they're also better in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has Tokimeki Memorial.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to see boobs in the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even get that here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did a Tokimeki for girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in this one, you can play as the girl or the guy, but it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both stories suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's the girl one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, she actually has to convince the guy to have sex with her because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they ever got it on, I just didn't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted that game out of my DS, it's that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for the record, the only game I've played that's worse than that is Pink Pals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chatroom Sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, PictoChat plus crappy minigames.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, last game, Castlevania Don Isaro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, a really, really good game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you liked the most recent Castlevania game that they put out on the Game Boy Advance, where you're collecting the souls and absorbing the souls, you're going to like this one because it's the exact same freaking thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a continuation in that story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's an absolute continuation of the story, except they added the magic seal thing, which is kind of hokey, but they did some other touchscreen elements, like certain souls that you absorb, you use the touchscreen as part of it, and that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can play as Alucard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't get that far yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe, because Dan showed me something on one of the sites, I believe that Alucard is an unlockable character in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then you meet with the other people and you can switch off like in Castlevania 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't gotten that far in the game yet, but I do know I like this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Symphony of the Night, one of the greatest video games ever, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although I haven't followed the advanced games so well, I did like this most recent one they had, the Aria of Sorrow, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The continuation, it's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's extra features, like a versus and a soul trading thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: For Castlevania fans, especially if you're a fan of Symphony Night, this one doesn't disappoint.
[SPEAKER_04]: My only complaints is that the drawing thing is a little bit hokey.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recommend Castlevania Dinosaur.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still love the opinion they need to do a US release of what was the Saturn version of Symphony of the Night in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, where you could play as Maria, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game, the one problem I had with it is that the 3D effects were not as good.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 2D effects were much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sound was infinitely better because as...
[SPEAKER_05]: The sound processor and 2D graphics in the Saturn were far superior to the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it had so much more to offer that I think that game would sell very well if it comes out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know a complaint I heard about Castlevania and Dinosaur... Symphony of the Night?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Castlevania and Dinosaur.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why I'm correcting myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: A complaint I heard was you don't get to use a whip.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's not a Castlevania game if you don't use a whip.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is totally a Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get that argument.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do unlock a character who is one of the Belmonts, and you do get to use a whip.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't get to use a whip.
[SPEAKER_04]: The swords play practically the exact same way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to use a whip in Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Richter is an unlockable character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, still, that's the same thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you play through Richter's story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Symphony of the Night is the greatest Castlevania game, period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even Simon's Quest, not even Castlevania 3, not even the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dracula X was infinitely better.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I, I, you show me Dracula X, I still think Symphony of the Night is the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dracula X was the last true Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could see that argument.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not the Super Nintendo version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the Super Nintendo version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even that was good, but when you started getting into the whole Metroid-style gameplay, it became... You can't... I don't think there's a comparison.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we've got to get into some other actual news going on this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as I could argue about Castlevania all night long... Hi, we're nerds.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do a radio show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hi, you're a nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're listening to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_04]: Geek!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God I did not vote for him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, honestly, I could say I didn't vote for him either, but it was written by a Democratic assemblyman.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really a bipartisan thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think there's... I don't think everything was truly being considered with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think there could have been a better option to do what they wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm cool with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how much I want to rehash the same topic, though, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go listen to an old podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I've talked about it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just have a quick description for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting more voters.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that could be said of either party in this case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the media kind of plays to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's taking the popular opinion and using the media hype to gain himself some more voters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a loser.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop and EB Games, the merger was approved.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked previously that GameStop was going to buy EB Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was approved.
[SPEAKER_04]: The merger went through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the names are changing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gizmondo White Screen
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a widescreen Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the phrase, though, that the rumors that Gizmondo is $210 million in the hole isn't going to stop the release on time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure the Phantom console is worse in the hole.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only reason it's widescreen is they're trying to compete with the Pop Station.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Taking a look at the image of the widescreen Gizmondo
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say, you know, and see, I liked the Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had absolutely no problem with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This thing does look pretty sleek.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but does it have sight talking?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they definitely changed the look of that from what they were showing at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's funny is I remember the original shots of the PSP back when it was conceptual still.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had shots of fish as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's kind of ironic in that picture of the widescreen Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's fish on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that is a favorable sign.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to be picking one of these up, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, ever since I got to play it at E3 and played that game, Johnny Whatever, that had the karaoke mode, we're sort of like guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: What other games are on this thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only one I really know anything about is the Johnny Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's the golden rule of gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: We brought this up on the three-hour show this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to hear less about the Gizmondo and more about the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what's going on in the hack and crack scene?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there was, of course, the mandatory PSP update that happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, 2.01.
[SPEAKER_03]: It adds no features whatsoever other than fixing the hole that allows you to do stuff with your PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, since people love the hack of the firmware, they're doing some more cosmetic modifications.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one is they have a guide to removing the broken icons.
[SPEAKER_03]: It requires you to hex edit your
[SPEAKER_03]: firmware and the runner program and basically just blanked out those icons instead of actually having them pop up.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other one is, you know those little wavy lines that are on there that prevent burn in?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get rid of those too as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just more cosmetic stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the wavy lines.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, but some people don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They just want to remove them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, by golly, they're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were talking earlier in the show a little bit about Nintendogs, and I was saying that I get a little burned out on Nintendogs, but the fun is just beginning for some of our other friends, right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 7th, Nintendogs was just released in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, didn't you post some photos from that in your blog?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was friggin' cute is what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they had some pictures of the people bringing their dogs with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just absolutely adorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got one where the dog's actually sniffing the... or licking the... Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dog licking the DS!
[SPEAKER_03]: Trying to be a celebrity.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, any word on how this game is selling?
[SPEAKER_05]: Over in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Taking a look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this is a cute picture of a puppy in a soccer ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that game so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got an 8 out of 10 by Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to read the small paragraph.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we're enchanted by it since it's a highly engaging and entertaining game and one that makes excellent use of the DS's unique capabilities.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, it's got puppies in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that sums it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, I will add, they did throw a puppy party to celebrate the launch of this game, which featured such wonderful events as dog-loving celebrities.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had actual canine celebrities as well, some dogs from different shows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had dog's eye video screens, a very important pooch chill out area, and the doggy Olympics as well as a doggy disco.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doggy disco?
[SPEAKER_03]: Doggy disco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, because Nintendogs is so big, there's other people out there that want to steal some of Nintendogs Thunder, correct?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm also trying to find the numbers, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, 03...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there screenshots up there on your screen there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hanadeka Club is sort of like The Dog with the fisheye camera, so it's all the puppies done the same way.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are eight breeds to choose from, including Pugs, Chihuahua, Shih Tzu.
[SPEAKER_05]: The dogs can talk with their owners, find out about their likes and dislikes, and will play games of fetch, frisbee, balls, and bones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that it's crap compared to the other one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, because I do like the Hanadeka Club.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd look at it, I wouldn't, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this actually is, so far it looks like that it's out, it will be released this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, there's some other stuff coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought this was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Square Enix, as we call them, Squeenix, but Square Enix is actually putting out a game called Mario Basket 3 vs. 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So shock, it's something that's not a role-playing game, although it's not the first time they haven't done a role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're kind of doing this little basketball-looking game, and it's a three-on-three game using the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a very Mario Kart-style look to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: which I think is very interesting considering it's being developed not by Nintendo but by Square.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did get Mario Baseball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That just recently came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Nintendo is unveiling a new Wario Land game that's coming out very soon and that'll also be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to mention this for PSP, our friends on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Detel has released a 4GB hard drive for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, because this is a hard drive, it also has a battery that goes with it, and it's supposed to boost your time that you play, or it's supposed to boost the loading times as well using the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's twice the battery power for one, because it's basically this giant battery that sticks out of your battery port there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then it's also got a 4GB drive in there as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the only bad thing about Daytel is they've got really bad... They have a really bad track record with their batteries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their batteries tend to explode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my gosh!
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hopefully this won't have the explosive feature in it, but hey, more storage space is always good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: And speaking of which, no price changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you want to store tons of crap... Especially since you can't buy actual 4GB hard drives anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you could, they'd be like $15.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're releasing that one peripheral that the team executor is working on that's actually going to be using CompactFlash and MicroDrives, which go up to 6GB.
[SPEAKER_03]: And those are a little bit less expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: But actually, if you get that on there...
[SPEAKER_03]: and then you add the, there's an adapter you can make or buy that converts laptop drives to work with CompactFlash, you can in a sense have, you know, a 30 gig, 120 gig drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you'd be spending that, you know, upwards to about $500 for it, but, you know, hey, if you want more space, I mean, that's one way to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm looking to see here real quick, because I know they had that going for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also had actually
[SPEAKER_03]: The PSP TV stuff, they've announced a price point for that as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know the price for that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The price for that is going to be $119.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're taking pre-orders right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the things that they added to it is an S-video out, so you can have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, the swappable, you can do 4.3 or 16.9 aspect ratios.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of money, but going to a different company...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's rumors going around this week, and I think some of it comes back to Joystick ran an article, that's Joystick with a Q, .com ran an article about Nintendo possibly releasing the Revolution for $99.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a rumor that's going around right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't that be very interesting, though, because the Xbox 360 is going to be, what, $300 for the core, $400 for a little more?
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3, we don't know yet, but we can expect it will probably be about the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what a way for Nintendo to catch up by being kind of the last one out the gate to really, you know, create interest in their system because it would only be $100.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be very smart.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to...
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing I can think of logically is if the system is not that expensive to make for parts and labor and however much they would pay per system for marketing and then for shipping, sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd have to see what their overhead is in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you can make enough product with even a minute profit to make back and pull a good profit.
[SPEAKER_05]: by selling more units.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this is really true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even so, it's comparable.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's half.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very competitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's half as much.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a real way for Nintendo to gain some ground if they were going to be the last ones out the gate, but
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the whole innovation thing with the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: But on top of that, Nintendo has always been oriented toward more family child games.
[SPEAKER_05]: What parent is going to want to buy their small child a $350 system when they can get a $150 system that would be easier to play?
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have something to add here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think we've heard everything about the revolution yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game Company out there, they're referring to one of the big three, is actually going to be using this in their next console.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think what it's going to be is, and this is my theory, is that they're going to have, it's not going to be as powerful photorealistic-wise, but it's going to be 3D.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which will be why you need a 3D remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Peter Jackson's King Kong Demo
[SPEAKER_05]: Available for download.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's probably hitting a lot of the major game sites because I actually saw a little clip of the game in action.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to see what the Xbox 360 might look like by using your PC, kind of, because the graphics are supposed to be comparable, check it out on your PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also a teaser for Tomb Raider Legends X360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And teaser would be not playable though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a little trailer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, but it is there to see some of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, one I'm kind of interested in myself is the Possession Zombie Takedown.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what are you going to tell the kids about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Today's piece of advice is how to jump from a moving train.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you never know when you're going to be having to jump from the train, or throw Mama from the train.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number one, make your jump from the end of the last, the rear car.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't jump from the middle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait for the train to slow as it rounds the bend in the tracks if you have time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pick your landing spot.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ideal spot is relatively soft and free of obstructions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get as low to the floor as possible, bending your knees.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jump perpendicular, that's sideways, children, to the train, leaping as far as you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cover your head with your arms and roll like a log when you land.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my final, final piece of advice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you hitchhike and stick to cars, much easier.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to jump from a train.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking for that piece of advice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what's going on with the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you like to talk about homebrew stuff for PSP, but now it sounds like there's independent stuff going on for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX Live Arcade Marble Blast Ultra
[SPEAKER_04]: That may not be a bad thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marble Madness is excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Project Gotham Racing 3, and this game looks friggin' awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of a combo between Asteroids, Rez, and Fantavision.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just tons of explosions on the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other ones that they were showing off, which actually is pretty cool, is Joust, the classic Atari game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you gotta love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they have Joust, but do they have Burger Time?
[SPEAKER_03]: No Burger King yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beer Tapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worst system ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: But actually, one of the things I was going to mention is the Xbox hard drive that they're coming out with, it does come with some other features.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was looking about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's this, like Hexic or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hexen.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Hexen's a different game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a Tetris game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually done by the guy that did Tetris.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be actually videos available.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: But all this crap's getting preloaded on if you buy the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and it's either if you buy it with the system or by itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you get a game, which is kind of cool, but you need the hard drive if you're going to play any of these games because you've got to download them to your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the arcade stuff, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other game that they showed was Wick and the Fable of Souls, and I have no idea what that was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just looks like some RPG or shooter game that has a tree in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: SkyTree, that's all I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good way to sum that up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the other thing to disappoint fans, unfortunately, at launch, a couple games have gone bye-bye, and those would be Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter for all those Tom Clancy fans, and, of course, Frame City Killer for all those Namco fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, starting to push back a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good Valentine's Day gift.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing says I love you like Tom Clancy's Advanced Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Xbox, might as well roll on with Microsoft here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week we had Doom 3 Resurrection of Evil come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too often on the consoles, I mean it's happened before, but not too often do you see expansions coming out for games where you have to already own the first game to play this expansion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what's going on with the Doom 3 here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not quite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's its own thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I misunderstand the article?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually their game's re-release.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Ninja Gaiden Black, uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically a re-release with the PC expansion stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got a couple more weapons and more levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not what somebody else told me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody else told me, well, I guess because maybe the PC version was like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, PC version, you have the original one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's nothing special then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just another game coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Doom 3 was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also, the price point's lower.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's $29.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comedic in Doom is the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see the trailer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, forget the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see it and laugh at it and then watch The Rock for an hour.
[SPEAKER_04]: That first person thing was so hokey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the Halo trailer ends up looking like that, I'm going to laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I still have to remind our listeners, speaking of movies, Silent Hill coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, didn't you have something about like a... I'm still trying to find more on it, but there's a couple more people listed on IMDb like we can really...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, say yeah, I am DB, but... Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a link to the article, to the, uh... Not an article, but an interview with Roger Avery that I had touched on a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I remembered us getting as far as some of the other actors in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have Jodell Fairland, Alice Cridge, is that how her name is pronounced?
[SPEAKER_05]: That also goes in a little bit more into the behind-the-scenes cast, but it's still Sean Bean.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess at this point, while we're getting a little late in the show, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's never too late to open up the old mailbag and see what's going on, what our listeners have said to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, you can email the show by just sending us an email to go at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura, she reads and sifts through the mail all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our our hundreds and hundreds of spam and our one or two actual emails that come in.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's in our email bag this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, our friend Mike from 1up.com, who had that very interesting article about the NDAs, sent me a movie file.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to try to find a way to get this up on our site, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure there's a way we can get it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's of one of the Nintendo Micro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the Game Boy Micro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I saw one of those today, and I was like, I'm not going to buy that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It involves a maze with a rat with a micro on one side and a piece of cheese on the other and the mouse showing its opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was humping the micro.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was probably the most messed up thing I've seen all day, but very hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, in response to Sasuke, I wanted to know what the Click-O-Vision is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe we were talking about the Coleco-Vision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the C-O-L-E-C-O-Vision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coleco also made swimming pools and Cabbage Patch Kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew about the Cabbage Patch Kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know about the swimming pools.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, a lot of gaming companies make other things you may not know about, like Konami and slot machines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there's others, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the one that comes to mind because I like to gamble.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Bradley, not to be confused with Arcadian42, also sent me the link to the GameSpot article about pocket dogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like it when the listeners try to clue us in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I got another email from Rob with two Bs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: He actually just had a little bit more about the super huge games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I like this one sentence in particular here.
[SPEAKER_05]: The industry is taking sides.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's Betamax versus VHS all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, with the HD DVD and Blu-ray?
[SPEAKER_05]: With the formats, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that does make perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, it absolutely makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I really hope before these things get into...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember Penny Arcade and their character, the Divics.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also about the worst game.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I always said it was E.T., but he said it was Firefly Magic Carpet.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about Zelda Wanda Gamelon?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are pretty rotten ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frickin' play Sprung and tell me you didn't just play the worst game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Ping Pals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pick up either one of those and tell me you just didn't play the worst game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually, at least Zelda amused me for a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, one of our listeners wrote in, Danny, and I want to read this email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I 100% freaking agree with it, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe I speak for some people when I say fuck IGN
[SPEAKER_05]: Just the other day I was trying to read a gaming article when all of a sudden a random yellow circle covered over the text I was reading.
[SPEAKER_05]: As it turned out, this was an ad.
[SPEAKER_05]: An ad that had obscured what I was reading.
[SPEAKER_05]: After realizing what it was, I was instantly irritated.
[SPEAKER_05]: IGN is notorious for planting obnoxious advertisements everywhere you try to visit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clicking a link, viewing an image, forced uncontrollable downloading of a video ad when you want to watch something.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be fair, this is a trend on the internet as a whole that IGN is...
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm sure is not the only gaming site but of course one of the most prevalent.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't get those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I paid for mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you're a corporate whore anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's the other thing on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how about disallowing QuickTime Media for the majority of the time?
[SPEAKER_05]: On a Macintosh, Windows Media Player is atrocious to use and watch on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then again, Windows Media Player is just atrocious, period.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I want to bitch about IGN?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is all their downloads stop halfway.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's also in here, you'd think with all the advertising IGN puts up that they'd have the bandwidth to allow QuickTime.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have QuickTime for everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you're like an insider.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to be a paid member.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when this bot came out of nowhere and blocked the article I wanted to read, it was the last straw.
[SPEAKER_05]: A few years ago, IGN was limiting how many images you could view per day, and now they're blocking the text you want to read.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Really good news on things that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have an excellent download section.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also 1UP, which I actually mentioned looking at 1UP.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've been good to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1UP's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like 1UP.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also like... I like the ones that are just the facts.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no pretty picture, just the facts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the media-oriented sites.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slashdot and Dig.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some of those ones are just, you know... If you're looking for trailers, GameTrailers.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, GameTrailers.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you just want movies and you don't gotta pay, and it's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there are all alternatives out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course,
[SPEAKER_04]: and other independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Support your independent podcaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, please do.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a good email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I have to say that voiced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, also, use Mozilla.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use Mozilla and there's an extension you can use.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use this to block flash, like ad block.
[SPEAKER_04]: Search for ad block Mozilla on Google and you'll find this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a thing that allows you to block
[SPEAKER_04]: like Mozilla as it is you can right click on an image and block it from ever seeing it but Adblock takes it like one step further where you can block plugins on the page and things so you can get rid of those little quick time movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really like Firefox for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just right click on it and you go to block images from I understand the websites are just trying to make their money and that's perfectly fine but at the same time there's smart ways of doing it and there's annoying ways of doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, opening up IGN should not crash my computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: We also got another email about ThePlay2O, and actually I'm so dumb I just closed the email.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll try to credit you next week, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: About ThePlay2O, combines water play with the world of video games featuring flashing lights and sounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Directional water jets move characters through traps and mazes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Pokemon, Super Mario Brothers, Donkey Kong, and in Canada only, SpongeBob SquarePants.
[SPEAKER_05]: But after looking at this thing, though, it looks like those little toys that you used to get in the 80s that you'd push the button and it shot water up into the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now this one, it's electronic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You control the direction on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This still makes me think of those things where you squish the water and try to hit the loop and put it on a pike or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to really see this thing in action, but that's really what it's making me think of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I want to... I don't feel like getting in the pool to just try this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you go to play20, the letter O, dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I do, but I think I will let somebody else talk for a moment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you insist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I insist.
[SPEAKER_05]: Must you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have it up, so you've got the email up.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one that was emailed to me, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you just accidentally closed the email box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get it up real fast here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'm glad that your roommate's not in the room when you say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it was... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why you guys are doing that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was... Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Shallon Monks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a question from Steven S...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who, by the way, has a hilarious email address, but of course I'm not going to read it on air, but it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, In Shaolin Monks, I've been playing with my friend, and every time he gets a fatality, mutality, or brutality, he gets it, and my character doesn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can help me figure this out, it would be much appreciated, because I'm about ready to give up on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I played Mortal Kombat Shaolin Monks, and the fatality thing was really ticking me off, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, you're going to have to check that out on GameFAQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameFAQSGameFacts.com
[SPEAKER_04]: because I unfortunately do not know the answer, and I'm okay with admitting that, that I do not know the answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um, go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you find out, let me know, because I want to know why I can't keep, why I can't unlock any more fatalities in that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just being stupid or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got a couple more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have, um, this week's UK releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've touched on a few of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have, uh, Brat Angels, Combat Elite, uh, World War II Paratroopers, Driver 3, uh, uh, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: Heart of Empire, I'm sorry, Rome Marvel Nemesis, Rise of the Imperfects Namco Museum, Battle Collection Rengoku Tower, Purgatory, Sirius Sam 2 Spy Toy, WRC Rally Evolution, those are all on the 14th On 21st, Buzz the Music Quiz Cold War, Crash Tag Team Racing Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tenkaichi Duel Masters, Shadow of the Code Fear, Fable, The Lost Chapters Genji, L.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rush, Pokemon Emerald And as I scroll down to see if there's anything else...
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: UFO Aftershock X3 Reunion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are all coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're starting to get kind of late on the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have one last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: One last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a quick one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, make it quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Australian High Court, to our Australian listeners, hello everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation mod chips are legal, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can mod the hell out of your PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's all legal.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing behind that is it was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Their decision found that PlayStation chips' functions were circumvented by mod chips to allow unauthorized games to be played are not primarily copy protection devices.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really don't give a rat's ass whatever you play on your system as long as it's not bootlegged.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, have fun down under with your mod chips.
[SPEAKER_05]: Import those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a few quick stories for you guys here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're trying to wind down here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to say one other thing about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: P-Safe P-1.1
[SPEAKER_03]: PS3, PS4, PS5, PS6, PS7
[SPEAKER_03]: and one of the things that they were demonstrating could be the possible evolution in the eye toy which is they actually had a demonstration where the eye toy took a picture of the person and recreated a 3D model of their head just like completely accurately
[SPEAKER_03]: and they're just saying that this is possible that later on something like this could be used in the PS3 to actually put you in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean... That's freaky.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I've got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know they've been trying to do that for years.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had that thing with the Game Boy camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Imperfect Dark, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but that was...
[SPEAKER_04]: And they've done it for some other eye toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Facial skinning.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have that for the eye toy now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But boy, that's just like pasting your face.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the 3D modeling and everything, that's crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this is a 3D head.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this is not just some stupid mapping.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to see how fat I look in a video game, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need no 3D model.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it is, but what just popped into my head is having the model taken and then for a new Rayman game, Raymanizing yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love manipulation like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know you like manipulating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just messing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know there was this big fan homebrew thing going on, King's Quest, brought up King's Quest earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: King's Quest 9, every cloak has a silver lining.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get this, they had all these volunteer people, like they had a 2,000 page script going for it, 9 chapters, 450 characters, original music, original voice acting being done for this whole thing, and a cease and desist was just laid on them this week by Vivendi Universal Games, which, you know, acquired Sierra some time ago, which Sierra made the King's Quest games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this Mac got put down on this, which is too bad because King's Quest is kind of one of those games where I kind of, I'm always like, I wonder whatever happened to King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I knew that there was like that eighth game that didn't really register on the radar too much, but then King's Quest kind of disappeared.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would have been excited to see something like this, a continuation of the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what a fan community, honestly, what a community to be getting that many people involved in a project like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, I guess when you get that many people involved,
[SPEAKER_04]: you start to draw attention to yourself so that's too bad I guess but
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll release it as like Queen's Trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Queen's Journey Part 9.
[SPEAKER_04]: Peasant's Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Curse you, Trogdor!
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, you know, maybe they could work out a deal where maybe Vivendi Universal could just distribute this game and, you know, make some money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Download it free off of their website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people still love King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, last story, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a brand new game coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how else to say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Care Bears Catch a Star is now coming out for the PC and Macintosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, this is coming out right before the Care Bears Big Wish movie, which is coming out on DVD October 8th.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, that actually would have already come out here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the Care Bears of the 80s.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brand new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least they haven't changed how they look like they did with Strawberry Shortcake.
[SPEAKER_03]: My big wish is that they would just stay in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need the Care Bears stare, don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki just needs a Care Bears stare.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: At all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still remember the Care Bears in Wonderland movie and that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's only 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't argue with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thoughts, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate the Care Bears.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thoughts, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Reject Posse icons and itchy, tasty.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought is, somebody's got a case of the Mondays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they really take my stapler, I'm going to set the building on fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for downloading and listening to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Support independent podcasting and, you know, just
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for taking time to listen to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else can I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, Monday is National Orange Lounge Radio Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it's really Columbus Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you work for a bank, you got the day off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use it well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to us all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, have a good one, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.